<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cooking the Books with Frances Cook on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/cooking-the-books-with-frances-cook/</link><description>Recent content in Cooking the Books with Frances Cook on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 15:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/cooking-the-books-with-frances-cook/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beware 'fake sales' at Christmas | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500387/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500387/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s how fake sales can lead to a overspend, and debt spiral. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Christmas is an expensive time of year, which can leave us vulnerable to tricky sales tactics, and getting pulled into a debt spiral.
Figures out from PriceSpy show some shops even indulge in ‘fake sales’ – the recent Black Friday sales saw 15% of products actually have a price increase before the sale was announced, so that the shop could claim a bigger percentage drop, and trigger our love of a bargain.</description></item><item><title>Quick Hits: The financial prep that's needed before a baby | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500001/</guid><description>Podcast Description A highlight clip from the February 2023 episode "How to baby-proof your finances… kind of", with Cat Emerson from Kernel.
If you have a question about this podcast, or a question you'd like answered in the next one, come and talk to me about it.
I'm on Facebook here, Instagram here, and Twitter here.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What happens when your identity is stolen | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500002/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s how to fight back when fraud is committed in your name. Hosted by Frances Cook.
It’s the sort of thing that makes for a good scary headline, but you might never think could happen to you.
Having your identity stolen, so that people can commit fraud and dodgy financial dealings in your name, while you suffer the consequences.</description></item><item><title>Quick Hit: How to budget hack the holidays | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500003/</guid><description>Podcast Description A highlight clip from the December 2019 episode "how other NZers stay on budget over Christmas", with Tom Hartmann, from the Commission for Financial Capability.
If you have a question about this podcast, or a question you'd like answered in the next one, come and talk to me about it.
I'm on Facebook here, Instagram here, and Twitter here.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why KiwiSaver needs to change | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500004/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week, BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackle a different money problem. Today, it’s how your KiwiSaver could be working harder for you. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Let’s start with the good - I’m a huge fan of KiwiSaver.
It helps you save up for a first home or retirement, when it can be daunting to do so by yourself.
It’s also full of little sweeteners, such as the employer contribution and Government contribution, which can double your money from the start.</description></item><item><title>Quick Hit: How to know when it’s time to sell your business | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s how to sell your business for a tidy profit. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Even the most successful business owner at some point faces the decision to step back, and let someone else take over.
If handled right, exiting the business can mean a sale for a tidy profit, and an easier retirement.</description></item><item><title>Why embracing a ‘personal brand’ could get you a pay rise | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500006/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s how a bit of personal marketing can land you the dream job. Hosted by Frances Cook.
It’s never been more needed, but more difficult, to get a pay rise.
The cost of living is shooting up, making it difficult for many people to pay the bills.
But the economy is also fairly rough, and businesses aren’t handing out fat pay packets just because you ask nicely.</description></item><item><title>Quick Hit: How to have a holiday on a shoestring budget | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500007/</guid><description>Podcast Description A highlight clip from the September 2019 episode "the most successful ways to travel on a budget", with Herald travel editor Stephanie Holmes
If you have a question about this podcast, or a question you'd like answered in the next one, come and talk to me about it.
I'm on Facebook here, Instagram here, and Twitter here.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why ignoring your KiwiSaver could cost you $88,000 | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500008/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week, BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackle a different money problem. Today, it’s how to check if your KiwiSaver is working as hard for you as it should be. Hosted by Frances Cook.
It’s the things we know we should do, but never quite get around to, that can be killers in the money world.
So I winced, but wasn’t all the surprised, when new research rolled across my desk showing that ignoring your KiwiSaver could mean you have $88,000 less in there by the time you retire.</description></item><item><title>Quick Hit: What businesses need to know about a rough economy | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s all about staying successful in challenging times. Hosted by Frances Cook. It’s been a rough time for business lately, with a maybe yes maybe no recession that appeared and then disappeared just as quickly. But in reality, there are always challenges in the business world. The key is how you tackle them.</description></item><item><title>What it’s really like to quit your job and travel with the family | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500010/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s how one family managed to travel the world on a shoestring budget. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Many of us will have thought of chucking in the day job and travelling the world, but it’s not always so easy to turn into reality.
Particularly if you have children – you obviously have to consider their schooling, extra costs from extra people, and also just whether they’ll be able to handle it.</description></item><item><title>How to budget without restriction | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500011/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s the ways to make a boring budget a bit happier. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Let’s start with the elephant in the room, nobody likes the idea of a budget.It immediately makes you think of cutting back, restricting, losing the little things that make life enjoyable.
But there’s also the reality that times are tough, and creating financial security means knowing where your money is going, and taking control of it so that you can have savings, and even investments.</description></item><item><title>Quick Hit: Four key drivers of cashflow success | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s all about the tricks to boost your cashflow. Hosted by Frances Cook.
One of the biggest killers for business is the pure and simple reality of cashflow.
So, today’s quick hit is all about getting to the heart of this problem, with four factors that can get that money coming into your business.</description></item><item><title>How high interest rates change your investing plan | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500013/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s why interest rates have changed the favoured investment types. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Interest rates have rocketed up both in New Zealand and around the world, and it’s safe to say, it’s changed the maths for a lot of investors.
While savings accounts, term deposits, and bonds were all a bit miserable for a while there, now they’re making more money.</description></item><item><title>Quick Hit: The buy and hold investment strategy | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500014/</guid><description>Podcast Description A highlight clip from the April 2018 episode "How to stop emotions hurting your finances", with Martin Hawes, Authorised Financial Advisor.
If you have a question about this podcast, or a question you'd like answered in the next one, come and talk to me about it.
Here is a link to the audience survey: https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/DRF9TBG
I'm on Facebook here, Instagram here, and Twitter here.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Would you trust AI with your investing portfolio? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500015/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s the reliability (or not) of AI and your money. Hosted by Frances Cook.
• Check out Frances Cook’s new money course, Money Made Simple, at francescook.co.nz, for a masterclass on everything from setting goals, creating a spending plan that works, mastering debt, beginning to invest, and understanding your KiwiSaver.
Everyone is abuzz about AI, and of course, that means people are hunting for ways to use it to make money.</description></item><item><title>Quick hit: How to take a small business international | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s all about expanding your customer base by going international. Hosted by Frances Cook.
When you’re on the hunt for customers, you usually would like as many as possible.
One way to increase those numbers is to increase the size of your hunting ground, by taking your business international.
Of course, that is better suited to some businesses than others, and you might need to change tactics in order for it to work.</description></item><item><title>Your bank account is changing - here's what you need to know | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500017/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s the changes coming from open banking law changes, and a Commerce Commission investigation. Hosted by Frances Cook.
• Check out Frances Cook’s new money course, Money Made Simple, at francescook.co.nz, for a masterclass on everything from setting goals, creating a spending plan that works, mastering debt, beginning to invest, and understanding your KiwiSaver.</description></item><item><title>Quick Hit: How one New Zealander became interested in FIRE | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500018/</guid><description>Podcast Description A highlight clip from the January 2018 episode "could you retire at 30?", with Alpha Leung. If you have a question about this podcast, or a question you'd like answered in the next one, come and talk to me about it.
I'm on Facebook here, Instagram here, and Twitter here.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is the wild side of investing worth the risk? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500019/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s how it works if you’re interested in riskier investments should as margin lending or crypto. Hosted by Frances Cook.
• Check out Frances Cook’s new money course, Money Made Simple, at francescook.co.nz, for a masterclass on everything from setting goals, creating a spending plan that works, mastering debt, beginning to invest, and understanding your KiwiSaver.</description></item><item><title>Why tough times mean you need to get serious about a business strategy | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s all about finding the growth strategy to take you to the top. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Once upon a time, doing well in business meant competing with someone down the road, or if you did really well, others throughout New Zealand.
Now, whatever your size, you’re often having to compete globally from day one.</description></item><item><title>Why most of us say we want to invest ethically, but don’t | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s all about how much power you really have as a shareholder. Hosted by Frances Cook.
This episode is brought to you by the Financial Markets Authority. Alright team, it’s a little bit of a good news, bad news, moment. The good news, is it’s world investor week. Now of course, every week is investing week in Cooking the Books land, but it’s also nice to have the excuse to talk about it even more.</description></item><item><title>Quick Hit: How a family man changed tactics for financial independence | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500021/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500021/</guid><description>Podcast Description A highlight clip from the January 2020 episode "The reality of one NZers journey to early retirement", with Nick Carr, from Your Money Blueprint. If you have a question about this podcast, or a question you'd like answered in the next one, come and talk to me about it.
I'm on Facebook here, Instagram here, and Twitter here.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>From 15yo high school drop out, to business owner with a $60k side hustle | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500023/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s the path from leaving school early, to becoming a business owner. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Sometimes school just isn’t for you, but that doesn’t mean you won’t be successful in life.
Today’s guest decided exactly that, leaving school at 15, in order to become a mechanic.
Even if she’d stopped there, that would have been a plenty successful, skilled career, for many people.</description></item><item><title>Quick Hit: How to get paid in business | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s all about making sure you get paid. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Getting that money flowing in is what separates a business from a hobby. But it sometimes can be easier said than done.
For the latest podcast, I talked to Joe Rastrick, head of paytech and emerging payments at BNZ.</description></item><item><title>How two mums started a baking business with $1000, a home printer, and glue sticks | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500025/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s how a home business became successful enough to be carried by major stores. Hosted by Frances Cook.
If you’re trying to do well with money, of course it helps to have more coming in the door.
One of the ways people choose to pursue that, is by starting their own business.</description></item><item><title>Quick Hit: How to write a business plan | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500026/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500026/</guid><description>Podcast Description A highlight clip from the September 2019 episode "How to start a business with profits in mind" with Jo-Anne Randall from Baker Tilly Staples Rodway.
If you have a question about this podcast, or a question you'd like answered in the next one, come and talk to me about it.
I'm on Facebook here, Instagram here, and Twitter here.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What to do if you’re feeling the mortgage pain | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500027/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s tactics for surviving high interest rates. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Keeping a roof over your head has to be one of the most important things for financial stability. And yet, it’s increasingly difficult for people right now, no matter what income they’re on.
Interest rates have shot up, and don’t start any nonsense in the comments about how people should have seen this coming, because the speed at which they’ve gone up is the fastest in about 30 years.</description></item><item><title>Quick Hit: The digital tools that can help your business fly | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s the software that can eliminate drudge work. Hosted by Frances Cook.
This episode is brought to you by BNZ.
A few digital tools at your fingertips can take a load off your plate as a business owner.
But the problem is, with so many to choose from, which do you pick?</description></item><item><title>Can you trust the bank to protect your savings? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500029/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s the new rules on what happens to your savings in a crisis. Hosted by Frances Cook.
When we talk about what to do with your money, there’s always a discussion of risk. And a savings account is supposed to be one of the safest options.
So New Zealanders might be surprised to learn that actually, they’ve had few legal protections on that front until recently.</description></item><item><title>What if your investments aren’t as ethical as you thought? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500030/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s how to invest smartly, while accusations of greenwashing run rampant. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Something I get asked about a lot is ethical investing, and whether it’s possible to make money without making the world a worse place.
My answer is a resounding yes. I truly believe that many of the best investments, with good profits, are ethical ones.</description></item><item><title>How to talk about money with your partner, parents, and kids | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500031/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s the best ways to start the money conversation, and avoid a fight. Hosted by Frances Cook.
This episode is brought to you by Milford Asset Management. Money is the great unspoken force in many of our lives, making certain things possible, and keeping other things out of reach. But there’s huge power in starting to talk about it, especially with those we’re close to.</description></item><item><title>Why most Lotto winners end up broke | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500032/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s how a windfall can mess with your money mindset, and how to fix that. Hosted by Frances Cook.
It’s a daydream that many of us have had. What would you do if you won the lottery?
Millions fall out of the sky and into your lap, and suddenly, the world is your oyster.</description></item><item><title>Quick Hit: What to know before starting a business | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500033/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s how to launch your business idea the right way. Hosted by Frances Cook.
When you’re setting up a business, it’s important to start off on the right foot.
So in a special quick hit episode of Cooking the Books, today is all about getting those foundations in place, so you can start with confidence.</description></item><item><title>Why weight-loss drug Ozempic is getting Wall St attention | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500034/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s the trends fund managers are watching, and banking on. Hosted by Frances Cook.
They say that change is the only constant, which is particularly true in the investing world. One moment there’s a hot stock rocketing in price, the next minute, the company is down again, and it’s on to the next.</description></item><item><title>How to find recession-proof stocks | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500035/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s the investments than can do even better in a downturn. Hosted by Frances Cook.
It’s no secret that I’m a fan of investing through a recession, as it can be a way to snap up bargains, and build wealth for the future.
But what if you’re looking for something a little more immediate?</description></item><item><title>How one woman paid off $187,000 of debt in two years | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500036/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s how one woman went from deeply in debt, to being rich enough to buy into a castle in Italy. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Sometimes you need a shock in order to make a change, and today’s guest certainly had one of those in the past.
She’d known she wasn’t doing well with money, but when she decided to face it head on, and add up how much she owed, she realised with horror that it was $187,000.</description></item><item><title>Quick Hit: How to cut the food budget without feeling deprived | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500038/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500038/</guid><description>Podcast Description A highlight clip from the January 2019 episode "How to cut waste and your food bill at the same time" with Jenny Marshall from Love Food Hate Waste.
If you have a question about this podcast, or a question you'd like answered in the next one, come and talk to me about it.
I'm on Facebook here, Instagram here, and Twitter here.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Could you make money investing in luxury handbags? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500037/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s how alternative investments like art, wine, and handbags, actually work. Hosted by Frances Cook.
I’m a big believer that the world of investing is open to everyone these days, and you can start growing your wealth if you have just $5 spare.
But it is also true that the investing world has some interesting pockets where you get a glimpse into how the other half lives.</description></item><item><title>Where to turn if debt is getting out of control | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s the strategies and organisations to help you pay off debt faster. Hosted by Frances Cook.
This episode is brought to you by BNZ.
Debt is one of those things that’s easy to get into, and harder to get out of.
But the good news is there are at least some tactics to make it a little bit easier, once you decide you want to get out of debt.</description></item><item><title>How a hobby instagram page turned into a six-figure business | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500040/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s how a social media challenge turned into a profitable six figure business. Hosted by Frances Cook.
There are so many good reasons to want to start a business – to do something you feel proud of, to have control over your schedule, or simply to earn more money.
All great reasons, but it’s easier said than done.</description></item><item><title>Quick Hit: How to know if debt will help or hurt you | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500041/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500041/</guid><description>Podcast Description A highlight clip from the December 2017 episode "Where to start when you're drowning in debt" with the Commission for Financial Capability's personal finance editor Tom Hartmann.
If you have a question about this podcast, or a question you'd like answered in the next one, come and talk to me about it.
I'm on Facebook here, Instagram here, and Twitter here.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nigel Latta on why the scam industry is booming | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500042/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s why scammers are on the rise, and how to stay ahead of them. Hosted by Frances Cook.
If you pride yourself on being great with money, and able to spot tricksters coming a mile off, I have bad news for you: you’re one of the people most at risk.
Scams, fraudsters, and rip-off artists are everywhere right now, and it’s horrifying the number of people who are losing their hard-earned money to them.</description></item><item><title>Quick Hit: Why you'll be a better investor than you think | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500044/</guid><description>Podcast Description A highlight clip from the June 2022 episode "busting the investing myths that hold you back" with Clarissa Hirst from the Financial Services Council.
If you have a question about this podcast, or a question you'd like answered in the next one, come and talk to me about it.
I'm on Facebook here, Instagram here, and Twitter here.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The climate change issue that will change your KiwiSaver and investments | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500043/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s how your KiwiSaver and investments will change under new climate rules. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Environmental issues can have a major impact on a company’s bottom line, and yet until now, it’s often been seen as a nice-to-have consideration for investors.
That’s about to change.
The government has put in new standards that require New Zealand companies to collect information on emissions and other climate related impacts, and give that information to investors along with their annual results.</description></item><item><title>Quick Hit: Why a drop in your KiwiSaver is normal | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500046/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500046/</guid><description>Podcast Description A highlight clip from the August 2022 episode "Your KiwiSaver questions answered" with Dr Claire Matthews, associate professor from Massey Business School.
If you have a question about this podcast, or a question you'd like answered in the next one, come and talk to me about it.
I'm on Facebook here, Instagram here, and Twitter here.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to take your business from start-up, to international success story | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500045/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week, BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackle a different money problem. Today, it’s how one NZ company landed a contract with an international giant of the beauty world. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Every now and then you’ll hear about a New Zealand business that made it big.
From being an idea dreamed up in someone’s garage, to landing on the world stage, suddenly working alongside titans of the business world.</description></item><item><title>Quick Hit: How to have difficult money conversations | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500048/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500048/</guid><description>Podcast Description A highlight clip from the March 2019 episode "How to talk to your partner about money" with AUT's Dr Ayesha Scott. If you have a question about this podcast, or a question you'd like answered in the next one, come and talk to me about it.
I'm on Facebook here, Instagram here, and Twitter here.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What it takes to succeed as a digital nomad | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500047/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s the reality behind the digital nomad dream. Hosted by Frances Cook.
There have been many promises made about the future of work, how increased digital connections would make it easier to design our own schedule, and work from anywhere in the world.
In reality, it’s often a little trickier than we might think.</description></item><item><title>Why your age totally changes the KiwiSaver strategy | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500050/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s what you need to know to get the most out of your KiwiSaver. Hosted by Frances Cook.
This episode is brought to you by Milford Asset Management. Your KiwiSaver is the biggest financial asset for many New Zealanders, but I’m sorry to say, many of us are doing it wrong. You need different types of KiwiSaver accounts depending on where you are in your life.</description></item><item><title>How a teacher saved 90% of her income, to retire early | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500049/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s how a teacher changed her finances to prioritise travel and spend time with family. Hosted by Frances Cook.
There are many different strategies to reach financial independence, some more extreme than others. If you have the freedom to travel, it can also mean the opportunity to take your financial strategies to the next level.</description></item><item><title>Quick Hit: Busting tax myths | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500052/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500052/</guid><description>Podcast Description A highlight clip from the February 2020 episode "The tax realities of making a side hustle work" with Hnry co-founder James Fuller. If you have a question about this podcast, or a question you'd like answered in the next one, come and talk to me about it.
I'm on Facebook here, Instagram here, and Twitter here.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why the share market has hit pause, and how you can make money from it | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500051/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s why ETF trading is down, and what it means for your strategy. Hosted by Frances Cook.
After a couple of years of hype and covid boredom, it looks like the shares investing scene is crashing back to earth. Figures from the NZX show New Zealand ETF trading down about 75% in the last year, aka, investors aren’t buying and selling as many of those Exchange Traded Funds.</description></item><item><title>Quick Hit: How not to buy the dip | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500054/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500054/</guid><description>Podcast Description A highlight clip from the September 2022 episode "How to invest in shares through a crisis" with Dean Anderson, CEO of Kernel Wealth. If you have a question about this podcast, or a question you'd like answered in the next one, come and talk to me about it.
I'm on Facebook here, Instagram here, and Twitter here.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>From living paycheque to paycheque, to mortgage free, in just seven years | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500053/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s how one New Zealander learned more about money and decided to get strategic. Hosted by Frances Cook.
It’s amazing what can happen when you’ve got a money goal, and this week’s guest is living proof of that.
From having no understanding of money, and living paycheck to paycheck, she turned things around to boost her income, build an emergency fund, and then pay off the mortgage in just seven years.</description></item><item><title>Quick Hit: How shops trick you with sales | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500055/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500055/</guid><description>Podcast Description A highlight clip from the December 2018 episode "why do sales make us irrational?" with AUT lecturer Sommer Kapitan.
If you have a question about this podcast, or a question you'd like answered in the next one, come and talk to me about it.
I'm on Facebook here, Instagram here, and Twitter here.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What first home buyers and investors need to know about the falling property market | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500056/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s what to make of the prediction that house prices will fall further. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Behind the headlines of the Government’s Budget, there’s a bunch of nerdy stuff that can help us make better decisions with our money.
At the same time as saying what the Government is going to spend its cash on, they also release documents and forecasts, showing how the wheels are turning in our economy.</description></item><item><title>Quick Hit: The maths of financial independence | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500058/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500058/</guid><description>Podcast Description A highlight clip from the October 2022 episode "How a NZ couple used sharemarket investments to become 'work optional' in 11 years" with Ruth Henderson, from The Happy Saver.
If you have a question about this podcast, or a question you'd like answered in the next one, come and talk to me about it.
I'm on Facebook here, Instagram here, and Twitter here.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>How much do you need to invest to get passive income? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500057/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s how to work out how much reliable income you can get from investments. Hosted by Frances Cook.
One of my favourite money sayings is ‘every dollar you invest gets you closer to the day you don’t have to work anymore’.
It’s no secret I’m a big fan of investing and the financial security it can bring by adding a stream of income that doesn’t rely on you heading off to work every day.</description></item><item><title>The 29-year-old who makes $700 a week through thrift flipping | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500059/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s a side hustle that could make your hundreds of dollars while only needing a few hours of your time. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Earning some extra money on the side can be useful for all sorts of reasons, but it’s important to make sure it doesn’t soak up all your free time, and that it actually makes you money.</description></item><item><title>Quick Hit: How to prioritise insurance | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500061/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500061/</guid><description>Podcast Description A highlight clip from the February 2020 episode "The common insurance mistake NZers are making", with then-Herald money editor Tamsyn Parker.
If you have a question about this podcast, or a question you'd like answered in the next one, come and talk to me about it.
I'm on Facebook here, Instagram here, and Twitter here.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Quick Hits: What's the 'golden ratio' for your budget? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500060/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500060/</guid><description>Podcast Description A highlight clip from the June 2019 episode "Myth busting the golden ratio for your money", with Dr Ayesha Scott from AUT.
If you have a question about this podcast, or a question you'd like answered in the next one, come and talk to me about it.
I'm on Facebook here, Instagram here, and Twitter here.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to make your credit card company give you money | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500062/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s how to make the most of your credit card, and the different deals at the moment. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Credit cards can be a divisive topic
On the one hand, they’re a source of debt, which often has high interest rates, and can hold you back. But on the other hand, if you use them carefully, you can get rewards and perks for no cost.</description></item><item><title>Quick Hit: The shares vs house debate | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500064/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500064/</guid><description>Podcast Description A highlight clip from the April 2021 episode, "Can you reach financial security without a house?" with then-Hatch CEO Kristen Lunman.
If you have a question about this podcast, or a question you'd like answered in the next one, come and talk to me about it.
I'm on Facebook here, Instagram here, and Twitter here.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The 25-year-old who ditched fast fashion to pursue financial freedom | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500063/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s how a 25-year-old has overhauled her finances to pursue financial independence. Hosted by Frances Cook.
When you talk to people about taking control of their money and learning to invest, you’ll often hear this particular phrase – “I wish I started earlier”.
Today’s guest, however, doesn’t have to worry about that.</description></item><item><title>Quick Hit: Why a goal can make you hate your budget less | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500066/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500066/</guid><description>Podcast Description A highlight clip from the November 2019 episode "How to budget without feeling deprived", with PocketSmith CEO Jason Leong.
If you have a question about this podcast, or a question you'd like answered in the next one, come and talk to me about it.
I'm on Facebook here, Instagram here, and Twitter here.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to invest in someone else’s mortgage | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500065/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s the pros and cons of peer-to-peer lending. Hosted by Frances Cook.
There’s been a lot of talk about bank profits lately, and whether or not they make too much money.
But if you had the opportunity to step into their shoes and make money in a similar way, would you?</description></item><item><title>Quick Hit: How to pick a financial adviser, with Gillian Boyes from the FMA | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500068/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500068/</guid><description>Podcast Description A highlight clip from the March 2021 episode "How to choose a financial advisor", with Gillian Boyes from the Financial Markets Authority.
If you have a question about this podcast, or a question you'd like answered in the next one, come and talk to me about it.
I'm on Facebook here, Instagram here, and Twitter here.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to take a business from bootstrapped, to VC investment | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500067/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s how the founder of Twiice is finding investment to help them break into Europe. Hosted by Frances Cook.
It’s one of those pieces of advice that gets trotted out like it’s so simple; if you want to increase your income, consider starting a business of your own.
Now it’s true that a successful business can create wealth, but that’s also the trick.</description></item><item><title>Quick Hit: Why KiwiSaver is such a sweet deal | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500070/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500070/</guid><description>Podcast Description A highlight clip from the August 2022 episode "Your KiwiSaver questions answered, part one", with Dr Claire Matthews, associate professor from Massey Business School.
If you have a question about this podcast, or a question you'd like answered in the next one, come and talk to me about it.
I'm on Facebook here, Instagram here, and Twitter here.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Can you still get a pay rise in 2023? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500069/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s the strategies to use to improve your chances of getting a raise. Hosted by Frances Cook.
It’s that time of year – the time when many people are getting their performance review. Which means it’s the perfect time to ask for a pay rise. Data from Seek shows that the top three reasons New Zealanders look for a new job are to get more money, progress their career, or find better work-life balance.</description></item><item><title>Quick Hit: The pros and cons of the “rule of 100” investing strategy | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500072/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500072/</guid><description>Podcast Description A highlight clip from the October 2019 episode "How the rule of 100 helps decide your investing strategy", with Mark Lister from Craig's Investment Partners.
If you have a question about this podcast, or a question you'd like answered in the next one, come and talk to me about it.
I'm on Facebook here, Instagram here, and Twitter here.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to win the staff talent war | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500071/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s what really matters to employees in 2023. Hosted by Frances Cook.
We hear a lot about the war for good talent right now, and how businesses are struggling to find and keep the best workers.
So it’s timely that Mercer has just put out its Global Talent Trends Survey for 2023, which for the first time includes data specifically looking at the New Zealand situation.</description></item><item><title>Quick Hit: Halfway to financial independence, this New Zealander changed tactics | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500074/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500074/</guid><description>Podcast Description A highlight clip from the January 2020 episode "The reality of one NZers journey to early retirement", with Nick Carr, from Your Money Blueprint. If you have a question about this podcast, or a question you'd like answered in the next one, come and talk to me about it.
I'm on Facebook here, Instagram here, and Twitter here.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why higher interest rates are causing banks to collapse | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500073/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s a banking expert on how safe savings are in New Zealand and Australia. Hosted by Frances Cook.
A bank collapse is the stuff of nightmares, with the potential to wipe out hard-earned savings, or a business’s ability to pay staff.
This nightmare has become reality in the US, with a run on Silicon Valley Bank, or SVB, that led to the bank collapsing.</description></item><item><title>Quick Hit: How can you pay off debt faster, with Kate Reddington from Sorted | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500076/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500076/</guid><description>Podcast Description A highlight clip from the October 2020 episode "How to pay off debt faster", with Kate Reddington from Sorted.
If you have a question about this podcast, or a question you'd like answered in the next one, come and talk to me about it.
I'm on Facebook here, Instagram here, and Twitter here.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What we’ve learned from small investors taking over the share market | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500075/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s how index investing changed the game, and what’s next. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Now don’t tell me you forgot it was our anniversary. It’s a big one too: 30 years, the pearl anniversary.
What’s it the anniversary of? Well, I’m glad you asked.
January 29 marked 30 years of the world’s longest-surviving exchange-traded fund, Standard &amp;amp; Poor’s Depository Receipt, mostly known by the acronym SPDR, or as the “spider”.</description></item><item><title>Quick Hit: When should your KiwiSaver be conservative? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500078/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500078/</guid><description>Podcast Description A highlight clip from the October 2019 episode "Should you protect your KiwiSaver by going conservative?", with Paul Gregory, then head of investments for Pie Funds and JUNO KiwiSaver Scheme.
If you have a question about this podcast, or a question you'd like answered in the next one, come and talk to me about it.
I'm on Facebook here, Instagram here, and Twitter here.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>The NZ couple who became semi-retired in five years | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500077/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s the couple who used shares and property investing to create the financial freedom to go travelling with their kids. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Living entirely off investments might seem like a dream for rich people, but what about the idea of changing your money so that you have some investments supporting you, and then you just work a little bit?</description></item><item><title>How insurance will be changed by climate change | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500079/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s how to figure out your insurance priorities, and how insurance will change in the future. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Insurance is meant to protect you against life’s worst moments, the things that can make life hard for not just you, but also your loved ones.
But it’s also a little tricky, because the various policies can be expensive, and you have to personalise your strategy.</description></item><item><title>Quick Hit: Budget travel tips, with Herald travel editor Stephanie Holmes | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500080/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500080/</guid><description>Podcast Description A highlight clip from the September 2019 episode "the most successful ways to travel on a budget".
If you have a question about this podcast, or a question you'd like answered in the next one, come and talk to me about it.
I'm on Facebook here, Instagram here, and Twitter here.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to invest through a recession | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500081/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s how to approach the sharemarket while the economy is down. Hosted by Frances Cook.
There’s an old saying that everyone is a genius in a bull market.
When the share market is going up, up, up, it’s easy to get sucked into the hype, and assume that you’re the one making brilliant investing decisions.</description></item><item><title>Quick Hit: Why pick a tiny house over a “normal” one, with Kyron Gosse | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500083/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500083/</guid><description>Podcast Description A highlight clip from the December 2020 episode "the pros and cons of a tiny home".
If you have a question about this podcast, or a question you'd like answered in the next one, come and talk to me about it.
I'm on Facebook here, Instagram here, and Twitter here.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to baby-proof your finances… kind of | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500082/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s the costs you should consider before having a baby. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Kids are a delight, a gift… a big old expense.
Adding a new person to the world and your family comes with costs, and it’s a reality that can put people off kids.
It’s a trend around the world.</description></item><item><title>Quick hit: The money changes that make you happiest, with Ben Kelleher from ANZ | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500085/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500085/</guid><description>Podcast Description A highlight clip from the May 2021 episode, "how to use money to boost your happiness".
If you have a question about this podcast, or a question you'd like answered in the next one, come and talk to me about it.
I'm on Facebook here, Instagram here, and Twitter here.
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is it still worth investing in property? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500084/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s how to handle a falling property market, whether you’re an investor or first home buyer. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Slides at the park might be a bit of fun, but when it comes to the property market, the latest downward slide has probably not left many people laughing.
Real Estate Institute data shows sales are way down, 39 per cent year-on-year, while Auckland house prices have fallen 18 per cent to a new median value of $1.</description></item><item><title>How one NZer hit financial independence, then started giving money away | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500086/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money issue. Today, it’s a woman who goes to work so that she can donate her salary. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Being focused on money can sometimes have a bad reputation.
People can decide it means you’re greedy, or self-interested.
Well today’s guest hit financial independence and decided, she still wanted to work, but so that she could give away much of that income, to causes she cares about.</description></item><item><title>What are the best options for DIY NZ share investors in 2023? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500087/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s how to figure out which online platform to invest through. Hosted by Frances Cook.
The last couple of years has seen a boom in DIY shares investors dabbling in the market.
One reason is the increased information out there, and people understanding that they need to invest their money in order to get ahead.</description></item><item><title>How to invest in real estate for $5 | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500092/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's how to get started in real estate investing when you don't have much spare cash. Hosted by Frances Cook.
We all know that New Zealanders have a mild property investment obsession. For decades now, it’s been one of the favourite ways for kiwis to build their wealth.
But as prices went up, fewer and fewer people found property investment to be a realistic option for them.</description></item><item><title>Why bonds are the underrated investment you didn’t know you needed | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500089/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s why bonds are the most attractive they’ve been in years. Hosted by Frances Cook.
While interest rates going up can hurt our money in a lot of ways, there’s a silver lining.
Certain investments, like bonds, start to make much more money.
So what are bonds, and why haven’t we talked about them as much on this podcast before?</description></item><item><title>The reality behind the digital nomad lifestyle | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500090/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s the true good, bad, and ugly of digital nomad life. Hosted by Frances Cook.
I’m sure we’ve all considered it at some point – whether we could chuck in the office job, and go make a life on the beach somewhere, maybe getting in some freelance work from a laptop to make sure the pina coladas keep flowing.</description></item><item><title>How to watch your pennies in 2023 | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500091/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s what to expect from the year ahead, and how you can prepare your money for it. Hosted by Frances Cook.
A new year often means it’s time to take stock, take a beat, and think about what’s next.
If you’re doing that this year, it might make you wince a little.</description></item><item><title>How one woman saved 50% of her income to fund a career change | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500088/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald’s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s how one New Zealander used financial independence to fund a career change. Hosted by Frances Cook.
We often talk about financial independence in terms of its most famous acronym, FIRE, for Financial Independence, Retire Early. But many people chasing financial independence aren’t actually interested in retirement. They’re instead after the financial security that allows them to make whatever career choice is best for them.</description></item><item><title>How a family of five cut their grocery spending to $170 a week | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500093/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's how a family went from living paycheck to paycheck, to saving 60% of their income. Hosted by Frances Cook.
One thing I’ve heard a lot when I talk to people about budgeting and money management is “just wait until you’ve had kids”. And it’s true – I had my first child, and life got more expensive, and slightly more difficult to manage.</description></item><item><title>How to spend less and still eat well | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500095/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's how to keep eating healthily when you're on a budget. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Health might be wealth, but these days it seems you need a lot of wealth in order to have access to the health. With cost of living soaring, a trip to the supermarket is likely to make you wince.</description></item><item><title>As interest rates rise, how to make sure your money survives and even thrives | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500094/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week, BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackle a different money problem. Today, it's the opportunities for your money in a high interest rate environment. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Talk about interest rates is everywhere right now, and for good reason.
They're the secret sauce that changes everything in the money world, even if you don't see the direct impact at first. Most recently, the Reserve Bank has yanked rates up again by an unprecedented 0.</description></item><item><title>Why a flatmate could be the secret to affording your first home | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500096/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's how to boost your income to get a mortgage application approved. Hosted by Frances Cook.
First home buyers are finally getting the breathing space they've needed for a while. The shocking house price increases have not only stopped, prices are falling and look like they'll continue to slide a little further.</description></item><item><title>How a near-death experience led to financial independence | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500097/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's how life priorities can change after a brush with death. Hosted by Frances Cook.
There are moments that really make you reassess what you want out of life, and losing both of your parents and then having a near death experience yourself, well, that's right up there. Combine that with a heaping dose of work burnout, and you've got the recipe for some big change.</description></item><item><title>What is shorting the share market, and should you be doing it? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500098/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's the risks and rewards of shorting the market. Hosted by Frances Cook.
There's a saying in the investing world, that you should never waste a good crisis. Another classic is that the best time to invest is when there's blood on the streets. Behind both of these is the idea that when most people are feeling fearful, there are still opportunities around for the bold, who can zig while others are zagging and get the financial rewards.</description></item><item><title>A career coach's top tips for earning more | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500099/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's how to earn more, whether that's through a pay rise or a side hustle. Hosted by Frances Cook.
One of the biggest investments you'll ever make is into your earning power. I'm a big believer that you can make changes on almost any income, but of course it's a lot easier to make progress when you're earning more.</description></item><item><title>Paying off the mortgage in five years, despite three kids | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500100/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's how one family plans to annihilate their mortgage. Hosted by Frances Cook.
It's hard enough to scrape together a house deposit and buy a place, but then comes the challenge of paying it off over 20 or 30 years. But what if you could pay it off faster than that, and get all the freedom that comes after you've got rid of one of your biggest expenses?</description></item><item><title>Five strategies to pay off the mortgage faster | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500101/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's how a few tweaks could set you free from your mortgage years earlier. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Buying and paying off your home is one of the biggest financial decisions many of us will make. But the financial journey doesn't stop on the day you buy the house. How you handle the mortgage in the years afterward can also change your financial future.</description></item><item><title>How a NZ couple used sharemarket investments to become 'work optional' in 11 years | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500102/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's the strategies one couple used to radically reduce how much they needed to work. Hosted by Frances Cook.
The idea of investing enough that you can live off the passive income often seems the stuff of dreams. Surely it's just for those who earn the mega big bucks? Or it'll take 20 years, 30 years, maybe even more.</description></item><item><title>Investing fundamentals to keep you stable through a market crash | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500103/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's strategies to stabilise your investments while the market is down. Hosted by Frances Cook, this episode is in partnership with the FMA.
For the first time, there are more people invested in shares than term deposits, and most New Zealanders over 18 have at least one investment. That's information out of the FMA's 2022 Investor Confidence research, and it means more people are taking the opportunity to build their wealth and financial security.</description></item><item><title>How to invest in shares through a crisis | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500104/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's what sharemarket investors need to know to weather the current storm. Hosted by Frances Cook.
There's a famous saying that when the tide goes out, you get to see who's been swimming naked. Well the tide is now definitely out, and there's a few people in trouble for indecent exposure. The economy is being hammered on multiple fronts, leaving the sharemarket down - way down.</description></item><item><title>Is renting dead money? Bonus episode! | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500105/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's whether you can still get ahead financially as a renter. Hosted by Frances Cook.
It's no secret New Zealanders love property, whether it's buying it for their own home, or as an investment. But is it the ticket to wealth? You'll often hear that renting is dead money, and that you shouldn't waste your time paying off someone else's mortgage.</description></item><item><title>How to deal when your property investment turns out to be a leaky home | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500106/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's property investing to become financially independent. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Investing in property is something many New Zealanders use as a way to secure their financial future. Today's guest planned to do just that, investing into properties with a plan to achieve financial independence. But the saying goes that if you want to make god laugh, tell him your plans.</description></item><item><title>How to get paid more through side hustles | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500107/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's how to find a side income that fits into your life. Hosted by Frances Cook.
We all know that life is getting more expensive by the day, and while cutting back is one way to tackle it, earning more can be a big help too. We've talked before on the podcast about ways to ask for a pay rise, but sometimes, it doesn't feel like an option right now.</description></item><item><title>Living in a tiny house on a llama farm, to become mortgage free at 31 | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500108/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's the couple who made a major lifestyle change in order to become mortgage-free. Hosted by Frances Cook.
If you needed to make a big lifestyle change, but only for five years and then you would achieve your financial goals - could you do it? That's what one couple decided to do when they had the idea to build their own tiny home, live in it, and use it to work towards building a bigger house and becoming mortgage free.</description></item><item><title>Should first home buyers buy a business instead? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500109/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's whether a business could be a better option than a first home. Hosted by Frances Cook.
A catch cry for years now has been that first home buyers feel locked out of any opportunity to buy their own home. There is a change in the air, for sure, with house prices now falling for the first time in years.</description></item><item><title>What happens to your KiwiSaver if you die? Your KiwiSaver questions answered, part two | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500110/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's part two of listener questions about KiwiSaver. Hosted by Frances Cook.
KiwiSaver has to be one of the areas where people send me the most questions, and for good reason. It’s easy to build up a big chunk of cash in there, and there pressure is on to make sure that you’re handling it right.</description></item><item><title>Your KiwiSaver questions answered, part one | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500111/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's listener questions about KiwiSaver. Hosted by Frances Cook.
KiwiSaver is a funny old thing. You tick yes on a box when you sign up to a job, start chucking some money in with each pay, and after a few years you notice to your surprise that you've built up tens of thousands of dollars.</description></item><item><title>How to take advantage of The Great Resignation, and get a pay rise | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500112/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's how to get a raise. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Your job is one of the first and biggest investments you make in your money future. Before you can save, invest, buy a house, or whatever else, you need money coming in to dedicate to your goals. Of course, the more money you have coming in, the more you can dedicate to your various goals and the faster you can achieve them.</description></item><item><title>The pitfalls DIY investors need to avoid | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500113/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's strategies to help out DIY investors. Hosted by Frances Cook.
One of the big trends of the last few years has been people trying out shares investing by themselves. Let's declare upfront, overall I'm a big fan of this. That people can now build their wealth and plan for the future by just logging into a website and putting in a few bucks is fantastic, and creates the opportunity for more people to have financial security.</description></item><item><title>How to stop buy now, pay later, unexpectedly trapping you in debt | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500114/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's how to stop debt becoming a problem. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Debt is one of those things that quite quickly becomes overwhelming. You start off with getting a few extra things on credit, but get behind on the payments. Soon the fees and interest are spiralling, and making you feel like you'll never get it paid off again.</description></item><item><title>How to spot greenwashing in your investments | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500115/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's how to avoid getting tricked by dodgy "ethical investing" claims. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Kermit the frog taught us that it's not easy being green, and boy was he right. The ethical investing sector is booming, and many investors say it's important to them that their money is going into companies doing the right thing.</description></item><item><title>Why talking about money is so hard | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500116/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's how to get on the same financial page with your partner. Hosted by Frances Cook.
They say that sunlight is the best disinfectant, but one of the most shadowy areas of our lives is also one of the most important – money. It's something that most of us don't like to talk about, even with those we live and share our lives with.</description></item><item><title>Is the housing market really about to crash? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500117/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's what's the truth behind the fear in the housing market. Hosted by Frances Cook.
There's nothing like the housing market to make us a bit hysterical. That's partly because it's such a mix of money and security. People are keen to own their own home not only to get it paid off and have a more secure financial future, but also for the lifestyle and security that owning gives you.</description></item><item><title>Brodie Kane on becoming a self-employed online creator | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500118/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500118/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's how to make self-employed life work for you. Hosted by Frances Cook.
It's a dream for many people – to start your own business, and be your own boss.
In an ideal world it allows you to focus on the projects that you find most fulfilling, and say no to the work you've always suspected was a waste of your time anyway.</description></item><item><title>Why is everything so expensive? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500119/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's what's behind the soaring cost of living, and what you can do about it. Hosted by Frances Cook.
If you're struggling to pay for, well, anything, you are far from alone right now. You'll see inflation has been hitting the headlines a lot lately, which is just the term for how things cost more as time goes by.</description></item><item><title>Why Mahé Drysdale changed everything to become a financial adviser | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500120/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500120/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's Mah&amp;eacute; Drysdale on his experience making a big career change, and his top financial tips. Hosted by Frances Cook.
I&amp;rsquo;m sure we&amp;rsquo;ve all considered it at least once &amp;ndash; completely changing careers, to something fresh, new and exciting.&amp;nbsp;
A change is as good as a holiday they say, but it&amp;rsquo;s also a great way to boost your earning power, learn new skills, and maybe just work in a field where you enjoy yourself more.</description></item><item><title>Busting the investing myths that hold you back | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500121/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's getting rid of the money mindsets that can hold you back. Hosted by Frances Cook.
A big part of the investing game is mental.&amp;nbsp;
I'm a believer that the actual nuts and bolts of investing aren't all that hard.&amp;nbsp;
You can choose to make it complicated if that's what floats your boat, but the simple ways work just as well, and arguably the simpler the better for many of us.</description></item><item><title>Is the KiwiSaver carnage as bad as it looks? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500122/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500122/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's the sea of red in your KiwiSaver, and how to work out if yours is as bad as it looks. Hosted by Frances Cook.
If you&amp;rsquo;ve looked at your KiwiSaver, or any investments lately, you&amp;rsquo;ve probably winced and wondered if you&amp;rsquo;re doing something wrong.&amp;nbsp;
For about 13 years now we&amp;rsquo;ve been in a bull market, which means values have been going up, and we&amp;rsquo;ve all got pretty used to the money game being a fairly easy one.</description></item><item><title>Would you put crypto in your KiwiSaver? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500123/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500123/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's what's happening now that the dust is settling from the crypto crash, and how the mainstream investing world is reacting to it. Hosted by Frances Cook.
The crypto world is just starting to catch its breath after what was one of the nastiest crashes in its history.
A supposedly safe stablecoin, Luna, cratered, and may never recover.</description></item><item><title>The ultimate guide to the financial help available for first home buyers | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500124/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's the ultimate guide to what first home buyers need to know to improve their chance at getting on the property ladder. Hosted by Frances Cook.
If you're a first home buyer, you need all the help you can get, and the good news is that you've just got access to a little bit more of it.</description></item><item><title>What the Budget means for your back pocket | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500125/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 20:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's the Government's announcements on tackling cost of living, and whether it will make a difference for you. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Budget day is a big deal for, well, basically all of us.&amp;nbsp;
The Government opens up its cheque book and decides who is getting what, with big ripple effects throughout the country and economy.</description></item><item><title>How to shield your investments from a chaotic year ahead | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500126/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's how to figure out an investing strategy that works in uncertain times. Hosted by Frances Cook.
It's easy to feel like a good investor when the conditions are good.&amp;nbsp;
And they've been very good for a long time now.&amp;nbsp;
Sharemarkets have been going up, property prices have been rising, debt was cheap and cheaper by the day as interest rates kept going down.</description></item><item><title>Can rising wages be a bad thing? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500127/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's why you might not feel richer despite rising wages, and how to change that. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Wages have just gone up by the highest percentage since March 2009.
That's according to the latest figures from Stats NZ, which show that wages went up 3 per cent for the quarter ending March 2022.</description></item><item><title>How to be smarter when donating to charity | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500128/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500128/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;lt;strong&amp;gt;Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, the smartest ways to donate to charity. Hosted by Frances Cook.&amp;lt;/strong&amp;gt;
You'll often hear the phrase that money can't buy happiness.
Which I agree with to a certain degree. Working yourself into the ground in order to have a pile of money that you use to simply buy more stuff, is something that won't bring most people happiness.</description></item><item><title>Mortgage wars: How to beat the banks at their own game | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500129/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500129/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week BusinessDesk and the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's how to beat the banks at their own game. Hosted by Frances Cook.
We&amp;rsquo;re back! Welcome to an all new season of the podcast.
I may have left to have a baby, but I couldn&amp;rsquo;t stay away for too long, and boy some interesting stuff happened while I was gone.</description></item><item><title>Trailer | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500130/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 03:36:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500130/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cooking the Books with Frances Cook is back for 2022! New episodes now launch Mondays at 5am - brought to you by BusinessDesk and NZ Herald!&amp;nbsp;
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to house hack your way to lower bills | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500131/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB's Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's how a few tweaks to your house could save you big bucks. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Just about everyone wants to cut back on their boring bills, so they can have more money to spend on the fun things in life.&amp;nbsp;
The biggest expenses for the average person are housing, transport and food, with housing easily taking out first place.</description></item><item><title>The KiwiSaver mistake younger people are making, that hurts first home buying | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500132/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 00:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500132/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald's Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it's the mistake being made with KiwiSavers, and how to fix it. Hosted by Frances Cook.&amp;nbsp;
KiwiSaver is really important, not only for our long term futures in retirement, but also our short term futures of buying first homes.&amp;nbsp;
Figures from the IRD show this year, in July alone, $125 million dollars was pulled out of KiwiSavers for first homes.</description></item><item><title>The career advice you need to ignore | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500133/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 16:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the career advice you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t listen to, and what you should do instead. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Your career is probably the most&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to save money while saving the planet | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500134/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 16:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the New Zealand Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how a greener lifestyle can help your back pocket. Hosted by Frances Cook.
We all know we should be doing more to save the&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why doing less can make you richer | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500135/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 16:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s a new win for the passive investing fans. Hosted by Frances Cook.
If you invest in shares, the later parts of last year probably&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Top tips to cut your food budget | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500136/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 16:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500136/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s top tips to reduce your food bill. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Food is one of those core expenses that soaks up a lot of our money, but that we can feel&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The psychology of why it's better to give than receive | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500137/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 16:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s why giving to others can give you a boost too. Hosted by Frances Cook.
This podcast focuses a lot on how to fix your finances, but once&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How the rule of 100 helps decide your investing strategy | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500138/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 16:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500138/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how a rule of thumb can give guidance on your personal investing strategy. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Time is everything when you&amp;rsquo;re&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Six ways New Zealanders save money over Christmas | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500139/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 16:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the New Zealand Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to get through the notoriously expensive Christmas season without blowing the budget. Hosted by Frances Cook.
You don&amp;rsquo;t&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why your emotions are the biggest danger when investing | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500140/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 16:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500140/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s keeping emotion in check to become a better investor. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Emotions and money are like petrol and fire. Try not to mix them if you&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Should you drain your KiwiSaver to buy a house? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500141/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 16:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s whether it&amp;rsquo;s worth draining your retirement savings to buy your first home. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Scraping together a deposit for&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The rising power of ethical investments | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500142/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 16:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500142/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s why a clean conscience could actually make you the most money. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Nobody wants to be a bad person, but sometimes,&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to successfully make money from your hobbies | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500143/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 16:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500143/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the things you need to know before monetising a hobby. Hosted by Frances Cook.
When you&amp;rsquo;re trying to get better with money, there&amp;rsquo;s on&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The tricks to op shopping like a pro | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500144/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 17:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500144/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the inside secrets to looking glam on a budget. Hosted by Frances Cook.
What&amp;rsquo;s the point of a podcast, if not abusing it to simply find&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The nuts and bolts of how to start investing | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500145/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 17:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500145/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the best ways to start investing in New Zealand. Hosted by Frances Cook.
There’s been lots of chat about whether you should be&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What to know before buying a house with friends | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500146/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 17:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500146/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the good and bad of buying a house with a friend. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Money can be particularly difficult when you&amp;rsquo;re flying solo&amp;hellip;.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The argument against maximising your KiwiSaver contributions | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500147/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 17:00:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500147/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the things you need to know before maxing out your KiwiSaver. Hosted by Frances Cook.
KiwiSaver is a wonderful scheme. You get free&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The NZer who paid off $94,000 debt in 3 years, by side hustling | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500148/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 17:00:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500148/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the woman who tackled $94,000 of debt in three years, and why she still side hustles now that she&amp;rsquo;s debt-free. Hosted by Frances Cook.
There are all&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The common insurance mistake New Zealanders are making | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500149/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 17:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500149/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to figure out what insurance is worth getting, and what&amp;rsquo;s not. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Insurance is one of those areas that gets&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to have fun for free | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500150/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 17:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500150/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how you can have fun without spending a cent. Hosted by Frances Cook.
A basic rule of personal finance is to live within your means&amp;hellip;.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>It's not goodbye, it's see you later | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500151/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 17:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500151/</guid><description>Podcast Description See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why you need a will much younger than you think | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500152/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 17:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500152/</guid><description>Podcast Description You need a will when you&amp;rsquo;re still young - much younger than you expect.
Yes I know, none of us like thinking about death, and frankly many of us feel broke and like we don&amp;rsquo;t have much to leave to loved ones, but you still should consider a will&amp;hellip;.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How the digital world is turbo-charging change in our money habits | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500153/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 17:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500153/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how smartphones are changing the way we handle our cash. Hosted by Frances Cook.
We&amp;rsquo;ve all heard about how Covid-19 forced us to do years worth of&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Will housing market changes be enough for first home buyers? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500154/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 17:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500154/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s an honest assessment of what&amp;rsquo;s next for property. Hosted by Frances Cook.
We&amp;rsquo;ve just had one of my favourite times of year – Budget Day, where the&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to make a budget that isn't about punishing yourself | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500155/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 17:00:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500155/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to write a budget that doesn&amp;rsquo;t make you miserable. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Budget.
Did you just get a shiver down your spine? Immediately clutch&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to use money to boost your happiness | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500156/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 17:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500156/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the balance between money and happiness. Hosted by Frances Cook.
I&amp;rsquo;m a firm believer that managing your money is actually about anything but money&amp;hellip;.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How far should we go in reimagining housing? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500157/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 17:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500157/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the changes that could make our housing more affordable. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Something needs to change in our housing market, that much is clear&amp;hellip;.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to decide if a do-up is worth it | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500158/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 17:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500158/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to decide whether to flex your DIY muscles. Hosted by Frances Cook.
As first home buyers struggle to get a foot on the housing ladder, a&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to land a good job and a pay rise, post-pandemic | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500159/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 17:00:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500159/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to turn the job hunt in your favour. Hosted by Frances Cook.
We&amp;rsquo;ve all seen the news about how the economy is bouncing back faster than expected,&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to financially prepare for a career break | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500160/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 17:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500160/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to make a career break financially possible. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Taking a career break sounds like a luxurious treat for the millionaires&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Can you reach financial security without a house? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500161/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 17:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500161/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how high house prices are changing the way we manage our money. Hosted by Frances Cook.
You&amp;rsquo;d have to be living under a rock to miss all the chat&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A guide to the free cash that boosts your home deposit | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500162/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 16:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500162/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s what financial help is available to first home buyers. Hosted by Frances Cook
So the government has had a jiggle around of what&amp;rsquo;s available to help&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to choose a financial advisor | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500163/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 16:00:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500163/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s what to know before you ask an expert for help with your finances. Hosted by Frances Cook.
It&amp;rsquo;s something we&amp;rsquo;ll often say on this show – we talk about&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What crypto traders expect from wary government regulators | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500164/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 16:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500164/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how the world of cryptocurrency could change as it becomes more mainstream. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Regular listeners to this podcast will know I&amp;rsquo;m&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to clean up your finances so the bank gives you a mortgage | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500165/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 16:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500165/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to get ready so the bank&amp;rsquo;s more likely to say yes to a mortgage. Hosted by Frances Cook.
We all know that house prices are soaring, making it&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>BONUS EPISODE: The OneRoof Property Panel, hot but for how long? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500166/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 16:00:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500166/</guid><description>Podcast Description See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The investing revolution that's giving smaller players more power | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500167/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 16:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500167/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s what to know if you&amp;rsquo;re a DIY investor diving into the sharemarket. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Even in the relatively small time that this podcast has&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to prepare your finances for having a baby | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500168/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 16:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500168/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s where to spend and where to skimp if you&amp;rsquo;re having a baby. Hosted by Frances Cook.
If you&amp;rsquo;re planning to have a baby it&amp;rsquo;s a really exciting time, but&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why your emotions are the biggest danger when investing | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500169/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 16:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500169/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s keeping emotion in check to become a better investor. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Emotions and money are like petrol and fire. Try not to mix them if you&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What would it take for house prices to cool down? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500170/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 16:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500170/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the forces behind house prices, and what&amp;rsquo;s likely to happen next. Hosted by Frances Cook.
If you&amp;rsquo;ve paid even the slightest attention to the news&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Do you invest or pay off debt, when interest rates are this low? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500171/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 16:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500171/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to figure out the new rules of a low interest rate environment. Hosted by Frances Cook.
It may sound unsexy, but interest rates are actually the&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What are your best job options in a post-Covid world? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500172/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 16:00:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500172/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s where to start if you&amp;rsquo;re wanting a job change. Hosted by Frances Cook.
We all know 2020 was a lot, not least because many of us found our working&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The numbers that could let you retire decades earlier | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500173/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 16:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500173/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the financial independence movement, and whether normal people can give it a try. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Financial independence is something you&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Welcome to splitting season, Covid-19 style | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500174/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 16:00:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500174/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to handle a split and the financial fallout. Hosted by Frances Cook.
January has a fun nickname in the lawyer world – &amp;ldquo;splitting season&amp;rdquo;.
After&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to watch your pennies in 2021 | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500175/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 16:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500175/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s what to expect from the year ahead of us. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Goodbye 2020, don&amp;rsquo;t let the door hit you on the way out. What a year that was.
If&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How can you prepare for the next financial emergency? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500176/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 16:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500176/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s what we can learn from how New Zealanders responded to Covid-19. Hosted by Frances Cook.
If you wanted to find out if New Zealanders are financially&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The pros and cons of a tiny home | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500177/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 16:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500177/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s whether a tiny house could be right for you. Hosted by Frances Cook.
With our housing market officially running way past hot and right into scalding&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Are alternative investments like bitcoin and gold worth it? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500178/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 16:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500178/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the allure of bitcoin, and whether it&amp;rsquo;s an investment you should consider. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Once you&amp;rsquo;ve started to dip your toe into the&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to start the money conversation with your partner | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500179/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 16:00:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500179/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to start talking money with your partner, so that you can work together better. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Talking to your partner about money is&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to check and fix your credit score | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500180/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 16:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to take control of your credit score. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Credit scores are important, but it can be hard to figure out how important they are&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to find financial stability in an unstable world | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500181/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 16:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500181/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to use your money to provide a safety net in a crazy world. Hosted by Frances Cook.
This year alone, we&amp;rsquo;ve had major wildfires in Australia and the&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What to buy when you can't buy a house | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500182/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 16:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500182/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the options for your financial future when houses are just too expensive. Hosted by Frances Cook.
OK, if you&amp;rsquo;re feeling a little frustrated by the&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The timeline of what to do with your money, when | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500183/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 16:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500183/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the different money moves you should make at different times in your life. Hosted by Frances Cook.
It&amp;rsquo;s all very well to know the basics of what you&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to pay off debt faster | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500184/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 16:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500184/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to pay off debt faster, and pay less overall. Hosted by Frances Cook.
There&amp;rsquo;s quite enough to be feeling nervous about these days, with the&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Side hustles that don't suck | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500185/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 16:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500185/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the best ways to make extra money, without wasting your time. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Well, it turns out that you guys really want to talk about side&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What the FMA makes of the explosion of new investors | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500186/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 16:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500186/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the astonishing rise of DIY investing since lockdown. Hosted by Frances Cook.
This year has seen a spike in new investors. Since the first Covid-19&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The KiwiSaver mistake younger people are making, that hurts first home buying | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500187/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 23:05:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500187/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the mistake being made with KiwiSavers, and how to fix it. Hosted by Frances Cook.
KiwiSaver is really important, not only for our long term futures&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to negotiate more money, even during a pandemic | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500188/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 20:57:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500188/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to have a conversation about pay rates that works for everyone. Hosted by Frances Cook.
It’s a little awkward to talk about pay rates at the best&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>It's time to Pivot - to The Pivot Pod | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500189/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 00:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500189/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you like Cooking the Books, you should also check out The Pivot Pod.
It’s my other podcast, focused on helping small businesses through the carnage of Covid-19.
Whether you’re a side hustler, a small business owner, or you just find that area&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to financially manage a career change | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500190/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 17:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500190/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to get yourself on firm footing so you can handle a career change. Hosted by Frances Cook.
The world tipped upside down recently, which means many&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The NZer who paid off $94,000 debt in 3 years, by side hustling | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500191/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 17:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500191/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the woman who tackled $94,000 of debt in three years, and why she still side hustles now that she&amp;rsquo;s debt-free. Hosted by Frances Cook.
There are all&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why Covid-19 has seen more people taking the leap into self-employment | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500192/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 21:13:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500192/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the rise in self-employed New Zealanders, and how to do it with more success. Hosted by Frances Cook.
What do you do when you lose your job, through no&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to save thousands on your mortgage, in good times and bad | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500193/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 22:13:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500193/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to master your mortgage whether your finances are going well, or are under stress. Hosted by Frances Cook.
If you have a question about this&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Young adults are saving and investing more – here's how to do it well | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500194/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 22:38:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500194/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how Covid-19 has shaped money management for a new generation. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Here’s the thing. Many people were already struggling&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Should you pay off the mortgage or invest? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500195/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 17:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500195/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s where to put any extra money so it&amp;rsquo;s working hardest for you. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Covid-19 shocked many of us into paying more attention to our&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The key to a budget that still lets you live life | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500196/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 17:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500196/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to build a budget that improves your life instead of restricting it. Hosted by Frances Cook.
For this year&amp;rsquo;s Money Week Sorted has pulled together&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The surprising confidence among KiwiSavers, even after Covid | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500197/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 17:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500197/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s what your KiwiSaver is trying to tell you, and how to use it. Hosted by Frances Cook.
It&amp;rsquo;s been a trial by fire lately, as the market nosedived, giving&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Top tips to cut your food budget | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500198/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 17:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500198/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s top tips to reduce your food bill. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Food is one of those core expenses that soaks up a lot of our money, but that we can feel&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why is the sharemarket strangely positive? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500199/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 17:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500199/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s why the sharemarket is acting strangely, and how to adapt your investing to that. Hosted by Frances Cook.
There’s a weird split at the moment for those&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Could a Universal Basic Income (UBI) work in NZ? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500200/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 17:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500200/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s whether a UBI could work in NZ, and what the alternatives are. Hosted by Frances Cook.
A rather radical idea has been getting more&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to use furniture flipping to make extra cash | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500201/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 17:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500201/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s a smart side hustle that could be easier than you think. Hosted by Frances Cook.
When you’re trying to manage your money, of course you&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Property is recovering, but is it enough? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500202/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 17:00:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500202/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the latest data and what could happen next for the housing market. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Property is traditionally a favourite&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why you should prepare for your KiwiSaver to go down again | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500203/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 17:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500203/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s why your KiwiSaver will probably go down again, and what to do about it. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Many of us got quite the fright in&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Core satellite: The shares investing strategy for those who like to pick winners | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500204/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 17:00:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500204/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s a shares investing strategy to give you the best of both worlds. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Here’s a conflicting issue. History and&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The easiest ways to start a garden and save on your food budget | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500205/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 17:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500205/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s reducing one of your core expenses by starting a garden. Hosted by Frances Cook.
When it comes to cutting down your budget, the biggest&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How a ‘portfolio career’ could boost your employment chances | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500206/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 17:00:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500206/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the increase in contract workers after Covid-19, and what you need to know before trying it. Hosted by Frances Cook.
When we talk about&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The tricks to op shopping like a pro | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500207/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 17:00:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500207/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the inside secrets to looking glam on a budget. Hosted by Frances Cook.
What&amp;rsquo;s the point of a podcast, if not abusing it to simply find&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Everything you need to know about renting post-lockdown | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500208/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 17:00:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500208/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s everything you need to know about your rights as a renter, and what financial help you can get. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Keeping a roof&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Your mortgage questions, answered | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500209/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 17:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500209/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s everything you need to know about mortgages and property ownership in a rapidly changing situation. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Owning your&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The easy way to claim expenses for working from home | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500210/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 17:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500210/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to get cash back for your work from home expenses. Hosted by Frances Cook.
If you’re one of the people who’s been lucky enough to&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tactics to stop your money from hurting your mental health | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500211/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 17:00:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500211/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to feel more in control of your money in the midst of uncertainty. Hosted by Frances Cook.
It’s tempting to think that money is all&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>OneRoof property panel bonus episode: How long will it take the housing market to recover from Covid-19? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500212/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 22:54:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500212/</guid><description>Podcast Description The OneRoof property panel featured a live discussion between REINZ CEO Bindi Norwell, ANZ chief economist Sharon Zollner, Valocity Global CEO Carmen Vicelich, and Barfoot &amp;amp; Thompson managing director Peter Thompson. Listen in for insights on where&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How will our work lives change after Covid-19? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500213/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 17:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500213/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s whether flexible working and changed work hours could be here to stay. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Times of crisis also give us the&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How your KiwiSaver is protected in a crisis | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500214/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 17:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500214/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how your KiwiSaver is protected, and the limits to that protection. Hosted by Frances Cook.
In a crisis our brains have a fun little&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The tech change shaping how we sell houses post-Covid 19 | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500215/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 17:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500215/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the digital changes reshaping how houses are sold. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Even as we come down to level three many businesses are&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The nuts and bolts of how to start investing | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500216/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 17:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500216/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the best ways to start investing in New Zealand. Hosted by Frances Cook.
There’s been lots of chat about whether you should be&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Scammers are already targeting you through Covid-19 | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500217/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 17:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500217/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to protect yourself from the new coronavirus scammers. Hosted by Frances Cook.
It&amp;rsquo;s a somewhat depressing quirk of humanity that in&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to boost your job prospects post-lockdown | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500218/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 17:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500218/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the first steps for finding a new job. Hosted by Frances Cook.
We’re leaving one of the longest periods of economic good times that&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The encouraging signs for our economy weathering Covid-19 | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500219/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 17:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500219/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the strengths in our economy, and how we can make the most of them. Hosted by Frances Cook.
In times of trouble, one of the best&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to make sense of the property market, whether you’re buying or selling | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500220/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 17:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500220/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to detangle the housing situation and make the most of it. Hosted by Frances Cook.
The housing market is one where there’s always&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to decide if you should make a KiwiSaver hardship application | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500221/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 17:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500221/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to weigh up whether you need to drain your KiwiSaver to survive Covid-19. Hosted by Frances Cook.
There’s been a lot of chat lately&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How you could make money from the share market going down | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500222/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 17:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500222/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s why now is actually a good time to invest, and how to do it safely. Hosted by Frances Cook.
It&amp;rsquo;s a fact of life that when the market&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What to do if you’ve lost your job and have no savings | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500223/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 17:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500223/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to sort through the different options available if you&amp;rsquo;ve lost your job. Hosted by Frances Cook.
As our economy struggles through&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Should you still buy a house in a post-Covid 19 world? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500224/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 17:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500224/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s what you should expect from the housing market, and how to adapt to it. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Your house may be your castle, but it&amp;rsquo;s&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Should you stop paying into KiwiSaver while the economy’s tanking? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500225/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 17:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500225/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s whether you should stop your KiwiSaver contributions while the market is taking a dive. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Fight, flight, or&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to prepare for a recession if you don’t have any savings | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500226/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 17:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500226/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how you can future-proof your finances even if you don&amp;rsquo;t have savings. Hosted by Frances Cook.
The rainy day has arrived. Now is the&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What to do if you’ve gone from a two income household to one | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500227/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 02:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500227/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the first steps you can take if you&amp;rsquo;ve lost your job. Hosted by Frances Cook.
We’re in tough times, and the sad reality is that many of&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Your KiwiSaver is down. Here's why it can be a good thing. | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500228/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 02:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500228/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackle a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s why the current KiwiSaver bloodbath could work in your favour. Hosted by Frances Cook.
This is the biggest test of our nerve since&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The pros and cons of taking a mortgage holiday | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500229/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 02:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500229/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how the mortgage holidays actually work, and whether you should consider one. Hosted by Frances Cook.
As jobs fall like dominoes around&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to stay calm when your money is falling apart | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500230/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 02:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500230/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s a bonus episode on how to stay calm, and access independent financial advice. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Keep calm and carry on is all&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A guide to the financial help for surviving Covid-19 | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500231/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 22:04:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500231/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s a bonus episode on what financial help is available so far, and what might be coming in the future. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Nothing&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why your KiwiSaver could be lulling you into a false sense of security | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500232/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 01:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500232/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s why you can&amp;rsquo;t just sign up to KiwiSaver, and leave it at that. Hosted by Frances Cook.
KiwiSaver is great, in that it&amp;rsquo;s helped those of&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What to be wary of when buying a house off the plans | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500233/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 16:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500233/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s what you need to check before signing a contract to buy a house off the plans. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Buying a new house off the plans&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Budgeting success comes from ditching your car, not coffee | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500234/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 16:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500234/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s why your big expenses often slip under the radar. Hosted by Frances Cook.
You&amp;rsquo;ll often hear the saying, to watch your pennies and the&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why prefab housing has been ignored until now | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500235/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 16:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500235/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s why all investments need a certain amount of safety, and how to organise that. Hosted by Frances Cook.
All but the most blinkered of&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The career advice you need to ignore | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500236/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 16:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500236/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the career advice you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t listen to, and what you should do instead. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Your career is probably the most&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to use bonds as a safe place for your money | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500237/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 16:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500237/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s why all investments need a certain amount of safety, and how to organise that. Hosted by Frances Cook.
No matter where you&amp;rsquo;re at in&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The common insurance mistake NZers are making | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500238/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 16:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500238/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to figure out what insurance is worth getting, and what&amp;rsquo;s not. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Insurance is one of those areas that gets&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The tax realities of making a side hustle work | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500239/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 16:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500239/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to stay ahead of the tax man if you&amp;rsquo;re side hustling, or self-employed. Hosted by Frances Cook.
One good way to grow your wealth&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to tell an ethical KiwiSaver from a greenwashed one | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500240/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 16:00:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500240/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to check that your retirement fund is only funding companies you&amp;rsquo;re ok with. Hosted by Frances Cook.
To say that New Zealanders&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trailer | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500241/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 23:29:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500241/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to Cooking the Books, your home for all things money.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to protect your cash in a split | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500242/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 16:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500242/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to stop a broken heart also breaking the bank. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Just like finding someone to team up with in the game of&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why financial stress could be hurting your career | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500243/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 16:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500243/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how your workplace could be helping with your money. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Money and work are clearly closely linked, but we don&amp;rsquo;t&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The reality of one NZers journey to early retirement | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500244/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 16:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500244/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how the FIRE movement works, and how New Zealanders are adapting it to their own circumstances. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Retiring&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to watch your pennies in 2020 | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500245/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 16:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500245/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s what&amp;rsquo;s changed in housing, and what it means for you. Hosted by Frances Cook.
This time last year when we tried to predict the future,&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The psychology of why it's better to give than receive | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500246/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 16:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500246/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s why giving to others can give you a boost too. Hosted by Frances Cook.
This podcast focuses a lot on how to fix your finances, but once&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How other NZers stay on budget over Christmas | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500247/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2019 16:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500247/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s why more New Zealanders are picking family time over presents. Hosted by Frances Cook.
It&amp;rsquo;s the most wonderful time of the year, or&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How money can be used to abuse | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500248/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 16:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500248/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s what needs to change to reduce financial abuse. Hosted by Frances Cook.
They say money is power, and it&amp;rsquo;s true. That&amp;rsquo;s exactly why we&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Housing is now a different game from the beginning of 2019 | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500249/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 16:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500249/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s what&amp;rsquo;s changed in housing, and what it means for you. Hosted by Frances Cook.
This year has been a huge one for changes to every New&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What to know before buying a house with friends | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500250/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 20:39:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500250/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the good and bad of buying a house with a friend. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Money can be particularly difficult when you&amp;rsquo;re flying solo&amp;hellip;.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Can passive investing be trusted? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500251/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 16:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500251/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the evidence behind the growing trend in passive investing. Hosted by Frances Cook.
The digital revolution is notorious for making&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why property investing can be so much more than renting homes | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500252/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 16:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500252/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s why ignoring commercial property could be a missed opportunity. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Getting a foot on the property ladder is part&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to budget without feeling deprived | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500253/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 16:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500253/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s why a budget could be the key to feeling less deprived, not more. Hosted by Frances Cook.
If someone tells you they&amp;rsquo;re trying to stick&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Could building be the way for first home buyers to get ahead? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500254/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 02:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500254/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s why building could be what helps those with a small house-buying budget. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Houses are now so expensive, first&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How the rule of 100 helps decide your investing strategy | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500255/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 02:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500255/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how a rule of thumb can give guidance on your personal investing strategy. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Time is everything when you&amp;rsquo;re&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Could changing KiwiSaver make home ownership easier? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500256/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 02:00:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500256/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the upcoming KiwiSaver changes you can have a say in. Hosted by Frances Cook.
A milestone of looking after your money in New Zealand is&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How money silence is hurting us all | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500257/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 02:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500257/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how just talking about money could change things. Hosted by Frances Cook.
If you would rather talk about literally anything other than&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to house hack your way to lower bills | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500258/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 02:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500258/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the newest episode of our OneRoof-partnered series, on how a few tweaks to your house could save you big bucks. Hosted by Frances Cook&amp;hellip;.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Should you protect your KiwiSaver by going conservative? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500259/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 02:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500259/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to look after your KiwiSaver now that everyone&amp;rsquo;s talking about possible recession. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Those who like to keep a&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to stop the land under your house causing headaches | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500260/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 03:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500260/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the newest episode of our OneRoof-partnered series, on how the land title could be the most important thing you&amp;rsquo;re ignoring. Hosted by&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to start a business with profits in mind | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500261/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 03:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500261/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking the Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to give your business the best chance of turning a profit. Hosted by Frances Cook.
People go into business to make money – that&amp;rsquo;s&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Could a do-up cost more than building a home? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500262/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 03:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500262/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the newest episode of our OneRoof-partnered series, on what to know before considering a do-up. Hosted by Frances Cook.
New Zealanders&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The most successful ways to travel on a budget | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500263/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 03:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500263/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to enjoy a holiday without ruining your finances. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Getting your money life sorted is important, but not at&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode! The OneRoof property panel | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500264/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 05:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500264/</guid><description>Podcast Description The OneRoof property panel makes a sneak appearance on the Cooking the Books podcast.
Hosted by Frances Cook, with panellists OneRoof editor Owen Vaughan, Lesley Harris from the First Home Buyers Club, and James Wilson from Valocity.
They discuss&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What to know when choosing between house vs apartment | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500265/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 03:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500265/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the newest episode of our OneRoof-partnered series, on how to avoid the specific pitfalls that come with each property type. Hosted by&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The NZ couple who paid off $566k of debt in three years | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500266/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 03:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500266/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the techniques used by ordinary people to pay off big debt. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Most of us know that debt isn&amp;rsquo;t good, but it&amp;rsquo;s&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to pay your mortgage off faster | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500267/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 03:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500267/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the newest episode of our OneRoof-partnered series, on the techniques that will pay off your mortgage fastest. Hosted by Frances Cook&amp;hellip;.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why term deposits aren't making the money they used to | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500268/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 03:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500268/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to master interest rates to better look after your money. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Interest rates are one of those sneaky things&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How location can give you a house that fits your lifestyle | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500269/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2019 03:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500269/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the newest episode of our OneRoof-partnered series, looking at how you can use location differently to get the house that works with&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to fix a bad credit history | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500270/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 03:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500270/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s why your history with debt matters, even if you think you&amp;rsquo;ve got it under control. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Debt can be the scary&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to get your mortgage right from the start | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500271/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 03:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500271/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the third episode of our OneRoof-partnered series, looking at the tricks to negotiating a mortgage which could save you thousands&amp;hellip;.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Finally, kids can be taught about money in school | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500272/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 03:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500272/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the changes underway to help our kids learn crucial money lessons. Hosted by Frances Cook.
I always invite you guys to send me your&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to save a house deposit on an average income | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500273/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 03:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500273/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the second episode of our OneRoof-partnered series, looking at ways to save a deposit even when you&amp;rsquo;re not rolling in it. Hosted by&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is 'degrowth' the answer to stopping workaholism? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500274/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 03:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500274/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s whether deliberately shrinking our economy could fix some of society&amp;rsquo;s problems. Hosted by Frances Cook.
The idea that growth is good&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Life stages where renting is better than buying a home | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500275/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 03:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500275/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the start of a partnership with OneRoof to walk you through the steps of buying a house. Episode one is rent vs buy. Hosted by Frances&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What you're ignoring in your KiwiSaver that could cost you $135,000 | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500276/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 03:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500276/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the KiwiSaver mistakes you can fix in minutes. Hosted by Frances Cook.
What you don&amp;rsquo;t know can definitely hurt you. Particularly when&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Myth busting the 'golden ratio' for your money | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500277/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 03:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500277/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s whether there&amp;rsquo;s an ideal way to allocate pots of money. Hosted by Frances Cook.
People seem to love the idea that you can set up a few&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The tricks to making a side hustle work | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500278/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 03:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500278/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the pitfalls to avoid when launching a side hustle. Hosted by Frances Cook.
A side hustle is one of those things that sounds great in&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why smaller houses are suddenly hot property | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500279/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 03:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500279/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, why affordable homes are bucking the trend in a property market that&amp;rsquo;s going flat. Hosted by Frances Cook.
The property market seems to&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why the sharing economy is becoming cool again | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500280/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 04:00:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500280/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how working together can stretch the budget further. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Make do and mend; it&amp;rsquo;s an old wartime slogan that more of&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What not to do in the sharemarket | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500281/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 03:29:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500281/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s what not to do in the sharemarket. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Shares are scary to some people, when they don&amp;rsquo;t need to be.
Investing in&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to turn a small windfall into a big deal, with the triangle method | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500282/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 03:30:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500282/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the triangle technique that can help you manage a small windfall. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Saving money regularly is a crucial part of&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>KiwiSaver has changed, and more is coming in the future | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500283/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 03:25:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500283/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to handle the changes to KiwiSaver, and what else might be waiting in the wings. Hosted by Frances Cook.
It’s the time of year when&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to Hatch your wagon to overseas companies | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500284/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 03:30:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500284/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the latest tech start-up aiming to make life easier for NZ investors. Hosted by Frances Cook.
People often think of investing in shares&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Unemployment is down, why aren't wages up? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500285/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 02:30:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500285/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s why pay rates are staying stubbornly low. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Workers should be thrilled right now. Unemployment is low and&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to talk to your partner about money | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500286/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 02:30:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500286/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to tackle financial infidelity. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Everyone has secrets, but there are some secrets that can do more harm than&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Can voting with your wallet force social media companies to change? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500287/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 02:30:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500287/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s whether voting with your wallet can push tech giants to change. Hosted by Frances Cook.
People power has never been so needed, after a&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to run a small business and still have a life | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500288/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 02:30:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500288/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s what small business owners need to do differently for work-life balance, and retirement. Hosted by Frances Cook.
A small business isn’t&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How robots are changing the way we invest | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500289/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 02:30:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500289/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how the digital age is changing how we handle our money. Hosted by Frances Cook.
The best thing about the digital era is how much&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How a capital gains tax will change your KiwiSaver | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500290/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 02:30:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500290/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the good and bad of a capital gains tax on your KiwiSaver. Hosted by Frances Cook.
If you heard howls of outrage and a collective&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Should first home buyers wait for the market to crash? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500291/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 02:30:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500291/</guid><description>Podcast Description See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What to do when asking for a raise doesn't work | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500292/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 02:30:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500292/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the tactics to use if you think you&amp;rsquo;re underpaid. Hosted by Frances Cook.
It’s a tough world out there trying to get a pay rise. Wages&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why doing less can make you richer | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500293/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 02:30:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500293/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s a new win for the passive investing fans. Hosted by Frances Cook.
If you invest in shares, the later parts of last year probably&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The rising power of ethical investments | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500294/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 02:30:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500294/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s why a clean conscience could actually make you the most money. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Nobody wants to be a bad person, but sometimes,&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What to do when you've left it too late to invest | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500295/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 02:30:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500295/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to tackle investing at different life stages. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Time is one of the biggest ingredients for investing success&amp;hellip;.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to cut waste and your food bill at the same time | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500296/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 02:30:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500296/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the various tactics to attack the food bill. Hosted by Frances Cook.
If you want to cut back your spending, it makes sense to focus on&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why a healthy budget can include a flamethrower | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500297/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 02:30:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500297/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s why you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be sucked in by budgeting&amp;rsquo;s image problem. Hosted by Frances Cook.
Budgeting has an image problem. Also, the sky is&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to watch your pennies in 2019 | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500298/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 02:30:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500298/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s what you need to know for the year ahead. Hosted by Frances Cook.
New year, new me, new money.
The last few years have been unstable,&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why do sales make us irrational? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500299/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2018 16:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500299/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how shops get into your head, and how to fight back. Hosted by Frances Cook.
We&amp;rsquo;re in the final throes of the season of excess, and New&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Can you afford your pet? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500300/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 03:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500300/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s what to consider before bringing home an animal companion. Hosted by Frances Cook.
We&amp;rsquo;re in the thick of puppy and kitten season, when&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ways to take a holiday without going broke | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500301/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 02:30:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500301/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to take a the best holiday for the least money. Hosted by Frances Cook.
I’m a big believer that having your money situation sorted&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: What do the mortgage changes mean for you? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500302/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 01:10:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500302/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today it&amp;rsquo;s what&amp;rsquo;s actually changed for mortgages, and how you can take advantage of it. Hosted by Frances Cook. For those who feel home ownership is&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: The argument against maxing your KiwiSaver contributions | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500303/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 01:02:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500303/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the things you need to know before monetising a hobby. Hosted by Frances Cook. KiwiSaver is a wonderful scheme. You get free money from&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: How to successfully make money from your hobbies | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500304/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 01:18:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500304/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the things you need to know before monetising a hobby. Hosted by Frances Cook. When you&amp;rsquo;re trying to get better with money, there&amp;rsquo;s on&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: Why a lotto win can ruin your finances | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500305/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 01:20:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500305/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to deal with an unexpected change in finances. Hosted by Frances Cook. Lying awake at night, dreaming of how things would be&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: Can buying with a friend get you a house? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500306/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 00:40:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500306/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to make shared equity work for you. Hosted by Frances Cook. As the talk-fest on what to do about our housing market continues, one&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: How to use the skills you have to get paid more | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500307/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 00:18:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500307/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to tip the job market in your favour. Hosted by Frances Cook. As we hurtle towards the end of the year, it can often be a time to&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: How KiwiSaver can help and hurt first home buyers | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500308/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 01:37:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500308/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the things to know if you want to buy a house using KiwiSaver. Hosted by Frances Cook. You don&amp;rsquo;t need me to tell you it&amp;rsquo;s difficult for&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: Why the OCR is the key to your financial life | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500309/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 01:10:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500309/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the subtle ways interest rates influence everything money. Hosted by Frances Cook. Talking interest rates, or the official cash rate,&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: Are the highs of high risk investing worth it? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500310/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 00:52:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500310/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s why people bother with volatile higher risk investments. Hosted by Frances Cook. When we talk about investing, we often take the time to&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: The NZ family man saving 50 percent of his income | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500311/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 01:33:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500311/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the strategies one New Zealander uses to get financial independence. Hosted by Frances Cook. Money stress is so common that the majority&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: Are you getting gouged on your electricity bill? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500312/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 01:36:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500312/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s what on earth is happening in our electricity sector. Hosted by Frances Cook. If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever shivered through a winter&amp;rsquo;s evening because&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: The smartest ways to buy a car | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500313/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 15:14:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500313/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s both the financial and practical aspects to buying the best car for you. Hosted by Frances Cook. Buying a car has so many different&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: How to shelter your KiwiSaver from life's storms | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500314/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 02:40:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500314/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s getting past the retirement scaremongering to figure out what you really need. Hosted by Frances Cook. KiwiSaver has to be the thing I&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: How to get started as a DIY investor | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500315/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 00:27:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500315/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the things to know if you want to fly solo in the sharemarket. Hosted by Frances Cook. Just getting started always seems to be the&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: What's the best investment for your life stage? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500316/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 02:50:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500316/</guid><description>Podcast Description Title: What&amp;rsquo;s the best investment for your life stage? Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the different ways to grow wealth in different stages of life. Hosted by Frances&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: How to set yourself up for a pay rise | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500317/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 02:43:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500317/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the best strategies to argue for a raise. Hosted by Frances Cook. Whether or not to give a pay rise has become a hot potato&amp;hellip;.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: The tricks to negotiating the best mortgage | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500318/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 01:01:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500318/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s why and how you should negotiate your mortgage. Hosted by Frances Cook. Hope is on the horizon for those who want to buy a house. The&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: How to talk to your kids about money | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500319/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 02:42:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500319/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to give your kids a good start with money. Hosted by Frances Cook. Family politics is hard enough without bringing money into it&amp;hellip;.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: Why a market downturn can be the best time to buy shares | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500320/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 03:08:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500320/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to brace for a market downturn. Hosted by Frances Cook. Those who like to dabble in shares have had a dream run in recent years. &amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: Have your own The Block without going broke | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500321/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 02:44:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500321/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the strategies for getting through a housing renovation. Hosted by Frances Cook. It&amp;rsquo;s easy to look at a TV show on housing renovation,&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: Why New Zealanders are scared of the sharemarket | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500322/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 03:37:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500322/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s what puts people off the sharemarket, and why it&amp;rsquo;s worth a rethink. Hosted by Frances Cook. New Zealanders have a love affair with&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: Should you drain your KiwiSaver to buy a house? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500323/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 02:03:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500323/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s whether it&amp;rsquo;s worth draining your retirement savings to buy your first home. Hosted by Frances Cook. Scraping together a deposit for your&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: The simple maths behind early retirement | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500324/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 02:49:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500324/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s what some say you need saved to achieve early retirement. Hosted by Frances Cook. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter how much you like your job, you&amp;rsquo;re&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking The Books: Is a side hustle worthwhile? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500325/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 02:27:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500325/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the options for earning more money on the side. Hosted by Frances Cook. Making extra money on the side can be an appealing idea. &amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: How to stay warm this winter without going broke | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500326/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 01:55:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500326/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to stay on top of the power bill in winter. Hosted by Frances Cook. You know it’s cold when everyone suddenly becomes a fan of&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: How much money do you need to retire? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500327/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 01:47:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500327/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s getting past the retirement scaremongering to figure out what you really need. Hosted by Frances Cook. There&amp;rsquo;s nothing more irritating&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: Know thy money personality | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500328/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 02:04:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500328/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how figuring out your money personality can give you back control. Hosted by Frances Cook. There&amp;rsquo;s a weird thing about economists, where&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking The Books: Why a simple savings account is the key to money happiness | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500329/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 00:44:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500329/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s why saving even a little bit could change your relationship with money. Hosted by Frances Cook. People often say it’s the simple things&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: The good and bad news for first home buyers | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500330/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 01:08:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500330/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the good change for first home buyers, but also a word of caution. Hosted by Frances Cook. After years of bad news for first home&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: How to squeeze the best mortgage out of your bank | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500331/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 02:18:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500331/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s what&amp;rsquo;s happening in the home loans market, and how to take advantage of that. Hosted by Frances Cook. If you manage to buy your own&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: How to stop emotions hurting your finances | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500332/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 03:25:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500332/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the strategy many people are turning to, to stop emotion hurting their finances. Hosted by Frances Cook. When it comes to watching your&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: Will political spats ruin your investments? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500333/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 01:43:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500333/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s whether grandstanding politicians could hurt your back pocket. Hosted by Frances Cook. I love a good rollercoaster. Hands in the air,&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: Should you help your kids buy a house? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500334/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 01:02:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500334/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s whether you should help your kids with the problem of getting a first home. Hosted by Frances Cook. Just when you thought the property&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: How to have fun for free | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500335/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 01:22:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500335/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how you can have fun without spending a cent. Hosted by Frances Cook. A basic rule of personal finance is to live within your means&amp;hellip;.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: Will a foreign buyers' ban help you get a house? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500336/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 01:17:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500336/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s whether it&amp;rsquo;s about to get easier to buy your own home. Hosted by Frances Cook. First home buyers will be crossing their fingers and toes&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: The unexpected ways you're hurting your credit score | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500337/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 02:01:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500337/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to use your credit score to your advantage. Hosted by Frances Cook. Most of us wouldn’t give much thought to our credit score. In&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: Don't panic, but your KiwiSaver has gone down | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500338/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 02:13:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500338/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the New Zealand Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s why you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t overreact to your KiwiSaver taking a dive. Hosted by Frances Cook. It’s satisfying watching your KiwiSaver&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why earning more won't make you rich | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500339/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 02:21:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500339/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the New Zealand Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s why a pay rise isn&amp;rsquo;t enough to solve money problems. Hosted by Frances Cook. If you&amp;rsquo;re hoping a pay rise will fix all your&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: How to save money while saving the planet | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500340/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 02:35:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500340/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the New Zealand Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how a greener lifestyle can help your back pocket. Hosted by Frances Cook. We all know we should be doing more to save the&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: Why bitcoin could be mainstream by 2019 | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500341/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 01:22:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500341/</guid><description>Podcast Description You could be forgiven for thinking cryptocurrencies, and particularly Bitcoin, are the victims of overexcited hype. That people need to cool their jets. You wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be that wrong. Through 2017 the price of Bitcoin went up over 1000 percent. Bitcoin&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking The Books: KiwiSaver myths, busted | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500342/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2018 01:03:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500342/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the New Zealand Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the common myths about KiwiSaver, and the truth behind them. Hosted by Frances Cook. If you don&amp;rsquo;t do anything else for your&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking The Books: Could you retire at 30? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500343/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 01:39:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500343/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the New Zealand Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s growing movement of people chasing financial independence, so they can retire early. Hosted by Frances Cook. There&amp;rsquo;s a reason&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books podcast: Why women need to save more for retirement | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500344/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 06:07:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500344/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the New Zealand Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s the reasons women need to save more for retirement, and how to deal with it. Hosted by Frances Cook. This episode is one of the&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: How to watch your pennies in 2018 | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500345/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 00:12:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500345/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the New Zealand Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s what to expect for your finances in the year ahead. Hosted by Frances Cook. It&amp;rsquo;s the time of year to take stock, and your&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: Where to start when you're drowning in debt | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500346/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 04:48:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500346/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the New Zealand Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s where to start if you&amp;rsquo;re in debt. Hosted by Frances Cook. This episode is one of the most popular from 2017, and originally&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: Are Boxing Day sales worth it? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500347/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 02:19:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500347/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the New Zealand Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to handle the notorious Boxing Day sales. Hosted by Frances Cook. Everyone loves to grab a bargain, but the problem is that&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: Six ways New Zealanders save money over Christmas | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500348/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 02:31:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500348/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the New Zealand Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to get through the notoriously expensive Christmas season without blowing the budget. Hosted by Frances Cook. You don&amp;rsquo;t&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: When is that golden investment a scam? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500349/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 02:51:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500349/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the New Zealand Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to protect yourself from the scammers. Hosted by Frances Cook. When you&amp;rsquo;re trying to make a buck, the lure of finding the&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: Stop friends sabotaging your career | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500350/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 03:21:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500350/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the New Zealand Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s what to do when friends and career collide. Hosted by Frances Cook. They do say that it&amp;rsquo;s not what you know, but who you know&amp;hellip;.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why sky rocketing house values won’t make you rich | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500351/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 02:48:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500351/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the New Zealand Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s why you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t start living it up just because your house value went up. Hosted by Frances Cook. If you&amp;rsquo;re anything like me,&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: The money mistakes to avoid while you’re young | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500352/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 04:15:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500352/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the New Zealand Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to make the most of your cash while you&amp;rsquo;re young. Hosted by Frances Cook. When you&amp;rsquo;re young is the best time to make the&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why you should be keeping an eye on bitcoin | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500353/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 02:44:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500353/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the New Zealand Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s working out what the fuss is about bitcoin, and whether you should be getting involved. Hosted by Frances Cook. Bitcoin,&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: How to become an investor without losing your soul | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500354/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 02:27:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500354/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the New Zealand Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to invest your money ethically. Hosted by Frances Cook. Kiwis have shown over and over again that they’re fans of ethical&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: The dangers of getting a loan from family members | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500355/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 03:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500355/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the New Zealand Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s what to stay alert for if you lend money to family. Hosted by Frances Cook. There&amp;rsquo;s an old rule that says don&amp;rsquo;t lend money to&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: Why a capital gains tax would be a good thing | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500356/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 22:12:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500356/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the New Zealand Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s what a capital gains tax would mean for the average person. Hosted by Frances Cook. Just the word - ‘tax’ - can be enough to&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: Make your KiwiSaver work harder, for free | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500357/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 03:41:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500357/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the New Zealand Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to supercharge your KiwiSaver without spending a cent. Hosted by Frances Cook. It&amp;rsquo;s been ten years since KiwiSaver&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: What to do if you’re not being paid enough | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500358/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 02:52:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500358/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the New Zealand Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to find out if you&amp;rsquo;re getting paid enough, and what to do about it. Hosted by Frances Cook. If you&amp;rsquo;re a regular Joe reading&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: Do you have what it takes to become your own boss? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500359/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 01:07:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500359/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the New Zealand Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s what it takes to start your own business. Hosted by Frances Cook. If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever dreamed of ditching the nine to five and&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: Ten ways to save a buck in your daily life | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500360/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 04:50:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500360/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the New Zealand Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s ten ways everyday people have cut their costs. Hosted by Frances Cook. Money experts are great, and can teach us a lot&amp;hellip;.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: How ignoring KiwiSaver will leave you in the lurch | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500361/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 01:11:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500361/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the New Zealand Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s what needs to change so that KiwiSaver works for those who need it the most. Hosted by Frances Cook. The idea of struggling&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the books: Can you budget and still have fun? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500362/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 04:48:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500362/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the New Zealand Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s balancing the need to budget with still letting yourself have fun. Hosted by Frances Cook. You say budget, I say no thanks. &amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: Becoming an investor for $5 | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500363/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 01:57:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500363/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the New Zealand Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s a new method for trying out the sharemarket, for those of us who aren&amp;rsquo;t already rich. Hosted by Frances Cook. Regularly saving,&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: One money tip from ... Jacinda Ardern | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500364/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 06:51:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500364/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. For the last three weeks we&amp;rsquo;ve gone political, asking the leader of each political party in Parliament for their best money tip for the average&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>One money tip from … Peter Dunne | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500365/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 03:39:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500365/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. For the last three weeks we&amp;rsquo;ve gone political, asking the leader of each political party in Parliament for their best money tip for the average&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: One money tip from … Te Ururoa Flavell | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500366/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2017 02:51:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500366/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. For the next three weeks we&amp;rsquo;ve gone political, asking the leader of each political party currently in Parliament for their best money tip for the&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: One money tip from ... PM Bill English | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500367/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 22:08:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500367/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. For the next three weeks we&amp;rsquo;ve gone political, asking the leader of each political party currently in Parliament for their best money tip for the&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: One money tip from... James Shaw | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500368/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 00:39:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500368/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the New Zealand Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. But for the next three weeks we&amp;rsquo;ve gone political, asking the leader of each political party currently in Parliament for their best money&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books podcast: One money tip from ... David Seymour | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500369/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 04:33:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500369/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. For the next three weeks we&amp;rsquo;ve gone political, asking the leader of each political party currently in Parliament for their best money tip for the&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: What do you do when the bubble bursts? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500370/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 01:03:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500370/</guid><description>Podcast Description OPINION: Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s why you need to expect investments to go bad, and what you can do about it. Hosted by Frances Cook.
It&amp;rsquo;s the age old advice:&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: Forget giving up coffee, save the big bucks | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500371/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 01:40:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500371/</guid><description>Podcast Description OPINION: Each week the New Zealand Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s targeting the biggest areas to make savings. Hosted by Frances Cook. Whenever people starting talking budget advice,&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: Why women need to save more for retirement | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500372/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 02:52:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500372/</guid><description>Podcast Description OPINION: Each week the New Zealand Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it’s the reasons women need to save more for retirement, and how to deal with it. Hosted by Frances Cook. Many of us aren’t&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: KiwiSaver dos and don’ts | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500373/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 00:59:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500373/</guid><description>Podcast Description OPINION: Each week the New Zealand Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s celebrating Kiwisaver&amp;rsquo;s birthday with the biggest dos and don&amp;rsquo;ts. Hosted by Frances Cook. Happy birthday, KiwiSaver&amp;hellip;.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: Is a university degree worth it? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500374/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 03:07:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500374/</guid><description>Podcast Description OPINION: Each week the New Zealand Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s whether university is still your golden ticket to a good career. Hosted by Frances Cook. When I was in high school,&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: Protect your money from the scammers | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500375/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 05:04:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500375/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how scammers will try to get your cash, and what you can do to stop them. Hosted by Frances Cook. Nigeria&amp;rsquo;s royal family must be&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: The false security of KiwiSaver | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500376/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 01:44:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500376/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s why KiwiSaver default schemes are a horrible idea, and what to do about it. Hosted by Frances Cook. If your KiwiSaver is in a default&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking The Books: Boost your karma while protecting your wallet | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500377/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 01:19:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500377/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week, the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to donate smart and make your charitable dollars go further. Hosted by Frances Cook. OPINION: Just because you&amp;rsquo;re feeling&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: How to save money on your power bill this winter | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500378/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 04:01:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500378/</guid><description>Podcast Description OPINION: Each week, the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to save money on your power bills this winter. Hosted by Frances Cook. Tomorrow is the first day of winter, and along&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: The rookie investor's guide to the sharemarket | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500379/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 04:02:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500379/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week, the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to ease into the sharemarket. Hosted by Frances Cook. Investing is a tricky thing to dip your toe into, especially if you&amp;rsquo;ve only&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: How to get your free government cash | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500380/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 21:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500380/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each week, the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to get your free government cash. Hosted by Frances Cook. Would you like free money? How about $500, and you barely have to do a&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: How to be better with money from today | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500381/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2017 01:04:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500381/</guid><description>Podcast Description OPINION: Each week, the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to change your money habits for the better, starting today. Hosted by Frances Cook. It&amp;rsquo;s so easy to ignore things that&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: Rent smarter and save money | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500382/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 22:46:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500382/</guid><description>Podcast Description OPINION: Each week, the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to guard your pennies if you&amp;rsquo;re renting your house. Hosted by Frances Cook. If it&amp;rsquo;s not enough that many people are locked&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: Is debt ever a good idea? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500383/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 02:10:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500383/</guid><description>Podcast Description OPINION: Each week, the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Hosted by Frances Cook. We&amp;rsquo;re a nation with a debt problem. Many New Zealand borrowers have debt that&amp;rsquo;s up to 12 times the amount they&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: Investing for rookies | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500384/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 00:40:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500384/</guid><description>Podcast Description OPINION: Each week, the NZ Herald and Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s Cooking The Books podcast tackles a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s how to start investing when you&amp;rsquo;re a rookie. Hosted by Frances Cook. I am a wage slave. I clock into work for a certain number&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking the Books: Is your boss ripping you off? | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500385/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 03:34:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500385/</guid><description>Podcast Description OPINION: Each week, the Herald/Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s new Cooking The Books podcast will tackle a different money problem. Today&amp;rsquo;s looks at older people and women being paid less for their work, on average. So what can employees do? Hosted by Frances Cook. Pay&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cooking The Books: What to buy when you can't buy a house | Cooking the Books with Frances Cook</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1848500386/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2017 01:59:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1848500386/</guid><description>Podcast Description OPINION: Each week, the Herald/Newstalk ZB&amp;rsquo;s new Cooking The Books podcast will tackle a different money problem. Today, it&amp;rsquo;s what first-home buyers can do if they&amp;rsquo;re feeling locked out of the market. Hosted by Frances Cook. You might have noticed a&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>