<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Murder in Apartment 12 on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/murder-in-apartment-12/</link><description>Recent content in Murder in Apartment 12 on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/murder-in-apartment-12/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Special sneak peek of “Morrison Mysteries” | Murder in Apartment 12</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9449190011/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9449190011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey, Dateline fans! As a bonus, we’re giving you a special preview clip from season 2 of our podcast Morrison Mysteries. This season, Keith Morrison is taking us to Victorian England for Charles Dickens’ classic, A Christmas Carol. If you like what you hear, just search “Morrison Mysteries” for the full story or click here: https://link.chtbl.com/mms2_fdlw
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Keith Morrison reads “A Christmas Carol” | Murder in Apartment 12</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9449190010/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9449190010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey Dateline fans! As a bonus for you, we’re sharing the trailer for season 2 of our podcast Morrison Mysteries… Each season, Keith Morrison takes listeners on a captivating ride through some of the most suspenseful and chilling works of fiction you’ll ever hear. Haunting stories of ghosts, love triangles, jealousy and rage – and now in the spirit of the holidays, he’s taking us to Victorian England for Charles Dickens’ classic, A Christmas Carol.</description></item><item><title>Dateline presents: Mortal Sin | Murder in Apartment 12</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9449190009/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9449190009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey, Dateline fans! As a bonus, we’re giving you a special preview clip of our new podcast series Mortal Sin. In Dateline’s latest original podcast series, Josh Mankiewicz tells a twisted tale about a seemingly perfect couple, sex, lies, religion…and murder. If you like what you hear, you can listen to the first 2 episodes now for free, or subscribe to Dateline Premium on Apple Podcasts to get access to new episodes 1 week early.</description></item><item><title>Introducing: Mortal Sin | Murder in Apartment 12</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9449190008/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9449190008/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a bonus for you, we’re sharing the trailer for Mortal Sin, an all-new original podcast series from Dateline. Dawn and Nick Hacheney are the perfect couple: spiritual, loving, and devoted to the church where Nick is a pastor. When Dawn is killed in a house fire the day after Christmas, the pastor and his flock are devastated. What few knew at the time was the dark prophecy that foretold it&amp;hellip; Follow now to get the first two episodes on December 5th completely free, or you can subscribe to Dateline Premium on Apple Podcasts to start listening now, ad-free: https://link.</description></item><item><title>6 - Another Night in December | Murder in Apartment 12</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9449190001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9449190001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nearly 13 years to the day after Nona’s murder, a woman has a chilling encounter with a predator in the night.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>5 - Receipts | Murder in Apartment 12</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9449190002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9449190002/</guid><description>Podcast Description A new suspect says he has an alibi, but can he prove it?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>4 - Ozark | Murder in Apartment 12</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9449190003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9449190003/</guid><description>Podcast Description A jury holds the fate of Nona’s boyfriend in its hands.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>3 - The Talk of the Town | Murder in Apartment 12</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9449190004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9449190004/</guid><description>Podcast Description When police name a suspect, the court of public opinion all but convicts him.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>2 - The Night of the Visitation | Murder in Apartment 12</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9449190005/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9449190005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Investigators focus on a man with Nona’s blood on his hands.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>1 - Death of a Beauty Queen | Murder in Apartment 12</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9449190006/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9449190006/</guid><description>Podcast Description The murder of 19-year-old Nona Dirksmeyer shakes the community of Russellville, Arkansas to its core.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Introducing: Murder in Apartment 12 | Murder in Apartment 12</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9449190007/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 14:27:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9449190007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nona Dirksmeyer is a young beauty queen. Smart and talented, her future is bright. But just days before her 20th birthday, Nona is murdered in her apartment. Police quickly decide their primary suspect is the young man who found her – her boyfriend, Kevin. After all, his bloody palm print is at the crime scene. Case closed? Not by a long shot. In Dateline’s latest original podcast series, Keith Morrison tells the story of three trials, two suspects, and one small town where things are not always what they seem.</description></item></channel></rss>