<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Rituals on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/categories/rituals/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Rituals on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/categories/rituals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Rituals - E50 • The Magical, Mystical HPB (NOT Haunted Peanut Butter)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600050/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600050/</guid>
        <description>0:04
It takes a special kind of person to be called the most important impostor and all of a called history.
But also the person who ran interpreted spiritualism to the point that she inspired the West to look to ancient traditions for spiritual guidance, I&amp;rsquo;m already in awe of this person, quite a logline for one person.
0:23
It is it is this is going to be a very adventurous episode about Madame blavatsky and you can call Her a fraud, but what you can&amp;rsquo;t say is she wasn&amp;rsquo;t impactful and this is a wild story, okay?</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E49 • The Lord of Gravity</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600049/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600049/</guid>
        <description>0:05
Hey, I&amp;rsquo;m do you think if an apple fell on my head that maybe I would come up with a super genius idea like the law of gravity that Sir Isaac Newton came up with.
So yeah, I will say only you because you&amp;rsquo;ve been through shockingly weirder things.
0:21
So I think if you said, oh yeah, an apple hit me in the head.
Now I&amp;rsquo;m a physicist world-renowned, that&amp;rsquo;s true, either.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E48 • Dion Fortune: Gatekeeper, Groundbreaker, Past-Life Priestess</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600048/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600048/</guid>
        <description>0:06
Am I gotta say not to brag, but I think we have the coolest jobs ever because we get to sit here every week and talk about all things magical and mystical.
First of all, we could not have done this job a few decades ago, there&amp;rsquo;s that Trend where it&amp;rsquo;s like, try telling a pilgrim, what life is like today.
0:22
Oh no, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t imagine having to tell somebody that we get to talk about all the spooky things.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E47 • The Countercultural Life of William S. Burroughs</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600047/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600047/</guid>
        <description>0:06
Back in the 40s and 50s writer.
William esper has helped create the Beat Generation which was a counterculture movement, the documented drug culture and inspired generations of artists.
So that should tell you that burrows was never part of a mainstream mindset, like most people in the world of rituals, the world of rituals, it&amp;rsquo;s full of weirdos like us.
0:24
We have ourselves a little Universe.
At this point, we&amp;rsquo;re all a bunch of oddballs.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E46 • Grimoires</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600046/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600046/</guid>
        <description>0:03
All right everyone pull out your book of spells.
It&amp;rsquo;s grimoires appreciation day grimoires.
If you&amp;rsquo;re wondering what on Earth just came out of my mouth are legendary books where you&amp;rsquo;ll find rituals charm spells instructions which craft laws.
0:19
And so on that have influenced generations of spiritualists.
It&amp;rsquo;s the only as equi pedia collection.
I think I would like to own.
Yeah.
Officially you&amp;rsquo;ll have a library and it&amp;rsquo;ll just be Renoir&amp;rsquo;s.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E45 • The Magic of “Pellars” &amp; The Life of Tamsin Blight</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600045/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600045/</guid>
        <description>0:04
The story of Tamsin blight, has it all sorcery a drama-filled marriage and an enterprising business woman / which at the center of it.
Okay?
TLC.
Are you on it?
The sounds like a reality show.
Well, all of it took place in the 1800&amp;rsquo;s in Cornwall England, which has been called the Salem of Britain.
0:24
So that&amp;rsquo;s, which has over there.
I take it back.
If I know I&amp;rsquo;ve said things about time travel, but if I were to time travel, I think this is my new destination.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E44 • Mesopotamian Magic</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600044/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600044/</guid>
        <description>0:04
All right, I&amp;rsquo;m on this podcast.
We often go back in time.
To examine some pretty old sometimes pretty obscure.
Rituals, people and Concepts, which is sort of like our way of time traveling through the world.
Mmm, it&amp;rsquo;s the closest we&amp;rsquo;ll ever get, certainly, yeah, and I&amp;rsquo;ll Embrace that for sure.
0:21
Good.
Well, today, we&amp;rsquo;re going back real far to the very birthplace of civilization to the very Genesis of Life.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E43 • Petronilla de Meath, the Wealthy Witch’s Scapegoat</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600043/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600043/</guid>
        <description>0:07
All right, I am I gotta warn you because when the research team at par cast, lets us know that an episode is going to be frustrating.
When many of our episodes are already frustrating, you got to think it means something.
So I want to warn you, today&amp;rsquo;s episode will be a little frustrating.
0:24
Will try to decide whether young servant took the fall for her wealthy boss or whether she was a willing, Participant in Witchcraft and perhaps both.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E42 • Witchcraft &amp; The Origins of Wicca</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600042/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600042/</guid>
        <description>0:03
When someone says Wicca, it&amp;rsquo;s hard to not immediately think of witches.
And this obviously makes me think of all my favorite, which has my personal favorite, obviously, the Scarlet Witch, also the Halliwell sisters, the Sanderson sisters, Sabrina my stepmom.
You name it.
I thought stinky, which was your favorite but I guess she&amp;rsquo;s at the bottom of the list low blow.
0:24
For those who don&amp;rsquo;t know.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E41 • What’s the Deal with Crystals?</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600041/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600041/</guid>
        <description>0:05
Crystal&amp;rsquo;s, they&amp;rsquo;re sparkly, shiny come in, all colors and shapes and can maybe help heal you.
So today we&amp;rsquo;re talking all about energy and the energy that crystals have.
I&amp;rsquo;m very excited about this one.
You had me at sparkly and shiny, their Glam, their Glitz &amp;amp; Glam.
0:23
I&amp;rsquo;ve always here for the glitz but I&amp;rsquo;m very excited.
All stuck energy.
Mine is especially odd today so let&amp;rsquo;s see.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E40 • Emma Hardinge Britten &amp; The 7 Principles of Spiritualism</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600040/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600040/</guid>
        <description>0:06
You know that feeling when you see someone so talented, smart driven, just crashing It All Around Me, Christine that it makes you wonder what you&amp;rsquo;re doing with your life.
Yeah, it&amp;rsquo;s like a year living in a permanent Shadow sounds familiar.
It does I feel for you often know really?
0:21
Is there anybody in your world that you admire particularly?
Yeah I mean a lot of people It&amp;rsquo;ll cool.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E39 • Astral Projection</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600039/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600039/</guid>
        <description>0:05
Have you ever wished?
You could just disappear and be somewhere else, completely?
And be careful what you say.
Cuz you better not offend me.
Well now I wish I wasn&amp;rsquo;t here often.
Yes.
Usually when I wish I was somewhere else.
It&amp;rsquo;s under the covers unconscious but do go on.
0:22
Yeah I thought maybe you would agree with me on that one.
Well today we&amp;rsquo;re going on a journey to another dimension but don&amp;rsquo;t worry.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E38 • Hermes Trismegistus, Father of Occult Wisdom</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600038/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600038/</guid>
        <description>0:05
If you&amp;rsquo;re a music fan, you know, that James Brown was called the hardest-working man in show business because he was a singer, a songwriter dancer and bandleader.
But today, we&amp;rsquo;ve got the hardest-working deity in Antiquity Hermes trismegistus.
This last ten syllables.
0:21
You just said, really threw me for a loop.
He&amp;rsquo;s also known as the hardest-working deity in Antiquity with the craziest name.
The yes, truly.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E37 • Drinking Blood (And Other Catholic Sacraments!)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600037/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600037/</guid>
        <description>0:04
All right, the day you&amp;rsquo;ve been waiting for has finally arrived.
It&amp;rsquo;s time to talk about Catholicism.
Oh, thank God.
I have been waiting.
I know, I know today.
My Catholic school education is taking Center Stage, because if you think about it, when people hear spiritualism or the occult, the things we talked about on this show, people tend to connect that with religion, often times organized, religion.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E36 • Chico Xavier and His Ghost Writers</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600036/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600036/</guid>
        <description>0:06
Christine, I have a morbid question to kick off today&amp;rsquo;s episode.
Oh, how many people would you think show up to a normal funeral?
Oh, let&amp;rsquo;s see, probably like 40 to 50, I don&amp;rsquo;t know.
Well I don&amp;rsquo;t actually have an average stat for you but oh well I just want to see what you&amp;rsquo;d say well in June 2002 and Brazil over the span of two days.
0:30</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E35 • The Vardø Witch Trials</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600035/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600035/</guid>
        <description>0:04
All right, I am today.
We&amp;rsquo;re talking misogyny.
Racism, intolerance.
Oh my, your typical Tuesday.
Got it.
Okay.
Difficulties day on this show, talking about every other Ordinary Day in the US of a.
Okay, let&amp;rsquo;s go the day-to-day Antics.
We always go through.
0:21
So today we have yet, another case, surprise, surprise of women being persecuted whoo-hoo and just what do you think?
Think it couldn&amp;rsquo;t get any worse.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E34 • The Occult Swindler</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600034/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600034/</guid>
        <description>0:04
Christine today&amp;rsquo;s episode is going to boil down to one little thing and that is persuasion, who.
Well as someone who is easily persuaded to do things, I will buckle up.
Lend me your ears Christine because you&amp;rsquo;re going to see, just how, how good one man, Giacomo Casanova was a persuading people to believe he was a full-time occultist and Got them to basically make him a social Elite Force.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E33 • Sex Coffins &amp; Moon Babies</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600033/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600033/</guid>
        <description>0:05
Am I have great news today, we re visiting an old friend from a past episode were revisiting mr.
Jack Parsons.
Oh, well I remember, freaking out about him last time because I realized he was involved, somehow, very distantly and Project, Pegasus?
Okay, excited to learn more about him today.
0:23
Besides my own fun fact, we&amp;rsquo;re full of fun facts today.
I cannot wait to tell you we often talk about a cult Groups or spiritual events that include certain people like Jack Parsons, but sometimes we need to get a little more personal and kind of dive into their life and figure out who they are.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E32 • The Book of the Dead</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600032/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600032/</guid>
        <description>0:08
It&amp;rsquo;s the question humans have been asking since the beginning of time.
What happens after you tie?
I hope you&amp;rsquo;re not asking me because I don&amp;rsquo;t know the answer.
Okay, well, good.
We&amp;rsquo;re starting strong, some cultures believe death was just the beginning.
A chance to wipe the Slate clean and be reborn for an eternity and Utopia.
0:26
But not before a little mummification and Magic.
Well, of course.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E31 • The Ancient Mystical Order of the Rose Cross</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600031/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600031/</guid>
        <description>0:04
If there&amp;rsquo;s one thing I know about you and me and it&amp;rsquo;s that we love a good secret society.
I&amp;rsquo;m so excited.
Imagine studying the mysteries of Life, maybe even finding some answers and then only sharing what you&amp;rsquo;ve learned with a secret group of people.
0:20
So like a juicy group chat.
Yeah, there you go.
It&amp;rsquo;s like its own little WhatsApp.
Just for all the secrets of Life, L League of Their Own Rosicrucianism, isn&amp;rsquo;t an attractive topic on Paper.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E30 • Secrets to Immortality</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600030/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600030/</guid>
        <description>0:05
We&amp;rsquo;ve got a double dose of a cult mythology today.
The life of Nicholas Flamel and the Mystery of the Philosopher&amp;rsquo;s Stone, both are forever connected to each other.
So it only makes sense that we have a twofer.
I love it.
I love a little, double whammy.
0:21
Did I agree with you and I hope you&amp;rsquo;re ready to search for the secrets to immortality Christy because some say it&amp;rsquo;s possible Nicholasville Well, is still out there alive even though he was born in the 14th century, okay?</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E29 • Demonic Naked Mole Rats!</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600029/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600029/</guid>
        <description>0:05
You know, I am.
I am tired of talking about humans on this show.
So later animals little baby, yeah, I was going to say fur babies.
I feel like that&amp;rsquo;s become kind of allergy.
Is that shoe?
You know, precisely.
I never know what to chew.
0:20
Guinea more, but I&amp;rsquo;ll just say chuji anymore.
Maybe that&amp;rsquo;s not cool anymore either.
I don&amp;rsquo;t know.
Is saying chuji, chuji.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E28 • Pranks or Paranormal The Fox Sisters</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600028/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600028/</guid>
        <description>0:05
It&amp;rsquo;s rituals, believe it or not today, because at the end of this episode, excuse you, I&amp;rsquo;m not allowing you to finish.
Just kidding.
Keep going.
Because at the end of this episode, we&amp;rsquo;re going to decide whether the story I&amp;rsquo;m about to tell you is true or pure fiction.
0:22
Oh boy.
Another one where we have to decide.
Yeah, it&amp;rsquo;s a thinker just like the mall and you&amp;rsquo;re about to hear the story of the Sisters, but not every detail but enough to make a judgment call but true or false.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E27 • The Exorcism of Roland Doe</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600027/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600027/</guid>
        <description>0:07
Buckle up em.
It&amp;rsquo;s story time.
It&amp;rsquo;s late at night at a home outside Washington, d.c. a group of priests gather around a sleeping child strapped, to a bed.
They&amp;rsquo;re ready to go to battle against a spirit trapped inside the teen.
Hmm.
0:22
It sounds stressful.
It sounds because I spooky but yeah, stressful also very so stressful.
The furniture shakes objects fly across the room and everyone is aghast as the child thrashes violently today.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E26 • Harry Houdini&#39;s Campaign Against Spiritualism</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600026/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600026/</guid>
        <description>0:08
I think it&amp;rsquo;s safe to say Harry.
Houdini is a legend and the World of Magic.
And one of the most iconic Escape artists who&amp;rsquo;ve ever lived.
Certainly I know he is a personal hero of yours, he sure is.
And the reason I&amp;rsquo;m bringing him up today is because while magicians don&amp;rsquo;t usually reveal the secrets to their tricks, Houdini once went on a crusade against spiritualism to expose mediums and psychics as frauds.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E25 • Hitler&#39;s Jewish Psychic</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600025/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600025/</guid>
        <description>0:05
Today&amp;rsquo;s story is going to be a wild ride to say, the very least.
It is the true story of a showman / psychic / tabloid publisher who advised Hitler and was known as the prophet of the Third Reich, right Reich.
I don&amp;rsquo;t know how you say it, your German.
0:21
So I don&amp;rsquo;t want to sound like to German, you know what I mean?
Well I don&amp;rsquo;t know if there&amp;rsquo;s such a thing.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E24 • The Ever-Subversive Éliphas Lévi</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600024/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600024/</guid>
        <description>0:05
Bonjour Christine, did you know?
My name is actually French, so that is a pretty fitting.
I don&amp;rsquo;t know how to say it in French usual.
Christine, I don&amp;rsquo;t know em, that&amp;rsquo;s beautiful.
Thank you were going to Paris today kids because we have to talk about arguably one of the most important figures in the Revival of ceremonial magic, Haley fast.
0:26
They be what?
Oh, my gosh.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E23 • The Evil Eye</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600023/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600023/</guid>
        <description>0:04
All right, picture this someone you know, who can give the most serious dirtiest look in the world.
And here is that me?
And how does that look make you feel em every time.
0:22
It makes me scared and intimidated and got wrenched, you name it and I&amp;rsquo;m that tough.
Well, okay, it&amp;rsquo;s working.
Well, I guess I&amp;rsquo;m doing things, right?
Okay, great.
You&amp;rsquo;re very good at it.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E22 • The Occult Legend You’ve Never Heard Of</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600022/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600022/</guid>
        <description>0:04
You&amp;rsquo;ve heard of rags to riches, but today we have a rags-to-riches shules story.
Christine.
I see what you did there.
It&amp;rsquo;s a man who faced tough obstacles in his personal life and you spiritualism and the Occult support himself up.
Whoo, I aspire to be that way.
0:19
One day, using a cult to pull myself up, you&amp;rsquo;ll get there.
And if you don&amp;rsquo;t know, Pascal, Beverly Randolph, there may be a reason why you don&amp;rsquo;t know him.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E21 • Man of Science, Goddess of Sexuality</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600021/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600021/</guid>
        <description>0:06
You know, the dinner scene in the movie, Beetlejuice, where they all become possessed.
Mhm.
Yeah, that&amp;rsquo;s dream dinner.
Party is what I call it, sort of seems like, what we do every Saturday night, but that aside the entire idea is contacting the spirit world and being able to talk to them in the real world, that&amp;rsquo;s kind of the idea there.
0:23
Aha, been there done that next.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E20 • William Butler Yeats</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600020/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600020/</guid>
        <description>0:03
It feels like a good time to meet another popular figure in the world of the occult and spiritualism and if you&amp;rsquo;re going to be in the game, we have to understand the players I say as an athlete I want to.
Yeah, I want to be part of the team.
Let me in William Butler Yeats is a poet that many people have probably studied in school and he&amp;rsquo;s not the first writer poet that we&amp;rsquo;ve talked about who has dabbled in the occult, and put it in their work, and he won&amp;rsquo;t be the last time.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E19 • The Emerald Tablet</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600019/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600019/</guid>
        <description>0:01
Hi podcast, listeners.
It&amp;rsquo;s Vanessa with some incredible news you can purchase your copy of our book Cults.
Inside the world&amp;rsquo;s, most notorious groups and understanding the people who joined them available.
Now at par cast.com, Colts Colts is an expanded.
0:17
Look at the people who led and followed the most radical groups in history with an unflinching exploration into what happens when the most vulnerable.
Recesses of the Mind are twisted into the lowest forms of violence details, not featured on our podcasts for so proud to bring you this fantastic compilation of stories.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E18 • The Hypnotic Life of Andrew Jackson Davis</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600018/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600018/</guid>
        <description>0:00
Hi listeners.
It&amp;rsquo;s Vanessa for years, park has worked.
Tirelessly to bring you an unprecedented.
Look at history&amp;rsquo;s.
Most radical True Crime events.
Your support has, not only allowed us to keep exploring these stories but has driven us to keep expanding as well.
0:17
So as a thank you to the park has listeners.
I am honored to announce the release of our first book Cults.
Inside the world&amp;rsquo;s most notorious groups and understanding the people who joined them it&amp;rsquo;s available.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E17 • The Mad Monk’s Mysticism</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600017/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600017/</guid>
        <description>0:08
It&amp;rsquo;s safe to say having a healthy skepticism around spiritualism is a good thing.
Especially when you hear stories about people who are described as self-proclaimed fill in the blank.
So either a Healer, a fortune teller, a again fill in the blank, it&amp;rsquo;s safe to say you can enter with a little bit of caution.
0:26
Healthy caution is definitely the way to go.
Yeah, I agree.
So we&amp;rsquo;re talking about Rasputin today.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E16 • The Witch Camps of Ghana</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600016/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600016/</guid>
        <description>0:06
I won&amp;rsquo;t sugarcoat the fact that today is not going to be a lights topic, but it is an important topic to bring attention to some abuses.
Under the guise of Witchcraft, which is still happening today.
This was not just centuries ago.
Wow, yeah.
I feel like we always kind of coat the stories we cover in, you know, old timey.
0:27
The fact that it happened a long time ago, makes it a little easier.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E15 • It’s My Party, I Can Scry If I Want To</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600015/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600015/</guid>
        <description>hi listeners it&amp;rsquo;s vanessa
for years parcast has worked tirelessly to
bring you an unprecedented
look at history&amp;rsquo;s most radical true crime events
your support has not only allowed us to keep exploring
these stories
but has driven us to keep expanding as well
so as a thank you to the parcast listeners i am
honored to announce the release of our first book
cults inside the world&amp;rsquo;s most notorious</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E14 • I’m King James, Witch!</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600014/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600014/</guid>
        <description>0:08
We&amp;rsquo;re talking about King James today, and let me say this, if there was social media in the 16th and 17th century King James would be a top influencer.
Oh, an influencer and influence are like you and me.
Right?
Well, I was verified like 14 months not that anyone&amp;rsquo;s counting after you were.
0:26
So I feel like if anyone&amp;rsquo;s a top influencer, it&amp;rsquo;s you, I&amp;rsquo;m not sure.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E13 • The Occultist’s Guide to Happiness</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600013/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600013/</guid>
        <description>0:08
He was called the wickedest man in the world by the press and proclaimed himself, the great Beast. 666 M.
Do you have any idea who I&amp;rsquo;m talking about?
And it&amp;rsquo;s not you before you save me.
Okay?
Well, let me edit that out of my notes.
My runner-up is like a Zak Bagans situation.
0:23
I feel like he would proudly claim either of those titles.
But yeah, he probably does have that tattooed on him somewhere.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E12 • Naked Baking (&amp; Other Things We Do For Love)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600012/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600012/</guid>
        <description>0:08
Once upon a time before dating apps where you could swipe your way to love, there were love potions and they were little treats made with special specific ingredients.
Some magic to get that special someone to love you back.
Not at all, toxic.
0:23
Not at all manipulative.
Yeah.
It seems like a big red flag in the making.
Yeah, and love potions can Only be glamorized.
But as you can probably assume.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E11 • The Occult Interests of Sylvia Plath</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600011/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600011/</guid>
        <description>0:07
Poets.
Like Sylvia, Plath, lived by that old adage write what, you know, sadly Sylvia Plath was diagnosed with depression and her work reflected, that at times.
But it&amp;rsquo;s also something people connected with in her work.
Sure.
Yeah, I think universally, we could all relate to that at some point and writing.
0:23
It&amp;rsquo;s a little, relatable little vulnerable.
Yeah, if you read all of Sylvia&amp;rsquo;s work, you&amp;rsquo;ll also find her talking about the occult witchcraft.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E10 • Spiritualism’s Favorite Board Game</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600010/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600010/</guid>
        <description>0:06
We&amp;rsquo;ve talked a lot about seances and mediums and the general concept of reaching out to the other side.
But the mainstream OG of connecting two Spirits has to be the Ouija board, classic classic stuff.
And you may or may not know, we just back story but it had a pretty fast rise to fame and there&amp;rsquo;s also some science behind how it works.
0:25
So grab your planchette and get ready.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E9 • The Voodoo Queen of New Orleans</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600009/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600009/</guid>
        <description>0:04
All right.
I&amp;rsquo;m today we get to talk about New Orleans, one of the most haunted places in America, according to most people including us as well.
We love New Orleans, spookiest town that you ever did see in the United States.
One of our favorites.
We love it there and New Orleans is also where you find the legend of Marie Laveau aka the voodoo queen of the city and some say, she&amp;rsquo;s still there, literally in spirit.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E8 • High School Hexes &amp; Oh, Holy Knights</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600008/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600008/</guid>
        <description>0:04
It feels more obvious with spiritualism where we see adaptations of ideas spread across a lot of different religions, but it happens with the occult as well.
Everything is connected is what you&amp;rsquo;re telling me.
So what we get is maybe a true origin story that then gets tainted by centuries of conspiracy theories and appropriation.
0:25
I mean, it sounds sounds about right.
Everything&amp;rsquo;s connected.
Everything&amp;rsquo;s at listen.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E7 • Seances in the White House</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600007/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600007/</guid>
        <description>0:07
Seances are one of those areas of spiritualism that can be polarizing, but spiritualism is also personal and seances can be very personal.
I cannot wait to hear about this topic.
I don&amp;rsquo;t even know what else to say except tell me more.
Well, I think today&amp;rsquo;s topic is super interesting because we have seances taking place in the white house.
0:29
But again for very personal reasons, okay?</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E6 • Angel Amulets and Demon Babies</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600006/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600006/</guid>
        <description>0:05
For those of you that have heard of Lilith Fair, the all-female Music Fest.
I&amp;rsquo;m curious, how many actually, no, its namesake.
Do you know who Lilith is or who she was?
I guess I&amp;rsquo;ve heard the name.
I don&amp;rsquo;t, I know it&amp;rsquo;s something potentially demonic but then again, so are you so high?
0:25
It&amp;rsquo;s baby a name you go by.
I&amp;rsquo;m not.
You just switched me.
Yeah, you&amp;rsquo;re confusing me until it happens.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E5 • Werewolf Trials</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600005/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600005/</guid>
        <description>0:05
I would say almost every Supernatural monster has a real life origin story and that includes werewolves.
Now.
I&amp;rsquo;m not saying they&amp;rsquo;re real but they do have a very real past.
They were real to me as a little kid, at least one actor did Lon Chaney jr.
He was a werewolf and like the some of the older movies.
0:23
I thought he was really a, really, a werewolf.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E4 • Your Future’s In These Cards</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600004/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600004/</guid>
        <description>0:07
A lot of people love to have answers or reassurance, or just a sense of foresight when it comes to their lives.
I personally crave reassurance wherever I can get it.
So quietly.
I&amp;rsquo;m in this camp and Taro is a way to get that in some ways.
I agree.
0:23
And I am 110% on board for this episode.
I cannot wait to learn more about tarot.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been wanting to for a long.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E3 • Fountain Drinks for the Youths</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600003/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600003/</guid>
        <description>0:07
It feels a little ironic that the idea of finding Miracle Waters to restore.
Our youth is actually one of the oldest spiritual stories ever told.
But it&amp;rsquo;s also not that surprising.
Yeah, here&amp;rsquo;s a concept that&amp;rsquo;s thousands of years old that could keep you looking less than 50.
I don&amp;rsquo;t know.
0:23
It&amp;rsquo;s true.
There are so many versions of people looking for those magical Waters.
There&amp;rsquo;s Hot Springs today that claim to have healing qualities, but how much can we really believe?</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E2 • A.C.D. Sees Spirits</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600002/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600002/</guid>
        <description>0:05
I&amp;rsquo;m not sure there is a lot of people who would associate Sherlock Holmes with spiritualism, unless maybe you&amp;rsquo;re a deep Avid Reader of those books.
I&amp;rsquo;m certainly not.
I have a feeling you aren&amp;rsquo;t either.
I am a big fan of the movies.
That&amp;rsquo;s for sure.
That&amp;rsquo;s one step in.
Well, there&amp;rsquo;s a little bit of a Twist because the author of the Sherlock Holmes books spent a big part of his life investigating psychic and paranormal phenomena, so, He was sort of a real life, spiritual detective.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Rituals - E1 • When Witches Brewed Weather</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1309600001/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309600001/</guid>
        <description>0:14
Imagine having the ability to create winds, storms and cold weather that could destroy fields of crops.
Sounds pretty darn evil.
It sounds pretty darn badass as someone who lives for the theatrics.
Controlling weather and destroying crops for the sheer Whimsy.
0:30
The of it all sounds right on par extremely Whimsical tornado coming through.
Well, the idea of whether witches or people who could harness the elements, like that seems far-fetched and yet we still use a groundhog to predict the length of winter.</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
