<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dan Carlin's Hardcore History on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/dan-carlins-hardcore-history/</link><description>Recent content in Dan Carlin's Hardcore History on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 12:14:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/dan-carlins-hardcore-history/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Show 70 - Twilight of the Aesir II | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6668900001/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 12:14:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6668900001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pagan Viking Sea Kings spend the 10th and 11th centuries morphing into Christian monarchs. But with rulers like Harald Bluetooth and Svein Forkbeard it&amp;rsquo;s debatable whether things will be any less horrific for Scandinavia&amp;rsquo;s neighbors
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Show 69 - Twilight of the Aesir | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6668900002/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 15:20:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6668900002/</guid><description>Podcast Description This show picks up where Dan&amp;rsquo;s Thor&amp;rsquo;s Angels show left off. In the early Middle Ages Pagan Germanic-language speakers like the Vikings are a dying breed. Many of their contemporaries wish they&amp;rsquo;d die faster.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Show 68 - BLITZ Human Resources | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6668900003/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 19:08:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6668900003/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Atlantic Slave Trade mixes centuries of human bondage with violence, economics, commerce, geo-political competition, liberty, morality, injustice, revolution, tragedy and bloody reckonings. That sounds like a lot, yet this show merely scratches the surface of this enormous subject.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Show 67 - Supernova in the East VI | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6668900004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 15:20:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6668900004/</guid><description>Podcast Description When do spirit, tenacity, resilience and bravery cross into madness? When cities are incinerated? When suicide attacks become the norm? When atomic weapons are used? Japan&amp;rsquo;s leaders test the limits of national endurance in the war&amp;rsquo;s last year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Show 66 - Supernova in the East V | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6668900005/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 17:08:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6668900005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can suicidal bravery and fanatical determination make up for material, industrial and numerical insufficiency? As the Asia-Pacific conflict turns against the Japanese these questions are put to the test. The results are nightmarish.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Show 65 - Supernova in the East IV | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6668900006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 15:20:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6668900006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Coral Sea, Midway and Guadalcanal are three of the most famous battles of the Second World War. Together they will shift the momentum in the Pacific theater and usher in the era of modern naval and amphibious warfare.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Show 64 - Supernova in the East III | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6668900007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 16:10:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6668900007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Japan&amp;rsquo;s rising sun goes supernova and engulfs a huge area of Asia and the Pacific. A war without mercy begins to develop infusing the whole conflict with a savage vibe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Show 63 - Supernova in the East II | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6668900008/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 10:07:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6668900008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Deep themes run through this show, with allegations of Japanese war crimes and atrocities in China at the start leading to eerily familiar, almost modern questions over how the world should respond. And then Dec 7, 1941 arrives&amp;hellip;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Show 62 - Supernova in the East I | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6668900009/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2018 12:05:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6668900009/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Asia-Pacific War of 1937-1945 has deep roots. It also involves a Japanese society that&amp;rsquo;s been called one of the most distinctive on Earth. If there were a Japanese version of Captain America, this would be his origin story.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Show 61 - (Blitz) Painfotainment | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6668900010/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 23:58:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6668900010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pain is at the root of most drama and entertainment. When does it get too real? This very disturbing and graphic show looks into some case studies and asks some deep questions. WARNING Very intense subject matter.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Show 60 - The Celtic Holocaust | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6668900011/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 15:20:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6668900011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Julius Caesar is our travel guide as he takes us through his murderous subjugation of the native Celtic tribal peoples of ancient Gaul. It sounds vaguely like other, recent European colonial conquests&amp;hellip;until the natives nearly win.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Show 59 - (Blitz) The Destroyer of Worlds | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6668900012/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 21:05:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6668900012/</guid><description>Podcast Description What happens if human beings can&amp;rsquo;t handle the power of their own weaponry? This show examines the dangerous early years of the Nuclear Age and humankind&amp;rsquo;s efforts to avoid self-destruction at the hands of its own creation.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Show 58 - Kings of Kings III | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6668900013/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2016 12:05:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6668900013/</guid><description>Podcast Description If this were a movie, the events and cameos would be too numerous and star-studded to mention. It includes Xerxes, Spartans, Immortals, Alexander the Great, scythed chariots, and several of the greatest battles in history.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Show 57 - Kings of Kings II | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6668900014/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2016 00:08:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6668900014/</guid><description>Podcast Description From Biblical-era coup conspiracies to the horrific aftermath of ancient combat this second installment of the series on the Kings of Achaemenid Persia goes where only Dan can take it. For better or worse…
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Show 56 - Kings of Kings | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6668900015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2015 17:35:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6668900015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Often relegated to the role of slavish cannon fodder for Sparta&amp;rsquo;s spears, the Achaemenid Persian empire had a glorious heritage. Under a single king they created the greatest empire the world had ever seen.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>