<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Off Air... with Jane and Fi on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/off-air...-with-jane-and-fi/</link><description>Recent content in Off Air... with Jane and Fi on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 18:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/off-air...-with-jane-and-fi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A wee of almost bovine quantities | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320255/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320255/</guid><description>Podcast Description The festive season is staggering towards us, and Jane and Fi are staggering with it. Not just that, but Jane has been doing Christmas shopping, and almost crying. Before that resumed, they talk hot drinks, disorganised criminals, and ask why is thrush called thrush? They're also joined by the legend Miriam Margolyes. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>I do give my chef the weekend off | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320001/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 09:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320001/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this special in&amp;nbsp;partnership with The National Lottery, Jane visited ‘Cook For Good’, the Islington based community kitchen and food pantry.
Whilst there, Jane sat down with co-founder Karen, and benefactor Amel, and talked about the ‘Cook For Good’ story, the need for services like these, the power of food to bring communities together, and the impact The National Lottery have had on this east-London charity.
And since 2021, Cook for Good has received&amp;nbsp;more than £18,000 in funding from National Lottery Players.</description></item><item><title>Has she farted in front of you? (with Maria McErlane) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 17:50:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320002/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's an all-girl action-pack this evening as team Jane and Fi are off for their Christmas dinner!
Jane and Fi are talking about avoiding social events (we're sure it's unrelated), awkward train rides and political cutlery.
They're joined by actress Maria McErlane to discuss her new memoir ‘Bumps in the Road'.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Trying to associate youths on the bus with whooshing romanticism | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 17:38:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320003/</guid><description>Podcast Description We're all getting giddy for Christmas as the team dinner looms! Before that can happen, Jane and Fi must do a couple more podcasts. They chat stamps, overnight trains and Saltburn... They're joined by writer and actor Katherine Jakeways to discuss her latest creation 'The Buccaneers'. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio Follow us on Instagram!</description></item><item><title>I don't want to see you when you're hangry (with Ade Edmonson) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 17:28:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi are very excited about their Christmas dinner, so they take a whistle-stop tour through topics including cats as neckwear, sophisticated frozen yogurt and being 'Britain's favourite natterers'.
They're joined by comedian and actor Adrian ‘Ade’ Edmondson to discuss his memoir 'Berserker!'
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Follow us on Instagram!</description></item><item><title>A bit of 'O Come, All Ye Faithful' before a few drinks | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 17:43:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320005/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's another email special and Jane's quite hungover so Fi's carrying this one. They chat dinosaur skulls, Sting's neck and adults drinking squash. There's no big guest today as we have been taking the Covid Inquiry live. Tune into Times Radio to get the latest. And make sure to get all of your emails in for Monday's email special: janeandfi@times.radio Follow us on Instagram! @janeandfi Assistant Producer: Eve Salusbury Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Book Club - Boy Swallows Universe, Trent Dalton | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320006/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 09:00:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi are back with their third book club instalment - they've been reading 'Boy Swallows Universe' by Trent Dalton.
Join them as they respond to your emails, Instagram messages, comments and voice notes.
Thank you so much for your engagement and interaction. We hope you'll join us for the next one. Get your suggestions in at: janeandfi@times.radio
Follow us on Instagram! @janeandfi
Assistant Producer: Kate Lee</description></item><item><title>It certainly sealed your bowels... | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320007/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's another email special and this one is all over the place. Jane and Fi chat different tube lines, wipe-clean book covers and Madonna's wedding. Plus, Jane shares her nugget of wisdom for life. You don't want to miss it. There's no big guest today or on Monday as we have been taking the Covid Inquiry live. Tune into Times Radio to get the latest. And make sure to get all of your emails in for Monday's email special: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>My urine is vertical (as decided by Fi) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane is still making sure to read out your compliments so do keep them coming. We fear what might happen if she runs out... In this email special, Jane and Fi also cover shopping centres they admire, speedy boarding and catheters filled with apple juice. There's no big guest today or tomorrow as we have been taking Boris Johnson speaking at the Covid Inquiry live. Tune into Times Radio to get the latest.</description></item><item><title>Ms. This App Is Crap (with Deborah Meaden) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320009/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 17:34:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane is bursting for a wee and Fi isn't helping matters. Before Jane dashes off, they discuss power cuts, greyhound suffragettes and asserting their fame.
Plus, businesswoman Deborah Meaden joins Jane and Fi to discuss appearing on Taskmaster. Taskmaster’s New Year Treat airs at 9pm, Tuesday 2nd January on Channel 4.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Awaiting the arrival of my pink ombré plastic tree | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 17:43:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fi is in the building!! This is not a drill!! She joins Jane back in the studio to discuss washing your duvet, the lack of catheters in TV shows and encounters with Sting, naturally. Plus, former Harry Potter stuntman David Holmes discusses the accident that changed his life and his new documentary 'The Boy Who Lived'. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Aside from being sexy, what do you do for a living? (with Kate Atkinson) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 17:44:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fi is still joining us through the ether, but we live in hope... Together Jane and Fi discuss awful pick up lines, non-traditional Christmas' and celebrity deaths. Plus, bestselling author Kate Atkinson joins Jane to discuss her career, her recent novel 'Shrines of Gaiety' and her new collection of short stories 'Normal Rules Don't Apply'. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Straight to the Tate with a breast pump | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 18:20:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320012/</guid><description>Podcast Description The much-missed Fi is battling new technology to join Jane for today's podcast.
It's the inaugural edition of 'Rays Reviews' - where Jane's 90-year-old dad gives us his thoughts on the new Napoleon film.
Louise Tickle joins to talk about her debut thriller 'Between The Lies'.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio</description></item><item><title>Are you alluding to my misspent youth? | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320013/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 17:44:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fi is back (sort of)! She joins Jane via Zoom from home. They cover non-noisy fruit, middle aged online dating and earliest memories. Plus, Jane speaks to American poet Shane McCrae to discuss memory and his memoir 'Pulling the Chariot of the Sun'. She also speaks to Professor Catherine Loveday about memory and why we might misremember events. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>I love nothing more than talking to myself (with Tim Rice) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 17:34:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fi is still sadly off with illness so Jane is flying solo! She gets through your emails and covers afternoon tea, twins and flooding.
Plus, Jane speaks to lyricist Sir Tim Rice about his career, his relationship with Andrew Lloyd Webber and his new BBC maestro course.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>I'm not a fully paid up anorak (with Anton Du Beke) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 17:53:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane² are back for day two as Jane Mulkerrins fills in for Fi. They chat waxing near the printers, having a freezer full of crumpets, and getting your 'oh be joyfulls'.
Jane G is joined by Strictly Come Dancing’s Anton Du Beke to discuss his new novel "The Paris Affair".
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>I'll keep her seat warm but I won't be licking it | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 17:36:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fi is off with illness so we bring you good old Jane² as Jane Mulkerrins fills in. The Janes discuss Nigel Farages' buttocks, bed-airing and Jane G's influencer status. Plus, Jane G speaks to food historian Pen Vogler about her new book 'Stuffed: A History of Good Food and Hard Times in Britain'. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Nostalgic for 'women's things' (with Laura Trevelyan and Clive Lewis) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 17:40:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Book club is wrapping up this week so Jane and Fi make their final bid for you to get your thoughts in! They also discuss period pants, London's train stations and tantric sex... obviously. Plus, they're joined by journalist Laura Trevelyan and Clive Lewis MP to discuss their new podcast 'Heirs of Enslavement', which is available wherever you get your podcasts. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Too much girth, not enough remuneration (with Philippa Gregory) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 17:34:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320018/</guid><description>Podcast Description The count down is on in this episode (I'm not joking)! As Fi's timer ticks away, they discuss celebrity toilet encounters, upgraded train seats and advent. Plus, they're joined by historical novelist Philippa Gregory discusses her latest non-fiction work 'Normal Women: 900 Years of Women Making History". And if you want to get a taste of Philippa's book, you can also check out her new podcast, also called Normal Women.</description></item><item><title>A quandary for the shorter lady | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 18:06:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last night, Jane and Fi were at an extremely important corporate event. Fi made a faux pas, and Jane fell off a chair. We're wrapping up the week with the essentials; cats, loyalty cards, and famous people in toilets. Jane and Fi are also joined by Chris Atkins, documentary maker and author of the prison memoir A Bit of a Stretch. The sequel, Time After Time, is out now.</description></item><item><title>Here's a genuine bit of sincerity for you | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 18:13:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Before today's email special episode begins, Jane is asking if she can move in with Fi, and Fi says no. Elsewhere, Jane and Fi go through all of the big topics you've been emailing in about recently. Jane's Cliff Richard anecdote is somehow still making the cut. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Giant buttons and esophageal passages (with Lee Child) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320021/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 17:54:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane has a giant button going down her esophageal passage, and Fi is less than impressed. Once they get over that, they're talking your most recent pet photos, whether women from history drive, and they have a big political prediction for Suella Braverman's next career move... Lee Child is our big guest today. The Secret, written in collaboration with his brother Andrew, is out now. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Age appropriate jiggery (with Martin Kemp) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 17:48:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320022/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this rather culture-infused episode, Jane and Fi chat Cliff Richard, the theatre and climbing onto stools at 83 years old. Plus, they're joined by Spandau Ballet's Martin Kemp to discuss his debut novel 'The Game'. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio Follow us on Instagram! @janeandfi Assistant Producer: Eve Salusbury Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>That itchy bum thing (with Caster Semenya) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today it's Jane, Fi and Fi's extremely loud tummy. The three of them discuss celebs in panto, Jane's need to show off and "FerGie". Plus, they're joined by double Olympic champion Caster Semenya to discuss her memoir 'The Race To Be Myself'. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio Follow us on Instagram! @janeandfi Assistant Producer: Eve Salusbury Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Face bras and twin peaks (with Jilly Cooper) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 17:54:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320024/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Jane and Fi are trying not to ramble... Naturally, this results in them discussing age gaps, face bras and Jane Austen. And, they're still trying to get you to buy their book! Plus, they're joined by the author Jilly Cooper to discuss her latest novel 'Tackle!' If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>But what if we can't share anecdotes from the same Olympic Games? (With Monty Don) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320025/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 17:58:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane has brought some interesting dating adverts with her to discuss with Fi. They also talk bikini lines, their ideas for the King's Speech, and Barbra Streisand. They're joined by the nation's favourite gardener, Monty Don, to talk about 'The Gardening Book', which is available to buy now. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Members of the long bosom WI (with Dolly Alderton) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320026/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 17:46:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fi's taking personal calls and Jane's doodling on herself. Amongst these distractions, they also discuss surfing events on The Seine, Christmas trees and EastEnders. Plus, they're joined by Dolly Alderton to discuss her new novel 'Good Material'. Out on 9/11/23. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio Follow us on Instagram! @janeandfi Assistant Producer: Eve Salusbury Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Another sturdy-booted middle age lady going about her business (with Matt Willis) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320027/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 17:53:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320027/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's almost the end of the week and there's lots to get through! Jane and Fi discuss surprising dog breeds, the tribulations of motherhood and Jane passively getting the munchies... Plus, they're joined by the Busted bass player Matt Willis to discuss his battle with addiction and his podcast 'On The Mend'. If you've been affected by any issues discussed in today's episode then email feedback@times.radio and we will point you in the direction of places to receive help.</description></item><item><title>Don't hide your light under a bushel... | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 17:51:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane's imagining a poodle in glasses reading the paper, and Fi's wondering what counts as an outdoor Christmas decoration.
They're joined by researcher and writer William Viney, to talk about his book 'Twinkind: The Singular Significance of Twins'.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Follow us on Instagram! @janeandfi
Assistant Producer: Kate Lee</description></item><item><title>THIS IS A HALLOWEEN SPECIAL, LEST WE FORGET! | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320029/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 18:02:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320029/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this spooky episode, Jane and Fi pose some important questions: How do we use colons? Is there such thing as the paranormal? Would you want to buy a house from Jane? Plus, they're joined by Debbie Weinstein,&amp;nbsp;the Vice President of Google and Managing Director of GoogleUk, to discuss 25 years of Google and look ahead to the future of tech. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Deja Vu in Bromley (with Clare Balding) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320030/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 17:43:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fi's back for this particularly spooky episode. They discuss long bosoms, late night thrashing thoughts and priest holes... Beware! Plus they're joined by Clare Balding (and her partner Alice) to discuss Clare's new book 'Isle of Dogs: A Canine History of Britain'. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio Follow us on Instagram! @janeandfi Assistant Producer: Eve Salusbury Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>That can be our safe word (with Ed Gamble) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320031/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 16:56:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Jane discuss the pros and cons of a fancy bagel, treating yourself on a Thursday and encounters of the other worldly kind.
Comedian Ed Gamble joins to talk about his memoir 'Glutton', which is available now.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Follow us on Instagram! @janeandfi
Assistant Producer: Kate Lee</description></item><item><title>Lessons from an older less-experienced woman (with The Hairy Bikers) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320032/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 16:51:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane G is a bit tongue tied by Jane M is here to support her. They cover having to work before lunch, middle-age men's hobbies and there's more sexuality chat. Plus, they're joined by Si King and Dave Myers, a.k.a. the Hairy Bikers. They discuss their new book 'Ultimate Comfort Food'. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>One's bosom just does change. | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320033/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 16:45:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane Mulkerrins is still sitting in for Fi, but who doesn't love a bit of Jane²? They chat well fitted bras, sexuality and brush up against book shelves... Plus, researcher and author Cat Bohannon discusses her book 'Eve: How The Female Body Drove 200 Million Years of Human Evolution'. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Head first into a tub of taramasalata! | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320034/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 16:45:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fi's off so friend of the show Jane Mulkerrins is sitting in! Jane and Jane discuss public transport, nipple free zones and the myth of jet lag. No big guest today but Jane Garvey will explain all... If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio Follow us on Instagram! @janeandfi Assistant Producer: Eve Salusbury Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Why would a Mexican bandit be wearing a corset? (with Shaun Keaveny) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320035/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 16:43:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fi's about to go off on her jollies but she has a podcast to get through first! Someone should probably tell her that... Before she dashes out the door (quite literally), they discuss fancy dress, testicles and what would happen if we soaked and rinsed Jane. Plus, they're joined by broadcaster Shaun Keaveny to discuss his brand new podcast 'Shaun Keaveny's Daily Grind'. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Who knows what happens after a Cliff concert? (with Krishnan Guru-Murthy) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320036/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 17:01:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi survived the shared black cab journey and are here to tell the tale. They also discuss first words, hotel freebies and Fi's Cliff Richard resistance. Plus, they're joined by Channel 4 News anchor Krishnan Guru-Murthy to chat Strictly Come Dancing and balancing the demands of his job with his dancing. Here's how to download the bonus episode: Make sure your iPhone has the latest iOS software up to date (you can check this in settings)&amp;nbsp; Go to the Apple Podcasts App and click on ‘Off Air with Jane and Fi’ Scroll down to the bonus episode with Aasmah from 6th October Hit Play: you’ll then to able to click on the option to say you have a Times Subscription Log into your Times account and bob's your uncle: you can download that episode and all the others coming over the next 12 months If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>I've clung to the idea I may be of regal blood (with John Whaite) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320037/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 17:16:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi are off to a book launch tonight... but Fi is less than thrilled about the prospect of sharing a taxi with Jane, who has been consuming lentils "well known for their wind manufacturing properties." Before that, they talk teaching, whether they're descended from royalty, and the bloodline of Fi's cat. They're joined by Bake Off winner John Whaite and they discuss his new memoir Dancing On Eggshells.</description></item><item><title>Jane the Imperious (with Iain Dale) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320038/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 16:46:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane the Imperious and Fi attempt to measure the satisfaction they get from theirs jobs... what can go wrong? They also discuss evening routines, dog walking dates and quiet quitting. Plus, they're joined by broadcaster Iain Dale to discuss his new book 'Kings and Queens: 1200 Years of English and British Monarchs'. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>I think there's a benign lazy streak in me (with Michael Ball) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320039/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 17:01:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi have come to the end of a jam-packed week, and need a quiet night in. But before that, they're talking about pet politics, hereditary laziness, and whether we should consider quietly quitting our jobs.
Plus, they're joined by the one and only Michael Ball OBE, to talk about his memoir Different Aspects. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Distracted by a couple of hippos having sex (with Matt Chorley) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320040/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 17:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi are back from Cheltenham Literature Festival and they have a lot of emails to get through! They tackle online dating, books they'd never return to and good customer service at Luton Airport. Plus, they're joined by Times Radio's very own Matt Chorley to discuss his brand new book 'Planes, Trains and Toilet Doors: 50 Places That Changed British Politics'. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Off Air Turns 1! (with Dom Joly and Peter Brathwaite at Cheltenham Literature Festival) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320041/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 17:06:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get your candles out, because Off Air turns 1 today! Jane and Fi are celebrating at Cheltenham. Deliciously delirious from both the festival and the cake, they mull over flat earth theories, ice cream flavours, and beans in ramekins. In this bumper episode, Jane and Fi speak to renowned UK opera singer Peter Brathwaite at the festival about his project and book 'Rediscovering Black Portraiture'. They're also joined by comedian Dom Joly to discuss his new book 'The Conspiracy Tourist'.</description></item><item><title>The hotel freebie tingle (with Shirley Ballas LIVE at Cheltenham Literature Festival) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320042/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 17:12:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi have ventured out of Times Radio Towers and are coming to you from Cheltenham Literature Festival today! Their main questions include: what's for dinner? And will my bed be facing the right way in my hotel room?&amp;nbsp; They're joined by Shirley Ballas: head judge on Strictly Come Dancing, one of the world's best dancers, and now, novelist. You can pre-order her new book 'Murder on the Dance Floor' at timesbookshop.</description></item><item><title>Rescuing your knickers from next door's buddleia | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320043/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 16:56:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi are making a seamless transition into today's podcast, and they're asking all the big questions: are curtains better than blinds? What would you do if you found your neighbour's underwear in the garden? And what's happened to all of Jane's money?
Author and journalist Emma Gannon joins to talk about her book 'The Success Myth'.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>But we've already humped? (with Kevin McCloud) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 16:48:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane shares, what she considers to be, the biggest issue of our time... washing pegs. Yes, really. They also discuss Tony's pepper mill, baths with steps and mound music. Plus, they're joined by Grand Designs' Kevin McCloud, who was speaking ahead of Grand Designs Live, taking place at the NEC from the 4th - 8th of October. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>'I was listening to Ronan Keating at least once a day' (with Dame Esther Rantzen) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320045/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 16:50:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320045/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Archers is still being discussed, to no one's surprise... But, they also manage to cover their journalistic capabilities, Nigel Farage on Strictly and Jane's pepper mill. Plus, friend of the show Dame Esther Rantzen joins them to reflect on her career, discuss her health and share her hopes for the future. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>My pepper grinder is in need of a service (with Victoria Hislop) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320046/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 16:54:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane's faffing so Fi kicks things off without her. Once she arrives, they chat high tech pepper grinders, the new book club pick and Miriam Margolyes' rider. Plus, Victoria Hislop joins them to discuss her new novel 'The Figurine'. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio Follow us on Instagram! @janeandfi Assistant Producer: Eve Salusbury Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>We hate each other really (with Kate Humble) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320047/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 16:48:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi have snacked their way through the day and are ready to talk about matching chocolate to your mood, swanning about in a slip, and Fi's past life as a vicar...
They're joined by Springwatch presenter Kate Humble to talk about her new book 'Where the Hearth Is'.
And we've got a podcast exclusive interview with The Times' Lucy Bannerman about her recently taxidermied tortoise.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Kefir on the verge (with Rose Tremain) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320048/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 16:41:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane is still trying to get Fi into The Archers and she's having none of it! They also reflect on the magic of time zones, neighbourhood Whatsapp groups and KissCams. Plus, Dame Rose Tremain joins them to discuss her new novel 'Absolutely &amp;amp; Forever'. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio Follow us on Instagram!</description></item><item><title>Boris' bag of bras (with Ken Follett) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320049/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 16:36:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane is reunited with Ken Follett and she's thrilled. In this particularly giddy episode, they also chat HRT dreams and getting better in your 50's. Ken joins them to discuss his new novel 'The Armour of Light'. The final book in the Kingsbridge series. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio Follow us on Instagram!</description></item><item><title>Who called their child 'Sex Fruit'?! (with Jeffrey Archer) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320050/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 16:49:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320050/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's a bit of a mixed bag today as Jane Mulkerrins sits in for the big interview but Fi is here for the bulk of the podcast! They chat worms of appreciation, banned baby names and Agent V. Plus, Jeffrey Archer joins Jane and Jane to discuss his new novel 'Traitors Gate'. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Book Club - My Sister the Serial Killer, Oyinkan Braithwaite | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320051/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 17:01:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi have picked another opinion-dividing book for their second Book Club episode: 'My Sister the Serial Killer' by Oyinkan Braithwaite.
Join them as they respond to your emails, Instagram messages, comments and voice notes.
Thank you so much for your engagement and interaction. We hope you'll join us for the next one. Get your suggestions in at: janeandfi@times.radio
Follow us on Instagram! @janeandfi
Assistant Producer: Kate Lee</description></item><item><title>Firm buttocks, that's what we want (with Michel Roux Jr) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320052/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 16:42:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Professional working mum, or concerned and thoughtful parent? Fi is facing a dilemma, while Jane is busy waving a loaf of sourdough bread around the office and asking for a 'rompathon' for next month's Book Club pick.
They're joined by Michelin starred chef Michel Roux Jr to talk about his new recipe book, 'Michel Roux at Home: Simple and delicious French meals for every day'.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Malibu Garvey? (with London Hughes) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320053/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 16:46:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi once again try to stay on track and fail miserably but along the way they cover Boots opening times, how Jane would fare in LA and uncomfortable workplace banter. Plus, they're joined by comedian London Hughes to discuss her frank and funny new memoir 'Living My Best Life, Hun'. Her book is out now. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Unsalvageable bean dishes (with Trinny Woodall) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320054/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 16:48:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi massively get the Tuesday giggles in this one but, before that, they chat Fi's chilli-con-carne-smugness, children flying the nest and shared baths. Plus, they're joined by TV personality and entrepreneur Trinny Woodall to discuss her new book 'Fearless'. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio Follow us on Instagram! @janeandfi Assistant Producer: Eve Salusbury Times Radio Producer: Kate Lee Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Whatever this is... (with Rory Cellan-Jones) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320055/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 16:49:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane's still saying 'cwassant' and Fi is still perplexed. Plus, they chat Russell Brand, tactical clothes drying and parental correspondents. They're joined by former BBC tech correspondent and journalist Rory Cellan-Jones to discuss his new book 'Ruskin Park: Sylvia, Me and the BBC'. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio Follow us on Instagram!</description></item><item><title>The oohs and the yahs (with Robert Peston) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320056/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 16:37:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fi has hopes of making her fortunes in the adult pesto industry, while Jane is discussing being woken up by 'the noise of shenanigans', surviving sixth months on a submarine, and unsuccessfully teaching boys to use a urinal.
They're joined by Robert Peston, Political Editor at ITV, to hear about his new book 'The Crash'.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Something nearly as good as pancakes... sex! (with Clive Myrie) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320057/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 16:40:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane is a tad hangover so bear with them as they tackle elocution lessons, Meryl Streep audiobooks and multi-use hotels in today's episode. Plus, they're joined by journalist and broadcaster Clive Myrie to discuss his new memoir 'Everything is Everything'. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio Follow us on Instagram! @janeandfi Assistant Producer: Eve Salusbury Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler</description></item><item><title>Welcome to The Jane Garvey Tribute Chamber (with Anne Enright) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320058/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi are having an unusual day... as per. They chat buttock revealing one pieces, what would happen if Robert Peston's last name was 'pesto' and provide some pension analogies. Plus, they're joined by Irish poet and author Anne Enright to discuss her new novel 'The Wren, The Wren'. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Thigh nipping fish?! (with Rory Stewart) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320059/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 16:54:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi are reunited and it feels so good. They have lots to cover including bald prime ministers, lidos and all the languages Jane speaks... Plus, broadcaster, academic and former politician Rory Stewart joins them to discuss his new memoir 'Politics On the Edge'.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Follow us on Instagram!</description></item><item><title>It's the-ATRE not THE-atre (with Anneka Rice and Stacey Solomon) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320060/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 17:02:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fi is joined by Anneka Rice for the final time and once again Fi is being pulled up on her pronunciation&amp;nbsp;of a certain word.
They also chat to TV personality Stacey Solomon about the new series of Sort Your Life Out.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Follow us on Instagram! @janeandfi</description></item><item><title>You can't beat The Greatest Showman (with Clare Balding and Jason Donovan) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320061/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 16:50:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fi is still joined by Clare Balding and they serenade you in this particularly bonkers episode of Off Air... plus, they discuss being studious, their playlists and the Olympics. They're also joined by Aussie heart throb Jason Donovan to discuss his role in Grease the Musical. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio Follow us on Instagram!</description></item><item><title>Almost like ABBA... almost (With Clare Balding and Lemn Sissay) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320062/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 16:48:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane is still off so another one of Fi's friends has stopped in. Clare Balding joins Fi to discuss cat monogamy, fear of carrots and tattoo choices. Plus, Lemn Sissay OBE is here to discuss his new collection of poetry 'Let the Light Pour In' and his adaptation of Kafka's 'Metamorphosis'. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Chaos trying to be reigned in (with Anneka Rice and Gyles Brandreth) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320063/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 17:17:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane is off on holiday, so it's up to Fi (with help from Anneka Rice) to wonder how many Camparis she's had so far. They're joined by Gyles Brandreth to talk about his new podcast 'Rosebud'.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Follow us on Instagram! @janeandfi
Assistant Producer: Kate Lee
Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler</description></item><item><title>Does S&amp;M include much chilli sauce? (with Sarah Beeny) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320064/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 16:59:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane G has been trying out a hot wings challenge, while Jane M was trying to escape Three Bridges Station.
They're joined by property TV presenter Sarah Beeny.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Follow us on Instagram! @janeandfi
Assistant Producer: Kate Lee
Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>Will I be additionally bonkers tonight? (with Maggie Alphonsi) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320065/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 16:56:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Jane are talking caravan holidays, howling at the moon and actively helping the environment by eating chips.
They're joined by Maggie Alphonsi, well known international women's rugby union player and World Cup winner with England in 2014. Her memoir 'Winning the Fight' is out now.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Drinking neat Campari at midday | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320066/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 17:04:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320066/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the absence of 'wee Fi', Jane G is joined by Jane M, and will only be reading emails from people named Jane this week (just kidding).
They discuss holiday surprises, world cup finals and how many Milka bars you can get for twelve euros. Today's guest is Martine Wright MBE, who lost both her legs in the 7/7 bombings in London.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Am I allowed to speak now? (with Sheela Banerjee) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320067/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 16:51:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi are reuniting decorative milk bottles with their international owners.
They're also talking step-parents, sombreros and spellings.
Sheela Banerjee joins to talk about her new book "What's in a Name?"
Follow us on Instagram! @janeandfi
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Assistant Producer: Kate Lee
Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler</description></item><item><title>No bobble was strong enough to contain the Garvey locks! | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320068/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 16:42:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi&amp;nbsp;are gearing up to turn their 'out of office' on but they've still got a show to do! They reveal who will be replacing them in their respective absences as well as discussing unhelpful cesarean partners, tea cakes and jet lag. Plus, they're joined by Darryn Frost AKA 'Narwhal Tusk Hero'. Darryn risked his life to tackle a terrorist on London Bridge in November 2019. He shares his story.</description></item><item><title>That's another nut going down (with Deborah Meaden) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320069/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 17:04:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi are recovering from an almost on-air crisis that nearly happened but didn't. They're joined by Deborah Meaden, to talk about her new book "Why Money Matters" - part of the Little Experts series.&amp;nbsp;
Follow us on Instagram! @janeandfi If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Assistant Producer: Kate Lee
Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler</description></item><item><title>I long to squeeze one of those tomatoes (with Fats Timbo) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320070/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 17:13:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fi is doing her best to cheer Jane up after a 're-shuffle' at her other job. They chat TV recommendations, hopeless babies and weeing on the collar of your jumpsuit.
They're joined by Fats Timbo, a comedian, model and influencer with more than two million fans on TikTok.
Follow us on Instagram! @janeandfi
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Fingers in the cream (with Sharron Davies) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320071/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 19:36:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320071/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's a sporty special today: Jane laments her full time job getting in the way of her golf progress, Fi has an apology to make about netball and they're joined by Olympian Sharron Davies who's talking about her new book, Unfair Play.
And our Museum of Taxidermy is now closed, but not before Jane and Fi speak to the creator of 'Stoned Fox'
Follow us on Instagram! @janeandfi</description></item><item><title>Wimpy and the queen's funeral | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320072/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 17:04:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi have been in touch with the creator of the taxidermy sensation: Stoned Fox. They also ask the big questions: are man buns sexy? And what happened to Wimpy?
They're joined by Dr Liz O'Riordan, the consultant breast surgeon who's been through cancer herself. Her memoir is called ‘Under The Knife’
Follow us on Instagram! @janeandfi
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>You know me, I like a chunk (with Laura Whitmore) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320073/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 17:06:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi talk family bathroom politics and delve into more taxidermy horrors. They also compare two on screen sensations: Barbie, and Greg Wallace's miracle meat. They're joined by Laura Whitmore, broadcaster and former host of Love Island, to talk about her new documentary mini series. It tackles cyber stalking, the incel movement, and rough sex. Follow us on Instagram! @janeandfi If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>See attached half giraffe | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320074/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 17:02:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi discuss whether taxidermy can grow on you, or if it belongs in the family freezer. It's also the end of the penny farthing (for now...)
They're also joined by Pat Nevin, former professional footballer, who's now a pundit and writer. Pat's&amp;nbsp;latest book is called Football and How To Survive It.
Follow us on Instagram! @janeandfi
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Spiritual blockages | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320075/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 17:08:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi discuss whether they would stuff their cats, and reflect on some sad aquariums and zoos. They also reveal the next book for their book club!
Follow us on Instagram! @janeandfi
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Assistant Producers: Megan McElroy
Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>Two fillings and a smear test | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320076/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 17:01:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi reflect on owning your success, trapped wind from both ends, and delve into more family holiday horrors. They're also joined by music journalist Ian Winwood, author of Bodies: Life and Death in Music. Follow us on Instagram! @janeandfi
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Assistant Producers: Megan McElroy
Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler</description></item><item><title>My long suffering pac-a-mac | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320077/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 16:59:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi chat about the highs and lows of family holidays, their desire for a hand cream amnesty, and terrible raffle prizes. They're also joined by Sir Nicholas Mostyn - the second longest serving High Court judge and co-hosts of the Movers and Shakers podcast - which is about life with Parkinson’s. Follow us on Instagram! @janeandfi If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>It's been ages since I measured mine (with Anna Richardson) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320078/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 17:17:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi chat about a certain person's miracle meat, the ongoing issue of Jane's trapped wind, and family holiday politics. They're also joined by TV presenter Anna Richardson, to talk about her podcast It Can't Just Be Me. Follow us on Instagram! @janeandfi
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Assistant Producers: Megan McElroy</description></item><item><title>Book Club - Fresh Water for Flowers | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320079/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 08:00:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320079/</guid><description>Podcast Description The first book club has finally wrapped and Jane and Fi can't quite come to an agreement... Join them as they respond to your emails, Instagram messages, comments and voice notes. Thank you so much for your engagement and interaction. We hope you'll join us for the next one. Get your suggestions in at: janeandfi@times.radio Follow us on Instagram! @janeandfi Assistant Producer: Eve Salusbury Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Capers in the basement | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320080/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 16:44:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi discuss the contents of Jane's basement and try to work out why Rear Admirals are called Rear Admirals. Answers on a postcard please. They're also joined by Ferdinand Mount to talk about his new book Big Caesars and Little Caesars.
Follow us on Instagram! @janeandfi
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>A couple of large fries stuck in your cleavage (with Carol Kirkwood) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320081/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 17:08:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane's got trapped wind and Fi's rather upset about it, Fi checked her carbon footprint and the results are revealed AND more animal PR... Plus, everyone’s favourite weather presenter Carol Kirkwood joins them to discuss her new novel ‘Secrets of the Villa Amore’. Follow us on Instagram! @janeandfi If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Ladies' fluff (with Eddi Reader) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320082/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 16:58:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi are pondering why beavers have such good PR, whether they would consent to being micro-chipped and if Jane should put the heating on. They're also joined by singer-songwriter Eddi Reader about her new project, a stage version of Brokeback Mountain. Follow us on Instagram! @janeandfi
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>To lick or not to lick? | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320083/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 17:25:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi reflect on the highs (and licks) of Latitude Festival, and England's somewhat lack-lustre win over Haiti. And they are STILL talking Penny-farthing sightings. They are also joined by campaigner Daisy, who discusses her campaign to change the law to make children born of rape legally recognised as victims. If you are affected by any of the issues discussed on today's episode please contact feedback@times.radio and we will direct you to support services.</description></item><item><title>Live from Latitude Festival (with Richard Curtis and Emma Freud) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320084/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 17:47:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi are live at Latitude and they talk air-con and licking Mary Berry.&amp;nbsp;
Richard Curtis and Emma Freud join to talk about their Suffolk themed cooking show at the festival and Richard’s new play&amp;nbsp;Christmas Actually.&amp;nbsp;
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Follow us on Instagram! @JaneandFi&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Assistant Producer: Elizabeth Highfield</description></item><item><title>He had three nipples and a lisp (with Lisa Jewell) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320085/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 16:56:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi discuss great-great uncles, ongoing extreme heat and Jane reminds us how busy she is, actually.
Plus, author Lisa Jewell joins Jane and Fi to discuss her new psychological thriller ‘None of This Is True’.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Follow us on Instagram! @JaneandFi&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Assistant Producer: Eve Salusbury&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>Tapestry on the Northern line (with Katriona O'Sullivan) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320086/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 16:54:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi chat about University Challenge and the prospect of sharing a bed.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Katriona O'Sullivan joins to speak about her memoir Poor, an insight into a life lived against the boundaries of poverty.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio.
Follow us on Instagram! @JaneandFi
Assistant Producer: Elizabeth Highfield
Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler</description></item><item><title>Nothing against Harrogate | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320087/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 17:33:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fi is back at Jane's side after a week away. They talk about her trip to the Cotswolds, Michael Ball (again), and recalling a Yorkshire visit where they once faced a closed hotel kitchen. Journalist Sean O'Neill from The Times shares a personal story about his late daughter Maeve and a crisis is affecting the coroners' courts. If you've been affected by any of the issues discussed in this episode please email feedback@times.</description></item><item><title>Penny-farthing watch (with Diana Bird) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320088/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 16:59:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320088/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s the final episode with Jane squared and they chat about the play Aspects of Love and bourbon balls.&amp;nbsp;
RAF Squadron Leader Diana Bird joins to speak about her new Channel 4 documentary called Evacuation - it's about the daring British airlift operation from Kabul.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio.
Follow us on Instagram!</description></item><item><title>Back-to-back Ball (with David Tennant) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320089/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 17:23:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320089/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's another instalment of Jane and Jane. They're chatting trips to Las Vegas, more Penny-farthing sightings, and seeing Michael Ball in the West End. Actor David Tennant joins to talk about the new series of his show Good Omens, which is back on Prime Video from July 28. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Swifties unite! (with Katherine Faulkner) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320090/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 16:54:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Jane discuss Taylor Swift ticket jeopardy, surprise Sunday morning visits from Showaddywaddy and Penny-farthing related journey delays.
Sunday Times Journalist turned novelist Katherine Faulkner joins to talk about her new thriller, The Other Mothers. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio.
Follow us on Instagram! @JaneandFi
Assistant Producer: Matt Murphy
Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler</description></item><item><title>A three day streak (with James May) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320091/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 17:26:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fi is off on her holidays, so it's a dose of double Jane - with Jane Mulkerrins in the hot seat all this week. They chat about getting your steps in, Fi's appearance on The Weakest Link and a very curious quiz called 'The Wheel of Meat'. They're also joined by The Grand Tour presenter James May, who talks about his new children's book Marvellous Vehicles. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>The pinnacle of their podcasting career (with Caitlin Moran) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320092/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 17:27:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320092/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's the last podcast before Fi goes on holiday, and she's 'slipped slapped up' a bit in a hot pink jacket (as a tribute to the forthcoming Barbie movie). Jane talks about her dad’s awful 21st birthday tea party and the trickiness of sticky back plastic. Caitlin Moran joins to speak about her new book What About Men? If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Don’t do a Madonna (with Kate Mosse) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320093/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 17:55:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today Jane agonises over her trainer socks, Fi is worried about appearing on The Weakest Link and they discover that the herb dill hangs about all day. Novelist Kate Mosse also joins the pair to discuss her latest book, The Ghost Ship. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio. Follow us on Instagram! @JaneandFi</description></item><item><title>On the front line of bants (with Ruth Jones) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320094/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 17:41:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi chat through
Fi is a vision in burnt orange and Jane doesn’t have drool on her but you wouldn’t know that as they aren’t in front of the cameras...today. Welsh actress, writer and comedian Ruth Jones is today's guest, she talks about her third novel Love Untold and how it mixes the Welsh landscape with family estrangement.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>The fun bus of feminism (with Wes Streeting) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320095/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 17:47:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi are reunited after a week apart, and to celebrate, the podcast is being filmed. They're discussing Jane's decolletage, if anyone has ever been to Madame Tussaud's twice, and a new feature is born: Focus on Hitchin. Shadow Health Secretary Wes Streeting is today's guest, who talks about the conflict he felt between his faith and his sexuality as a young man, and being frequently asked whether he's in the running for Number 10.</description></item><item><title>Pelvic floor exercises on the radio (with Rob Rinder) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320096/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 17:05:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fi and Louise (The Minch) Minchin are back with a final episode of Off Air together before Jane returns next week.
They cover when you should do your pelvic floor exercises, 'I'm a Celebrity' secrets and how many hours there are in a day. Louise is sure it's 23. TV personality and lawyer Rob Rinder joins to talk about his new book 'The Trial'.
Please note: this episode contains discussion of allegations of sexual assault made against Daniel Korski.</description></item><item><title>Tech is my rage place (with Daisy Goodwin) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320097/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 16:07:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fi and Louise are being very brave using a new studio... next door to their usual one.
They cover awkward interviews, why it matters what side of the sofa you're on, and filming fitness videos in the Caribbean.
They're joined by Daisy Goodwin, the woman who has accused Tory London Mayor hopeful Daniel Korski of sexual assault - this was recorded before he pulled out of the race. Korski has denied the claims.</description></item><item><title>Profane and profound (with Wendy Mitchell) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320098/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 16:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fi and Louise have shaken up the routine and recorded this episode of Off Air before they've done the live show (no one tell Jane we let them do that, or she'll start getting ideas).
They're joined by best-selling author Wendy Mitchell&amp;nbsp;on her new book&amp;nbsp;One Last Thing&amp;nbsp;about living with a diagnosis of young-onset dementia.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>The Pavlov's dog of Times Radio (with Louise Minchin) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320099/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 17:08:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Louise Minchin joins Fi for today's episode of Off Air, while Jane is off enjoying her holiday (in her own words, 'splurging on Elton!').
They cover reading habits, extreme physical challenges, and the perils of TV vs. radio. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio.
Follow our instagram! @JaneandFi
Assistant Producer: Kate Lee</description></item><item><title>Every picnic needs a tart (with Karin Slaughter) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320100/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 17:03:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi have decided they bring out the worst in each other, but they're here nonetheless to talk about horror films, more erotic novels, and failed careers in advertising.
Karin Slaughter joins them to talk about her new book&amp;nbsp;'After That Night'
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio.
Follow our instagram! @JaneandFi</description></item><item><title>Comparing your manhood to a chipolata (with Peter Andre) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320101/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 17:11:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi are having 'all the fun of the fair' at work today as they talk about what women want on television, what to call an erotic novel, and how to put a bit of rock in your pomp. They're joined by TV star and singer Peter Andre, to talk about his new cook-book with Ben Smith - '#itsfine'
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Does nobody speak their mind in the South of England? | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320102/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 17:10:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi glide through today's episode, touching on all the important bits - from the decline of local newspapers to the waning tradition of thank you cards and the skills of map reading.
In today's Big Interview,&amp;nbsp;we spoke to Afua Hirsch, a journalist and creative - she's written a book on race, identity and belonging and she also runs a fashion business.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Now, she is presenting a three part TV programme about the upsurge in creativity across Africa - it’s called ‘Africa Rising’.</description></item><item><title>Why do we keep 'putting off' talking about the care system? [With Emily Kenway] | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320103/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 17:39:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi roll through a host of different topics on today's episode - from holiday luggage to men's underwear, Fi's love of Coldplay and Britain's care system.
In today's Big Interview,&amp;nbsp;writer and activist Emily Kenway&amp;nbsp;joins Jane and Fi to discuss her book 'Who Cares' - which delves into her experiences being a carer for her mum who had cancer. She argues for legal rights for people caring for family members who become ill or disabled.</description></item><item><title>A urine-soaked bus-stop and a Londis (with Richard Coles) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320104/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 16:52:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi are about to head off to their belated Christmas dinner... in the middle of June.
But they're here with another bumper episode of former Prime Ministers, ventriloquist dummies, and toys banished to the cupboard of history.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Follow our instagram!&amp;nbsp;@JaneandFi
Assistant Producer: Kate Lee</description></item><item><title>She's got her iced buns out (with Sally Gunnell) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320105/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 21:59:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi are very excited about their recent desk move - but they've just about got time to speak about general elections, Miriam Margolyes in a glacial blue silk stiff and power struggles at the top of Vogue...
Sally Gunnell was the 400 metres hurdles Olympic gold medallist in Barcelona in 1992 - she joins Jane and Fi to tell them about her 'deskercise' routine.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>I'm actually quite cynical about everybody (with Bob Harris) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320106/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 16:54:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320106/</guid><description>Podcast Description The heat just keeps getting to Jane as she becomes borderline delirious in this episode. They also chat Jane's intentions to get in the House of Lords, the joys of white bread and Coldplay (again).
Plus they’re joined by radio presenter “Whispering Bob” Harris. Details of The Songs The Beatles Gave Away UK tour are available at bobharris.org&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Can you hear the sounds of Elephant and Castle? | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320107/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 17:10:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320107/</guid><description>Podcast Description The heat has got Jane and Fi in a bit of a tizzy! They discuss 'self appointed characters', hating Coldplay and Fi provides another uncomfortable beep... Plus they’re joined by Dr. Olivia Chapple. You can check out her charity at www.horatiosgarden.org.uk. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio. Follow our instagram! @JaneandFi Assistant Producer: Eve Salusbury</description></item><item><title>Not many people have actually walked into an oven… (with Judy Murray) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320108/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 17:06:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi are talking about Jane’s gift of the second sight, getting angry about idioms, and asking why we can hear the British couple shouting at each other from twelve tents away... They're joined by Judy Murray to talk about her book 'The Wild Card'. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio Follow our instagram!</description></item><item><title>It is odd that he didn't have any genitalia (with Sathnam Sanghera) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320109/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 17:01:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi talk cat wounds, mint chocolate buttons and sliding into DMs...
They're joined by journalist and writer Sathnam Sanghera to talk about his new book 'Stolen History' .
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio Follow our instagram! @JaneandFi
Assistant Producer: Kate Lee
Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>The Archers is to you what Succession is to me (with Diana Evans) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320110/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 17:02:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi chat male contraception, London's transportation system and syphilis... as you do. They’re joined by novelist Diana Evans to discuss her most recent novel 'A House for Alice'. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Assistant Producers: Catherine Fusillo
Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>I've got these huge knickers, do you want them? (with Gareth Thomas) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320111/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 17:05:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi are very excited because they've launched an instagram account! You can get involved by following @JaneandFi. Plus rugby legend Gareth Thomas joins them from the side of a mountain as he completes the 3 Peak Challenge for his charity TackleHIV. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Assistant Producer: Eve Salusbury</description></item><item><title>Am I potty-mouthed? | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320112/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 17:07:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane is looking for a trucker's tan and a couple of burgers, while Fi is singing a little song about boob separators... They're joined by Ukrainian writer Victoria Belim, to talk about her memoir 'The Rooster House'&amp;nbsp;
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio Assistant Producer: Kate Lee Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Never ending dance floors of heaven (with DJ Fat Tony) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320113/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 17:02:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi get stuck into some award winning journalism and discuss the afterlife, being a bridesmaid, and some 'frin-tastic' emails.
They're joined by DJ Fat Tony to discuss his memoir 'I Don't Take Requests'. If you've been affected by any issues in this interview - send us an email at feedback@times.radio and we'll point you in the right direction to the resources and help you need. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>I don't believe in jet-lag (with Sir David Omand) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320114/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 16:59:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane has just about recovered from jet-lag after her trip to Glasgow a month ago. So much so that she considered a trip to B&amp;amp;Q this bank holiday Monday. She's joined by another Jane, Jane Mulkerrins, to talk about poetry, pinafores and penises. Professor Sir David Omand is today's big interview, he talks about his book 'How to Survive a Crisis'. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>A vigorous seesaw manoeuvre | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320115/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 16:00:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi are busy sunning themselves this bank holiday Monday but they took the time to record an email special. From Joe and the Juice to over-plucked eyebrows and inappropriate itching on public transport...there's much to cover!
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Assistant Producers: Eve Salusbury
Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler</description></item><item><title>The cheese calls to you (with Alvin Hall) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320116/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 16:57:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Buckle up for an extra existential episode, because Jane and Fi are asking if life would be easier as a sherbet fountain? Or maybe a two-fingered sloth in a zoo? What about a young cat having a wee in the middle of a mattress in the spare room? They're joined by Alvin Hall to talk about his book 'Driving the Green Book'. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Maybe they were just drunk (with Gary Kemp) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320117/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 17:00:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is a tabard a housecoat? Is a housecoat a tabard? And what's a dressing gown? Jane and Fi are asking the big questions in today's podcast. They're joined by popstar Gary Kemp, to talk about the Rockonteurs podcast's first live recording as part of The Podcast Show 2023 on 25th May.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>What kind of tog is your summer dressing gown? (With Jo Nesbø) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320118/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 16:58:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320118/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi grapple with the difference between a house coat and a dressing gown and Jane shares the savage lessons she learnt from the time she stroked a bee...
Plus, they’re joined by Norwegian crime writer Jo Nesbø to discuss the latest instalment of his Harry Hole detective series as well as anxiety induced dreams involving an old football coach.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Another day, another buttock (with Stephen Mangan) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320119/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 17:04:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi have swapped chairs for today's episode and it's causing chaos. They attempt some serious questions about flatulence when they're joined by actor Stephen Mangan, to talk about his new children's book 'The Unlikely Rise of Harry Sponge'.
They also discuss losing parents at a young age, playing Postman Pat and whether Stephen would ever do a superhero movie.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>A calming, cold flannel of a person | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320120/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 17:11:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320120/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi are talking about pet insurance that's a trifle suspicious, the little moments of joy in raising toddlers and, of course, sex. They're joined by Rory Cellan-Jones to talk about his podcast 'Movers and Shakers: a podcast about life with Parkinson's'
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Assistant Producers: Kate Lee</description></item><item><title>Head first into an absolutely delicious meal... | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320121/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 16:49:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fi's shower is juddering and Jane reckons we should get the plumbers in to have a look...
Plus, Claire Powell finally joins them ‘Off Air’ to discuss her debut novel (much championed by our Jane), which addresses family dynamics over a series of meals.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Assistant Producers: Eve Salusbury</description></item><item><title>Let loose on Noddy (with Jacqueline Wilson) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320122/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 17:06:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320122/</guid><description>Podcast Description Once Fi's finished eating her tuna sandwich, she and Jane get to work planning their twin room in the News UK Retirement Home for the Complex and Demanding.
They're joined by one of Britain's best loved children's authors, Jacqueline Wilson.
The Magic Faraway Tree: A New Adventure will be published on May 25th 2023.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>I've blinked twice...let me out! (with Annie Mac) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320123/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 17:23:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320123/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Jane &amp;amp; Fi take you through the mechanics of shopping in John Lewis, the tricky dynamics of sex in a long-term relationships, and the heartache of estrangement in families.
Plus Jane and Fi are joined by DJ-turned-novelist Annie Macmanus, known as 'Annie Mac', who talks about her new book 'The Mess We're In', her life philosophies and her relationship to her Irish identity. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>An orgy in suburbia | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320124/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 17:20:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Following an afternoon of slightly challenging radio performance, Jane and Fi bring you an all email special. There's plenty to discuss - like what excuse would you use to get out of an embarrassing situation? What happened when Jane almost interviewed Hilary Clinton? And why does Fi keep asking that poor man what CDs he's buying? If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>These enormous knickers are on and they stay on (with Joanne Harris) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320125/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 17:24:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Another joyous episode and this time Jane and Fi are talking the joys of naked swimming, elasticated clothing and the controversial twirl.
Plus, they're joined by bestselling author Joanne Harris, author of ‘Chocolat’, to discuss her new novel ‘Broken Light’ all about middle age, menopause and female anger.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Helping Grandma into her girdle | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320126/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 16:49:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi plan their re-enactment of the coronation and make their apologies to Jane's late cat Mittens, who is definitely an 'Off Air' fan. They're joined by Gabby Logan, sports presenter, former gymnast and brilliantly successful podcaster. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio Assistant Producers: Kate Lee Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Covered in Coronation glitter and glitz (with Emma Bridgewater and the American Viscountess) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320127/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 08:16:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320127/</guid><description>Podcast Description One more sleep until Coronation day, and Jane and Fi are struggling to contain their excitement. So, they're bringing you an extra special coronation countdown episode of Off Air. Jane and Fi are joined by Emma Bridgewater, ceramics and pottery designer, and by Julia Montagu, known as the American Viscountess If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Someone alert Westminster council that the clock face is broken! | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320128/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 17:30:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320128/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s the final episode before the Coronation on Saturday and hopefully you’re not sick of it yet because Jane and Fi come to you live from a balcony overlooking Westminster Abbey where the new king will soon be crowned…
Plus Jane and Fi are joined by Lord Soames - grandson to Winston Churchill, former Tory MP and close friend of King Charles. He shares his memory of the late Queen’s coronation in 1953.</description></item><item><title>Strangled by our robot carers (with Julie McDowall) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320129/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 16:52:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320129/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane explained why she won't be throwing a Eurovision party, they talk anxiety inducing meetings and softy civil servants.
Plus, they’re finally, finally, finally joined by nuclear threat specialist and journalist Julie McDowall…and its just as disconcerting as you’d expect. Her book ‘Attack Warning Red!’ is out now.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>All the ingredients for a Christmas hit (with Philippa Gregory) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320130/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 16:40:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320130/</guid><description>Podcast Description What’s putting a pep in Fi’s step? Why isn’t Jane a bestselling author? Have you ever swum naked and not smiled? Plus, Jane and Fi come up with a plan to make their fortune with a soft rock classic… They’re joined by historical novelist Philippa Gregory to talk about all things royal. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Beat me on the bottom with a Woman's Weekly (with Alex Jones) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320131/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 17:12:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi are full of coronation chicken sandwiches and ready to talk about everything from nuclear war to safe sex. They're joined by The One Show presenter Alex Jones, to hear about her new show Reunion Hotel. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio Assistant Producer: Kate Lee Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Oh I'm not discreet at all | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320132/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 16:45:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320132/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane continues to fear for the end of world but its not over yet.... we've got a podcast episode to do! Jane and Fi run you through some top radio jargon, Jane heavily 'trails' next week and a man called Terry is trying to stay with Jane and Fi.
Plus they’re joined by Emma Sky OBE, an expert on conflict, reconciliation and stability, who has worked mainly in the Middle East, to pick her big brains.</description></item><item><title>A sip of Kylie's Cava and a gulp of Beefy Botham’s Sauvignon | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320133/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 17:10:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane’s having tummy troubles but Fi’s by her side offering kind words of support (as always), plus coronation plans commence but Fi has banned Jane from getting drunk…
They're joined by music journalist Sylvia Patterson to discuss her second memoir ‘Same Old Girl: Staying Alive, Staying Sane, Staying Myself’, a story of cancer, friendship and ageing.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>I don't mean to immediately degrade the podcast (with Matt Baker) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320134/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 17:25:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi are battling on despite technical difficulties to talk about longevity, whether you can ever really own a pet and when is the best day for a dawn chorus... They're joined by TV presenter Matt Baker, to hear about his new show Matt Baker's Travels in the Country: USA. Normal sound quality service will resume tomorrow. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>It's one of my little icks (with Larry Lamb) | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320135/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 17:05:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Once the effects of half a paper cup of Kylie Minogue's Prosecco have worn off, Jane and Fi discuss school prizes, knowing your limitations and coronation themed snacks.
They're joined by actor Larry Lamb, about the show B﻿&amp;amp;B By The Sea and a Gavin and Stacey reunion.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Jane to the power of two - with Lorraine Kelly | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320136/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 17:17:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320136/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Jane talk poetry, self esteem, and poor Brian's goolies. They're joined by Lorraine (yes, all the names on this podcast have to rhyme today) Kelly to discuss the 'No Butts' campaign. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio Assistant Producer: Kate Lee Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>I'm full of good bacteria - with Angela Hartnett | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320137/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 16:43:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane is ready to ramble as she's flying solo today. Michelin star chef Angela Hartnett stops by to talk about the latest series of her podcast 'Dish'.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio Assistant Producer: Kate Lee Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A moment to think about little Brian's balls - with Curtis Sittenfeld | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320138/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 16:48:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320138/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi discuss small talk at parties and school dinners whilst poor Brian awaits collection from the vets having parted with his manhood.&amp;nbsp;
Plus they're joined by the best-selling American author Curtis Sittenfeld to talk about her SNL inspired new novel ‘Romantic Comedy’.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Assistant Producer: Eve Salusbury</description></item><item><title>Actually, just call an ambulance - Professor Tim Spector | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320139/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 17:04:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane is back, but has she brought Fi any presents from her holiday? Who can help Jane fix her satellite? And can a cool, successful man ever be a keeper? They're joined by co-founder of Zoe, Professor Tim Spector to discuss the future of food and keeping your gut healthy. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>I was a binge smoker... - with Stig Abell | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320140/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 16:44:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320140/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's the last day of Jane’s absence but the wonderful Jane Mulkerrins, associate editor of The Times Magazine, has filled the Jane-shaped hole in everyone's hearts.
Plus Times Radio’s very own Stig Abell stops in for a chat about his new novel ‘Death Under a Little Sky’. They chat work, sex scenes and having no friends.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>I can't cope with your youthful success - with Cecelia Ahern | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320141/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 17:00:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ed Vaizey, who's sitting in for Jane today, is impressed by Fi's youthful success - Fi's trying not to be offended.
Ed's also kicking himself that he didn't get a selfie with today's big guest, author Cecelia Ahern, who's just released her 19th novel 'In a Thousand Different Ways'.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>I've crashed the junction - with Jenny Eclair | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320142/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 17:02:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320142/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane's away and, in her absence, Fi is teaching Ed Vaizey all the radio lingo. What's the difference between a bed and a jingle? What's "crashing the junction"? And what does that big red light mean?
They're joined by comedian Jenny Eclair to talk about Taskmaster, podcasting, and everything else in between.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Just another manic Monday | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320143/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 17:05:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320143/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fi is still under the weather so joins via zoom, meanwhile, Jane’s away on holiday so Ed Vaizey is sitting in… what could go wrong?
Plus Suzanne Heywood joins them to discuss her memoir ‘Wavewalker: Breaking Free’ which recounts an astonishing childhood involving her parents having the wild idea to retrace Captain Cook’s third voyage for the best part of a decade…
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>It's a two-patch kind of day | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320144/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 17:09:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320144/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fi is still under the weather so Jane's on her lonesome again this episode, but she's making the most of her "splendid isolation".
Pre-ailment, Jane and Fi spoke to Nicola Fox, the woman who made it all the way from Hertfordshire to NASA.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Assistant Producer: Kea Browning</description></item><item><title>Jane goes it alone - with Christine Flack | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320145/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 16:46:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320145/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fi isn't feeling well so Jane's flying solo for this episode. Christine Flack speaks to Jane about her daughter, the TV presenter Caroline Flack, who took her own life in 2020 at 40 years old. If you’ve been affected by anything discussed in this interview, please email feedback@times.radio and you’ll be sent a list of resources. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>A handbag full of vomit | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320146/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 17:03:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320146/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a long day of arts and crafts in the newsroom, Jane and Fi discuss the pros and cons of a 'pimped up M&amp;amp;S hot cross bun'. They're joined by Alice Winn author of 'In Memoriam'. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio Assistant Producer: Kate Lee Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>My inner philatelist is a-flutter - with Elizabeth Day | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320147/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 17:17:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320147/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane's asking what people did in the old days on a Sunday afternoon when all the shops used to be closed, while Fi's mangling adjectives in her sleep. They're joined by Elizabeth Day, to talk about her new book 'Friendaholic'. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio Assistant Producer: Kate Lee Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Countdown to The Coronation | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320148/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 16:00:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320148/</guid><description>Podcast Description For this special Friday episode, Jane and Fi are joined by two royal experts to count down to The Coronation of King Charles III.
They also discuss whether or not Harry and Meghan will be there, what on earth to do about Prince Andrew, and why people aren't celebrating Princess Anne enough. Royah Nikkhah is Royal Editor at The Sunday Times and Valentine Low is Royal Correspondent for The Times.</description></item><item><title>We're a little bit raggedy around the edges | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320149/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 17:08:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320149/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can the production team fool Jane and Fi with an AI generated email? They're joined by Nigerian writer Ayobami Adebayo about her second novel 'A Spell of Good Things'. And, Deputy Food Editor at The Times, Hannah Evans, tells Jane and Fi about Michelin starred kids menus. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Pithy with a twinkle - with Mel Giedroyc | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320150/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 17:08:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320150/</guid><description>Podcast Description The pair take a glimpse down memory lane and reminisce over maypole dancing, and look to the future as they decide what they'd spend their lottery winnings on. Jane and Fi are joined by comedian, actress and television presenter Mel Giedroyc to discuss her new podcast series for Tortoise - Mel's Electric Adventure. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>De-moulding a jelly rabbit | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320151/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 17:08:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320151/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi's friendship may be over after a terrible Kent-based ant-breeding company name suggestion. They're joined by journalist and food critic Jimi Famurewa, to talk about his new podcast Where's Home Really? If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio Producer: Kate Lee Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Daddy pig really is a useless lummox | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320152/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 17:16:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320152/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fi's pitching her latest invention to help women to avoid bathroom queues, and Jane wants Russell Crowe to come around and give her an exorcism.
They're joined by award-winning investigative journalist and author Paul Morgan-Bentley, who's written a book about parenting equality.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Producer: Kea Browning
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Où est Greggs? - with Eddie Izzard | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320153/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 18:12:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320153/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi soldier on through a printing nightmare. They cover everything from daytime TV to French oral exams, and still find time to discuss Greg Wallace twice. And, Eddie Izzard joins Jane and Fi to talk about her new one woman performance of Great Expectations.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio</description></item><item><title>Some very frank details about prostate examinations - with Tony Robinson | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320154/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 18:45:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320154/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane is considering speed-learning the lute, while Fi wonders whether we've lost the art of cooking with a mould.
They're joined by actor, writer and presenter Tony Robinson, whose new podcast Cunningcast launches tomorrow.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Assistant Producer: Kea Browning
Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>We must keep a veneer of showbiz | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320155/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 18:05:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320155/</guid><description>Podcast Description There's no time for shilly shallying or dilly dallying on today's episode... Jane is on the run from her dream tortoise and Fi's promised everyone biscuits tomorrow. They're joined by psychotherapist Stella O'Malley, author of 'What Your Teen is Trying to Tell You: Surviving, thriving and re-connecting through the teenage years'. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Haphazard on a conveyor belt | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320156/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 18:03:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320156/</guid><description>Podcast Description We've got a new theme tune, a new moisturising regime for Jane and a new supermarket checkout career for Fi.
They're also joined by Asma Khan, UN World Food Programme Chef Advocate and the founder of the super successful restaurant Darjeeling Express.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Assistant Producer: Kate Lee</description></item><item><title>Live at WOW Festival | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320157/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 09:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320157/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this bonus episode of Off Air, Jane and Fi are live from WOW - Women of the World Festival at the Royal Festival Hall in London.
They're joined onstage by comedian and writer Meera Syal and Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander Social Justice Commissioner June Oscar.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>We're here because we're authentic - with Anneka Rice | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320158/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 18:06:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320158/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fi discusses her former ambitions to be a professional oboe player, and Jane claims Barack Obama is actually a bit of a 'cold fish' in real life.
They're joined by Anneka Rice, who's talking about Challenge Anneka, which is returning after a 30-year hiatus. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Assistant Producer: Kea Browning</description></item><item><title>'Jane, get your dad to call me.' | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320159/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 17:43:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320159/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi make cultural comparison and dissect the perplexing nature of a Boots...
Also, they're are joined by Roma Agrawal, the structural engineer who helped design the Shard, to consider the seven small inventions that changed the world. Her new book ‘Nuts and Bolts’ is out now.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Let's park Gary Lineker and talk about toasters - with Spencer Matthews | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320160/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 17:52:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320160/</guid><description>Podcast Description The dial on the side of the toaster has inspired a critical debate - could this be the most important experiment of our time?
Also, Jane and Fi are joined by Made in Chelsea's Spencer Matthews, who's released a documentary about the journey to find his brother's body on Mount Everest.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Rich people in the public eye - with Dan Snow | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320161/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 18:11:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320161/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi pitch a device to help short people feel more comfortable in the bath.
They're also joined by historian Dan Snow, who chats about his latest documentary&amp;nbsp;about the Black Death.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Assistant Producer: Kea Browning
Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>A cosy festival of hunker-downer-dom | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320162/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 18:28:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320162/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi start a fond and long farewell to the podcast music, and Jane gives her latest theatre review. They're also joined by Pulitzer Prize winning journalist James B. Stewart, on his new book "Unscripted." If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Assistant Producer: Kate Lee
Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>‘Get Off Air…’ - with Donna Leon | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320163/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 17:59:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320163/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's International Women's Day and Jane and Fi are busy empowering. Plus Jane and Fi consider what to name their dating platform...
And crime novelist Donna Leon joins them, lulling them with her pronunciation of ‘risotto’.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Assistant Producer: Eve Salusbury
Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>That’s a substantial sword the lady is baring - with Vanessa Feltz | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320164/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 18:46:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320164/</guid><description>Podcast Description Seven years of podcasting, and Jane reveals at last why handbags put her off joining the Navy.
Meanwhile Fi’s asking: why isn’t there a Poundland on the moon?&amp;nbsp;
And, they’re joined by legendary broadcaster Vanessa Feltz.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Assistant Producer: Kate Lee
Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>God doesn't notice cheese - with Adjoa Andoh | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320165/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 18:12:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320165/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why won't Jane leave Fi's olives alone? Why does Fi say magazine like that? And where are have Jane's varifocals gone? They're joined by Bridgerton star Adjoa Andoh, who is directing and starring in a brand new version of Shakespeare's 'Richard III'. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio Assistant Producer: Kate Lee Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Never go for double denim - with Sally Wainwright | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320166/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 18:20:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320166/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi ponder their fashion icon status and discuss the upcoming 'Spring Thor' - a term which may or may not catch on.
They're joined by screenwriter Sally Wainwright, the mind behind Happy Valley, Gentleman Jack, Scott and Bailey, and Last Tango In Halifax.&amp;nbsp;
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Assistant Producer: Kea Browning</description></item><item><title>Raisins with consequences | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320167/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 18:02:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320167/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane gives us her favourite facts about Saint David, while Fi ponders an acorn of an idea for a matchmaking service. They're joined by Richard Reeves, writer and academic, to discuss his book 'Of Boys and Men: Why the modern male is struggling, why it matters, and what to do about it'. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Triggered by the word 'teats' | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320168/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 18:12:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320168/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi are talking all things breastfeeding.
They're joined by art historian Joanna Wolfarth to discuss her book Milk: An Intimate History of Breastfeeding; it's out now.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Assistant Producer: Kea Browning
Times Radio Producer: Kate Lee
Podcast Executive Producer: Ben Mitchell
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>Hedgehog on hedgehog action | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320169/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 18:13:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320169/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi enjoy a slice of cake for Fi's birthday.
They're joined by Ben Bailey Smith (AKA Doc Brown) to discuss his podcast, Shrink the Box, which is out now.
They also hear from Professor Dawn Scott, who's got some surprising research on violent hedgehogs.&amp;nbsp;
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio</description></item><item><title>Move over Starsky and Hutch | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320170/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 18:18:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320170/</guid><description>Podcast Description Should you sing your own theme music? Jane and Fi find out. They're also joined by surgeon Averil Mansfield, where they talk about why surgery is a male dominated profession, what makes a good doctor and performing surgery on stuffed animals. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Assistant Producer: Kate Lee
Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler</description></item><item><title>Self-care? Just get cats! | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320171/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 18:12:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320171/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sourdough starters, kombucha, mindfulness and jade vagina balls - has self care gone too far? Dr. Pooja Lakshmin thinks so. She joins Jane and Fi to help debunk the wellness industry and discuss her new book ‘Real Self-Care’. Plus, Jane and Fi discuss Rod Stewart in a high-vis and street party ice breakers...
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>A lot of people swear by luncheon meat | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320172/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 17:56:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320172/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi are joined by Patricia Field, the costume designer behind Sex and the City, Emily in Paris, The Devil Wears Prada and more. Can Jane tell the difference between noodles and spaghetti? What would Fi talk to Boris Johnson about if they got stuck in a lift together? And where are Yorkies made? If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>We're full of joie de vivre! - with Rev. Richard Coles and Charles Spencer | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320173/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 18:06:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320173/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi are back and well rested from their week away.
They're joined by Reverend Richard Coles, cosy crime King and Radio 4 jock, and his old neighbour Charles Spencer,&amp;nbsp;9th Earl Spencer to discuss their new history podcast.
The podcast 'The Rabbit Hole Detectives' is hosted by Dr. Cat Jarman, Rev. Richard Coles and Charles Spencer,&amp;nbsp;9th Earl Spencer. It's out now.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>It's NOT a pie | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320174/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 17:51:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320174/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi have swanned off on holiday, so Chloe Tilley and Calum Macdonald are here to hold down the fort for the last time before their return on Monday.
They're joined by Dr. Maggie Aderin-Pocock, space scientist and science communicator.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Assistant Producer: Kate Lee
Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler</description></item><item><title>This is my Super Bowl! | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320175/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 17:35:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320175/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi have swanned off on holiday, so Chloe Tilley and Calum Macdonald are here to hold down the fort. They're joined by Director Shekhar Kapur to talk about his new film 'What's Love Got to Do with It?', in cinemas on February 24th. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio Assistant Producer: Kate Lee</description></item><item><title>Head first into glory - with Matty Lee | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320176/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 17:42:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320176/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi have swanned off on holiday, so Chloe Tilley and Calum Macdonald are here to hold down the fort.
They’re joined by GB diver Matty Lee to chat Olympic gold, I’m A Celeb and performance pressure.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Assistant Producer: Eve Salusbury
Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler</description></item><item><title>We had a really great thirty minutes... | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320177/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 17:44:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320177/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi have swanned off on holiday, so Chloe Tilley and Calum Macdonald are here to hold down the fort.
They're joined by Adam Vaughn, Environment Editor of The Times to talk about water pollution, and by Lola Tambling, the 14 year old skateboarder who placed sixth in the World Skateboarding Championship this weekend.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Good luck finding your nipples | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320178/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 18:04:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320178/</guid><description>Podcast Description After their last live show before their holiday, Jane and Fi discuss smuggling diet coke into the studio and bad directions from the production team.
They were also joined by Professor Dame Lesley Regan who is the UK's first women's health ambassador.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio Assistant Producer: Kate Lee</description></item><item><title>How many inches do you think yours is? | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320179/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 18:15:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320179/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi get giddy as their holiday looms and they talk TV inches and cauliflower soup for breakfast.
Also poet, artist and performer Debris Stevenson joins them to talk about overcoming adversity and her new adaptation of 'Much Ado About Nothing'.
Much Ado About Nothing is playing at the Duke of York's Theatre until Friday 10th of February.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Chicken shoes and a compound brown sauce - with Steven Moffat | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320180/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 18:20:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi are joined by the writer behind Dr Who and Sherlock, Steven Moffat, to hear about his new play 'The Unfriend'. They also discuss the answer to the question of £1 daffodils, chicken hunter vs chicken shoes, and how many nipples the average person has. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Like something out of a Victoria Wood sketch | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320181/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 18:02:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320181/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi talk ready-made home-made dinners, 50th birthday parties, and the juxtaposition of urban virility. They're also joined by CNN's chief international anchor, Christiane Amanpour. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio Assistant Producer: Kate Lee Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler Podcast Executive Producer: Ben Mitchell Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>I've never been able to look at a pigeon the same way again | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320182/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320182/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi have been at the Destinations Show at Kensington Olympia to explore all things travel.
The film-maker and travel writer Ash Bhardwaj discusses his recent 8,500 km overland trip from the top of Norway to Romania, at a time of increased tensions between Russia and the West.
Also they talk pet food and the theme tune dance challenge.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>A "fly by the seat of your pants-er" - with Jojo Moyes | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320183/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 18:18:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320183/</guid><description>Podcast Description Award-winning author Jojo Moyes joins Jane and Fi to discuss her new book Someone Else's Shoes.
Also they consider what job they'd have done in Victorian times and endometriosis pain.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Assistant Producer: Sameer Merali
Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler
Podcast Executive Producer: Ben Mitchell
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Women shouting angrily - with Sarah Polley | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320184/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 18:14:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320184/</guid><description>Podcast Description Director Sarah Polley joins Jane and Fi to discuss societal victim blaming, Oscars snubs and her new film ‘Women Talking’.
Also top water cooler moments and the daffodil debacle continues…
'Women Talking' out in select cinemas from the 10th of February and UK wide from the 17th.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Problematic Uteri | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320185/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 18:02:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320185/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi are joined by Lauren Fleshman, the celebrated American distance runner and author of Good For A Girl My Life Running In A Man's World.
Also they discuss the delights of the hotel breakfast buffet and an appeal to get themselves invited onto a men-only Whatsapp group.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>The ski lifts beckon, darling | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320186/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 18:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320186/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi are joined by 'Diva Divorce Lawyer' Ayesha Vardag on her strict dress codes and high profile clients.
Also, the news you've all been waiting for: what did Jane think of Othello?
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Assistant Producer: Kate Lee
Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler
Podcast Executive Producer: Ben Mitchell</description></item><item><title>It's what Shakespeare would have wanted... | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320187/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 17:46:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320187/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi are joined by Paulette Hamilton, the first black woman to become an MP in Birmingham. Also - how did Fi's kittens get their names? Will Jane enjoy a modern take on Shakespeare's Othello? And what are 'Wendy bits'!? If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio Times Radio Producer: Kate Lee Podcast Executive Producer: Ben Mitchell Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Everyone’s grandma should be their number one fan | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320188/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 17:58:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320188/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi discuss the homelessness crisis and systemic failure as well as why your Grandma should always be your best cheerleader with journalist Daniel Lavelle.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Assistant Producer: Eve Salusbury
Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler
Podcast Executive Producer: Ben Mitchell
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>My perplexometer is off the charts - with Amanda Owen | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320189/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 18:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320189/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi chat £58 sheep, giving birth in the living room and the challenges of modern farming with Yorkshire&amp;nbsp;Shepherdess Amanda Owen. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio Assistant Producer: Kate Lee Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler Podcast Executive Producer: Ben Mitchell Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>I love a Tuesday - with Alex Edelman | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320190/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 18:11:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320190/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi chat flexitarians, maternity leave and what is the best day to go to the theatre….
They're also joined by American comedian Alex Edelman on his latest show ‘Just For Us’.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Assistant Producer: Erin Carney
Times Radio Producer: Kate Lee
Podcast Executive Producer: Ben Mitchell</description></item><item><title>Love and loss - with Jason Watkins | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320191/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 18:05:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320191/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi chat childbirth, royalty and the tennis champion that won £40…
They're also joined by actor Jason Watkins, who speaks about losing his two year old daughter a decade ago to sepsis and why he's trying to raise awareness of the illness now through a documentary with his wife.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>If music be the food of love, order her a happy meal - with Fred Sirieix | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320192/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 18:03:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320192/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane is back after her day off, and Fi is struggling to keep the peace... They're joined by the star of Channel 4's 'First Dates' Fred Sirieix to talk about the link between food and love. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio Assistant Producer: Kate Lee Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler Podcast Executive Producer: Ben Mitchell Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Any Jane will do - with Cariad Lloyd | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320193/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 18:12:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320193/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane's taking a well deserved day off so Fi is joined by our second favourite Jane, Associate Editor of The Times Magazine, Jane Mulkerrins. Comedian and podcaster Cariad Lloyd joined Fi and Jane 2.0 in the studio to talk about her new book 'You Are Not Alone'. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>BBC Director of eye level - with Ross Kemp | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320194/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 18:15:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320194/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you were thinking...er...Ross Kemp doing a light entertainment game show…how does that work? So were we. And so was he.
TV tough guy turned Mr. Saturday Night Prime Time, Ross Kemp, joined Jane and Fi in the studio to talk about Bridge of Lies.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler</description></item><item><title>That seal has a malevolent look about him - with Michaela Strachan | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320195/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 17:57:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320195/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi are joined by 'Winter Watch' presenter Michaela Strachan, who solves the mystery of why there's no 'Summer Watch'... Also, do you like going to school reunions? What will happen when radio presenters are replaced by robots? And what's that seal doing in M&amp;amp;S? If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio Assistant Producer: Kate Lee Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler Podcast Executive Producer: Ben Mitchell Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>I didn't take up much space and I wasn't any bother | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320196/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 18:15:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320196/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you didn't study geography, would still have gone on all the trips? Jane did?
Also, historian Katy Hessel discusses the power of the lost women of the art world with her new book 'A history of art without men'.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler
Podcast Executive Producer: Ben Mitchell</description></item><item><title>Litter training, it's the natural world in all its glory - with Omid Djalili | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320197/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 17:54:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320197/</guid><description>Podcast Description Omid Djalili the actor and comedian&amp;nbsp;joins Jane and Fi to talk about his new high-concept podcast 'Please Tell Me A Story'. Plus, Fi tries to work out what name her phone would auto-correct to 'catheter' and Jane teaches us how to get a shy kitten to poo... If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>I draw the line at the Sugababes | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320198/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 18:00:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320198/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ding! Ding! Gloves up gentlemen.
As extracts from 'Spare' hit the papers Stig Abell joins Jane and Fi to talk sibling rivalry and picks through the accusations Prince Harry has levelled at his brother, Prince William, and the revelations about his own personal life.
Also, lawyer turned bestselling author Nadine Matheson discusses her new police procedural 'The Binding Room' - the sequel to 'The Jigsaw Man' in the DI Henley series</description></item><item><title>I'm completely over beavers | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320199/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 18:15:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320199/</guid><description>Podcast Description Anoosheh Ashooori was held in an Iranian prison for five years only to be released last year alongside Nazanin Zagari-Radcliffe. He joins Jane and Fi to relive his harrowing ordeal. Today PM Rishi Sunak announced his wish for all UK students to continue studying some form of maths until the age of 18. University challenge star, broadcaster and math's teacher, Bobby Seagull, discusses why he thinks this is a good idea.</description></item><item><title>I love Nando's mash - with Romesh Ranganathan | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320200/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 18:13:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320200/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you still partake in a cheeky Nandos? What would you do for a famous 'black card'? Fi suggests a tattoo may get you there?
Comedian Ramesh Ranganathan reveals the story behind one of his fascinating tattoos, talks about his new sitcom with Katherine Ryan 'Romantic Getaway', and with his former math's teacher hat on he discusses what his plans would be do to fix the UK education system.</description></item><item><title>A whole degree in umbilical scrutiny | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320201/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 17:58:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320201/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi talk about their favourite presents this Christmas, campaign for cat's eyes on the roads in the US, and discuss the ins and outs of blind baking. They're joined by bestselling author Gill Hornby to discuss her new book 'Godmersham Park'. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio Assistant Producer: Kate Lee Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler Podcast Executive Producer: Ben Mitchell Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Drunk Funcles | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320202/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 00:01:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320202/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today's final best-of before Jane and Fi return next week, they talk to the award winning food critic, columnist and broadcaster Grace Dent, about her hit podcast Comfort Eating.
Plus, Hollywood director of Bridesmaids, The Heat and Ghostbusters, Paul Feig, talks all things cocktails.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Assistant Producers: Kate Lee, Emma Sherry, Eve Salusbury</description></item><item><title>It's a strange time of year isn't it | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320203/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 00:01:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320203/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ready for a second helping of the very best of 'Off air with Jane and Fi'? Today, the author and How to Fail podcast host Elizabeth Day joins them in the studio to talk about friendship, writing for different audiences, and what happened when she interviewed Liz Truss.
Plus, the chef and campaigner Jamie Oliver talks about his new book, how families can continue to cook good food during the current cost of living crisis, and stopping the government U-turn on health eating for children.</description></item><item><title>Crimbo limbo | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320204/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 00:01:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320204/</guid><description>Podcast Description Another Christmas cracker of a best-of 'Off air... with Jane and Fi' for you today featuring the comedian Tom Allen who talks about how he channelled the loss of his father into his memoir "Too Much", and slipping on lubricant in aa gay sauna.
Plus, the legendary chef Yotam Ottolenghi on his new cookbook "Extra Good Things" and which cultural recipes he has "bastardised" and which he would never dream of touching.</description></item><item><title>Gloves off for Boxing Day | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320205/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 00:01:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320205/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to the first of our best-of episodes of 'Off air' with some of Jane and Fi's favourite interviews of the year.
Today they are joined by Monty Python star and seasoned traveller, Sir Michael Palin, to talk about his latest journey through Iraq. Plus, Britain's second astronaut, and first to be a resident of the International Space Station - Major Tim Peake.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Wine Times LIVE - with Jane and Fi | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320206/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 12:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320206/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you've been enjoying 'Off air... with Jane and Fi' then perhaps you might be interested in another podcast here at The Times? So let us introduce you to Wine Times.
And discussing and decanting with Suzi Ruffell and Will Lyons on a special live edition of Wine Times - up on the 17th floor of the News Building and in front of an audience of lucky - are Times Radio's newest presenting duo.</description></item><item><title>Imagine Uncle Dave is a bit drunk | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320207/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320207/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's the final day of Jane's solo career in the studio with The Times science editor Tom Whipple filling in the guest presenter's chair.
Also, journalist and author Rachel Clarke joins them in the studio to talk through her book about working in the NHS palliative care team - and discusses what she believes needs to be done in order for the current NHS strikes to come to an end.</description></item><item><title>I really can't fathom a minestrone | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320208/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 18:57:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320208/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's day three with no Fi, so to help her cheer up, Jane is joined by three guests this episode. Historical author Julia Boyd discusses the news that a 97-year-old former typist at a Nazi concentration camp has been convicted of aiding in the murder of more than 10,000 people. Times Radio's Chief Political Commentator Lucy Fisher shares her most memorable interview of the year, and Asa Bennett, former speechwriter for Liz Truss, sheds some light on working for the UK's shortest serving PM.</description></item><item><title>I'm starting to miss the little thing | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320209/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 18:30:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320209/</guid><description>Podcast Description Another day flying solo and Jane is already starting to look forward to Fi's return.
The Times Technology Business Editor, Katie Prescott, is Jane's presenters friend today and tries her best to explain a bizarre cryptocurrency fraud story.
Also, the novelist and creator of Grantchester, James Runcie, discusses his new book - and ode to his wife Marilyn's - 'Tell me Good Things'.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>I don't run the organisation...yet | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320210/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320210/</guid><description>Podcast Description With Fi off on her Christmas holidays Jane is flying solo...with a little help from her friends.
Fellow Jane and associate editor of The Times Magazine, Jane Mulkerrins, is in the hot seat to discuss some of her favourite stories of the year - and the lengths she will go to in order to get a story...including naked walks in the the British countryside.
Also, former supermodel Paulina Porizkova discusses her new book "</description></item><item><title>I'm not driving home for Christmas | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320211/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320211/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the last podcast of the year for Fi before she follows Santa on a merry jaunt in the sky for her Christmas hols - they celebrate by talking all things snakes.
Jennie Bond reviews the second instalment of the Harry and Meghan Netflix documentary - and novelist Barbara Kingsolver discusses her new book "Demon Copperhead"
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>At least I'm owning my own hypocrisy | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320212/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 18:01:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320212/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi discuss Joanna Lumley's recent comments, being given presentation pickles, and the need for more lollipop people in Marrakesh. They're joined by Teresa Weiler, who opens up about the process of finding out her birth parents were siblings, and why it meant she didn’t want children of her own. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Walruses, they're not lookers | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320213/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 18:28:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320213/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi come up with a new safe word, and have to use it quite a few times. They're joined by Andrea Elliott, Pulitzer prize winning author of 'Invisible Child: Poverty, Survival &amp;amp; Hope in an American City' If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio Assistant Producer: Kate Lee Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler Podcast Executive Producer: Ben Mitchell Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Royal flush - with Susannah Constantine | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320214/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320214/</guid><description>Podcast Description What would you do if you blocked the loo at a high powered event? Turn to the sister of the Queen and use a cake slice? Surely not...but if you did you certainly wouldn't keep that cake slice...would you?!
Fashion guru Susannah Constantine answers that and so much more in her new memoir "Ready For Absolutely Nothing" including how it feels to be ghosted by Dolph Lungren, stalking Scissor Sisters front-man Jake Shears until he agreed to become her friend, and whether Elton John falls under 'E' or 'J' in her address book.</description></item><item><title>A multi-purpose royalspert - with Gyles Brandreth | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320215/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 18:20:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320215/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gyles Brandreth joins Jane on Fi to discuss his podcast 'Something Rhymes&amp;nbsp;With Purple' with Susie Dent, and it's perfectly timed on the day that Harry and Meghan's Netflix documentary dropped. In the meantime, Jane's still attempting to predict the outcome of England's World Cup match, and Fi's got a handbag full of used turkey... If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>A little playful smile resting around my face - with Jake Humphrey | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320216/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 18:27:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320216/</guid><description>Podcast Description Will Jane's dreams of becoming a lounge crooner ever come true? Does Fi have an incredibly serious face? Can the pair still unlock their full potential?
Jane and Fi are joined by sports broadcaster and host of "The High Performance" podcast, Jake Humphrey, for this week's edition of Wellness Wednesday.
Also, author AM Homes discusses her new book "The Unfolding".
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>My laughable weekly shop | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320217/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 18:05:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320217/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi ask; are you still drifting in with us? Should a broadcaster come to work with a blocked nose? Can a student live on Dairylea and two loaves?
Also, the award winning author Adele Parks talks about her newest book 'One Last Secret'.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Assistant Producer: Kate Lee</description></item><item><title>I've never got on with a rhombus | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320218/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 18:13:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320218/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi ask what shape vegan food should be, how best to make small talk at parties, and do pilots ever get used to aeroplane toilets?
Pilot and author of 'How to Land a Plane' and 'Imagine a City' Mark Vanhoenacker has the answers to at least one of those questions.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Standards: we've got to have some - with Michael and Hilary Whitehall | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320219/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 17:58:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320219/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michael and Hilary Whitehall join Jane and Fi to talk about their podcast 'Wittering Whitehalls' and give their advice on what to tell a client who's been in a terrible play. Also - why is this podcast called Off Air? Why do vegans like meat shaped meat substitutes? And can Jane correctly predict the score of England's next World Cup game? If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>You've declared yourself a cockle convert | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320220/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 18:00:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320220/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi discover the benefits of Sea Moss with Sea Moss Boss boss Tee McKen. They're joined by Dr Anne Marie Imafidon, the&amp;nbsp;youngest ever girl to pass A level computing and founder of Stemettes, about her new book 'She's In Ctrl'. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio Assistant Producer: Kate Lee Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler Podcast Executive Producer: Ben Mitchell Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>No craic - with Michelle Gallen | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320221/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320221/</guid><description>Podcast Description Would you skip the football to hunt for your stopcock? Fi might be doing that very thing whilst you're listening. They are also joined by the Irish author Michelle Gallen to discus her latest novel Factory Girls. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler Podcast Executive Producer: Ben Mitchell Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Porn, the family business - with Jamie Morton and Alice Levine | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320222/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 18:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320222/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fi: "We've had too much sex already...and it's only Monday!"
Stars of the hit podcast series My Dad Wrote a Porno, Jamie Morton and Alice Levine, reveal why the show is ending, and answer Fi's obsessive question...what's happening to the RSS feed (one for the podcast nerds).
Also - some amazing emails including a nudity based excursion that will leave you questioning your next summer holiday.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Slipping on lubricant - with Tom Allen | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320223/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 18:15:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320223/</guid><description>Podcast Description The comedian Tom Allen joins Jane and Fi in the studio to talk about how he channelled the loss of his father into his new book "Too Much".
Also, how slipping on lubricant in a gay sauna was his first foray into slapstick comedy, his affinity with middle-aged women, and how American toilets are different to ours in the UK.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Gasping for a lovely drink - with Paul Feig | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320224/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 18:26:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320224/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi discuss beauty therapists reviewing their patients, and ask if a group of elderly nuns who encounter a naturist on a ramble are entitled to be alarmed...
They're joined by Paul Feig - the Hollywood director of Bridesmaids, The Heat and Ghostbusters about turning his attention to mixology with his new book 'Cocktail Time!'
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Not everyone is a card carrying naturist | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320225/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 18:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320225/</guid><description>Podcast Description To be, or not to be...in the buff?
Jane and Fi ask why almost 7 million Brits have claimed to be throwing out their wardrobe in favour of their birthday suit, if it's appropriate to microwave a jacket potato and reveal a top tip to dealing with a diary clash.
They're also joined by the writer and campaigner Rachel Kelly to talk about her new book "You'll Never Walk Alone"</description></item><item><title>Fantastically successful Pink Ladies - with Grace Dent | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320226/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 17:48:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320226/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi discuss loos at motorway service stations, removing the glue from HRT patches, and how to deal with awkward supermarket encounters...
They're joined by award winning food critic, columnist and broadcaster Grace Dent, to talk more about the fourth season of her podcast Comfort Eating.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Ding dongs and dong dings | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320227/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 18:30:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320227/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nice bums, strong thighs, and easy on the eyes...but should we be objectifying the likes of Jack Grealish and the rest of the England football team?
Also, with the Spanish team being refused their favourite chorizo in Qatar they ask what the British equivalent would be.
They're also joined by the author and journalist Sali Hughes to talk about her new book Everything is Washable.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Amiable tosh indeed - with Emma Donoghue | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320228/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 18:03:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320228/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi discuss royal hands, the renaming of stopcocks, and deliciously voluble Spanish...
And, they're joined by novelist and screenwriter Emma Donoghue on the new adaptation of her book The Wonder.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Assistant Producer: Kate Lee
Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler
Podcast Executive Producer: Ben Mitchell</description></item><item><title>Hummus abominations - with Yotam Ottolenghi | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320229/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 18:15:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320229/</guid><description>Podcast Description Beetroot or chocolate infused hummus anyone? Well not in an Ottolenghi restaurant.
The legendary chef Yotam Ottolenghi joins Jane and Fi to talk about his new cookbook "Extra Good Things" and reveals which cultural recipes he has "bastardised" and which he would never dream of touching.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio</description></item><item><title>The perils of balancing baked potatoes - with Professor Green | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320230/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 17:56:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320230/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi talk eating lunch at your desk, extravagant gifts from love interests, and putting your golf balls in the dishwasher...
And they're joined by rapper Professor Green to hear more about his work with the Post Office and British Gas to give advice on how to get through the cost-of-living crisis.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>It's (probably not) coming home...is it? | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320231/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320231/</guid><description>Podcast Description With the World Cup in Qatar now just days away and off the back of Gareth Southgate's squad announcement, Jane and Fi look ahead to the competition with The Times chief football writer Henry Winter.
They also question the longstanding criticism surrounding the tournament with the sports broadcaster Kate Mason - whose new podcast documentary Inside Qatar, with Football Ramble, charts her first hand experience of the human stories behind the controversial competition.</description></item><item><title>Quality time with my orb goblet | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320232/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 18:15:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320232/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is kindness getting rehabilitated?
The award-winning science journalist and broadcaster Claudia Hammond joins Jane and Fi in the studio to talk about her latest book The Keys to Kindness and asks which politicians will pass her kindest test.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler
Podcast Executive Producer: Ben Mitchell</description></item><item><title>The voice of Gen Z? | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320233/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 18:00:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320233/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi talk to author, artist, feminist and influencer, Florence Given about what it's like to be labelled the 'voice of Gen Z', her feminist journey, and social media which she explores in 'Girlcrush'.
Her new book, and debut novel, 'Girlcrush' is available now.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Assistant Producer: Emma Sherry</description></item><item><title>1000-mile journey - with Michael Palin | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320234/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 18:02:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320234/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi talk to comedian, writer, actor, presenter, and seasoned traveller Sir Michael Palin about his 1000 mile journey down the River Tigris. His journey took him from Turkey and through Iraq, and has been documented in his new book.&amp;nbsp;
'Into Iraq' is available now.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio</description></item><item><title>Horribly exposed to Ned's bits - with Monty Don | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320235/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 18:15:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320235/</guid><description>Podcast Description We waited...and waited..and waited for Rishi Sunk to make an appearance at Cop27 - and whilst he pondered his speech Jane and Fi discussed the power of medical maggots. Honestly.
Also, they were spoke to the Don of gardening, lovely Monty, who was joined by his puppy Ned, to talk about his new book Venetian Gardens.
They also discussed the power of allotments for community spirit, the changing influence of gardening on climate change, and how to combat the effects of Seasonal Affective Disorder.</description></item><item><title>If I blink twice come and get me | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320236/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 18:30:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320236/</guid><description>Podcast Description Only one month into the new show and already one listener is beginning to worry about Jane and Fi's professional and personal relationship?
As the cost of living crisis continues to worsen the Managing Director of Iceland, Richard Barker, discusses what the supermarket chain is doing to help their customers.
And as we continue to reflect on the removal of troops from Afghanistan, documentary maker Matt Heineman talks about his new work, Retrograde, filmed from a unique perspective on the front lines.</description></item><item><title>A bit of gentle encouragement helps - with Ian Hislop | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320237/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 18:12:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320237/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi are joined by lifestyle journalist and Wellness Wednesday regular, Rosamund Dean, to find out how to cope when everything feels a bit bleak.
And, Ian Hislop talks about his new play "Spike" and the continued influence of Private Eye on the news and laws in the UK.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Where the magic happens - with Bryony Gordon | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320238/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 18:16:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320238/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi talk to journalist, columnist and author, Bryony Gordon, about social media, Prince Harry, being a parent, and her experiences with alcoholism.
Her latest book, a young adult novel, 'Let Your&amp;nbsp;Hair Down', is out now.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Assistant Producer: Emma Sherry
Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler</description></item><item><title>Yogababble - with Prof Scott Galloway | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320239/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 18:27:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320239/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi discuss economics, prison, immigration and how to help the younger generation with Scott Galloway, New York Times best-selling author and Professor of Marketing at NYU Stern School of Business.
His new book, Adrift: America in 100 Charts is out now.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Assistant Producer: Emma Sherry</description></item><item><title>Been too free with Sir Richard - with Susie Dent | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320240/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 11:30:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320240/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi talk words with lexicographer, etymologist and the woman in Dictionary Corner, Susie Dent.
Susie Dent's new book, 'An Emotional Dictionary: Real Words for How You Feel, from Angst to Zwodder' is out now.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Assistant Producer: Emma Sherry
Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler
Podcast Executive Producer: Ben Mitchell</description></item><item><title>I am my cat's Queen - with Dawn O'Porter | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320241/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 17:21:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320241/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi discuss pet&amp;nbsp;grief,&amp;nbsp;intimacy with pets and writing sex scenes with writer and former TV host, Dawn O'Porter. Her latest novel, 'Cat Lady', is out now
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Assistant Producer: Emma Sherry
Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler
Podcast Executive Producer: Ben Mitchell
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Beware the Breton jumper - With Nick Grimshaw | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320242/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 17:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320242/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi discuss the risks of horizontal stripes, and Nick Grimshaw talks about his new memoir, 'Soft Lad'.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.radio
Assistant Producer: Kate Lee
Times Radio Producer: Rosie Cutler
Podcast Executive Producer: Ben Mitchell
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cabinet musical chairs - Rishi's first day as PM | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320243/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 17:04:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320243/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rishi Sunak has started appointing his cabinet after being officially asked by King Charles to form a new government.
Jane and Fi chat about that and the other big stories of the day including a shortage of cat skin in Japanese banjo making...
And, they're joined by Britain's first black female professor of history, Dr Olivette Otele.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>First job as PM? Panic! | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320244/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 17:18:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320244/</guid><description>Podcast Description Penny Mordaunt pulls out of the Conservative leadership race - meaning Rishi Sunak will be our next Prime Minister.
Jane Garvey and Fi Glover discuss the significance of the UK's first British-Asian PM with Sunder Katwala and Ayesha Hazarika.
And, Sir Anthony Seldon explains what's first on the to do list for Sunak now that he's in charge. If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>Not another one - Liz Truss resigns | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320245/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 17:18:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320245/</guid><description>Podcast Description Another resignation and another Prime Minister leaves office this year - with Liz Truss becoming the shortest reigning PM in British history.
They're joined by a series of journalists, commentators and politicians including Labour's Shadow Foreign Secretary David Lammy and the leader of the Liberal Democrats Sir Ed Davey.
And Jane and Fi reflect on a fortnight of big events in Westminster - and ask is it a coincidence, or are they cursed?</description></item><item><title>Clean my gong | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320246/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320246/</guid><description>Podcast Description Moments after Suella Braverman departs as Home Secretary, Jane and Fi chat about the jeopardy of live radio.
They're joined by human rights barrister Adam Wagner to talk about his new book Emergency State: How We Lost Our Freedoms In the Pandemic and Why It Matters.
And Skip Innes tells Jane and Fi about the benefits of cold water swimming for this week's instalment of Wellness Wednesday.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>A saccharine note of journo pap - with Elizabeth Day | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320247/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 17:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320247/</guid><description>Podcast Description One day on from having to tear up the script and start yesterday's show again, Jane and Fi return to discuss Hugh Edwards 10 second warning about The Queen's death and when else they've had to be quick on their feet in the studio.
They are joined by the author and How to Fail podcast host Elizabeth Day; to talk about friendship, writing for different audiences, and what happened when she interviewed Liz Truss.</description></item><item><title>"The lady's not for turning...UP!" | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320248/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 17:00:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320248/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi review the day's big political news which forced them to throw out their entire show and start again.
They are joined by Times Radio chief political commentator, Lucy Fisher, and Red Box podcast host Matt Chorley live from the press gallery in Westminster to discuss the infamous governmental U-turn.
Also, were Jane's daughter's student digs as horrific as she feared and will Fi become the recipient of the key to the town of Slough?</description></item><item><title>From politics to podcast - with Jess Phillips | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320249/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320249/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's the end of the first week of the podcast and already Jane and Fi have a bonus edition with Labour politician Jess Phillips; Shadow Minster for Domestic Violence and Safeguarding.
They spoke together at Podcast Day 24 for a panel discussion about how she manages to juggle being a working politician with hosting her hugely successful podcast Yours Sincerely - where she gives her guests a chance to celebrate three people that mean the world to them.</description></item><item><title>Ground Control to Major Tim - with Tim Peake | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320250/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320250/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi have reached the end of their first week in the new job and are very much looking forward to the weekend. But before they can recharge the batteries ready for more they sit down for another edition of the podcast.
Joining them today is the astronaut Major Tim Peake, who is embarking on a new adventure...writing a children's book. 'The Cosmic Diary of our Incredible Universe is out today.</description></item><item><title>Welcome to the club | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320251/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 17:30:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320251/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi question whether it's a good idea for "Royal adjacent" former rugby star Mike Tindall to enter the I'm a Celebrity Jungle.
Joining them today is the campaigner and Times Radio's own Mariella Frostrup to discuss the findings of the Menopause All-Party Parliamentary Group.
Also, Rosamund Dean kicks off "Wellness Wendesday's" a new feature to help Jane and Fi take better care of themselves.
If you want to contact the show to ask a question and get involved in the conversation then please email us: janeandfi@times.</description></item><item><title>New Royals and a brave bride | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320252/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320252/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane and Fi discuss the fallout from footballer Iker Casillas's alleged joke about being gay in a sport where coming out for men seems almost impossible.
Joining them today is the Royal broadcaster Katie Nicholl to talk about her new book "New Royals" and answer why it's so hard being a female member of the Royal family.
Also, Kayley Stead, the brave bride who continued with her wedding after her husband-to-be decided not to attend.</description></item><item><title>Chat and Chop - with Jamie Oliver | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320253/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320253/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fresh from their Times Radio debut Jane and Fi welcome you to their new podcast series, Fi debates the best way to approach starting a new job and the truth is revealed about Jane's "favourite" tomato curry recipe.
Joining them today is the chef and campaigner Jamie Oliver to talk about his new book, One Pot, how families can continue to cook good food during the current cost of living crisis, stopping the government U-turn on health eating for children, and of course…whether or not he is a member of the anti-growth coalition.</description></item><item><title>Off air...with Jane and Fi - COMING SOON | Off Air... with Jane and Fi</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2189320254/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 10:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2189320254/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fresh from their all new Times Radio show Jane Garvey and Fi Glover keep the mics on, grab a cuppa and say what they really think - unencumbered and off air.
Off air...with Jane and Fi, Monday to Thursday, on Apple Podcasts, Spotify, the Times Radio app or wherever you get your podcasts.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>