<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Casefile True Crime on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/casefile-true-crime/</link><description>Recent content in Casefile True Crime on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 17:23:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/casefile-true-crime/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>See You Soon! | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650001/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 17:23:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650001/</guid><description>Podcast Description To our loyal Casefile listeners, that time of year is upon us again. This is just a heads-up to let you know that the show will be taking a short break, with our final episode of 2023 dropping on the main feed on Saturday December 2nd. But don't worry, we're not going anywhere - the Casefile team will be busy working behind the scenes in the meantime, with brand new episodes out in early February 2024.</description></item><item><title>Case 269: Caroline Crouch | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650002/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 11:11:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650002/</guid><description>Podcast Description *** Content warning: Animal cruelty ***
In May 2021, residents of the affluent Athens suburb of Glyka Nera were left shaken by news of a violent home invasion. Three masked intruders had killed 19-year-old Caroline Crouch as she slept beside her 11-month-old daughter before ransacking the house. Caroline’s husband, Babis Anagnostopoulos, was the only witness, but he’d been bound and blindfolded during the attack. The desperate search for those responsible led investigators down a path no one saw coming.</description></item><item><title>Case 268: Colleen Stan (Part 2) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650003/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 08:01:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650003/</guid><description>Podcast Description *** Content warning: Extreme sexual violence, captivity ***
[Part 2 of 2]
As the years of abuse, torture and confinement to the bed box continued for Colleen Stan, she remained paralysed by her fear of The Company. But one thing changed. Her captors Cameron and Janice Hooker slowly started granting Colleen small privileges, including time outside of their Red Bluff trailer. Did this mean they were finally going to set their slave free?</description></item><item><title>Case 268: Colleen Stan (Part 1) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650004/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 10:03:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650004/</guid><description>Podcast Description *** Content warning: Extreme sexual violence, captivity ***
[Part 1 of 2]
When Colleen Stan’s family received an unexpected phone call from Colleen in June 1980, they were stunned. No one had seen or spoken to Colleen since she hitched a ride to California from her home in Oregon three years earlier. Colleen assured her family that all was well, but they could tell something wasn’t right. What exactly was Colleen Stan trying to hide?</description></item><item><title>Case 267: Brian Barrett | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650005/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 10:03:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650005/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the spring of 2005, two 18-year-olds met in an online chat room and immediately hit it off. Jessi went by the username TalHotBlond, while her new friend Tommy called himself MarineSniper. It wasn’t long before the two had fallen in love and gotten engaged… But less than a year into their relationship, the romance would be destroyed by a shocking revelation that ultimately led to devastating consequences…</description></item><item><title>Casefile Presents: The Bakersfield Three | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650006/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 17:32:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650006/</guid><description>Podcast Description When three friends disappeared or were murdered within a 30-day period in a California town, an investigation began that would ultimately unearth dark secrets and revelations no one was prepared for.
Written and reported by award-winning investigative crime reporter Olivia LaVoice. All 15 episodes of The Bakersfield Three are available to stream right now, wherever you get your podcasts.
Listen here: Website - https://casefilepresents.com/the-bakersfield-three
Apple Podcasts - https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-bakersfield-three/id1713527997</description></item><item><title>Case 266: Circleville Letter Writer | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650007/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650007/</guid><description>Podcast Description In March 1977, school bus driver Mary Gillespie started receiving threatening letters delivered to her home in Circleville, Ohio. It wasn’t long before her husband, Ron Gillespie, also received the letters which accused Mary of having an affair with the local school superintendent, Gordon Massie.
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Jessica Forsayeth
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.</description></item><item><title>Case 265: Marea Yann | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650008/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 07:12:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650008/</guid><description>Podcast Description For Marea Yann, two things mattered most in life - family and community. When the 69-year-old was found violently bludgeoned to death in her Healesville home, the small Victorian town was left shaken. It seemed impossible that anyone would want to hurt this doting grandmother and dedicated volunteer worker. But as investigators learned more about Marea’s life, it quickly became clear that Marea had been living in fear of one person in particular.</description></item><item><title>Case 264: Andrew Gosden | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650009/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 08:42:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650009/</guid><description>Podcast Description *** Content warning: Child victim, child abuse, suicide, grooming ***
When 14-year-old Andrew Gosden mysteriously disappeared from his home in the UK suburb of Doncaster, evidence emerged to indicate that he’d left of his own free will. But Andrew was a gifted, intellectual teenager who came from a loving and supportive family – not your typical teenage runaway.
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Elsha McGill</description></item><item><title>Case 263: Kim Barry | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650010/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 07:30:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650010/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Brian and Beverly Barry returned from a weekend away to discover their 19-year-old daughter Kim was gone, they initially assumed she was out with friends. Then news broke that a body had been found in some bushland south of their home in Wollongong, New South Wales, and it wasn’t long before the truth came out...
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Erin Munro
Creative direction – Milly Raso</description></item><item><title>Case 262: Samia Shahid | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650011/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 08:10:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650011/</guid><description>Podcast Description *** Content warning: Domestic violence, sexual assault ***
In Pakistani culture, arranged marriages are common. So when the parents of Samia Shahid chose a husband for her, Samia agreed to the marriage. Despite being raised in England, Samia took her Pakistani heritage very seriously and would do anything to make her family proud. But Samia’s arranged marriage to her first cousin, Choudhry Shakeel, was far from what she expected.</description></item><item><title>Case 261: Shari Smith &amp; Debra May Helmick (Part 2) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650012/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 08:16:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650012/</guid><description>Podcast Description *** Content warning: Sexual assault ***
[Part 2 of 2]
When nine-year-old Debra May Helmick was abducted from the front of her family’s trailer in Richland County, South Carolina, there were immediate concerns that her kidnapping could be linked to the recent murder of Lexington teenager, Shari Smith. Those fears were confirmed when Shari’s sister Dawn received a chilling phone call directing authorities to Debra May’s body. The news that a serial killer was on the loose had South Carolina residents gripped by fear.</description></item><item><title>Case 261: Shari Smith &amp; Debra May Helmick (Part 1) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650013/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 20:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650013/</guid><description>Podcast Description *** Content warning: Sexual assault ***
[Part 1 of 2]
When 17-year-old Shari Smith disappeared from the end of her family's driveway in Lexington, South Carolina, there were immediate concerns for her wellbeing. Shari had a rare medical condition that could turn fatal without her medication. But any concerns that Shari’s illness could have caused her disappearance were quickly quashed after the Smith family received an odd phone call, prompting the largest manhunt in South Carolina’s history.</description></item><item><title>Case 260: The Alpine Manor Murders | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650014/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 08:06:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650014/</guid><description>Podcast Description *** Content warning: Elder abuse ***
The Director of Nursing at the Alpine Manor Nursing Home in Grand Rapids, Michigan, was thrilled when Catherine Wood and Gwen Graham joined their team of nursing aides in the mid-1980s. They were hard-working, enthusiastic and well-liked. But soon after they started, some residents of Alpine Manor began telling the staff that their lives were in peril. When those same residents began to pass away, their deaths were put down to natural causes.</description></item><item><title>Case 259: Jamie Lavis | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650015/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 07:56:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650015/</guid><description>Podcast Description *** Content warning: Child victim, child sexual abuse ***
When eight-year-old Jamie Lavis failed to return home on Monday, May 5 1997, his family quickly raised the alarm. Soon, it seemed as though all of Greater Manchester was searching for the missing boy – including a bus driver named Darren Vickers...
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Erin Munro
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas</description></item><item><title>Case 258: Kay Mortensen | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650016/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 08:16:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650016/</guid><description>Podcast Description On November 16 2009, a 911 call was placed to the Utah County Sheriff’s Department by 34-year-old Pamela Mortensen. According to Pamela, her father-in-law Kay Mortensen was brutally murdered in his own home...
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Erin Munro
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.B. Joslyn
Sign up for Casefile Premium:
Apple Premium
Spotify Premium
Patreon
For all credits and sources, please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Anonymous Host first interview (Unfiltered podcast) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 22:11:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Follow and subscribe to Unfiltered on Apple Podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you listen to podcasts. In 2021, I sat down and had a series of hour-long phone calls with the anonymous host of Casefile, or “Casey,” as he’s been dubbed by fans of the show. At the time, Casey was recovering from an unexplained medical issue. Our chats reminded me of the power of real and raw conversations, and it paved the way for ‘Unfiltered,’ the new Casefile Presents podcast where guests from all walks of life join me for a conversation about justice and transformation.</description></item><item><title>Case 257: Joe Gliniewicz | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650018/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 08:14:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650018/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a routine check on suspicious activity turns to tragedy for Illinois Police Lieutenant Joe Gliniewicz, Fox Lake locals struggle to come to grips with the loss of their hero cop. A statewide manhunt ensues, but when the perpetrators aren’t immediately apprehended, the question is raised - could this have been a targeted attack?
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Elsha McGill Creative direction – Milly Raso</description></item><item><title>Case 256: Jill Rosenthal | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650019/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 07:52:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650019/</guid><description>Podcast Description *** Content warning: Crimes against children, child abuse, domestic abuse, alcoholism ***
On April 27 1964, young mother Dora Fronczak was in her hospital bed feeding her one-day-old son, Paul, when a nurse entered the room and said she had to take Paul back to the nursery. Dora handed her baby over, and the nurse hurried out of the room. Still carrying baby Paul, the nurse fled the hospital through a rear entrance and disappeared into Chicago’s city streets.</description></item><item><title>Case 255: Rudolf Rupp | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650020/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 07:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650020/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 52-year-old German farmer Rudolf Rupp failed to return home from a night out drinking in the town of Neuburg an der Donau, several questions were raised. Had Rudolf accidentally driven into the nearby Donau River? Had he taken his own life? Or was he the victim of something more sinister? ---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Elsha McGill
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas</description></item><item><title>Case 254: Winsie Hau | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650021/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 06:33:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650021/</guid><description>Podcast Description *** Content warning: child victim ***
On the afternoon of January 14, 2012, 15-year-old Winsie Hau was attacked with a knife by a 14-year-old boy. Winsie's father was also attacked, and while he survived his injuries, Winsie did not. ---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Holly Hoyd
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.B. Joslyn
Sign up for Casefile Premium:
Apple Premium
Spotify Premium
Patreon
For all credits and sources, please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 253: Aarushi Talwar &amp; Hemraj Banjade | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650022/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 09:22:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650022/</guid><description>Podcast Description *** Content warning: child victim, sexual assault ***
When Rajesh and Nupur Talwar went to wake their 13-year-old daughter Aarushi on the morning of Friday, May 16 2008, the couple were shocked to find her brutally murdered in her bed.
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Erin Munro
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.B. Joslyn
Sign up for Casefile Premium:
Apple Premium
Spotify Premium
Patreon
For all credits and sources, please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 252: Margaret Maher, Mersina Halvagis &amp; Nicole Patterson | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650023/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 09:14:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650023/</guid><description>Podcast Description *** Content warning: serial rapist and killer, sexual assault, stalking ***
When Melbourne women Margaret Maher, Mersina Halvagis and Nicole Patterson were found brutally murdered in the late 1990s, police didn’t immediately link the crimes. The killer left behind no incriminating evidence, indicating he was an experienced offender who knew how to beat the system. Little did investigators know, the story began almost 30 years earlier, when a 15-year-old boy knocked on his neighbour’s door and asked to borrow a knife.</description></item><item><title>Case 251: The Caldwell Farmhouse Murders | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650024/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 10:06:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650024/</guid><description>Podcast Description *** Content warning: Child victim, animal cruelty ***
When single mother Nadja Medley met an older man named Mike Bullinger, she finally found happiness after a difficult few years. As well as being a fun, kind-hearted partner, Mike was a wonderful father figure to Nadja’s 14-year-old daughter Payton. In May 2017, the three of them moved from Ogden, Utah, to a farmhouse Mike had just bought in Caldwell, Idaho.</description></item><item><title>Case 250: Amy Boyer | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650025/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650025/</guid><description>Podcast Description *** Content warning: Mental illness, stalking, gun violence ***
Amy Boyer was a popular teen in her hometown of Nashua, New Hampshire. Her life was busy between school, work and social commitments. Full of joy and love, Amy naturally drew in those around her – including a troubled young man named Liam Youens.
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Milly Raso
Creative direction – Milly Raso</description></item><item><title>Case 249: Lorraine Wilson &amp; Wendy Evans | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650026/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 09:43:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650026/</guid><description>Podcast Description *** Content warning: Sexual assault ***
When trainee nurses Lorraine Wilson and Wendy Evans failed to return to work in Sydney after a holiday around Australia in 1974, fears arose that they could have fallen victim to the so-called Gold Coast Hitchhiker Murderer. But when a discovery is made in the rural town of Murphy’s Creek years later, an even more disturbing possibility emerges...
---
Narration – Anonymous Host</description></item><item><title>Case 248: Abraham Shakespeare | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650027/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650027/</guid><description>Podcast Description *** Content warning: Gun violence ***
When 41-year-old Abraham Shakespeare won the 30 million dollar Florida Lottery prize, his underprivileged life changed overnight. Yet, he quickly realised his newfound wealth was a curse. Despite showing limitless charity, he became demoralised by the pressure and expectations thrust upon him by those seeking his money...
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Milly Raso
Creative direction – Milly Raso</description></item><item><title>Case 247: Nina Puganova, Irina Trasyn &amp; Anastasia Mikhailova | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650028/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 08:01:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650028/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the summer of 1980, Theodosius Glukharev received a series of harrowing deliveries to his home in Kishinev, Soviet Moldova. The contents ultimately unravelled the murders of three women – Nina Puganova, Irina Trasyn &amp;amp; Anastasia Mikhailova...
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Holly Boyd
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.B. Joslyn
Sign up for Casefile Premium:
Apple Premium
Spotify Premium
Patreon
This episode's sponsors:</description></item><item><title>Case 246: Grégory Villemin (Part 2) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650029/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 09:04:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650029/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 2 of 2]
*** Content Warning: child victim ***
After grieving father Jean-Marie Villemin takes revenge for his son’s death into his own hands, the investigation into Grégory Villemin’s death takes a series of unexpected turns. ---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Elsha McGill
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas and Andrew Joslyn
Subscribe for ad-free episodes and bonus content:
Join Apple Premium
Join Spotify Premium
Join Patreon
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 246: Grégory Villemin (Part 1) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650030/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 08:05:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650030/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 1 of 2]
*** Content Warning: child victim ***
The extended Villemin family lived in the Vosges region of north-eastern France. From 1981, several members of the family started to receive anonymous, threatening phone calls from a mysterious caller they eventually labelled The Crow. ---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Elsha McGill
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas and Andrew Joslyn</description></item><item><title>Case 245: Sherri Papini | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650031/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2023 07:57:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650031/</guid><description>Podcast Description When married mother of two, Sherri Papini, goes missing near her home in Redding, California, the community is gripped by fear. Suspicion immediately falls on Sherri’s husband, Keith Papini, but an even darker theory emerges – what if Sherri was the victim of a human trafficking ring?
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Elsha McGill
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas</description></item><item><title>Case 244: Engla Höglund &amp; Pernilla Hellgren | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650032/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 06:40:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650032/</guid><description>Podcast Description *** Warning: This case involves a child victim ***
On April 5 2008, 10-year-old Engla Höglund went missing while cycling home from soccer practice near the small Swedish town of Stjärnsund. As news spread, a witness came forward who had captured Engla in a photograph just moments before she disappeared.
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Holly Boyd Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas</description></item><item><title>Case 243: Deidre Kennedy | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650033/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 08:11:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650033/</guid><description>Podcast Description *** Warning: This case involves a child victim ***
On April 14 1973, the Kennedy family awoke in their Ipswich, Queensland unit to discover the unthinkable. 16-month-old Deidre Kennedy was missing from her cot, having been abducted by an intruder overnight.
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Elsha McGill Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.B. Joslyn</description></item><item><title>Case 242: The Investor Murders | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650034/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650034/</guid><description>Podcast Description *** Warning: This case involves a child victim ***
On the afternoon of Tuesday, September 7 1982, residents of the tiny Alaskan fishing village of Craig noticed smoke across the harbour. A fishing vessel was on fire. It belonged to successful Washington fisherman Mark Coulthurst, who was travelling with his wife Irene, their two children, Kimberley and John, and four teenage deckhands: Dean Moon, Michael Stewart, Jerome Keown and Chris Heyman.</description></item><item><title>Case 241: Harry &amp; Nicola Fuller | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650035/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650035/</guid><description>Podcast Description On February 10 1993, East Sussex police were summoned to conduct a welfare check at the Wadhurst cottage of newlyweds, Harry and Nicola Fuller. What they found inside left the tight-knit community in shock. ---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Elsha McGill
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.B. Joslyn
Sign up for Casefile Premium:
Apple Premium
Spotify Premium
Patreon
This episode's sponsors:</description></item><item><title>Case 240: JasonInHell | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650036/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 08:41:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650036/</guid><description>Podcast Description *** Warning: This case involves a child victim ***
By late 2016, Jason and Brandi Worley’s marriage was crumbling. Regardless of what happened between them, they promised to always put their two children, Tyler and Charlee, first. Meanwhile, a user going by the name of JasonInHell logged onto Reddit and clicked on a forum titled: relationship_advice.
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Milly Raso
Creative direction – Milly Raso</description></item><item><title>Case 239: Peggy Carr | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650037/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 10:05:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650037/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 41-year-old waitress Peggy Carr succumbed to a mysterious illness in October 1988, doctors in Alturas, Florida struggled to figure out what was wrong with her. As other members of Peggy’s family became sick too, one neurologist came to suspect they were dealing with a case of poisoning. Tests soon confirmed the family had been deliberately poisoned with the rare heavy metal thallium, but no one could understand why.</description></item><item><title>Case 238: Renae Marsden | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650038/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 15:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650038/</guid><description>Podcast Description 20-year-old Renae Marsden was a bright and bubbly young woman who valued her family above all else. Her mother Teresa Marsden was therefore shocked when she received a message from Renae’s boyfriend, Brayden Spiteri, on August 5 2013 warning: “Sort your daughter out. Threatening to kill herself.”
Criminalising Catfishing Petition
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Elsha McGill
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas</description></item><item><title>Case 237: Rena &amp; Danny Paquette | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650039/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650039/</guid><description>Podcast Description In February 1960, the city of Manchester, New Hampshire, was rocked by the violent murder of teenager Sandra Valade. Three years later, another teenager, Pamela Mason, was killed in the same manner. A quiet housewife named Rena Paquette confided to police that she knew who murdered the two teens. Just days after coming forward, she was found dead under mysterious circumstances by her son, Danny Paquette. ---
Narration – Anonymous Host</description></item><item><title>Case 236: Sophie Lionnet | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650040/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 08:55:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650040/</guid><description>Podcast Description When residents of the affluent Southfields area of south-west London notice foul smelling smoke coming from a home on Wimbledon Park Drive in September 2017, firefighters arrive to make sure the house isn’t in danger. Nothing could prepare them for what they find instead – the burning human remains of French au pair, 21-year-old Sophie Lionnet. ---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Elsha McGill
Creative direction – Milly Raso</description></item><item><title>Case 235: House of Horrors (Part 3) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650041/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 08:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650041/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 3 of 3]
More disturbing secrets are unearthed at 25 Cromwell Street as the investigation into Fred West leads detectives into the remote English countryside. Fred steadfastly asserts that his wife knew nothing of his crimes, and tight-lipped Rose maintains her innocence...
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Milly Raso
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas and Andrew Joslyn</description></item><item><title>Case 235: House of Horrors (Part 2) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650042/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 10:04:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650042/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 2 of 3]
By 1992, Fred and Rose West were raising their children at their Cromwell Street home. At first glance, the Wests appeared to be a model family. Neighbours viewed Fred as a modest, kind and soft-spoken man. Rose was a dedicated mother and housewife... ---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Milly Raso
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas and Andrew Joslyn</description></item><item><title>Case 235: House of Horrors (Part 1) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650043/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 10:10:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650043/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 1 of 3]
In early 1969, 15-year-old Rose Letts was waiting alone at a bus stop in the English town of Cheltenham when she was approached by a much older man. 27-year-old Fred West was poorly dressed, dirty, and had a mouthful of green, chipped teeth from years of neglect. While Rose found Fred repulsive, something about him excited her. From this chance encounter, the pair initiated an intense relationship that culminated in their marriage three years later.</description></item><item><title>Case 234: Franca Viola | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650044/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 09:37:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650044/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1963, on the Italian island of Sicily, a wealthy young bachelor named Filippo Melodia began a courtship with a teenager named Franca Viola, much to the displeasure of Franca's father... ---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Holly Boyd
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.B. Joslyn
Sign up for Casefile Premium:
Apple Premium
Spotify Premium
Patreon
This episode's sponsors:</description></item><item><title>Case 233: Denise Amber Lee | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650045/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 09:50:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650045/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Nathan Lee arrived at his home in North Port, Florida, on January 17 2008, he immediately knew something was wrong. His two young sons were home alone, and his wife, 21-year-old Denise Amber Lee, was missing.
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Erin Munro
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.B. Joslyn
Sign up for Casefile Premium:
Apple Premium
Spotify Premium
Patreon
This episode's sponsors:</description></item><item><title>Case 232: Jo, Michelle &amp; Christe Rogers | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650046/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 09:14:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650046/</guid><description>Podcast Description For Jo Rogers and her two teenage daughters, Michelle and Christe, a trip to Florida seemed like a dream come true. In May 1989, the trio left their dairy farm in Willshire, Ohio and set out on their first ever interstate holiday. ---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Jessica Forsayeth
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.B. Joslyn</description></item><item><title>Case 231: Anna-Jane Cheney | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650047/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 09:42:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650047/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1994, 29-year-old Adelaide lawyer Anna-Jane Cheney was looking forward to her dream wedding. But just six weeks before she was due to walk down the aisle, her fiancè Henry Keogh called paramedics to report that he’d found Anna-Jane lying unconscious in the bath of their Magill home. ---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Elsha McGill Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas</description></item><item><title>Case 230: Rubí Frayre &amp; Marisela Escobedo | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650048/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 09:56:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650048/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 16-year-old Rubí Frayre went missing from the Mexican city of Juarez, police showed little interest. Exasperated, Rubí's mother, Marisela Escobedo, took it upon herself to uncover the truth about her daughter’s fate. ---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Holly Boyd
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.B. Joslyn
Sign up for Casefile Premium:
Apple Premium
Spotify Premium
Patreon
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 229: The Killer Realtor | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650049/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 08:30:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650049/</guid><description>Podcast Description On November 6 2003, a customer entered the Superbike Motorsports dealership in Chesnee, South Carolina. Nothing could prepare them for the grisly scene inside. Four employees had been gunned down in cold blood - Scott Ponder, Beverly Guy, Brian Lucas, and Chris Sherbert. ---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Erin Munro
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.</description></item><item><title>Case 228: The Harrison Family | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650050/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 08:10:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650050/</guid><description>Podcast Description In April 2009, 64-year-old Bill Harrison, a much-loved member of the community of Mississauga, Canada, was found dead in his home. An autopsy revealed that he died of natural causes. Just over one year later, Bill’s wife, Bridget Harrison was also found deceased in the family home.
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Jessica Forsayeth
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas</description></item><item><title>Case 227: Mike Williams | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650051/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 08:00:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650051/</guid><description>Podcast Description The weekend of December 16 2000 was shaping up to be a good one for Tallahassee man Mike Williams. With a romantic getaway planned to celebrate his sixth wedding anniversary to his wife Denise, Mike got up early to sneak in a couple hours of duck hunting on Lake Seminole. When he failed to return home, Denise quickly raised the alarm. ---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Elsha McGill</description></item><item><title>Case 226: El Mataviejitas | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650052/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 08:21:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650052/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2003, 12 elderly women were killed in their homes in Mexico City. Most were strangled and robbed. Fears arose that a serial killer was on the loose, with the media dubbing the perpetrator ‘El Mataviejitas’ - The Little Old Lady Killer. Police initially dismissed the serial killer notion, until the victim count continued to rise and the evidence became too strong to ignore. ---
Narration – Anonymous Host</description></item><item><title>Case 225: Raheel Siddiqui | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650053/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 08:55:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650053/</guid><description>Podcast Description The United States Marine Corps is known for its tight-knit culture, as solidified in their motto, ‘Semper Fidelis,' which means ‘Always Faithful.’ 20-year-old Raheel Siddiqui was looking for his next move in life. A brilliant student, he determined that joining the Marine Corps would be a great way to pursue his dreams while also serving his country. ---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Erin Munro</description></item><item><title>Case 224: Evelyn Hartley | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650054/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 07:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650054/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 15-year-old Evelyn Hartley agreed to babysit for the Rasmussen family on the evening of October 24 1953, it sounded like a relatively easy job...
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Erin Munro
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.B. Joslyn
Sign up for Casefile Premium:
Apple Premium
Spotify Premium
Patreon
This episode's sponsors:
ShipStation – Try ShipStation FREE for 60 days with promo code ‘CASEFILE’</description></item><item><title>Case 223: The Kuřim Case | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650055/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 07:53:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650055/</guid><description>Podcast Description *** Warning: This case involves a child victim ***
When Czech Republic man Eduard Trdý inadvertently intercepted the video feed of his neighbour’s security camera in May 2007, he was so alarmed by the footage that he contacted the police...
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Holly Boyd
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.B. Joslyn
Sign up for Casefile Premium:
Apple Premium
Spotify Premium
Patreon
This episode's sponsors:</description></item><item><title>Case 222: Karina Holmer | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650056/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 08:39:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650056/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1996, Karina Holmer left her small Swedish village of Skillingaryd to travel to Boston, Massachusetts. The 19-year-old had plans to work as an au pair with an American family who lived in an affluent neighbourhood called Dover. Karina settled in well with her host family: married couple Frank Rapp and Susan Nichter and their two young children. But just three months after arriving in Dover, Karina suddenly disappeared after a night out with friends.</description></item><item><title>Case 221: Frank &amp; Carol Hilley | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650057/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 07:53:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650057/</guid><description>Podcast Description In May 1975, 45-year-old Frank Hilley began experiencing severe nausea, vomiting and stomach cramps in his home in Anniston, Alabama. He died just over a week later. Soon after, his wife Marie Hilley began to receive threatening phone calls, messages and damage to her property. When her teenage Carol Hilley began to show the same symptoms as her late father, Marie flew into a panic trying to get to the bottom of what was happening.</description></item><item><title>Case 220: Hannah Witheridge &amp; David Miller | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650058/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 08:40:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650058/</guid><description>Podcast Description When the bodies of British tourists 23-year-old Hannah Witheridge and 24-year-old David Miller were found brutally murdered on the remote Thai island of Koh Tao, the police immediately concluded that the killer had to be a foreigner, as a Thai person couldn’t be capable of such brutality. ---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Elsha McGill
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas</description></item><item><title>Case 219: Doctor John | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650059/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 07:50:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr John Schneeberger’s charming and gentle manner made him a popular and trusted figure in the tiny Canadian town of Kipling. So when a young woman named Candice accused him of raping her in 1992, most townsfolk were left shocked and found the allegation impossible to believe. ---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Erin Munro
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas</description></item><item><title>Case 218: The Blackout Killers (Part 2) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650060/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 07:38:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650060/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 2 of 2]
In Berlin, Germany at the height of World War Two, a man took advantage of the Blackout orders at night to frighten and assault women in an isolated garden colony. Soon, he progressed to attacking and killing women on the S-Bahn train by throwing them from the carriage door while the train was in motion.
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Jess Forsayeth
Creative direction – Milly Raso</description></item><item><title>Case 218: The Blackout Killers (Part 1) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650061/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 08:39:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650061/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 1 of 2]
At the height of World War Two in London, a serial killer roamed the streets. In just one week in February 1942, he killed four women and attempted to kill others, taking them by surprise at night during the enforced blackout periods.
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Jess Forsayeth
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
This episode's sponsors:</description></item><item><title>Case 217: Kathleen Marshall | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650062/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 09:28:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650062/</guid><description>Podcast Description In March 1998, members of the Cat Protection Society in Brisbane, Australia were shocked at the murder of one of their own, a 52-year-old Veterinarian named Dr Kathleen Marshall. An outspoken crusader for animal rights, Kathleen seemed an unlikely target for such a brutal assault...
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Jessica Forsayeth
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.</description></item><item><title>Case 216: The Itzkovitz Family | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650063/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 07:55:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eliahu Itzkovitz spent much of his childhood confined behind the walls of Romania’s Chișinău Ghetto – a place where he and other Romanian Jews were held prisoner by their government...
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Holly Boyd
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.B. Joslyn
This episode's sponsors:
Patreon – Support Casefile and get early access to ad-free episodes and additional content
Calm – Get 40% off Calm Premium subscription The Jordan Harbinger Show – Learn the stories, secrets, and skills of the world’s most brilliant and interesting people
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 215: The One-Man Crime Wave | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650064/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 08:34:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650064/</guid><description>Podcast Description *** Warning: This case involves a child victim ***
On May 26 1978, four-year-old Eric Christgen suddenly disappeared while playing in a park in St Joseph, Missouri. The next day, his body was discovered near the Missouri River, sparking a manhunt like the small town had never seen before.
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Jessica Forsayeth
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas</description></item><item><title>Case 214: Kevin Hjalmarsson | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650065/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 09:01:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650065/</guid><description>Podcast Description *** Warning: This case involves a child victim ***
When the body of four-year-old Kevin Hjalmarsson was found floating on a wooden pallet in Sweden’s Kyrkviken bay, police determined that it wasn’t a tragic drowning, but a cold-blooded murder.
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Elsha McGill
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.B. Joslyn
This episode's sponsors:
Peloton – Learn more about Peloton
Calm – Get 40% off Calm Premium subscription
Best Fiends – Download Best Fiends for free
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 213: The Noordhoek 'Ripper Rapists' | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650066/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 06:52:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650066/</guid><description>Podcast Description It was around 2:30 am on Sunday, December 18 1994, when a group of friends stumbled across the bloody and brutalised body of a young woman, lying in the middle of a road in Gqeberha, South Africa. She was the latest victim of Frans Du Toit and Theuns Kruger; two men who the press would come to dub The Noordhoek ‘Ripper Rapists’. ---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Erin Munro
Creative direction – Milly Raso</description></item><item><title>Case 212: The Forgotten Cannibal | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650067/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 06:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650067/</guid><description>Podcast Description On December 21 1924, itinerant beggar, Vincenz Olivier, knocked on the door of an apartment building on the outskirts of Münsterberg in Weimar, Germany. Father Denke, the elderly man who answered the door, gladly offered Vincenz 20 pfennigs to help him write a letter to his brother. Vincenz accepted and was welcomed into Father Denke’s home...
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Holly Boyd
Creative direction – Milly Raso</description></item><item><title>Case 211: Cari Farver | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650068/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650068/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Omaha mechanic Dave Kroupa met Cari Farver in late 2012, he thought he’d found the perfect woman. Unfortunately, their relationship soon turned sour and when Dave ended things, Cari began to obsessively stalk him, turning his life into a living nightmare...
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Erin Munro
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.B. Joslyn
This episode's sponsors:
Peloton – Learn more about Peloton
Article – Get $50 off your first order of $100 or more
SimpliSafe – Get 40% off the entire security system The Jordan Harbinger Show – Learn the stories, secrets, and skills of the world’s most brilliant and interesting people
Calm – Get 40% off the Calm Premium subscription
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 210: Jayna Murray | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650069/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650069/</guid><description>Podcast Description On March 11, 2011, two employees of the Lululemon Athletica yoga store in Bethesda, Maryland fell victim to a brutal attack carried out by two masked men. 30-year-old Jayna Murray was murdered, while 28-year-old Brittany Norwood survived the ordeal which included sexual assault, torture, repeated stabbings and burglary.
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Jessica Forsayeth
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas</description></item><item><title>Case 209: Urban Höglin &amp; Heidi Paakkonen | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650070/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650070/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Swedish backpackers Urban Höglin and Heidi Paakkonen go missing during a camping trip around New Zealand’s Coromandel Peninsula, concerns are quickly raised that the newly engaged couple could have fallen victim to foul play. Worries increase once it’s discovered that convicted killer, David Tamihere, was on the loose in the area at the time, having jumped bail on a rape charge. ---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Elsha McGill
Creative direction – Milly Raso</description></item><item><title>Case 208: John Chau | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650071/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 07:58:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650071/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2018, American missionary John Chau sailed out to North Sentinel, a forested island off the coast of India. He intended to spread the word of God to the Sentinelese, a small population of indigenous people considered the most remote tribe in the world. Yet, the Sentinelese have made it very clear to outsiders that they desire isolation above all else.
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Erin Munro
Creative direction – Milly Raso</description></item><item><title>Case 207: Suzanne Armstrong &amp; Susan Bartlett | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650072/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 08:47:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650072/</guid><description>Podcast Description In early January 1977, residents of Easey Street in Melbourne’s inner-city suburb of Collingwood noticed they hadn’t seen the tenants at number 147 for several days...
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Elsha McGill
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.B. Joslyn
This episode's sponsors:
Peloton – Learn more about Peloton
The Detective’s Dilemma – New podcast from Casefile Presents
Truebill – Take control of your finances and save money
The Jordan Harbinger Show – Learn the stories, secrets, and skills of the world’s most brilliant and interesting people
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 206: Julio &amp; Candra Torres | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650073/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 08:15:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650073/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Tuesday, July 27 1976, 16-year-old Candra Torres and a man named Tom Brown showed up in an Oregon sheriff’s department to report a terrible incident. Candra’s husband, 21-year-old Julio Torres, had been accidentally shot and killed while the three were on a camping trip deep in Mount Hood National Forest...
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Erin Munro
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas</description></item><item><title>Case 205: Bernd Brandes | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650074/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 08:40:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650074/</guid><description>Podcast Description On March 9 2001, 43-year-old computer engineer Bernd Brandes disappeared from his home in Berlin, Germany. Although his absence was extremely out of character, investigations into his whereabouts proved unsuccessful... ---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Jessica Forsayeth
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.B. Joslyn
This episode's sponsors:
The Detective’s Dilemma – New podcast from Casefile Presents
Babbel – Get 6 months free with a 6-month subscription.</description></item><item><title>Case 204: The Glendale Train Crash | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650075/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 08:49:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650075/</guid><description>Podcast Description On January 26 2005, 25-year-old Juan Alvarez parked his car on a railway line in Glendale, Los Angeles, causing an explosive train crash that killed and injured dozens of commuters. Alvarez, plagued by family troubles and a difficult past, claimed it was an accident but those who witnessed the crash said otherwise. Was Alvarez an innocent victim or a calculating killer?
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research – Holly Boyd
Writing – Jessica Forsayeth
Creative direction – Milly Raso</description></item><item><title>Case 203: Bob Chappell | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650076/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 09:47:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650076/</guid><description>Podcast Description On January 26 2009, defacto couple Bob Chappell and Sue Neill-Fraser spent the public holiday working on their yacht, The Four Winds, in Tasmania’s Sandy Bay. ---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research – Jessica Forsayeth
Writing – Elsha McGill
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.B. Joslyn
This episode's sponsors:
Allbirds – Discover your perfect pair of sneakers
Peloton – Learn more about Peloton</description></item><item><title>Case 202: Moira Anderson | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650077/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 09:20:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650077/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Saturday, February 23 1957, 11-year-old Moira Anderson set out in a blizzard to run a quick errand. When she failed to return home, locals in her hometown of Coatbridge, Scotland began searching the area for any sign of her... ---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Erin Munro
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.B. Joslyn
This episode's sponsors:</description></item><item><title>Case 201: Janet Chandler | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650078/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 07:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650078/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 22-year-old Janet Chandler was abducted while working the night shift at the Blue Mill Inn on January 31 1979, her disappearance appeared to be part of a robbery... ---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Elsha McGill
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.B. Joslyn
This episode's sponsors:
Searching for Sarah MacDiarmid – New podcast from Casefile Presents
Crime Weekly – Listen to new episodes released every Friday
ShipStation – Try ShipStation FREE for 60 days with promo code ‘CASEFILE’
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 200: The Zodiac (Part 4) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650079/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2022 08:52:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650079/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 4 of 4]
On March 22 1970, 22-year-old Kathleen Johns suffered a terrifying encounter when her car broke down on a California highway. Was it possible she’d encountered the Zodiac Killer? ---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research – Jess Forsayeth and Milly Raso
Writing – Elsha McGill, Erin Munro, Milly Raso and Jess Forsayeth
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.</description></item><item><title>Case 200: The Zodiac (Part 3) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650080/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 09:56:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650080/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 3 of 4]
On September 27 1969, friends Cecelia Shepard and Bryan Hartnell were relaxing at Lake Berryessa, California, when their afternoon was suddenly interrupted by the arrival of a menacing figure. His face was concealed by a black hood, painted with a crosshair symbol. The man unleashed a brutal attack on the pair before fleeing the scene.
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research – Jess Forsayeth and Milly Raso
Writing – Elsha McGill, Erin Munro, Milly Raso and Jess Forsayeth
Creative direction – Milly Raso</description></item><item><title>Case 200: The Zodiac (Part 2) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650081/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 08:31:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650081/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 2 of 4]
On December 20 1968, teenagers David Faraday and Betty Lou Jensen were gunned down in the middle of the night on a deserted road in Benicia, California. Six months later, another young couple, Darlene Ferrin and Michael Mageau, were shot in a parking lot in nearby Vallejo. When an anonymous caller informed the police that he’d committed both attacks, the hunt was on. ---</description></item><item><title>Case 200: The Zodiac (Part 1) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650082/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 09:46:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650082/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 1 of 4]
During the 1960s, California saw a wave of senseless, unsolved slayings. Cab driver Ray Davis was murdered in cold blood after an anonymous killer warned of his intentions. Two young couples – Robert Domingos and Linda Edwards, and Johnny and Joyce Swindle – were gunned down in separate yet similar attacks.
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research – Jess Forsayeth and Milly Raso
Writing – Elsha McGill, Erin Munro, Milly Raso and Jess Forsayeth
Creative direction – Milly Raso</description></item><item><title>Case 199: Truro | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650083/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 09:13:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650083/</guid><description>Podcast Description During the summer of 1976 and 1977, seven young women mysteriously disappeared from the streets of Adelaide. Veronica Knight, Sylvia Pittman, Julie Mykyta, Connie Iordanides, Vicki Howell, Tania Kenny, and Deborah Lamb were all last seen near main roads or waiting at bus stops.
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Elsha McGill
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.</description></item><item><title>Case 198: Tami Reay | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650084/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 08:29:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650084/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Kmart employee Tami Reay failed to show up at work in Pierre, South Dakota on the morning of Wednesday, February 8 2006, her co-worker Brian Clark called the police to report her missing. Brian had reason to suspect that Tami might have fallen victim of foul play. He and Tami had been having an affair, and her husband had just found out.
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Elsha McGill
Creative direction – Milly Raso</description></item><item><title>Case 197: The Austrian Ripper | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650085/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 10:18:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650085/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1974, a young woman named Margaret Schafer was strangled to death in her hometown of Ewersbach, Germany...
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Jessica Forsayeth
Editing – Erin Munro
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.B. Joslyn
This episode's sponsors:
Searching for Sarah MacDiarmid – New podcast from Casefile Presents
Best Fiends – Download Best Fiends for free
Scribd – Get a free 60 days trial to Scribd’s unlimited number of full-length books, audiobooks, and other content
SimpliSafe – Get 50% off the entire security system
Truebill – Take control of your finances and save money
ShipStation – Try ShipStation FREE for 60 days with promo code ‘CASEFILE’
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 196: Boy A | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650086/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 10:38:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650086/</guid><description>Podcast Description *** Warning: This case involves a child victim ***
In March 1997, residents of Kobe, Japan were horrified when dead and mutilated cats began appearing at random along the city's sidewalks... ---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Jessica Forsayeth
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.B. Joslyn
This episode's sponsors:
Searching for Sarah MacDiarmid – New podcast from Casefile Presents
Wine52 – Get 3 bottles of wine for free – just pay the £5.</description></item><item><title>Case 195: The Costa Mesa Murders | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650087/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 11:15:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650087/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the evening of May 22 2010, Steve Herr drove over to his son Sam’s apartment in Costa Mesa, California. The 26-year-old college student was supposed to be spending the weekend with his parents but when he never showed up, Steve decided to check on him...
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Erin Munro
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas</description></item><item><title>Case 194: Lake Bodom | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650088/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 09:17:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Saturday, June 4 1960 seemed like the beginning of an idyllic summer break for Finnish teenagers, Nils Gustafsson, Seppo Boisman, Maila Irmeli Björklund and Anja Tuulikki Mäki. The four friends had decided to go camping at Lake Bodom, a picturesque region not far from their homes in Helsinki...
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Holly Boyd
Editing – Erin Munro
Creative direction – Milly Raso</description></item><item><title>Case 193: Suesan Knorr &amp; Sheila Sanders | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650089/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 07:23:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650089/</guid><description>Podcast Description On July 17, 1984, a deceased female was located in a deserted area near Lake Tahoe, California. Investigators were stumped as to her identity or her killer, who had horrifically murdered her by setting her alight... ---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Jessica Forsayeth
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.B. Joslyn
This episode's sponsors:
Daily Harvest – Get up to $40 off your first box with promo code ‘CASEFILE’
BetterHelp – Get 10% off your first month of professional counselling with a licensed therapist
Shudder – Try Shudder FREE for 30 days with promo code ‘CASEFILE’
Truebill – Take control of your finances and save money
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 192: The Sodder Children | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650090/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 08:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650090/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Christmas Eve 1945, while most citizens of the town of Fayetteville, West Virginia celebrated the end of World War Two, Italian immigrants - George and Jennie Sodder watched their house go up in flames... ---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Jessica Forsayeth
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.B. Joslyn
This episode's sponsors:
ShipStation – Try ShipStation FREE for 60 days with promo code ‘CASEFILE’</description></item><item><title>Case 191: Sheree Beasley | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650091/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 11:17:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Melbourne psychotherapist Margaret Hobbs was used to dealing with sex offenders. Many of her clients were men who had been referred to her through the court system after committing terrible crimes...
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Erin Munro
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.B. Joslyn
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-191-sheree-beasley
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 190: The Butcher Baker (Part 2) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650092/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 09:56:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650092/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 2 of 2]
In June 1983, Cindy Paulson ran out onto a highway in Anchorage, barefoot and handcuffed. She was the prized prey of a prolific serial killer who was plaguing the region and had escaped his plans to hunt her down in the Alaskan wilderness – something he had done with many other women...
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Erin Munro and Milly Raso
Creative direction – Milly Raso</description></item><item><title>Case 190: The Butcher Baker (Part 1) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650093/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 08:03:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650093/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 1 of 2]
During the 1970s and ’80s, a predator was stalking the streets of Anchorage, Alaska. By day, he was a respectable family man who ran his own business. But at night, he would prowl Anchorage’s infamous Tenderloin District, looking for vulnerable or destitute women...
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Erin Munro and Milly Raso
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production &amp;amp; music – Mike Migas</description></item><item><title>Case 189: JoAnne Chambers | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650094/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 08:11:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650094/</guid><description>Podcast Description When JoAnne Chambers was hired to teach at Coolbaugh Learning Centre in Pennsylvania she arrived with glowing reviews from her former school. So when an anonymous harasser began targeting the popular school teacher, she was left stunned...
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Jessica Forsayeth
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-189-joanne-chambers
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 188: Robert Wone | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650095/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 13:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650095/</guid><description>Podcast Description On August 2 2006, 32-year-old lawyer Robert Wone knocked off after a long day at his office in Washington DC. To save making the journey home so late at night, he arranged to stay at a friend’s house... ---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Jessica Forsayeth
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.B. Joslyn
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 187: Peter &amp; Joan Porco | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650096/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 08:21:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650096/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the early hours of Monday, November 15 2004, husband and wife Peter and Joan Porco were savagely attacked with an axe while they slept...
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Jessica Forsayeth
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.B. Joslyn
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-187-peter-joan-porco
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 186: The Bowraville Murders | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650097/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 08:07:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650097/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 16-year-old Colleen Walker suddenly vanished from the New South Wales town of Bowraville in September 1990, her family and friends knew something was terribly wrong. But local police dismissed their concerns, suggesting that the Indigenous teenager had simply “gone walkabout”... ---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Erin Munro
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.B. Joslyn
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 185: Kim Chol | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650098/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2021 09:30:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650098/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Siti Aisyah and Doan Thi Huong were offered the chance to star on a prank show that aired on YouTube, the young women thought it was the opportunity of a lifetime. All they had to do was approach strangers on the street and rub oil on their faces...
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Erin Munro
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas</description></item><item><title>Case 184: Gay Gibson | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650099/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2021 08:01:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Early on the morning of October 18 1947, a stewardess working on the ocean liner Durban Castle discovered something strange. The cabin belonging to an actress named Gay Gibson was empty...
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Erin Munro
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.B. Joslyn
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-184-gay-gibson
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 183: The MacKenzie Family | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650100/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Aug 2021 09:35:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Karen MacKenzie resided in Greenough with her three children - Daniel, Amara, and Katrina. The 31-year-old single mother had recently gotten together enough money to rent a small house on the rural outskirts of town...
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Elsha McGill
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.B. Joslyn
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 182: Freda Burnell &amp; Florence Little | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650101/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 08:11:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650101/</guid><description>Podcast Description On February 5 1921, eight-year-old Freda Burnell went missing in the small coal-mining town of Abertillery, Wales. The unusual disappearance reached a tragic conclusion when her bound and beaten body was found dumped inside a sack in an alleyway...
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Jessica Forsayeth
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.B. Joslyn
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 181: The Vampire of Nuremberg | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650102/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 08:04:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650102/</guid><description>Podcast Description During the early ’70s, cemeteries and mortuaries throughout Germany were targeted by a particularly disturbing grave robber. Not only did he steal the personal belongings of the dead, but he also exhumed, mutilated, molested, and gnawed upon the bodies...
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Milly Raso
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 180: Bill Payne &amp; Billie-Jean Hayworth | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650103/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 11:08:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650103/</guid><description>Podcast Description “This is going to be the stupidest thing you’ve ever heard. This is going to be the craziest thing you’ve ever heard. There is nothing in your lives or background that has prepared you to understand the Potter family. You have never seen anybody like them.”
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Eileen Ormsby
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.</description></item><item><title>Case 179: Christie Marceau | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650104/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 07:32:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650104/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the morning of September 6 2011, Auckland teenager Christie Marceau was woken by a troubling phone call from an acquaintance named Akshay Chand. The two 18-year-olds had previously worked together at a supermarket, and Chand was now threatening to take his own life. ---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Erin Munro
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.</description></item><item><title>Case 178: The Woman Without a Face | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650105/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 06:51:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Between 1993 and 2009, DNA discovered at 40 crime scenes across Germany, Austria, and France were linked to an unknown woman of eastern European descent. Dubbed ‘The Woman Without a Face’, her crimes ranged from petty theft to murder. After her DNA was linked to the murder of Heilbronn police officer, Michele Kiesewetter, the suspect was renamed ‘The Phantom of Heilbronn’.
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research – Holly Boyd
Writing – Jessica Forsayeth
Creative direction – Milly Raso</description></item><item><title>Case 177: 657 Boulevard | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650106/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 08:18:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Married couple Derek and Maria Broaddus were house hunting when a property in the affluent neighbourhood of Westfield, New Jersey immediately caught their attention. 657 Boulevard was a striking six bedroom, four bathroom Dutch Colonial style home that was the perfect place to raise their family – or so they thought. ---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Jessica Forsayeth
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 176: Yingying Zhang | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650107/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2021 09:42:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650107/</guid><description>Podcast Description On June 9 2017, Yingying Zhang vanished on her way to an appointment in Urbana, Illinois. The Chinese visiting scholar missed her bus and after she failed to return to work that day, her colleagues quickly raised the alarm... ---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Erin Munro
Creative direction – Milly Raso
Production and music – Mike Migas
Music – Andrew D.B. Joslyn
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 175: Gail &amp; Rick Brink | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650108/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 09:00:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650108/</guid><description>Podcast Description When newlyweds Gail and Rick Brink failed to show up to their respective jobs on the morning of November 23 1987, the alarm was immediately raised. The couple’s bodies were discovered at the ranch house they had only just purchased. Both had been shot multiple times in the head, execution-style. The slayings shocked the quiet community of Holland, Michigan, and everyone had a theory as to what might have happened.</description></item><item><title>Case 174: Vicki Arnold &amp; Julie-Anne Leahy | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650109/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2021 08:15:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650109/</guid><description>Podcast Description One cold winter night in 1991, best friends Vicki Arnold and Julie-Anne Leahy vanished from their town of Atherton, Queensland. The two women had left for a late-night fishing trip but never came home. Two weeks later, their bodies were found in Julie-Anne’s car on a remote bushland track, in the opposite direction from where they’d been headed. ---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Erin Munro
Creative direction – Milly Raso</description></item><item><title>Case 173: Rocio Wanninkhof &amp; Sonia Carabantes | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650110/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 08:37:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650110/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 19-year-old Rocio Wanninkhof failed to return home after a night out with friends, her mother Alicia was immediately worried. The family lived in the small town of La Cala de Mijas, Spain – where teenagers felt safe going out alone. Alicia’s concern quickly turned to distress when she discovered Rocio’s shoes lying abandoned in a clearing near their home, alongside a pool of blood.
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Victoria Dieffenbacher
Editing – Erin Munro
Additional writing &amp;amp; editing – Milly Raso
Creative direction – Milly Raso</description></item><item><title>Case 172: Michael Gregsten &amp; Valerie Storie | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650111/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 08:35:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650111/</guid><description>Podcast Description In August 1961, Michael Gregsten and Valerie Storie were sitting in their car in Dorney Reach, UK when an intruder forced his way into the backseat brandishing a gun. After driving them around the English countryside for hours, the intruder shot both Michael and Valerie, leaving them on the side of the road at a location known as Deadman’s Hill.
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research &amp;amp; writing – Jessica Forsayeth
Creative direction – Milly Raso</description></item><item><title>Case 171: The Gladbeck Hostage Crisis | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650112/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 10:16:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650112/</guid><description>Podcast Description On August 19 1988, two armed offenders entered a branch of the Deutsche Bank in Gladbeck, West Germany with the intention of holding it up. Hans-Jürgen Rösner and Dieter Degowski planned to steal a large sum of money, then make a quick getaway.
---
Special thanks to Stef for her assistance in the creation of this episode
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research – Milly Raso and Erin Munro
Writing – Erin Munro
Creative direction – Milly Raso</description></item><item><title>Case 170: The Caffey Family | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650113/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 10:03:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650113/</guid><description>Podcast Description On February 29 2008, members of the Caffey Family were sleeping soundly in their Texas home when intruders suddenly stormed in and launched a brutal attack. After setting the house on fire, the intruders fled, unaware that one family member was still alive. Patriarch Terry Caffey emerged from the burning building barely clinging to life, his body riddled with bullet wounds.
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research and writing – Jessica Forsayeth
Creative direction – Milly Raso</description></item><item><title>Case 169: Corinna Mullen | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650114/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Mar 2021 09:35:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650114/</guid><description>Podcast Description On October 2 1987, a council employee in Central City, Kentucky called police after finding an abandoned, blood-smeared Pontiac outside his workplace. When Lieutenant Billy Fields arrived at the scene, he found the savagely assaulted body of 20-year-old Corinna Mullen in the boot. Corinna hadn’t been seen since the previous night when she’d gone out drinking with her roommate Angela Smith.
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research – Holly Boyd
Writing – Erin Munro
Creative direction – Milly Raso</description></item><item><title>Case 168: Guðmundur &amp; Geirfinnur Einarsson | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650115/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 08:27:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650115/</guid><description>Podcast Description In January 1974, 18-year-old Guðmundur Einarsson enjoyed a night out with friends in the town of Hafnarfjordur, Iceland. At the end of the evening, he walked into a wild snowstorm and was never seen again. Ten months later, in November 1974, 32-year-old Geirfinnur Einarsson (no relation) also disappeared from the Icelandic fishing town of Keflavik. In a country with next to no homicide, foul play was considered immediately. ---</description></item><item><title>Case 167: Jai, Tyler &amp; Bailey Farquharson | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650116/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 11:46:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650116/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Australia, Father’s Day falls on the first Sunday of September and is typically a time for families to gather together and celebrate. But on Father’s Day in 2005, the small Victorian town of Winchelsea was rocked by news that a local man named Robert Farquharson had driven his three young sons – Jai, Tyler and Bailey – into a dam. Robert survived, but all three boys drowned. ---</description></item><item><title>Case 166: The Family | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650117/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 09:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650117/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1979, residents of Adelaide were gripped by fear when several young men began to go missing under mysterious circumstances. 17-year-old Alan Barnes, 25-year-old Neil Muir, 14-year-old Peter Stogneff, 18-year-old Mark Langley and 15-year-old Richard Kelvin were later found dumped in the Adelaide Hills and surrounds. They had been drugged and subject to horrific sexual abuse and torture.
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research and writing – Jessica Forsayeth
Creative direction – Milly Raso</description></item><item><title>Case 165: Nicholas Barclay | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650118/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2021 08:16:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650118/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1994, 13-year-old Nicholas Barclay disappeared after playing basketball with his friends in his home town of San Antonio, Texas. Years went by with no sign of him. Just when his family thought all hope was lost, in October 1997 they received a call from a police officer in the Spanish city of Linares. Nicholas had been found wandering the local streets, alive and well.
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research and writing – Jessica Forsayeth
Creative direction – Milly Raso</description></item><item><title>Case 164: Cindy James | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650119/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 09:43:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650119/</guid><description>Podcast Description During the 1980s, Canadian nurse Cindy James was tormented by an unknown assailant at her home in Vancouver, British Columbia. She was subject to threatening phone calls, break-ins, arson attacks and even physical assaults. Cindy tried everything to protect herself, from installing an alarm system to moving house, but nothing – not even her policeman roommate – could deter the assailant.
---
Narration – Anonymous Host
Research and writing – Jessica Forsayeth
Creative direction – Milly Raso</description></item><item><title>Case 53: The Golden State Killer (Part 6) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650120/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 08:44:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650120/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 6]
This is the final instalment in a Casefile series that was first released in 2017.
It covers recent developments in the case and mentions incidents detailed in previous episodes. If you haven’t already, we recommend you go back and listen to the first five parts of Case 53: The East Area Rapist before proceeding with Part Six.
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched and written by Elsha McGill, Erin Munro and Milly Raso
Creative Director: Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 163: Joanne Ratcliffe &amp; Kirste Gordon | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650121/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 21:15:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650121/</guid><description>Podcast Description On August 25 1973, 12,000 South Australian National Football League spectators packed into Adelaide Oval to watch the North Adelaide Roosters take on the Norwood Redlegs. During the game’s third and penultimate quarter, 11-year-old Joanne Ratcliffe was given permission by her parents to escort 4-year-old Kirste Gordon to the toilet. But the girls never returned.
---
Casefile would like to give a special thanks to Suzie Ratcliffe for her assistance with this episode</description></item><item><title>Case 162: Lawrence Haggart | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650122/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Nov 2020 10:18:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650122/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1995, 15-year-old Scottish schoolboy Lawrence Haggart’s dreams came true when he was signed to join Celtic, an elite Scottish football club. The future looked bright for young Lawrence, until one night in March 1996 when his brother John Haggart awoke to the smell of something burning. He discovered Lawrence downstairs, beaten and set on fire. --- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched by Milly Raso, Elsha McGill &amp;amp; Erin Munro
Written by Erin Munro
Creative Director: Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 161: The Yosemite Sightseer Murders (Part 2) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650123/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2020 10:34:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650123/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 2 of 2]
After the decapitated body of 26-year-old naturalist Joie Armstrong is found in Yosemite’s Foresta region, investigators are quick to deny that her murder is linked to that of Carole and Juli Sund and Silvina Pelosso. But when suspicions are cast on a local maintenance worker, the investigation takes a shocking turn.
---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched by Jessica Forsayeth
Written by Elsha McGill Creative Director: Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 161: The Yosemite Sightseer Murders (Part 1) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650124/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2020 10:21:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650124/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 1 of 2]
Carole Sund and her teenage daughter Juli were excited to take their family friend and Argentinian exchange student, Silvina Pelosso, on a trip to see the natural wonders of Yosemite National Park. But when they fail to arrive at the San Francisco Airport for their scheduled flight home, investigators suspect that the trio might have met with foul play. ---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched by Jessica Forsayeth</description></item><item><title>Case 160: Beverly McGowan | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650125/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 09:57:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650125/</guid><description>Podcast Description In late July 1990, siblings Steve and Jane McGowan both received a letter in the mail from their sister, 34-year-old Beverly McGowan, advising that she had quit her job and was selling her condo in order to go travelling. This made no sense to Steve and Jane.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched and written by Erin Munro
Creative Director: Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 159: James Craig Anderson | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650126/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 07:52:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650126/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 47-year-old Mississippi resident James Craig Anderson realised he’d locked his keys in his car in the early morning hours of Sunday, June 26 2011, he was thankful when a vehicle pulled up offering to help. But it soon became clear that the occupants were anything but good samaritans. ---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched by Holly Boyd
Written by Elsha McGill
Creative Director: Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 158: Russell Martin | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650127/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2020 09:49:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650127/</guid><description>Podcast Description 31-year-old Russell ‘Stabba’ Martin was well known around the small town of Stawell in Victoria’s west. A staple of the local pubs and footy club, it wasn’t unusual for Russell to leave town for days at a time. No matter where he went or why Russell’s journey always led him back home to his wife Helen and their four children. ---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched and written by Eileen Ormsby
Creative Director: Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 157: The Strip Search Scam | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650128/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 10:21:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650128/</guid><description>Podcast Description ** Warning: This episode contains descriptions of sexual violence ***
The evening of April 9, 2004, started as a regular, uneventful shift for employees at a McDonald’s restaurant in Mount Washington, Kentucky. Until 4:56 PM, when the phone rang and the man on the other line introduced himself as Officer Scott. ---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched and written by Erin Munro
Creative Director: Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 156: Shergar | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650129/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 07:33:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650129/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Ireland in 1968, a period known as The Troubles began. Years of extreme protesting and violence culminated in low morale and widespread despair throughout the country, and the economy struggled, resulting in high unemployment rates and mass emigration.
---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched by Jessica Forsayeth
Written by Elsha McGill
Creative Director: Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-156-shergar
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 155: Danniella Vian | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650130/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2020 09:25:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650130/</guid><description>Podcast Description It wasn’t unusual for 25-year-old Danniella Vian to lose her phone. So when her mother-in-law Julie received a phone call from a stranger saying he had Danniella’s mobile, this wasn’t a cause for concern. The previous day, Danniella had made a highly anticipated car purchase and spent the night out celebrating with friends.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Written by Eileen Ormsby
Creative Director: Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 154: Steven Stayner | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650131/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 09:43:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650131/</guid><description>Podcast Description When seven-year-old Steven Stayner fails to return home from school on December 4 1972, life changes irrevocably for the Stayner family. As the years pass by with no sign of their beloved son and brother, they do their best to adjust to life without him.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched by Jessica Forsayeth
Written by Elsha McGill
Creative Director: Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 153: Anni Hindocha | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650132/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 09:31:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650132/</guid><description>Podcast Description Newlyweds Anni Hindocha and Shrien Dewani were looking forward to celebrating their honeymoon in South Africa. After a traditional wedding in India, they set off for a luxury stay at Kruger National Park before making their way to Cape Town.
---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched by Holly Boyd
Written by Erin Munro
Creative Director: Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-153-anni-hindocha
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 152: Cindy &amp; Mona Lisa Smith | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650133/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 09:28:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Note: Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander peoples should be aware that this episode contains the names of people who have passed away. The families of Cindy and Mona Lisa Smith have given Casefile permission to air this content.
---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched by Jessica Forsayeth
Written by Erin Munro
Creative Director: Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-152-cindy-mona-lisa-smith
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 151: Dan O’Connell &amp; James Ellison | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650134/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 08:38:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Residents of Hudson, Wisconsin are left rattled when funeral director Dan O’Connell and his trainee James Ellison are found shot to death in The O’Connell Family Funeral Home. The two were hardworking men with no known enemies and nothing about their murders seem to add up. --- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched by Jessica Forsayeth
Written by Erin Munro
Creative Director: Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 150: The Murchison Murders | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650135/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2020 07:37:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650135/</guid><description>Podcast Description After the Western Australian gold rush of the late 1800s, there was little work available in the isolated Murchison region. Those lucky enough to find jobs were the ones willing to tough it out in the harsh conditions of the small towns and stations along the Rabbit Proof Fence. Due to the transient nature of these communities, it wasn’t unusual for people to leave without ever being heard from again.</description></item><item><title>Case 149: Anan Liu | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650136/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 09:09:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650136/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the morning of September 15 2007, an elderly couple were walking through Melbourne’s Southern Cross Station when they noticed a young Asian girl standing alone near the escalator. Assuming she was lost, police were quickly notified and attempted to identify the toddler. Unable to verify who she was, they nicknamed her “Pumpkin.”
---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched by Holly Boyd
Written by Erin Munro
Creative Director: Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 148: The Miyazawa Family | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650137/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2020 09:01:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650137/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Miyazawa’s were a seemingly normal family who lived in a semi-detached, three-storey house in Setagaya’s Kamisoshigaya district. But when their bodies are found brutally slaughtered in their own home, questions begin to emerge as to whether the family could be hiding any secrets. --- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched by Holly Boyd
Written by Elsha McGill
Creative Director: Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 147: Julie Dart &amp; Stephanie Slater | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650138/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 08:54:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650138/</guid><description>Podcast Description On July 10 1991, 18-year-old Julie Dart disappeared after a night out in Leeds. Two days later, her boyfriend Dominic Murray received a letter from Julie that read: “Help me, please. I’ve been kidnapped and I’m being held as personal security… Please go and tell my mum straight away.” The following week, a group of farmers working in a field alongside an abandoned railway line come across Julie’s decomposing body.</description></item><item><title>Case 146: Brittany Phillips | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650139/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2020 07:46:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650139/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 18-year-old Brittany Phillips enrolled to study at Tulsa Community College in Oklahoma, she was excited to move into her own apartment. With the help of her mother Maggie Zingman, she soon found the perfect place – a one-bedroom apartment in the Glen Eagles housing complex on East 65th Street.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Written by Jessica Forsayeth
Additional writing and editing by Elsha McGill
Creative Director: Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 145: Michael Dippolito | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650140/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 07:40:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650140/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the morning of August 5 2009, 26-year-old Dalia Dippolito was working out when she received a voicemail from a detective at the Boynton Beach Police Department. He instructed Dalia to return to her home immediately, saying, “It involves your husband. There’s been an incident. I’ll tell you everything you need to know when you get here.”
---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched by Holly Boyd</description></item><item><title>Case 144: The Muswell Hill Murderer (Part 3) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650141/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 May 2020 08:03:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650141/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 3 of 3]
As Dennis Nilsen prepares to face trial and the true extent of his murder spree begins to emerge, so many questions remain unanswered. What drove him to kill? Who were his victims? And how did he manage to get away with his crimes for so long?
---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched by Holly Boyd
Episode written by Elsha McGill Creative Director: Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 144: The Muswell Hill Murderer (Part 2) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650142/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 07:45:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650142/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 2 of 3]
By the time Dennis Nilsen moved out of his flat at 195 Melrose Avenue in Cricklewood, he had already taken the lives of twelve victims. Eager to start afresh, he set himself up on the top floor at 23 Cranley Gardens in Muswell Hill and focused on putting the past behind him.
---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched by Holly Boyd</description></item><item><title>Case 144: The Muswell Hill Murderer (Part 1) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650143/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 08:20:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650143/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 1 of 3]
When specialty plumbers arrived to inspect the drains at a property in the north London suburb of Muswell Hill in early February 1983, it seemed like any regular job. Upon closer inspection, they were baffled by the presence of the “porridge-like substance” that appeared to be clogging the drains underneath the house. ---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched by Holly Boyd</description></item><item><title>Case 143: Leigh Leigh | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650144/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 08:26:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650144/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teenagers in the New South Wales town of Stockton Beach were excited as they gathered at the North Stockton Surf Club to celebrate the sixteenth birthday of a schoolmate. 14-year-old Leigh Leigh promised her parents she’d be waiting at their designated meeting spot in four hours time. When she didn’t arrive, they immediately knew something was wrong.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched and written by Eileen Ormsby
Creative Director: Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 142: The Churchill Fire | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650145/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2020 08:16:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650145/</guid><description>Podcast Description Australia is no stranger to bushfires. But when Victorian Premier John Brumby warned residents that the weather conditions for February 7, 2009, could be “the worst day in the history of the state,” no one could have predicted the damage that lay ahead. ---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched and written by Milly Raso
Creative Director: Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-142-the-churchill-fire
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 141: Natalee Holloway | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650146/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 08:32:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650146/</guid><description>Podcast Description 18-year-old Natalee Holloway had been looking forward to her senior class trip to Aruba all year. The tropical vacation was a rite of passage for students at Mountain Brook High School, who celebrated their newfound freedom with five days of sightseeing, swimming and bottomless booze in the idyllic Caribbean location. ---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched and written by Elsha McGill
Creative Director: Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 140: Richmond Hill | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650147/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 10:38:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650147/</guid><description>Podcast Description Just after midnight on November 10 2012, a loud and frightening sound erupted in the Indianapolis subdivision of Richmond Hill. The force was so powerful that it registered on a regional earthquake sensor and homes were left rattling from the impact. Emergency services raced to the scene but were unable to save the lives of two residents, Dion and Jennifer Longworth. ---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host</description></item><item><title>Case 139: Beryl &amp; Geraldine Evans (Part 2) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650148/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 10:46:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650148/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 2 of 2]
On March 24 1953, a tenant at 10 Rillington Place was renovating their kitchen when they made a shocking discovery. After police arrive at the property, the true extent of the horror becomes clear. ---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched and written by Erin Munro
Creative Director: Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-139-beryl-geraldine-evans-part-2
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 139: Beryl &amp; Geraldine Evans (Part 1) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650149/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 02:11:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650149/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 1 of 2]
When newlyweds Beryl and Timothy Evans found out they were expecting their first child, they set about finding a place of their own to live. They soon found a suitable rental property in London’s Notting Hill district, located at 10 Rillington Place.
---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched and written by Erin Munro
Creative Director: Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 138: The Batavia | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650150/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 11:34:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650150/</guid><description>Podcast Description In October of 1628, the newly constructed Batavia embarked on its maiden voyage from the shores of The Netherlands, setting sail for the Dutch East Indies. The 341 individuals on board were oblivious to the fact that the journey would eventually be described as one of the worst horror stories in maritime history.
---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched and written by Erin Munro
Creative Director: Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 137: Arlis Perry | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650151/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 09:28:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650151/</guid><description>Podcast Description 19-year-old Arlis Perry took her Christian faith seriously. After fighting with her husband Bruce on the night of October 12 1974, she decided to clear her head by stopping in at the Stanford Memorial Church to pray. When she still hadn’t returned an hour later, Bruce checked the church but the doors we locked. He waited a few more hours before reporting Arlis missing. ---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host</description></item><item><title>Case 136: Azaria Chamberlain | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650152/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 09:16:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650152/</guid><description>Podcast Description On August 17 1980, the Chamberlain family were camping at Uluru when Lindy Chamberlain went to put her nine-week-old daughter Azaria to sleep in the tent. Moments later, the other campers heard Lindy cry out, “My God, my God, a dingo has got my baby!”
---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode written and by Elsha McGill and Erin Munro
Episode researched by Erin Munro
Creative Director: Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 135: The Santa Claus Bank Robbery | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650153/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2019 10:29:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650153/</guid><description>Podcast Description On December 23 1927, the streets of Cisco, Texas were full of festive cheer as residents prepared for Christmas. When a man dressed as Santa Clause entered the First National Bank of Cisco, customers chuckled that even Saint Nick had finances to attend to during the holiday season. ---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode written and researched by Eileen Ormsby
Creative Director: Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 134: Martha Puebla | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650154/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 09:12:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650154/</guid><description>Podcast Description 16-year-old Martha Puebla was no stranger to gang violence. She lived in California’s San Fernando Valley, where Latin American organisations like the 18th Street Gang and the Vineland Boyz controlled the streets. So when Martha inadvertently witnessed a gang-related murder, she knew to keep her mouth shut. --- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode written and researched by Eileen Ormsby
Creative Director: Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 133: Tom &amp; Eileen Lonergan | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650155/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 10:24:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650155/</guid><description>Podcast Description When American couple Tom and Eileen Lonergan set out to visit Australia, they were particularly looking forward to putting their diving skills to good use. On January 25 1998, they took advantage of the perfect weather conditions and boarded a charter boat at the Port Douglas Marina for a day out exploring the Great Barrier Reef.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode written by Elsha McGill and Milly Raso Episode researched by Erin Munro
Creative Director: Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 132: Rui Pedro Teixeira Mendonça | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650156/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 10:36:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650156/</guid><description>Podcast Description On March 4 1998, the parents of Rui Pedro Teixeira Mendonça grew concerned when their son failed to show up for a lesson with his tutor. The 11-year-old had last been seen riding his bike near their family home in Lousada, Portugal. P
---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched, written, and edited by Milly Raso, Erin Munro, and Elsha McGill
Creative Director: Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 131: Mr Stinky | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650157/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 09:43:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650157/</guid><description>Podcast Description During the 1970s and 80s, a series of terrifying sexual assaults occurred inside homes throughout the Victorian suburb of Donvale. The unidentified perpetrator was initially referred to as The Donvale Rapist, but after several survivors described him as having a distinctly offensive odour, he was given a new nickname – ‘Mr Stinky.’
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched and written by Milly Raso and Erin Munro
A special thank you to Louise Raso and Andrew Rule for their assistance in the creation of this episode
Creative Director: Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 130: Joe Cinque | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650158/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2019 10:11:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650158/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Sunday, October 26 1997, an emergency services dispatcher in Canberra received a hysterical call from a young woman who refused to provide clear answers to basic questions. Between sobs, she requested an ambulance to treat a suspected heroin overdose.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched by Jessica Forsayeth
Episode written by Elsha McGill
Creative Director: Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 129: The Dupont de Ligonnès Family | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650159/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2019 07:57:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650159/</guid><description>Podcast Description In early April 2011, several friends and relatives of Nante’s Dupont De Ligonnès family received an unexpected letter that read: “Hi everyone! Huge surprise: we have to leave urgently for the U.S due to a very particular set of circumstances that we will explain below. When you read this letter, we will no longer be in France and won’t be able to return for an as-yet-undetermined period of time.</description></item><item><title>Case 128: Joan Vollmer | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650160/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 19:23:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650160/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 49-year-old Joan Vollmer begins acting strangely, her husband Ralph blames spiritual problems and turns to religion for answers. Rather than seeking help for Joan’s obvious mental health issues, Ralph consults with other members of the couple’s church, who believe they know the truth – that Joan has fallen victim to demonic possession.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched and written by Erin Munro Creative Director: Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 127: Killer Petey | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650161/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2019 10:03:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650161/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brazilian born Pedro Rodrigues Filho first felt the desire to kill at the age of 13. It wasn’t long before he gave into his desires and claimed his first victim. Over the years that followed, Pedro’s thirst for violence grew. He soon became one of Brazil’s most prolific serial killers, with his crimes earning him the nickname of ‘Killer Petey.’
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched and written by Eileen Ormsby
Creative Director: Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 126: Johnny Altinger | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650162/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 09:40:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650162/</guid><description>Podcast Description After 38-year-old Johnny Altinger goes on a date with a woman he met online, his friends start receiving strange emails. Things appear to have gone so well that Johnny decided to join the woman on an impromptu trip to Costa Rica. He even sends a resignation letter to his work, indicating that he has no immediate plans to return to Canada.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host</description></item><item><title>Case 125: The Angels of Wynarka &amp; Belanglo | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650163/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 08:05:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650163/</guid><description>Podcast Description In mid-July 2015, a motorist was travelling down the Karoonda Highway in South Australia when he pulled over near the small town of Wynarka to urinate. As he made his way into the thick bushland framing the side of the road, he noticed an array of dirty, torn children’s clothing strewn under a patch of trees. In front was an abandoned suitcase. He crouched down to unzip the case and began rummaging through its contents.</description></item><item><title>Case 124: Hinterkaifeck | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650164/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 09:38:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650164/</guid><description>Podcast Description The small rural property of Hinterkaifeck lay approximately 70 kilometres north of the German city of Munich. Members of the Gruber-Gabriel family could usually be seen milling about, but in early April 1922, locals noticed that the Hinterkaifeck farmhouse was unusually void of activity.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched and written by Erin Munro Creative Director: Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 123: Mark Kilroy | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650165/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2019 09:39:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650165/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 21-year-old Mark Kilroy and a group of his friends headed to South Padre Island in Texas for Spring Break, all they had in mind was sun, sand and celebration. However, when they crossed the border into the Mexican city of Matamoros to party with their fellow college students, things soon took a dark turn.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched by Erin Munro Episode written by Elsha McGill and Milly Raso
Creative Director: Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 122: Leeann Lapham | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650166/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2019 12:15:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650166/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Australia, one woman is killed by her current or former domestic partner every week. So when 29-year-old Leeann Lapham went missing from her short term accommodation in Innisfail in 2010, suspicion was immediately cast on her boyfriend, Graeme Evans. Although the two were known to have a volatile and often violent relationship, Graeme maintained that Leeann had left on her own accord.
--- Episode researched by Anonymous Host and Elsha McGill with assistance from the Queensland Police Homicide Investigation Unit Episode written by Elsha McGill
Creative Director: Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 121: The Freeway Phantom | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650167/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2019 09:54:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650167/</guid><description>Podcast Description During the early 1970s in Washington, D.C, six black girls aged between 10 and 18 were abducted and murdered in separate brutal attacks. The bodies of Carole Spinks, Darlenia Johnson, Brenda Crockett, Nenomoshia Yates, Brenda Woodard and Diane Williams were all found alongside busy roads, with most showing evidence of strangulation and sexual assault. The unidentified perpetrator, thought to be Washington’s first serial killer, became known as The Freeway Phantom.</description></item><item><title>Case 120: Bill McGuire | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650168/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 11:01:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650168/</guid><description>Podcast Description On May 5 2004, the first of three suitcases containing dismembered human remains washed up on the shores of the Chesapeake Bay in Virginia. Detectives had two difficult tasks ahead of them. First, they needed to identify who the remains belonged to. Secondly, they had to figure out who was responsible for the murder and why. ---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched by Flossie Arend
Episode written by Flossie Arend, Elsha McGill, and Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 119: Abigail Williams &amp; Liberty German | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650169/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2019 09:42:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650169/</guid><description>Podcast Description Monday, February 13, 2017, was a bonus day off school for students in the small American town of Delphi, Indiana. Best friends Abigail Williams and Liberty German decided to spend the day hiking and taking photographs on the Monon High Bridge Trail, which forms part of Delphi’s Historic Trails. Later that evening, when they fail to meet Liberty’s father at their designated pick-up spot, it’s soon suspected that the two teenagers met with foul play.</description></item><item><title>Case 118: The Chicago Tylenol Murders | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650170/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 09:57:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650170/</guid><description>Podcast Description After seven residents of Chicago passed away suddenly and unexpectedly in 1982, authorities discovered they shared a common link. In the hours before their deaths, each of the individuals had taken Tylenol branded paracetamol. ---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched by Milly Raso and Anonymous Host
Episode written by Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-118-the-chicago-tylenol-murders
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 117: Hannah Foster | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650171/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 20:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650171/</guid><description>Podcast Description At 11:00 PM on March 14 2003, an emergency services operator in the United Kingdom answered a phone call on the nation’s 999 helpline. The person on the other line was silent. As was protocol, the operator transferred the call through to the ‘Silent Solutions’ department, where the call was ultimately disconnected.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode written by Elsha McGill
Episode researched by Erin Munro
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 116: Chloe Ayling | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650172/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 10:09:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650172/</guid><description>Podcast Description British glamour model Chloe Ayling was ecstatic to be hired for a photoshoot in Milan. But after failing to return to the United Kingdom on her scheduled flight, it appears that the golden opportunity was too good to be true.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched and written by Eileen Ormsby
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-116-chloe-ayling
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 115: Operation Cathedral | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650173/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 09:46:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650173/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the mid-1990s, police caught wind of an online paedophile ring known as The Orchid Club, in which members were using chat rooms to create and trade child exploitation material. Several American men were arrested, but detectives soon discovered The Orchid Club was just the tip of the iceberg. ---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched and written by Milly Raso
Edited by Elsha McGill
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 114: Elisa Claps &amp; Heather Barnett | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650174/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2019 09:21:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650174/</guid><description>Podcast Description When teenager Elisa Claps mysteriously disappears after going to meet a friend in the Southern Italian town of Potenza, all possibilities are explored. Initial suspicions are cast on 21-year-old Danilo Restivo, but when reported sightings of Elisa begin to come in from across Italy and as far away as Albania, the investigative waters are muddied.
---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Written by Elsha McGill
Researched by Mike Migas and Paulina Szymanska For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 113: Brendan Bernard | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650175/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 09:27:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650175/</guid><description>Podcast Description In February 2015, Victorian police were called to the eastern banks of the Maribyrnong River in Moonee Ponds after two passersby made a grim discovery. Floating downstream was a plastic grocery bag containing a human forearm.
---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched and written by Rick Best
Edited by Milly Raso and Elsha McGill
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-113-brendan-bernard
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 112: Rachel Barber | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650176/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 08:50:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650176/</guid><description>Podcast Description 15-year-old Rachel Barber was thrilled to make the move from a conventional high school to a special performing arts school in Melbourne’s inner-city suburb of Richmond. On the evening of March 1 1999, she waved goodbye to her classmates after making plans to meet them for breakfast the following morning. Little did they know, it was the last they’d ever see of her.
---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host</description></item><item><title>Case 111: Shauna Howe | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650177/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2019 09:25:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650177/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1992, the children of Oil City, Pennsylvania were excited as Halloween approached. But when 11-year-old Shauna Howe fails to return home after a church Halloween party on October 27, the typically festive atmosphere quickly turns to one of anxiety and fear.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched and written by Eileen Ormsby, author of ‘The Darkest Web – Drugs, Death and Destroyed Lives: The inside story of the internet’s evil twin.</description></item><item><title>Case 110: Muriel McKay | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650178/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 08:11:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650178/</guid><description>Podcast Description On December 29 1969, News of the World deputy chairman Alick McKay returned to his manor in London’s upscale Wimbledon district to find the place ransacked. His wife, Muriel McKay, was nowhere to be seen.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched and written by Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-110-muriel-mckay
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 109: Belanglo (Part 5) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650179/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2019 09:50:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650179/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 5 of 5]
Accused serial killer, 51-year-old Ivan Milat sat motionless before the court dressed in a navy suit, white shirt and grey checkered tie...
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched by the Anonymous Host
Episode written by Elsha McGill
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-109-belanglo-part-5
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 109: Belanglo (Part 4) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650180/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 08:01:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650180/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 4 of 5]
At 6:36 am on May 22 1994, a team of heavily armed police surrounded the Cinnabar Street home of Ivan Milat and instructed him to exit the house with his arms raised. Dumbfounded, Ivan responded: “Okie dokie. Just let me put me pants on…”
---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched by the Anonymous Host
Episode written by Elsha McGill
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 109: Belanglo (Part 3) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650181/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2019 10:07:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650181/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 3 of 5]
After a witness comes forward to report a suspicious incident that occurred near Belanglo years earlier, the investigation quickly gains momentum. The spotlight is placed on a local family when one name keeps coming up repeatedly – Milat.
---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched by the Anonymous Host
Episode written by Elsha McGill
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-109-belanglo-part-3</description></item><item><title>Case 109: Belanglo (Part 2) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650182/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2019 11:35:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650182/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 2 of 5]
After the remains of two bodies are found in Belanglo State Forest, New South Wales police establish a task force to oversee the investigation into the double homicide. Fearing that more remains will be discovered, a wide-scale search of Belanglo is conducted but the murder is ultimately considered to be an isolated incident.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched by the Anonymous Host</description></item><item><title>Case 109: Belanglo (Part 1) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650183/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 11:18:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650183/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 1 of 5]
In the late 1980s and early 1990s, backpackers from across the globe flocked to Australia in search of sun, surf and adventure. Although hitchhiking was frowned upon, it remained a popular option for those seeking a cheap, convenient method of transit.
---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched by the Anonymous Host
Episode written by Elsha McGill
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 108: The Kicevo Monster | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650184/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2019 13:04:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650184/</guid><description>Podcast Description When three women – Mitra Simjanoska, Ljubica Licoska and Zivana Temelkoska – are murdered in the Macedonian city of Kicevo, local journalist Vlado Taneski takes it upon himself to cover the stories in detail. Unbeknownst to him, police set their eyes on an unlikely suspect and start closing in to make an arrest.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched by Mike Migas and Paulina Szymanska</description></item><item><title>Case 107: Lucie Blackman &amp; Carita Ridgway | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650185/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 13:16:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650185/</guid><description>Podcast Description In early 2001, 21-year old Lucie Blackman left her job as a flight attendant for British Airways in search of new adventures. She embarked on a working holiday to Japan, where she secured a job as a hostess at Club Casablanca in Tokyo’s bustling Roppongi district. Lucie struggled with the transition, writing in her diary: “I’m not coping well here. I can’t pull myself out of this hole I’ve fallen into… I just want to disappear.</description></item><item><title>Case 106: Peter Nielsen (Part 2) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650186/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 13:14:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650186/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 2 of 2]
After 46-year-old Vitaly Kaloyev loses his entire family in the Überlingen mid-air collision, he becomes consumed by grief. Unable to move on, he pours his energy into finding the air traffic controller he believes is responsible for the death of his wife and children. As Kaloyev discovers whether revenge really is the best medicine, the question emerges – is he a hero or a villain?</description></item><item><title>Case 106: Peter Nielsen (Part 1) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650187/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2019 08:46:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650187/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 1 of 2]
As midnight approached on July 1 2002, the German village of Owingen was disturbed by a deep rumbling from above. Residents assumed an unforecast storm was brewing, but seconds later a thunderous explosion roared as a large ball of fire illuminated the night sky.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched and written by Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 28: Lindsay Buziak | Update | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650188/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 14:44:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650188/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is an update on the Lindsay Buziak case in Case 28.
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-28-lindsay-buziak
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 105: Louise Bell | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650189/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2019 10:32:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650189/</guid><description>Podcast Description During recess and lunchtime at Hackham West Primary School in 1982, teachers patrolled the schoolyard to oversee the young children as they ran around and played together between lessons. Yet, there was often one student separated from the others, preferring to stick by her teachers’ sides rather than go off and play with her peers – 10-year-old Louise Bell...
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched and written by Elsha McGill</description></item><item><title>Case 104: Mark &amp; John | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650190/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2018 11:09:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650190/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the early 2000s, the internet became increasingly affordable and readily available, which led to online chat rooms soaring in popularity. Logging into the local Manchester Teens chat room became a regular occurrence for 16-year-old Stockport student, “Mark”, who longed to find a girlfriend online.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched and written by Eileen Ormsby, author of ‘The Darkest Web – Drugs, Death and Destroyed Lives: The inside story of the internet’s evil twin.</description></item><item><title>Case 103: The Gonzales Family | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650191/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 15:38:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650191/</guid><description>Podcast Description On 10 July 2001, New South Wales police received a frantic phone call from 21-year-old Sef Gonzales. He’d just returned home to discover that his mother Loiva, father Teddy, and younger sister Clodine had been the victims of a brutal murder. ---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched and written by Gemma Harris
Additional writing and editing by Milly Raso and Elsha McGill For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 102: Britt Lapthorne | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650192/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2018 09:52:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650192/</guid><description>Podcast Description 21-year-old Britt Lapthone developed a passion for travel at a young age, so it came as no surprise to her friends and family when she announced her plans to backpack solo through Europe. In mid-2008, Britt took off in search of adventure, lapping up many unforgettable experiences before eventually arriving in the Croatian town of Dubrovnik. --- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched and written by Milly Raso and Elsha McGill</description></item><item><title>Case 101: Sian Kingi | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650193/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Nov 2018 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650193/</guid><description>Podcast Description 12-year-old Sunshine Coast schoolgirl Sian Kingi was looking forward to her friend’s upcoming birthday party. She joined her mother at the shops in Noosa Heads to buy fabric for a new outfit and then rode her usual bike route home.
---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched and written by Eileen Ormsby, author of ‘The Darkest Web – Drugs, Death and Destroyed Lives: The inside story of the internet’s evil twin’</description></item><item><title>Case 100: The Beaumont Children | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650194/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Nov 2018 11:31:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650194/</guid><description>Podcast Description On January 26 1966, siblings Jane, Arna and Grant Beaumont joined the hundreds of Adelaide residents who flocked to Glenelg beach to find respite from the scorching summer heat. It was a trip they’d made on their own many times before, and as usual, their mother Nancy sent them off with just enough money to buy bus fare and lunch from the bakery. ---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host</description></item><item><title>Case 99: Becky Watts | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650195/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 11:53:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650195/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Bristol teenager Becky Watts failed to show up for a planned lunch date with her boyfriend and then stopped responding to text messages from her friends, they immediately suspected that something was wrong. Although it wasn’t like Becky to be out of contact for so long, there was nothing to indicate she had run away from home or met with foul play.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host</description></item><item><title>Case 98: The Pillow Pyro | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650196/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 09:54:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650196/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the night of October 10 1984, a fire broke out at Ole’s Home Centre in South Pasadena that claimed the lives of four victims – Ada Deal, Matthew Troidl, Carolyn Kraus and Jimmy Cetina. Glendale arson investigator John Orr suspected the blaze had been deliberately lit, but his theory was dismissed and the fire was ruled a tragic accident.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched and written by Elsha McGill Additional editing by Milly Raso</description></item><item><title>Case 97: Rebecca Schaeffer | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650197/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 09:45:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650197/</guid><description>Podcast Description When aspiring actress Rebecca Schaffer secured the second lead in a new Hollywood sitcom, My Sister Sam, it felt like all her dreams were finally coming true. As she was thrust into stardom, she learned the truth the hard way – that fame comes with a dark side.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched and written by Eileen Ormsby
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 96: The Toy Box (Part 3) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650198/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Oct 2018 18:17:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650198/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 3 of 3]
While viewing a video of one of David Parker Ray’s assaults, investigators successfully identify yet another victim. The cases go to trial, but will it be the outcome his survivors and the public are hoping for?
__
Items and Artifacts in David Parker Ray Case
__
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched and written by Victoria Dieffenbacher
Additional editing by Milly Raso and Elsha McGill</description></item><item><title>Case 96: The Toy Box (Part 2) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650199/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2018 10:59:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650199/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 2 of 3]
As the investigation into David Parker Ray’s alleged crimes continued, an officer recalled a past encounter with a hitchhiker that he believed could be connected. When the woman finally comes forward to report her story, the true extent of Parker Ray’s crimes becomes clear. What’s more, it becomes apparent that he didn’t act alone.
---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched and written by Victoria Dieffenbacher</description></item><item><title>Case 96: The Toy Box (Part 1) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650200/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 08:12:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650200/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 1 of 3]
On March 22 1999, Sierra County police were dispatched to conduct a welfare check at a property in Hot Springs Landing, a small suburban community in the New Mexico town of Elephant Butte. Along the way, they ran into a visibly shaken witness who reported seeing a naked woman covered in blood running down the road with a chain clearly visible around her neck.</description></item><item><title>Case 95: The Vampire of Krakow | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650201/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2018 11:29:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650201/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1964, an unknown offender took to the streets of Krakow to stab elderly women in what appeared to be a string of senseless, unprovoked attacks. The victims had no connection to one another, nor were they robbed or sexually assaulted, leaving police with no obvious motive to go by.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched by Paulina Szymanska and Mike Migas
Episode written by Elsha McGill</description></item><item><title>Case 94: Millie &amp; Trevor Horn, Janice Saunders | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650202/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 10:03:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650202/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the morning of March 3 1993, Vivian Rice pulled up outside the Silver Spring home of her sister, Millie Horn, and immediately noticed that something was wrong. The garage door was wide open and Millie’s minivan was nowhere to be seen. After cautiously entering the house, Vivian discovered the slain bodies of Millie, her eight-year-old quadriplegic son Trevor, and Trevor’s nurse Janice Saunders.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host</description></item><item><title>Case 93: Susan Snow &amp; Bruce Nickell | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650203/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2018 14:21:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650203/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 40-year-old bank manager Susan Snow collapsed in her shower after complaining of a headache, the cause of her sudden death wasn’t clear. In a bid for answers, an autopsy was conducted, during which the medical examiner notices a distinct smell that immediately alerts her to the possibility that Susan was poisoned.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched and written by Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 92: Dnepropetrovsk Maniacs | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650204/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 11:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650204/</guid><description>Podcast Description Throughout June and July of 2007, residents of the Ukrainian city of Dnepropetrovsk were gripped by fear after a spate of murders occurred seemingly at random. Victims were brutally beaten using hammers and steel pipes, while some were tortured, with children, the elderly and homeless most vulnerable to the attacks.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched and written by Eileen Ormsby, author of ‘The Darkest Web – Drugs, Death and Destroyed Lives: The inside story of the internet’s evil twin.</description></item><item><title>Case 91: Carly Ryan | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650205/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 08:31:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650205/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2006, Myspace was the biggest social media platform in the world, surpassing Google as the most visited website. Like many teenagers, 14-year-old Carly Ryan turned to the internet to interact with friends and meet new people. It wasn’t long before she struck up a friendship with 18-year-old Brandon Kane, who went by the username ‘KuruptKoala.’ ---
We would like to add a special thanks credit for Karina Natt and The Carly Ryan Foundation for the help in the creation of this episode.</description></item><item><title>Case 90: Hoddle Street | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650206/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 10:41:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650206/</guid><description>Podcast Description 19-year-old Julian Knight was obsessed with war and combat from a young age. He enrolled in the Royal Military Academy of Duntroon with dreams of one day defending his country, but there was one problem – he didn’t like authority.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched and written by Elsha McGill
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-90-hoddle-street
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 89: Ella Tundra | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650207/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2018 10:52:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650207/</guid><description>Podcast Description In September 2012, former Countdown champion Richard Britton walked into a pub and was served by a 21-year-old bartender, whom he nicknamed “Ella Tundra”. From that moment on, Britton developed a fixation with Ella that filled the typically outgoing and confident young woman with paranoia and anxiety.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched and written by Eileen Ormsby, author of ‘The Darkest Web – Drugs, Death and Destroyed Lives: The inside story of the internet’s evil twin.</description></item><item><title>Case 88: Stephen Hilder | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650208/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 10:50:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650208/</guid><description>Podcast Description Most people who try skydiving do it just once – it’s something to tick off the bucket list. But for a small minority, skydiving becomes an obsession, a way of life. While accidents are expected, skydiving deaths are uncommon. On the rare occasion that a jumper loses their life, a universal toast is given: “Blue skies, black death.”
---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched and written by Eileen Ormsby, author of ‘The Darkest Web – Drugs, Death and Destroyed Lives: The inside story of the internet’s evil twin.</description></item><item><title>Case 87: Elaine O’Hara | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650209/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 10:20:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650209/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Irish childcare worker Elaine O’Hara went missing in 2012, her family and friends feared she may have taken her own life. Although she’d recently spoken about an abusive affair she was having with a married man, Elaine struggled with mental illness and was prone to telling tales. Her stories were therefore written off as fictional.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched by Bonnie Lavelle Robinson</description></item><item><title>Case 86: Amy Allwine | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650210/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2018 08:35:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650210/</guid><description>Podcast Description When FBI agents received word that online hackers had cracked their way into the dark web and uncovered an Albanian murder-for-hire organisation known as the Besa Mafia, they never expected their investigations would lead them to the quiet suburbs of Cottage Grove, Minnesota.
---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Episode researched and written by Eileen Ormsby, author of ‘The Darkest Web – Drugs, Death and Destroyed Lives: The inside story of the internet’s evil twin.</description></item><item><title>Case 85: Tom Brown | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650211/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 16:24:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650211/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 18-year-old Canadian High School student Tom Brown failed to return home by his midnight curfew on Thanksgiving of 2016, his mother Penny immediately knew something was wrong. It wasn’t like Tom to stay out late or not respond to text messages.
---
Episode researched and narrated by the Anonymous Host
Writing by Milly Raso
Additional edits by Tayla Vos
Open and download the map for Tom Brown’s episode casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 84: Lesley Molseed (Part 2) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650212/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 13:47:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650212/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 2 of 2]
With Stefan Kiszko behind bars for the murder of Lesley Molseed, West Yorkshire and Greater Manchester police were commended for their exceptional work in bringing the child killer to justice. The people of Rochdale once again felt safe knowing that the monster had been locked away… or so it seemed.
---
Episode researched and written by Milly Raso
Additional edits by Tayla Vos
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 84: Lesley Molseed (Part 1) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650213/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2018 15:29:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650213/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 1 of 2]
On October 5 1975, April Molseed sent her 11-year-old daughter Lesley Molseed to the nearby corner store in Rochdale to buy a loaf of bread. Hours later, she still hadn’t returned. Fears quickly escalated when it was discovered that Lesley never made it to the shop at all.
---
Episode researched and written by Milly Raso
Additional edits by Tayla Vos For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 83: Chantelle &amp; Leela McDougall, Tony Popic | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650214/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2018 15:50:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650214/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2007, 28-year-old Chantelle McDougall told her family she was moving to Brazil for spiritual purposes, along with her daughter Leela, partner Simon Kadwell, and friend Tony Popic. The group packed up their farmhouse in the small Western Australian town of Nannup and vanished, but there was no evidence to confirm they ever left the country.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 53: EAR-ONS/Golden State Killer | Update | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650215/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 01:47:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650215/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is an important update on the EAR-ONS/Golden State Killer case in Case 53 (25.04.18).
For all credits and sources, please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-53-original-night-stalker-part-5.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 03: Lauria Bible and Ashley Freeman | Update | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650216/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 00:42:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650216/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is an update on the Lauria Bible and Ashley Freeman case in Case 03 (23.04.18).
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-03-lauria-bible-and-ashley-freeman
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 82: Maria Korp | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650217/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 16:51:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650217/</guid><description>Podcast Description 50-year-old Maria Korp was a devoted mother of two, so when she went missing from her Mickleham home in Melbourne’s north in February of 2009, it was clear that she hadn’t left on her own accord.
_ _ _ Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched and written by Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-82-maria-korp
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 81: Brian Wells | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650218/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2018 17:04:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650218/</guid><description>Podcast Description Around midday on August 28 2003, 46-year-old delivery driver Brian Wells clocked in for his usual lunchtime shift at Mama Mia’s Pizzeria in Erie, Pennsylvania. At 1:30 PM, he was called to deliver two pizzas at an address at the end of a dirt road on Peach Street. _ _ _ Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched and written by Gemma Harris
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 80: Beth Barnard | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650219/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2018 15:31:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650219/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Vanishing of Vivienne Cameron delves deep into the murder of Beth Barnard and the disappearance of Vivienne Cameron, as previously covered on episode 80 of Casefile. Join us and true crime author Vikki Petraitis as we take you back to Phillip Island to understand - what really happened that night.....and where is Vivienne?
Listen here: https://phillipislandpodcast.com
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 79: Rayna Rison | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650220/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 15:47:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650220/</guid><description>Podcast Description 16-year-old Rayna Rison was a devoted animal lover who dreamed of one day becoming a veterinarian. On March 26 1993, she arranged to meet her ex-boyfriend Matt Elser at the animal hospital where she worked part-time in the small Northern Indiana city of LaPorte. But when Matt arrived to pick Rayna up, the lights were off in the building and she was nowhere to be seen. _ _ _ The Rayna Rison Memorial Scholarship</description></item><item><title>Case 78: The Janabi Family | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650221/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 13:12:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650221/</guid><description>Podcast Description During the Iraq War, four members of the Janabi Family were found brutally massacred in their farmhouse in the rural village of Yusufiyah. 14-year-old Abeer Qassim Hamza al-Janabi had been violently raped and the family’s home had been set on fire.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched and written by Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-78-the-janabi-family
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 77: Mia Zapata | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650222/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2018 16:37:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650222/</guid><description>Podcast Description The evening of July 6, 1993, was a typical one for Mia Zapata. The 27-year-old was a staple of Seattle’s music scene, having fronted punk rock band The Gits since the group’s inception in Ohio in 1986. She spent the night at a live music venue, The Comet Tavern, before visiting a friend at their apartment.
---
Opening poem titled; ‘Slaughter of Bruce’, written by Mia Zapata.
Closing song titled; “Bob - Cousin O” performed by The Gits, written by Mia K Zapata, Matthew F Dresdner, Andrew L Kessler and John Stephen Moriarty © Fishheadhotdogburrito Music, licensed courtesy of Rogue Octopus.</description></item><item><title>Case 76: Silk Road (Part 3) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650223/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2018 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650223/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 3 of 3]
The investigation into The Silk Road and Ross Ulbricht heats to boiling point as Homeland Security, the Drug Enforcement Administration and the FBI hone in on their suspect. Will Ulbricht’s attempts to create a new identity pay off and will his emergency plans succeed?
---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched and written by Victoria Dieffenbacher
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 76: Silk Road (Part 2) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650224/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2018 16:41:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650224/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 2 of 3]
As The Silk Road continued to expand, problems started piling up for Ross Ulbricht, AKA The Dread Pirate Roberts. With business booming and concerns that law enforcement were lurking on the site, Ulbricht created an emergency ‘To Do List’ in case he ever came under real danger of getting caught. It read: ‘Encrypt and backup important files on laptop to memory stick; destroy laptop’s hard drive and hide/dispose; destroy phone and hide/dispose; find place to live on Craigslist for cash and create new identity.</description></item><item><title>Case 76: Silk Road (Part 1) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650225/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 17:20:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650225/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 1 of 3]
Pennsylvania State University student Ross Ulbricht had been fascinated with mathematics and science from a young age. During his college years, he developed a new fascination with libertarianism, a political philosophy that values individual freedom above all else. For Ross, this became more of an interest – it became a way of life.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched and written by Victoria Dieffenbacher</description></item><item><title>Case 75: Graeme Thorne | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650226/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 16:07:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650226/</guid><description>Podcast Description On June 1 1960, Sydney resident Bazil Thorne received a phone call informing that he’d just won one hundred thousand pounds in a Sydney Opera House Lottery. Bazil couldn’t believe his ears – he’d never won anything of significance before.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched and written by Anna Priestland
Additional research by Bonnie Lavelle Robinson
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-75-graeme-thorne
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 74: Eric Coy | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650227/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2018 16:17:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650227/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the morning of January 24 1987, nine-year-old Eric Coy hopped on his bike to make the one-mile journey to his cousin Eddrick’s house in the Northern Californian town of Martinez. The two boys were best friends and it was a trip Eric had made countless times before. Eager to get there as quick as he could, Eric took a shortcut. --- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host</description></item><item><title>Case 73: The Lady in the Barrel | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650228/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 07:45:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650228/</guid><description>Podcast Description On September 15 1878, three teenage boys were tending to cattle in the woods near Silver Lake in Staten Island when they discovered a wooden barrel sticking out of the mud. Excited about the potential treasure that lay within, they frantically dug at the barrel with sticks.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched and written by Anna Priestland
This episode's sponsor:
The Alienist – New TV mystery drama based on a novel by Caleb Carr</description></item><item><title>Case 72: Wilhelmina Kruger &amp; Anna Dowlingkoa | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650229/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 15:51:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650229/</guid><description>Podcast Description For several weeks, 56-year-old Wilhelmina Kruger was unable to shake the feeling she was being watched. Her anxiety became so strong that on the night of January 29 1966, she had her partner drive her to her shift at the Piccadilly Centre in Wollongong, where she worked as a cleaner. It turned out Wilhelmina’s suspicions were right. The following morning, her mutilated body was found at the bottom of the basement stairs in what was considered one of the most brutal attacks in New South Wales history.</description></item><item><title>Case 71: Elodie Morel | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650230/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2017 14:04:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650230/</guid><description>Podcast Description On May 2 2005, an officer at the Aigues-Mortes police station in Southern France received a phone call from a panicked man who warned, “A guy who just left my place is about to kidnap a girl. He’s armed, and I think he’s about to do something horrific.” The caller directed police to a nearby cafe and told them to be on the lookout for a man accompanied by an attractive young woman.</description></item><item><title>Case 70: The Kimberley Killer | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650231/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2017 16:12:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650231/</guid><description>Podcast Description In June 1987, the bodies of Phillip Walkemeyer, Julie Warren and Terry Bolt were found shot dead at a campsite at the Pentecost River Crossing in Western Australia’s Kimberley Region. Their burnt-out vehicle was found nearby. Similarities were drawn to the double homicide of father and son, Marcus and Lance Bullen, that occurred days earlier at a remote river hundreds of kilometres away in the Northern Territory.
---</description></item><item><title>Case 69: Gary Patterson | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650232/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2017 16:28:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650232/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the morning of May 3 1997, 33-year-old Gary Patterson woke up early at his home in Waco, Texas. Gary was excited, as he was flying out to El Paso to complete the final stage in a series of job interviews. He had an appointment with the company’s CEO and by the end of the day, he hoped to be the new head of a large housing development project.</description></item><item><title>Case 68: Escape from Alcatraz | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650233/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 16:13:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650233/</guid><description>Podcast Description Following the failed 1946 escape turned violent siege, safety measures at Alcatraz Federal Penitentiary were made even more stringent and inmates were kept under harsher controls. In the decade following the Battle of Alcatraz, no further escapes were attempted.
---
Researched and written by Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-68-escape-alcatraz
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 67: The Battle of Alcatraz | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650234/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2017 16:01:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650234/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the 1940s, Alcatraz Federal Penitentiary in the San Francisco Bay was a state-of-the-art facility. Deemed to be completely escape-proof, convicts from all over the United States who were regarded as dangerous and incapable of rehabilitation were often transferred to the gloomy island prison.
---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched and written by Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-67-battle-alcatraz
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 66: The Black Widow | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650235/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2017 10:08:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650235/</guid><description>Podcast Description North Carolina residents James Napoleon Taylor and Raymond Reid died 13 years apart from seemingly natural causes, and doctors felt there was nothing suspicious about their deaths.
---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched and written by Anna Priestland
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-66-black-widow
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 65: Allison Baden-Clay | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650236/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2017 17:17:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650236/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Brisbane based real estate agent Gerard Baden-Clay woke up at 6 AM on the morning of April 20 2012, there was no sign of his wife, Allison. This wasn’t completely out of the ordinary, as Allison sometimes went for early morning walks around their Brisbane neighbourhood. She was always home in time to get the couple’s three daughters ready for school, but when 7:15 rolled around, there was still no sign of her.</description></item><item><title>Case 64: Peter Weinberger | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650237/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2017 15:34:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650237/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Weinberger family was emblematic of 1950s suburban America. Husband and wife Betty and Morris lived in a modest home in Westbury, New York, where they were raising their two-year-old son Lewis and their newborn baby, Peter. –––
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched and written by Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-64-peter-weinberger
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 46: The Frankston &amp; Tynong North Serial Killer | Update | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650238/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2017 12:17:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650238/</guid><description>Podcast Description An important update on the case from Victoria police on October 21st, 2017.
MAPS:
Frankston North Killings map
Frankston and Tynong North points of interests map
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-46-frankston-tynong-north-serial-killer
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 63: Catherine Holmes &amp; Georgina Watmore | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650239/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 17:59:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650239/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the evening of April 14 1987, 28-year-old Catherine Holmes hosted a small party at her home in the small New South Wales town of Cowra. When she failed to show up at work the following day, a friend went to Catherine’s home to check on her. There, they discovered Catherine’s badly beaten body, along with that of her friend and colleague, 24-year-old Georgina Watmore...
---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host</description></item><item><title>Case 62: The Honolulu Strangler | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650240/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2017 14:07:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650240/</guid><description>Podcast Description Between 1985 and 1986, five young women went missing on the Hawaiian island of Honolulu. The victims – Vicki Purdy, Regina Sakamoto, Denise Hughes, Louise Medeiros and Linda Pesce – were each found strangled to death with their hands bound behind their backs.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched and written by Anna Priestland
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-62-honolulu-strangler
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 61: The Lin Family | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650241/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2017 16:42:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650241/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the morning of July 18 2009, customers gathered outside Min Lin’s news agency in North Epping, New South Wales. The family-run business always opened on time, but on this particular day its doors were locked and there was no sign of anyone inside.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched and written by Anna Priestland
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-61-lin-family
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 60: Jonestown (Part 3) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650242/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 17:32:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650242/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 3 of 3]
On November 17 1978, Congressman Leo Ryan travelled to Guyana to inspect Jonestown for himself. When a number of Peoples Temple members expressed a desire to leave with him, Jim Jones was furious. What followed next would go down in history.
---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched and written by Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-60-jonestown-part-3
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 60: Jonestown (Part 2) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650243/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2017 15:55:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650243/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 2 of 3]
In the late 1970s, Jim Jones and hundreds of his followers relocated to The Peoples Temple Agricultural Project in the South American country of Guyana – more commonly known as ‘Jonestown’.
---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched and written by Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-60-jonestown-part-2
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 60: Jonestown (Part 1) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650244/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2017 15:52:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650244/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 1 of 3]
During childbirth, Lynetta Jones’ deceased mother appeared to her in a vision and prophesied that the baby would one day become a great man. Lynetta’s son was Jim Warren Jones, who grew up to become the leader of a new religious movement he named ‘The Peoples Temple’.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched and written by Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 59: Amy Lynn Bradley | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650245/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 17:24:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650245/</guid><description>Podcast Description In March 1998, 23-year-old Amy Lynn Bradley joined her parents and brother on a weeklong cruise through the Caribbean. While the rest of her family was excited about the trip, Amy was reluctant. She had an apprehensive feeling that she just couldn’t shake.
---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched and written by Anna Priestland
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-59-amy-lynn-bradley
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 58: Shannon Matthews | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650246/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 16:33:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650246/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nine-year-old Shannon Matthews lived with her family at the Moorside Council Estate in West Yorkshire, England. On February 19 2008, she said goodbye to her mother Karen before setting off on the half-mile walk to school.
---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched and written by Anna Priestland
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-58-shannon-matthews
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 57: Walsh Street | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650247/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2017 16:08:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650247/</guid><description>Podcast Description At 11 PM on October 11 1988, Victoria Police Constables Steven Tynan and Damian Eyre began working the night shift in the Melbourne suburb of Prahran. After attending to a number of routine policing matters, they were called out to inspect a Holden Commodore that had been abandoned in Walsh Street, South Yarra.
---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched and written by Milly Raso
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 56: Anita Cobby | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650248/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2017 16:34:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650248/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the morning of February 4 1986, a dairy farmer in the outer Sydney suburb of Prospect noticed his cows had been behaving strangely. For hours, they had stood gathered at one particular spot in his paddock. The farmer went to see what they were doing and found the brutalised body of 26-year-old nurse Anita Cobby.
--- Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched and written by Victoria Dieffenbacher</description></item><item><title>Case 54: Daniel Morcombe | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650249/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2017 15:08:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650249/</guid><description>Podcast Description On December 7 2003, 13-year-old Daniel Morcombe set out from his home in Queensland’s Sunshine Coast to walk the one-kilometre journey to the nearby bus stop. He was planning to go to a local shopping centre to get a haircut and buy some Christmas presents for his parents. It was a trip Daniel made often, usually with his twin brother, Bradley.
---
Episode narrated by the Anonymous Host
Researched and written by Milly Raso</description></item><item><title>Case 53: The East Area Rapist/Original Night Stalker (Part 5) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650250/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2017 17:13:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650250/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 5 of 5]
In 1979, the East Area Rapist’s three-year-long crime spree came to an abrupt halt. Residents of Northern California could finally breathe a sigh of relief. Although the perpetrator hadn’t been captured, the nightmare was finally over... ---
Researched and written by Anna Priestland
Download the map of the attacks here
Download "The Homework" files here
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-53-original-night-stalker-part-5
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 53: The East Area Rapist 1978–1979 (Part 4) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650251/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2017 17:09:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650251/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 4 of 5]
As the 1970s drew to a close, the East Area Rapist continued terrorising residents of Northern California. His attacks became increasingly violent, with one psychologist warning that the perpetrator would most likely escalate to murder as soon as he felt killing was justified.
---
Researched and written by Anna Priestland
Download the map of the attacks here
Download "The Homework" files here
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 53: The East Area Rapist 1977–1978 (Part 3) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650252/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2017 17:02:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650252/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 3 of 5]
Throughout the summer of 1978, the East Area Rapist continued to stalk, attack and assault women and their families. He extended his hunting grounds, moving beyond Sacramento County to target victims in other Northern California communities.
---
Researched and written by Anna Priestland
Download the map of the attacks here
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-53-east-area-rapist-1977-1978-part-3
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 53: The East Area Rapist 1977 (Part 2) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650253/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2017 18:12:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650253/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 2 of 5]
By the start of 1977, panic had well and truly set in throughout Sacramento County as news of the East Area Rapist spread. Despite residents preparing for possible attacks and police forming a special task force, the perpetrator continued his crime spree unabated. ---
Researched and written by Anna Priestland
Download the map of the attacks here
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 53: The East Area Rapist 1976 (Part 1) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650254/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2017 16:04:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650254/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 1 of 5]
In the summer of 1976, a serial offender began terrorising several quiet, suburban communities throughout Northern California’s Sacramento County. He would stalk his victims before breaking into their homes under the cover of darkness, binding them and raping them repeatedly. By the end of the year, he’d committed a total of ten attacks. ---
Researched and written by Anna Priestland
Download the map of the attacks here</description></item><item><title>Case 52: Mary &amp; Beth Stauffer, Jason Wilkman | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650255/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2017 08:48:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650255/</guid><description>Podcast Description In May 1980, Mary Stauffer was a happily married mother-of-two, living in Minnesota. She and her family were about to make a big move to the Philippines, where Mary and her husband had previously worked as Christian missionaries. In the lead up to their departure, Mary took her eight-year-old daughter Beth for a haircut at a local beauty salon.
---
Researched and written by Victoria Dieffenbacher
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 51: Tina Watson | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650256/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 19:02:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650256/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Great Barrier Reef is one of the seven natural wonders of the world and one of Australia’s most famous tourist attractions. Its warm, clear waters and tropical marine life make it popular with scuba divers the world over.
---
Researched and written by Anna Priestland
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-51-tina-watson
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 50: Jennifer Pan | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650257/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2017 16:48:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650257/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the evening of November 8 2010, 25-year-old University of Toronto student Jennifer Pan was relaxing in the bedroom of her family home in the Ontario neighbourhood of Unionville. Her parents, Bich Ha and Hann Huei, were also home at the time. Suddenly, Jennifer heard unfamiliar voices downstairs, followed by thudding footsteps. She immediately knew that something was very wrong.
--- Researched and written by Anna Priestland
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 49: The Moors Murders (Part 3) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650258/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 18:54:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650258/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 3 of 3]
After Ian Brady and Myra Hindley are arrested for the string of horrific slayings dubbed ‘The Moors Murders’, the true horror of their crimes finally comes to light. As the couple are brought to trial, the nature of their twisted relationship is scrutinised by law enforcement, the justice system, and England’s media.
---
Researched and written by Victoria Dieffenbacher
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 49: The Moors Murders (Part 2) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650259/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2017 20:31:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650259/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 2 of 3]
Ian Brady had fantasies about committing the “perfect murder.” After sharing his secret with his girlfriend, Myra Hindley, the fantasy soon became a reality.
--- Researched and written by Victoria Dieffenbacher
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-49-moors-murders-part-2
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 49: The Moors Murders (Part 1) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650260/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2017 18:41:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650260/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 1 of 3]
In 1963, two youths disappeared during separate incidents in and around the northern English city of Manchester. First, 16-year-old Pauline Reade vanished while on her way to a dance. Then, four months later, 12-year-old John Kilbride disappeared from a market in Ashton-under-Lyne.
--- Researched and written by Victoria Dieffenbacher
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-49-moors-murders-part-1
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 48: Suzy Lamplugh | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650261/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2017 19:32:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650261/</guid><description>Podcast Description At midday on July 28 1986, 25-year-old British real estate agent Suzy Lamplugh left work to attend an appointment. The only clue as to where she was headed was a note scrawled in her diary that read: “12:45 Mr Kipper – 37 Shorrolds Road”...
---
Researched and written by Anna Priestland.
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-48-suzy-lamplugh
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 47: Yara Gambirasio | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650262/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2017 14:06:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650262/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Italian town of Brembate di Sopra is home to a quiet, close-knit community, and like the other local youths, 13-year-old Yara Gambirasio felt safe navigating the streets alone. On November 26 2010, Yara left the town’s sports centre and didn’t hesitate to walk the 700-metre journey home by herself. However, when she failed to arrive, it turned out the streets of Brembate di Sopra weren’t as safe as everyone thought.</description></item><item><title>Case 46: The Frankston and Tynong North Serial Killer | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650263/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2017 18:18:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650263/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the 18 month period between May 1980 and October 1981, six women went missing from the Frankston and Tynong North areas in Melbourne’s south-east. The victims – Bertha Miller, Catherine Headland, Ann-Marie Sargent, Narumol Stephenson, Allison Rooke and Joy Summers – were later found murdered and dumped in remote scrubland. Obvious efforts had been made by the offender to prevent the victims from being identified.
--- Researched and written by the Anonymous Host</description></item><item><title>Case 45: Port Arthur | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650264/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2017 10:22:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650264/</guid><description>Podcast Description On April 28 1996, a lone gunman entered the Broad Arrow Café in Tasmania’s historic Port Arthur site and opened fire. By the end of his shooting spree, 35 lives had been lost and 24 others were injured, including two young children...
--- Researched and co-written by Anna Priestland
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-45-port-arthur
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 44: Peter Falconio | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650265/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2017 17:10:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650265/</guid><description>Podcast Description The desert roads of the Northern Territory are as long as they are desolate. If you stand still, the loudest sound you’ll hear is your own heartbeat. For British tourists Peter Falconio and Joanne Lees, the prospect of driving from Adelaide to Darwin along the expansive, open road was the thrill of a lifetime and unlike anything, they’d ever experienced before.
---
Episode researched and co-written by Anna Priestland</description></item><item><title>Case 43: Keith Warren | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650266/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2017 19:59:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650266/</guid><description>Podcast Description The summer of 1986 was a busy one for 19-year-old Silver Spring resident, Keith Warren. Having recently graduated from John F. Kennedy High School, Keith worked two jobs to save money for college. Popular and sociable, he spent his spare time hanging out with friends and was excited about what the future held.
---
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-43-keith-warren
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 42: Sherri Rasmussen | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650267/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2017 10:08:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650267/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 29-year-old Sherri Rasmussen married the love of her life, John Ruetten, the future looked promising. But just three months after their wedding, Sherri was found shot to death in the couples Van Nuys apartment. One thing was clear – Sherri had fought for her life until the very end...
---
Assisted in research and co-written by Anna Priestland
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-42-sherri-rasmussen
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 41: Mr Cruel | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650268/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2017 17:30:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650268/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the late 1980s and early 1990s, Melbourne was gripped by fear when a masked assailant began breaking into suburban family homes and abducting young children. The attacks were particularly callous, earning the assailant the title of Mr Cruel.
--- For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-41-mr-cruel
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 26: Lisa Marie Young | Update | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650269/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2016 11:31:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650269/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is an update on the Lisa Marie Young case in Case 26.
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-26-lisa-marie-young
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 40: John Newman | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650270/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2016 10:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650270/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the 1980s and 1990s, the Sydney suburb of Cabramatta was a hotbed for criminal activity. Heroin use was rife and users flocked to the area looking for their next fix. As was to be expected, the drug epidemic resulted in an increase in violent crime, including gangs, home invasions, robberies, extortions, kidnappings, and worse.
---
Research for this episode by Victoria Dieffenbacher. Co-written by Victoria Dieffenbacher and the Anonymous Host.</description></item><item><title>Case 39: Janelle Patton | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650271/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2016 11:14:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650271/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a string of failed relationships and other disappointments, Janelle Patton made the decision to relocate from Australia to Norfolk Island in search of a fresh start. With a population of around 2000 people, the small South Pacific island was considered a safe and friendly place, with no major crimes having occurred there in over a century.
--- Victoria Dieffenbacher researched and co-wrote this episode.
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 38: The Pikuls | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650272/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2016 21:00:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650272/</guid><description>Podcast Description Indiana born Diane Whitmore always dreamed of making it big in New York City. When she met Wall Street securities analyst Joseph Pikul, she thought she was on the way to the perfect life. But her marriage to Joseph Pikul wasn’t perfect. In fact, it was far from it...
---
Victoria Dieffenbacher researched and co-wrote this episode.
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/the-pikuls
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 37: The Yorkshire Ripper (Part 3) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650273/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 21:55:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650273/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 3 of 3]
With the West Yorkshire Police no closer to identifying The Yorkshire Ripper, the department came under intense scrutiny. Prime Minister Margaret Thatcher offered to take over the investigation, while the media and public demanded that Scotland Yard be called in to find the killer. ---
Research for this episode by Victoria Dieffenbacher. Co-written by Victoria Dieffenbacher and the Anonymous Host.
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 37: The Yorkshire Ripper (Part 2) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650274/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2016 19:45:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650274/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 2 of 3]
With the Yorkshire Ripper showing no sign of slowing down, police appealed directly to the killer himself in the hopes of putting an end to the crime spree.
---
Research for this episode by Victoria Dieffenbacher. Co-written by Victoria Dieffenbacher and the Anonymous Host.
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/yorkshire-ripper-part-2
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 37: The Yorkshire Ripper (Part 1) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650275/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2016 19:36:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650275/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 1 of 3]
West Yorkshire is a county in England that has a population of over 2 million people. It covers an area of over 2,000 km² and is formed by five cities: Leeds, Bradford, Wakefield, Kirklees, and Calderdale. Each one of these cities has its own history, its own identity, and its own voice.
But during the 1970’s, they were all united. The residents of each city were looking over their shoulders, praying they wouldn’t be the next victim, in one man’s reign of terror who the press named, “The Yorkshire Ripper.</description></item><item><title>Case 36: Amok | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650276/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2016 20:34:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650276/</guid><description>Podcast Description In late 2000, the owner of a Polish advertising company, Dariusz Janiszewski, went missing after going to meet a client. His body was later found floating in a lake, but police had no idea who could be responsible and the Polish press ultimately dubbed the case “the perfect murder.”
---
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-36-amok
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 35: Operation Mayan | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650277/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2016 21:48:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650277/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the evening of March 18 2001, 22-year-old Sian O’Callaghan enjoyed a night out with friends in the Old Town of Swindon in South West England. The flat she shared with her boyfriend Kevin Reape was less than a kilometre away, making it an easy walk home.
--- For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-35-operation-mayan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 34: The Catholic Mafia | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650278/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2016 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650278/</guid><description>Podcast Description [WARNING – This episode deals with child sex abuse. It will not be suitable for all listeners.]
In the early 1960s, Victorian Detective Denis Ryan was transferred from Melbourne to the regional town of Mildura where he soon ran into a familiar face – local priest, Father John Day. The two had encountered one another before during a less than savoury incident in St Kilda several years prior. ---
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 33: Jaycee Lee Dugard | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650279/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2016 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650279/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the early 1990s, South Lake Tahoe was considered a safe and sheltered place to live. All that changed on June 10 1991, when 11-year-old Jaycee Lee Dugard was abducted in broad daylight while walking to her school bus stop.
Almost two decades later, convicted sex offender Phillip Garrido visited the University of California’s Berkeley campus, where a staff member noticed something suspicious about the way he was behaving.</description></item><item><title>Case 32: Grace &amp; Kathleen Holmes | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650280/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2016 02:04:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650280/</guid><description>Podcast Description After migrating from England to Australia after World War II, the Holmes family were looking forward to embracing a safer and higher quality of life. They’d experienced trauma and hardship during the war years and were ready to start afresh. That dream was shattered on August 29, 1950, just weeks after their arrival, when 18-year-old Grace Holmes and her 11-year-old sister Kathleen went for a walk along the Canton Beach foreshore in Toukley and never returned home.</description></item><item><title>Case 31: The Killer Couple | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650281/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2016 22:23:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650281/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over a five-week period in 1986, four young women went missing from around Perth in Western Australia. 22-year-old Mary Neilson, 15-year-old Susannah Candy, 31-year-old Noelene Patterson and 21-year-old Denise Brown all disappeared without a trace, but police were sceptical that some were runaways and no links were drawn between the missing women.
That was until November 10 1986, when a man standing outside a vacuum cleaner store was suddenly approached by a hysterical, barefoot young woman.</description></item><item><title>Case 28: Lindsay Buziak | Follow Up | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650282/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 08:54:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650282/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is an update on the Lindsay Buziak case in Case 28.
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-28-lindsay-buziak
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 30: The Claremont Serial Killer | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650283/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 21:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650283/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode of Casefile was released in 2016 when the case was still unresolved. Major developments have since occurred and as a result, we have elected to remove the episode, with a view to releasing an updated version in the future.
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-30-claremont-serial-killer
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 29: The Burgate House Murders | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650284/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2016 20:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650284/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 80-year-old retired publisher Joseph Clever lived with his wife Hilda at Burgate House, a secluded mansion on the edge of New Forest in Hampshire, England. On the evening of September 1 1986, they invited their son Tom and his wife Wendy over for dinner. The following morning, two maintenance workers arrived to find the property engulfed in smoke. Investigators rushed to the scene soon realised that fire was the least of the problems.</description></item><item><title>Case 28: Lindsay Buziak | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650285/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2016 16:53:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650285/</guid><description>Podcast Description 24-year-old Lindsay Buziak loved her job as a Vancouver Island real estate agent and was looking forward to carving an impressive career for herself. So in early 2008, she was eager to please when she received a phone call from a woman who had recently relocated to the area and wanted Lindsay’s help in finding a one million dollar property that was available immediately. On February 2, Lindsay organised to meet the woman and her husband at a house in the suburb of Saanich.</description></item><item><title>Case 27: The West Mesa Bone Collector | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650286/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2016 22:13:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650286/</guid><description>Podcast Description The eastern side of the city of Albuquerque, New Mexico, is closed in by mountains. On the city’s west side, a mesa rises out of the Rio Grande Valley.
In 2005, subdivisions and new housing were being built along the West Mesa. The construction pressed up against the vast desert that stretches beyond where you will find tumbleweeds, high tension wires and trash. It is a desolate isolated spot.</description></item><item><title>Case 26: Lisa Marie Young | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650287/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2016 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650287/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vancouver Island. Known for its breathtaking scenery, astonishing postcard beauty and amazing wildlife. Heaven on earth.
But on certain parts of the island, beneath the beauty, some will tell you there lies a dark underbelly. And in the early hours of the morning, June 30th, 2002, that underbelly came to the surface.
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-26-lisa-marie-young
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 25: Prue Bird | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650288/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2016 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650288/</guid><description>Podcast Description “If any bastard ever thought about going to the cops about us, they’ll be killed and so will their fucking families. And if we don’t get them, our mates will. It would be a shame if anything happened to your sweet little Prue, wouldn’t it”.
Those words were allegedly said by one of the men convicted for the Russell Street Bombing that we covered the last episode.
The person he said those words to?</description></item><item><title>Case 24: Russell Street Bombing (Part 2) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650289/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2016 22:29:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650289/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 2 of 2]
We left part one just after the government announced a 500 thousand dollar reward for any information to help solve the case. It was hoped this large reward would be enough to entice a male caller to make contact again.
He had already called numerous times before, claiming to know who the bombers were…
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-24-russell-street-bombing-part-2
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 24: Russell Street Bombing (Part 1) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650290/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2016 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650290/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 1 of 2]
Haros Avenue in Nunawading (Melbourne) presented a problem for the police surveillance team following the red Jaguar. It was a small dead-end street. No way to observe the house there bank robbery suspect was heading to, without being obvious…
To avoid being detected the police had no choice but to let the suspect out of there sight. There was only one way in and out of Haros Avenue, so the suspect would have to come back past them eventually…</description></item><item><title>Case 23: The Frankston Serial Killer (Part 2) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650291/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2016 21:00:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650291/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 2 of 2]
Part 2 of the Frankston Serial Killer. At the end of part 1 police had found out who owned the suspicious vehicle parked on Skye Road at the time of Natalie Russell's murder. Will it get them anywhere though?
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-23-the-frankston-serial-killer-part-2
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 23: The Frankston Serial Killer (Part 1) | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650292/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2016 21:00:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650292/</guid><description>Podcast Description [Part 1 of 2]
Donna had recently received a few prank calls and she was getting nervous. She had a young baby and didn’t like the idea of being alone at night. Her boyfriend Les worked as a pizza delivery driver, and she decided to spend the night driving around in the car with him, rather than stay home alone.
The first thing Donna saw when she returned home was her cat on the lounge room floor, dead.</description></item><item><title>Case 22: Marguerite Edwards | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650293/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2016 21:00:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650293/</guid><description>Podcast Description It was Wednesday the 2nd of August 1989. 41-year-old Marguerite Edwards started the day like any other. Making sure her three daughters were up, and ready for school.
Marguerite was happily married to Iain Edwards, a successful orthodontist with a surgery in Bondi. They lived in a two-storey house on Victoria Road, Woollahra in Sydney’s Eastern suburbs.
After getting her daughters organised, Marguerite dropped them at Ascham school, in the nearby suburb of Edgecliffe.</description></item><item><title>Case 21: Pamela Lawrence | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650294/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2016 21:00:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650294/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Monday the 23rd of May 1994, a violent storm hit the city of Perth, Western Australia. Peter Lawrence was starting to become concerned.
It was getting late and his wife Pamela Lawrence hadn’t gotten home from work yet. He called her at 6:15 pm, when he didn’t get an answer he decided he had better go down and check on her….
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 20: Stoni Blair &amp; Stephen Berry | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650295/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2016 21:00:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650295/</guid><description>Podcast Description The details of this case are extremely difficult to hear. Extreme child abuse and child murder are involved. This episode won't be for everybody. There is far more courtroom audio than narration. It is a one-off for this episode. It is not something that will be a regular feature in the future. The courtroom confession is detailed and horrific. Listener discretion is advised.
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 19: Snowtown | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650296/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2016 21:00:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650296/</guid><description>Podcast Description Living in Australia, I had heard of the Snowtown case. I knew it as the bodies in the barrels case. But that’s all I knew. I had no idea about the who, the what, the why, or the when.
So I didn’t know it was the worst case of serial killing in Australia’s history, involving torture and dismemberment. None of the murder victims are children. However, child sexual abuse is prominent throughout.</description></item><item><title>Case 18: The North Hollywood Shootout | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650297/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2016 21:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650297/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the 28th of February 1997 Los Angeles police officers, Perello and Farrell were on routine patrol driving along Laurel Canyon Blvd, North Hollywood.
As they were driving past the Bank of America they saw two large figures enter the bank. Both were dressed in black, both were wearing ski masks and both were carrying automatic rifles. What followed, was 44 minutes of mayhem…
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 17: The Eriksson Twins | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650298/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2016 10:24:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650298/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the 17th of May 2008, two motorway patrol officers attended to a call that a pedestrian had been hit by a vehicle on the M6 motorway, near the city Stoke-on-Trent, in England.
Expecting the worst, the two officers were surprised when they arrived to see two pedestrians standing calmly and uninjured on the shoulder of the motorway. It didn’t look like much was going on at all…</description></item><item><title>Case 16: Chris &amp; Cru Kahui | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650299/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2016 11:26:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650299/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris and Cru Kahui were twins, aged just three months old when they died in hospital, both suffering from traumatic brain injury. Their death was the result o a severe impact, either from direct blows or being hit, thrown or slammed against a hard surface.
Violent shaking was another possible cause, and couldn’t be ruled out. What was clear was that the twins' injuries weren’t accidental…
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 15: The Weepy Voiced Killer | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650300/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2016 11:38:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650300/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the early 80’s a series of attacks occurred in the twin city area of Minnesota, USA. The victims were all women. Police struggled in the initial part of the investigation. There was no physical evidence, and there were no witnesses.
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-15-the-weepy-voiced-killer
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 14: Helen Munnings | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650301/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 11:44:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650301/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the 23rd of July 2008 young mother, Helen Munnings disappeared from the port city of Burnie, on the North West Coast of Tasmania, Australia.
She was last seen by the father of her child Adam Taylor, who picked her up for a drive that afternoon. His actions later that night were described as “interesting”. Extensive searches have been conducted, but no trace of Helen has ever been found…</description></item><item><title>Case 13: The Family Court Murders | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650302/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2016 12:07:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650302/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the 1980's in Sydney Australia, Justice David Opas was shot dead outside his home and bombs were exploded at the homes of Justice Richard Gee and Justice Ray Watson. All three were Family Law Court judges.
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-13-the-family-court-murders
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 12: Katherine Knight | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650303/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2016 12:11:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650303/</guid><description>Podcast Description The crime scene was described as looking more like the set of a horror movie, than real life. It is one of the most horrific crimes ever committed.
Not only did it shock the small town of Aberdeen in country NSW, where the crime occurred, it shocked the entire nation of Australia and parts of the world. What could possibly drive somebody to do this? A psychiatric illness? Or premeditated, pre-planned, pure evil?</description></item><item><title>Case 11: Anneliese Michel | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650304/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2016 12:17:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650304/</guid><description>Podcast Description First came the seizures and sleep paralysis. Then came the hallucinations and violent behaviour.
Anneliese Michel made endless visits to doctor’s and specialists only to be either referred to another doctor or placed on medication that wasn’t helping her. Her condition became so bad that at times she started to growl and speak in a horrific deep voice…
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-11-anneliese-michel
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 10: Peter Shellard | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650305/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 12:24:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650305/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 7th of May 2005 was a typical run of the mill day for Shirley Withers. She worked the full day in her Melbourne fashion boutique and once the shop had closed, she bought a take-out meal and headed to the North Caufield mansion of her millionaire boyfriend Peter Shellard…
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-10-peter-shellard
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 09: Jonathan Luna | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650306/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2016 12:26:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650306/</guid><description>Podcast Description He was implicated in a case of missing money from a courthouse evidence vault. He was facing allegations of misconduct and illegal handling of a witness in a major drug trafficking trial, which lead to the judge ordering a federal investigation.
One way to stop that federal investigation would be to come up with a quick plea deal to end the case. One problem, there was no way to do the plea deal without violating federal law.</description></item><item><title>Case 08: Holly Wells &amp; Jessica Chapman | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650307/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 12:28:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650307/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the 4th of August 2002, best friends Holly Wells and Jessica Chapman disappeared from the small town of Sohom in England.
One of England’s biggest ever manhunts followed. The media became critical of the lack of progress police were making on the case….but they did have a suspect.
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-08-holly-wells-and-jessica-chapman
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 07: Julian Buchwald &amp; Carolynne Watson | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650308/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2016 12:31:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650308/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the 4th of March 2008, Julian Buchwald and his girlfriend Carolynne Watson went for a romantic picnic lunch in country Victoria. They didn't return home.
It wasn't long before a terrifying, threatening note was located. Was this really the work of a satanic cult? Or was there something even more sinister going on…
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-07-julian-buchwald-and-carolynne-watson
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 06: Roger Dean | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650309/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 12:35:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650309/</guid><description>Podcast Description "You won't believe it, but it was like, satan saying to me that it's the right thing to do."
In the early hours of the 18th of November 2011 a fire was deliberately lit at the Quakers Hill Nursing Home. The nursing home housed 89 residents, a lot of whom were highly dependent patients who were immobile, suffering dementia and Alzheimer's disease.
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 05: Donna Wheeler | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650310/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2016 12:37:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650310/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Tuesday the 2nd of November 1999 Donna Wheeler was found murdered in her home in Berala, Western Sydney. There were several suspects.
Was it her ex-husband John who found her body and called the police? Was it her violent ex-boyfriend Keith who was recently arrested for assaulting Donna. Keith wasn't happy that Donna was spending a lot of time with his brother Colin since they separated…
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 04: Who Put Bella In The ‘Witch’ Elm | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650311/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2016 12:40:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650311/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the 18th of April 1943, four boys discovered a skeleton buried in the hollow of a wych-elm tree in Hagley Woods, England.
Police immediately got to work on identifying the remains and trying to determine the cause of death, however, the investigation hit a wall…
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-04-who-put-bella-in-the-witch-elm
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Case 03: Lauria Bible &amp; Ashley Freeman | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650312/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2016 12:44:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650312/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the 29th of January 1999, best friends Lauria Bible and Ashley Freeman had a sleepover at Ashley’s house to celebrate her 16th birthday.
Ashley’s parents Danny and Kathy Freeman were also home. It was a quiet uneventful evening, nothing seemed out of the ordinary until 6 am the next morning when a neighbour reported the Freeman house was on fire.
For all credits and sources please visit http://casefilepodcast.</description></item><item><title>Case 02: The Somerton Man | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650313/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2016 09:13:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650313/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the first of December 1948, a body of a man was located along the seawall of Somerton Beach, just near Adelaide in South Australia.
At first, the police thought it was going to be a straightforward matter, but as the weeks and months went on, it became apparent that this case was anything but straightforward… To this day we don’t know who he is, we don’t know where he came from and we don’t know how he died.</description></item><item><title>Case 01: The Wanda Beach Murders | Casefile True Crime</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9170650314/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2016 09:08:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9170650314/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the 11th of January 1965, two fifteen-year-old schoolgirls Christine Sharrock and Marianne Schmidt were found murdered in the Wanda sand hills, just north of Cronulla Beach in Sydney's south.
The crime remains one of the most horrific Australia has ever seen. Despite an exhaustive police investigation, the killer remains unknown…
For all credits and sources please visit casefilepodcast.com/case-1-the-wanda-beach-murders
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>