<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>MrBallen Podcast: Strange, Dark &amp; Mysterious Stories on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/mrballen-podcast-strange-dark-mysterious-stories/</link><description>Recent content in MrBallen Podcast: Strange, Dark &amp; Mysterious Stories on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/mrballen-podcast-strange-dark-mysterious-stories/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Episode 156 - "Jackpot" (PODCAST EXCLUSIVE EPISODE) | MrBallen Podcast: Strange, Dark &amp; Mysterious Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3165850001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3165850001/</guid><description>Podcast Description In April of 2009, 42-year-old Florida lottery winner Abraham Shakespeare seemed to disappear off the face of the earth.&amp;nbsp;But a series of text messages from Abraham – and a phone call he made to his mother – would lead police to make a gruesome discovery. And what they found would expose months of lies, and help lead to a new law in Florida.
For 100s more stories like these, check out our main YouTube channel just called "</description></item><item><title>Episode 146 - "The Puppet Master" (PODCAST EXCLUSIVE EPISODE) | MrBallen Podcast: Strange, Dark &amp; Mysterious Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3165850002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3165850002/</guid><description>Podcast Description On December 13, 2001, 35-year-old Tracey Roberts was running a bath upstairs in her house in the rural town of Early, Iowa. But then, Tracey heard the front door open and footsteps downstairs. And when she walked into the hall to see what was happening, she saw two men rushing upstairs towards her.&amp;nbsp;So in a panic, Tracey ran to her bedroom, but one of the men grabbed her from behind and started strangling her.</description></item><item><title>Episode 128 - "Man on a Mission" (PODCAST EXCLUSIVE EPISODE) | MrBallen Podcast: Strange, Dark &amp; Mysterious Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3165850003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3165850003/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the night of June 17th, 1977, Chuck Morgan, the father of four young girls, sped down a dark road outside of Tucson, Arizona, and as he drove, he constantly checked his rearview mirror to make sure no one was following him. Chuck was wearing a bulletproof vest, on his hip was a .357 Magnum revolver, and in his pocket was one of his own teeth, wrapped up in tissue paper.</description></item><item><title>Episode 105 - "Medical Mishaps" | MrBallen Podcast: Strange, Dark &amp; Mysterious Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3165850004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3165850004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s podcast features 3 unique stories about "medical mishaps." The audio from all three of these stories has been pulled from our main YouTube channel and has been remastered for today's episode.
Story names, previews &amp;amp; links to original YouTube videos:
#3 -- "Side Effects" -- A healthy young man's life is turned upside down after a seemingly minor pain in his leg reveals a major problem (Original YouTube link --&amp;nbsp;https://www.</description></item><item><title>Episode 102 - "House of Cards" (PODCAST EXCLUSIVE EPISODE) | MrBallen Podcast: Strange, Dark &amp; Mysterious Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3165850005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3165850005/</guid><description>Podcast Description One afternoon in the summer of 2001, a man pulled up to a pump at a gas station and began fueling his car. Once his car was full, the man put the nozzle back into its holster, he hopped back inside of his car, and he was about to fire up the engine again when he stopped. Because something had caught his attention. There was something or someone moving around outside of his car to the left.</description></item><item><title>MrBallen Podcast Trailer | MrBallen Podcast: Strange, Dark &amp; Mysterious Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3165850006/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 22:42:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3165850006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hello fans of the Strange, Dark and Mysterious delivered in story format! Our first podcast episode will go live on the morning of February 14th, and from there on out we will be releasing 2 weekly podcasts!
Mondays = NEW story only available in podcast form
Thursdays = BONUS episode, Best of MrBallen's YouTube stories
See you soon!
Love, @mrballen
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.</description></item></channel></rss>