<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/comedy-bang-bang-the-podcast/</link><description>Recent content in Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 07:05:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/comedy-bang-bang-the-podcast/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Holiday Spectacular 2023 w/ Jason Mantzoukas, Paul F. Tompkins, Tim Baltz, Lily Sullivan, Shaun Diston, Vic Michaelis, Carl Tart, Drew Tarver, Lisa Gilroy, Dan Lippert, Gil Ozeri, Will Hines | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600134/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join Scott and guest co-host Jason Mantzoukas for that special time of year when old and new friends of the show stop by to celebrate the Comedy Bang! Bang! Holiday Spectacular! Expect appearances from Fred Guinness, Randy Snutz, Carissa, Room Tone Tony, Scott’s lawyer Terry Alamander, professional baseball player Shohei Ohtani, the Pig Shit Twins, Dr. Marty Goldstein, world’s busiest man Ned Belanela, and Harvey the Devil. Happy Holidays from CBB!</description></item><item><title>Edi Patterson, Dave Theune, Jacob Wysocki, Allison Dunbar | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600133/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Co-host with the Co-most Bean Dip (aka Bean Dip the ShopliftahBabiee) joins Scott to discuss their love for the game, Bean Dip&amp;rsquo;s thoughts on the afterlife, and what&amp;rsquo;s with the Friday after Thanksgiving? Then, Robby Delmuda - child lawyer - joins to introduce his lady-friend Deeana Bermuda. After they make a specific request of Scott and his friend Jack UCLA, property manager Rhonda Batuchi opens up about her go-cart dreams and time in a cult, and RJ Dudley (aka the beloved Fart Sack) shares industry woes.</description></item><item><title>John Early, Mitra Jouhari, Amanda Lund | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600132/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600132/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian extraordinaire John Early joins Scott to talk about his HBO comedy special John Early: Now More Than Ever, Beatlemania, and his Toni Collette fan website. Then, composer Angelina Leviosa stops by to share some of her TV interstitial songs. Plus, author Marabel May drops by with tips on how to save your marriage.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chelsea Peretti, James Mannion, Ben Rodgers | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600131/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Beloved comedian Chelsea Peretti of Farts and Pro fame joins Scott once again to talk about the relaunch of her iconic podcast Call Chelsea Peretti, bear attacks, and her bio. Then, census taker Micah Fellows stops by to talk about his life as a census taker. Plus, Uncle Jellyfish brings Little Pepper the Singing and Dancing Boy for a very special performance.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jon Hamm, Drew Tarver, Ryan Gaul | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600130/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600130/</guid><description>Podcast Description The strike is over and stars are back! Actor and friend of the show Jon Hamm returns to talk about the new fifth chapter of FX’s Fargo, The Morning Show, and how actors secretly memorize lines on set. Then, music festival expert Jesse stops by to recommend what to do at Coachella. Plus, finance expert Doug Gropes returns to discuss his program to make people financially secure and read real reviews from program participants.</description></item><item><title>Edgar Wright, Paul F. Tompkins, Vic Michaelis, Matt Apodaca | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Writer/director extraordinaire Edgar Wright joins Scott to talk about his new animated Netflix series “Scott Pilgrim Takes Off.” Then, undersea explorer Brock Lovett returns to talk about his quest to recover twenty billion dollars from a sunken Spanish Galleon. Afterwards, visual artist Quiet the Mime stops by to talk about their journey into miming. Plus, henchman Marcus Green joins the gang to explain why he’s organizing a class-action lawsuit against Spider-Man.</description></item><item><title>Dan Wilson, Paul Rust, Erin Keif, Casey Feigh | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Singer-songwriter Dan Wilson joins Scott to talk about the return of Semisonic, his meeting with Liam Gallagher, and performs a song from the new Semisonic album “Little Bit of Sun.” Then, entertainment reporter AJ Zap stops by to share his entertainment predictions for 2024. Later, illusionist Criss Angel drops by to talk about his Vegas show Mindfreak. Plus, the world’s greatest podcast guest Donk Poop swings by with pitches to make the podcast go viral.</description></item><item><title>Felicia Day, Betsy Sodaro, Mano Agapion, Devin Field | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor/writer Felicia Day joins Scott to talk about her new fantasy comedy Audible original Third Eye, Comic-Con parties, and brand deals. Then, twin actors Selma and Blair stop by to talk about spooky pranks they have pulled. Plus, director David Lynch drops by to pitch some new movie ideas.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sam Jay, Gil Ozeri, Greg Hess | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600004/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stand-up comedian extraordinaire Sam Jay joins Scott to talk about her latest stand-up special Salute Me or Shoot Me, her time writing on SNL, and the differences between New York and Boston. Then, anarchist Bane returns to test out new material for his hour comedy special. Plus, entertainer Benny Sands stops by to talk about what happens during his Vegas show.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Reggie Watts, Matt Gourley, Amanda Lund, Katie Rich, Holly Laurent | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Friend of the show Reggie Watts sticks around after singing the theme song and talks to Scott about his new book “Great Falls, MT”, hamsters, and Superman. Then, Disneyland enthusiasts Cody and Codi stop by to talk about their love for Disney. Plus, soccer moms Janet and Leanne drop by to talk about their hobbies.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bob Odenkirk, Edi Patterson, Tim Baltz, Heather Anne Campbell | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Longtime friend of the show Bob Odenkirk joins Scott to talk about his new book “Zilot &amp;amp; Other Important Rhymes,” which he co-wrote with his two children. Then, W Hotel owner Bean Dip returns to talk about her experience with vampires. Later, LinkedIn’s Chief Innovation Officer Tom Boreman stops by to talk about what’s new at LinkedIn. Plus, Telli Charcuterie drops by to talk about directing animal mating encouragement videos for endangered species at the zoo.</description></item><item><title>Paul F. Tompkins, Mitra Jouhari, Lisa Gilroy | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600007/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ballroom dancing instructor Dolores Brainwater joins Scott to talk about making a fortune dancing, her former dancing partner/sweetheart, and MAS*H. Then, intern Casey from Ohio stops by to talk about working on the reality show Botched. Plus, concerned citizen Cockroach Rick drops by to talk about getting into politics.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Aparna Nancherla, Will Hines, Holly Laurent | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stand-up comedian extraordinaire Aparna Nancherla joins Scott to talk about her new book “Unreliable Narrator: Me Myself, and Imposter Syndrome,” coffee tables, and dark chocolate. Then, musician Kurt Slammer stops by to promote his new Blues-Rock album. Plus, actress Ruth Debevoise drops by to talk about her acting career.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Gary Gulman, Dan Lippert, Dan O'Connor | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600009/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stand-up comedian extraordinaire Gary Gulman joins Scott to talk about his new book “Misfit: Growing Up Awkward in the ’80s,” flat foods, and a full circle moment when he appeared on Late Night with guest host David Brenner. Then, legendary music producer Rick Rubin drops by to help Scott produce the podcast. Plus, playwright Ian Chiswick stops by to offer Scott a role in his new play.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Flula Borg, Shaun Diston, Lily Sullivan | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor and former DJ Flula Borg joins Scott once again to talk about his new podcast Flula Makes Five, a Hans Gruber prequel, and area codes. Then, manager/producer Sprague the Whisperer returns to talk about producing Fyre Fest II. Plus, Kayla Dickie returns to talk about being on a new reality TV show.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jack Quaid, Tawny Newsome, James Mannion | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600011/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two friends Jack Quaid and Tawny Newsome join Scott to talk about babies learning about holidays, food delivery robots, and Top 5 human beings. Then, professor Robert Canasta stops by to talk about his current psychology research. Plus, podcasters Brigadoon and Greg drop by for a cross-over episode of their show “Aaahh!!! Real Cocktails.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Paul F. Tompkins, Erin Whitehead, John Hartman | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Aspiring commercial voice-over actor Abernathy Combs joins Scott to talk about his time as an army general, horror movies, and making a new voice-over demo tape. Then, entertainer Ursula stops by to talk about her transition from reality show star to stand-up comedian. Plus, private investigator Ken Lunch drops by to talk about his private practice exclusively for parents.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Andy Richter, Vic Michaelis, Alex Fernie | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600013/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andy Richter returns to talk to Scott about raising a child, his favorite cartoon character, and how he approaches interviewing a guest on his podcast The Three Questions. Then, teen foreman Susie Tewman returns to talk about issues with her non-union construction crew and having to choose between her crush and her best friend. Plus, viral guru Daniel Kolodjiez stops by to talk about how to go viral.</description></item><item><title>Ellie Kemper, Matt Apodaca, Jacob Wysocki, Hannah Pilkes | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor and comedian Ellie Kemper joins Scott to talk about her new podcast &amp;ldquo;Born To Love&amp;rdquo;, her famous high school acting teacher, and learning how to type. Then, exotic snake breeders Ronnie &amp;amp; Gunk Little stop by to talk about making snakes fall in love. Plus, local brewer Brett drops in to talk about his brewery with the most wheels and to help select craft beers for the group.</description></item><item><title>Mike Hanford, James Austin Johnson, Ele Woods | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chef Adjacent Mantzoukas joins Scott to talk about holiday themed episodes of his YouTube grilling show, burglaries in his neighborhood, and his bike karaoke show. Then, music producer VAAMM stops by to build a TikTok style beat. Plus, LA legend Young Miss Willow Panloose drops by to talk about her long and storied career.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Manchester Orchestra, Tawny Newsome, Edi Patterson, Dave Theune | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Returning champions Robert McDowell and Andy Hull of the indie rock group Manchester Orchestra join Scott to play songs off their new record “The Valley of Vision.” Then, Tawny Newsome stops by to talk about her personal life. Later, W Hotel owner Bean Dip drops by to talk about her new salon business. Plus, Scott’s assistant Mirk stops by to get some face-to-face time with Scott. Finally, wellness expert Tierna Smarg drops by to share knowledge from the future.</description></item><item><title>Anna Konkle, Mitra Jouhari, Christine Bullen | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor/writer/director Anna Konkle joins Scott to talk about the new season of The Afterparty, the future of PEN15, and body swap superheroes. Then, interior decorator Leila stops by to help Scott with his space. Plus, widow Myrtle McGee returns in search of a new husband who is a comedian.
NOTE: This was recorded before the SAG-AFTRA strike began on July 13.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Adam DeVine, Ryan Rosenberg, Ify Nwadiwe | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian and actor Adam DeVine joins Scott to talk about his new Netflix movie The Out-Laws, Pitch Perfect: Bumper in Berlin, and The Righteous Gemstones. Then, lounge singer Mr. Sing stops by to sing some tunes. Plus, vigilante Shadow Vision drops by in search of a car.
NOTE: This was recorded before the SAG-AFTRA strike began on July 13.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Vera Drew, Tim Baltz, Casey Feigh | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Writer/director Vera Drew joins Scott to talk about her new film The People’s Joker, being an editor on the Comedy Bang! Bang! TV show, and Scott’s role as Mr. Freeze in her film. Then, Randy Snutz returns to talk about his new endeavor operating a traveling karaoke station. Plus, composer Joey Salsa returns to sing songs from his new musical about his life.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Paul F. Tompkins, Lisa Gilroy, Neil Campbell | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fred Guinness of the Guinness Book of World Records returns to talk to Scott about the world record he is close to acquiring, bakers vs. donut makers, and bootstraps. Then, financial advisor Kyle Chutney stops by to share investing advice. Plus, smuggler Noel drops by to help Scott get from the ad break to the end of the show.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Myq Kaplan, Greg Hess, Erin Keif | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Myq Kaplan joins Scott to talk about his new comedy special “Live From The Universe”, his new book “Heart Brain Art Train”, and getting into comedy via singing. Then, folk singer Glen Plapinger stops by to play a few of his original songs. Plus, critic Candle St. Louis drops by to share some of her famous one-word reviews.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nick Kroll, John Gemberling, Gil Ozeri | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Returning champion Nick Kroll joins Scott to talk about the new season of the Big Mouth spin-off Human Resources, Don’t Worry Darling, and working with Hugh Jackman. Then, genuine extra-terrestrial Korbato Krim stops by in search of food. Plus, nostalgia guide Yargo Lamento drops by to channel everyone’s childhood memories.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jack Quaid, Lily Sullivan, Carl Tart | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Award nominated actor Jack Quaid joins Scott to talk about his animated character from Star Trek: Lower Decks being live action in the new season of Star Trek: Strange New Worlds, how a Facebook video he made at 15 appeared in a Scream movie, and the Transformers universe. Then, author Bridget Jones returns to read new entries from her diary. Later, TV host The Crypt Keeper stops by to talk about his audition for Tales from the Crypt.</description></item><item><title>Fortune Feimster, Paul F. Tompkins, Matt Apodaca | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian extraordinaire Fortune Feimster joins Scott to talk about hanging with Arnold Schwarzenegger on the Netflix series FUBAR, her Live Laugh Love stand-up comedy tour, and one of her first jokes about strawberries. Then, songwriter Lord Andrew Lloyd Webber returns to talk about his musical Bad Cinderella closing on Broadway. Plus, content creator Mr. Monster stops by to talk about his next big island viral video.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sarah Silverman, Suzi Barrett, Shaun Diston | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian and old friend of the show Sarah Silverman joins Scott to talk about her new HBO stand-up special “Someone You Love,” her musical The Bedwetter, and musicals she did in high school. Then, Destiny stops by to talk about being a student of The Institute. Plus, Scott’s old cat Crenshaw drops by to talk about being on tour with the band 311.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jena Friedman, Heather Anne Campbell, Jacob Wysocki | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600026/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian/writer/author Jena Friedman joins Scott to talk about her new book “Not Funny,” how her senior thesis led her to doing stand-up, and some of the interview questions she’s received as a female comedian. Then, macaroni holer Grance Prebs stops by to talk about the macaroni holing process. Plus, Marty Motorcycle drops by from his great American road trip to talk about searching for his origin.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sean Clements, Hayes Davenport, Will Hines, Christine Bullen | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600027/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sean Clements and Hayes Davenport of Hollywood Handbook join Scott to talk about the big guest for their 500th episode of their podcast, a pitch for a new movie podcast for CBB World, and Star Trek. Then, sober man Kenny Kicks stops by to talk about trying to get ahold of his hooch. Plus, nymph roast comic Fifinella drops by to test out some of her material.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dan Ahdoot, Vic Michaelis, Casey Feigh | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600028/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor and comedian Dan Ahdoot (Cobra Kai) joins Scott to talk about his new book “Undercooked,” his food podcast Green Eggs and Dan, and the original name he picked for his character on Bajillion Dollar Propertie$. Then, small business owner Taylor Stephanie stops by to apologize for a mistake her oil rig business made. Plus, stand-up comedian Weed Foxworthy drops by to tell some jokes.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>14th Anniversary: Jason Mantzoukas, Andy Daly, Paul F. Tompkins, Jessica McKenna, Shaun Diston, Drew Tarver, Lisa Gilroy, Lily Sullivan, Tim Baltz, Carl Tart, Will Hines, Dan Lippert | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600029/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Scott celebrates the 14th Anniversary of Comedy Bang! Bang! with co-host Jason Mantzoukas, and special guests water skier Hot Dog, Fred Guinness of the Guinness Book of World Records, acrobat Dagmar the Small, Rudi North, the Pig Shit Twins, Bicky from the Gym, podiatrist Harry Footman, the President of Domino’s Snake Eyes, Anniversary Man the Demon, NBA legend Bill Walton, and The Chief. Thanks for listening to CBB for all these years!</description></item><item><title>Live At The Bell House #2 w/ Jason Mantzoukas, Paul F. Tompkins, Ego Nwodim, Connor Ratliff | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600030/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Recorded live at the Bell House in Brooklyn, NY, Scott is joined by Jason Mantzoukas, Cal Solomon, Pastor Pasta, and Mr. Books for the second night celebration of the release of Comedy Bang! Bang! The Podcast: The Book.
Visit https://www.comedybangbangworld.com/book/ to get your own copy of Comedy Bang! Bang! The Podcast: The Book!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Live At The Bell House #1 w/ Jason Mantzoukas, Adam Scott, Paul F. Tompkins, Mike Hanford, Griffin Newman | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600031/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Recorded live at the Bell House in Brooklyn, NY, Scott is joined by Jason Mantzoukas, Adam Scott, Big Chunky Bubbles, John Lennon, and Silver Screen Sammy to celebrate the release of Comedy Bang! Bang! The Podcast: The Book. Visit https://www.comedybangbangworld.com/book/ to get your own copy of Comedy Bang! Bang! The Podcast: The Book!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Live at Largo w/ Jason Mantzoukas, Paul F. Tompkins, Andy Daly, Carl Tart, Tim Baltz, Lily Sullivan, Gil Ozeri | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600032/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Recorded live from Largo at the Coronet in Los Angeles, Scott welcomes to the stage Jason Mantzoukas, Drew L. Barrymore, Dalton Wilcox, The Chief, Randy Snutz, Francesca Bolognese, and Dr. Sweetchat the Small Talk Robot to celebrate the release of Comedy Bang! Bang! The Podcast: The Book.
Visit https://www.comedybangbangworld.com/book/ to get your own copy of Comedy Bang! Bang! The Podcast: The Book!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Aunty Donna | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600033/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Broden Kelly, Zachary Ruane, and Mark Bonanno of the Australian absurdist comedy group Aunty Donna return to talk to Scott all about their new world tour “The Magical Dead Cat Tour.” Then, American Jimmy stops by to talk about working at an all-American Diner. Later, Silly Boy drops by to point out silly behavior. Plus, an Australian Dad on a Holiday stops by to talk about his current trip across the country.</description></item><item><title>Jon Gabrus, Dave Theune, Ben Rodgers | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600034/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Intern Gino Lombardo joins Scott to talk about screen testing for a Marvel movie, George Santos, and commercials. Then, attorney Robby Delmuda returns to talk about his permanent old man voice. Plus, Ernest Taylor stops by to talk about his wet nurse services.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Paul F. Tompkins, Drew Tarver, Ryan Gaul | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600035/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wet Day co-creator Paul F. Tompkins joins Scott to chat about Wet Day traditions, the man upstairs, and blue checkmarks. Then, brothers Ike and Spike Minksalmon return to talk about their new musical that involves a granddaughter. Plus, Pudge returns in search of his golden retrievers. Happy Wet Day to all and to all a Wet Night!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>David Wain, Katie Rich, Hannah Pilkes | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600036/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Director/actor/writer David Wain joins Scott once again to talk about his Fruit Loops sponsorship, being in a Freaky Friday situation, and submitting himself to the Guinness Book of World Records. Then, Scott’s mom’s friend Leia stops by to talk about what’s going on back home. Plus, Scott’s neighbor Susan Christmas drops by to talk about how Paris has changed her.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jay Pharaoh, Bobby Moynihan, Tim Baltz | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600037/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600037/</guid><description>Podcast Description SNL alum Jay Pharaoh joins Scott to talk about his new film Spinning Gold, current impressions he’s working on, and his SNL dream cast. Then, Batman returns in search of who murdered his parents. Plus, museum curator Darren Matichek returns to talk about the new bobbleheads at the National Bobblehead Museum and Hall of Fame.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Andy Samberg, Neil Campbell, Lily Sullivan | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600038/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Show favorites Andy Samberg and Neil Campbell join Scott to spread the word about their new Comedy Central animated series Digman! as well as the whole gang from South Park. Then, Sister Margaret drops by to blow up the spot of her &amp;ldquo;bad&amp;rdquo; sisters cheating at their nightly games, and Dirty Dog joins - bark bark - for the one nasty reason of reminding kids to do their homework.</description></item><item><title>Jason Mantzoukas, Andy Daly, Paul F. Tompkins | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600039/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Friend of the show Jason Mantzoukas joins Scott to celebrate the 800th episode of Comedy Bang Bang! Jason and Scott chat about Tron, their paper route jobs, and Grogu parody songs. Then, royal watcher Byron Denniston returns to talk about King Charles III’s upcoming coronation. Plus, Lord Andrew Lloyd Webber returns to talk about writing a song for the coronation.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nick Kroll, Ike Barinholtz, Mitra Jouhari, Gil Ozeri | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600040/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Returning champions Nick Kroll and Ike Barinholtz join Scott to talk about their new Hulu series/four night event History of the World Part II, Tulsa King, and Celebrity Jeopardy. Then, Andi stops by to talk about being an aspiring cosmetologist. Plus, the world’s busiest man Ned Belanela returns to take a couple of important calls.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>David Cross, James Mannion, Holly Laurent, Greg Hess | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600041/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hollywood celebrity David Cross joins Scott to talk about his latest Worst Daddy In The World stand-up tour, Mr. Show, and his joke writing process. Then, firefighter Ryan Headboard stops by to talk about his anti-bullying PSA. Later, manicurist Sherry Pie drops by to talk about brow coaching. Plus, hostage negotiator Jim Bolt stops by to share some hostage negotiation tips.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jason Alexander, Peter Tilden, Shaun Diston, Jessica McKenna | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600042/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jason Alexander and Peter Tilden join Scott to talk about their podcast “Really? No, Really?”, talking dogs, and Pretty Woman. Then, sound guy Tony Nails stops by to talk about the movies he’s worked on. Plus, acting coach Filomena Trappp drops by to talk about the Trappp Method.
Check out Jason and Peter’s podcast Really? No, Really? from iHeartPodcasts here: https://www.iheart.com/podcast/1119-really-no-really-107027693/
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Zach Galifianakis, Edi Patterson, Andy Daly | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600043/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Movie star Zach Galifianakis joins Scott and guest co-host Bean Dip for a special episode of CBB in which Zach auditions for world traveler August Lindt’s pretzel based movie. Plus, August talks about his recent trip to Snake Island.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>John Hodgman, Paul F. Tompkins, Lisa Gilroy | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600044/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Humorist John Hodgman joins Scott to talk about his new musical romantic comedy series Up Here, pancakes vs. waffles, and a terrific moment in Super Bowl history. Then, treasure hunter Brock Lovett returns to talk about a new service he’s advertising. Plus, singer Elvis Presley drops by to talk about where he’s been in the last couple of years.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dan Mangan, Lauren Lapkus, Ryan Rosenberg | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600045/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Musician and returning champion Dan Mangan joins Scott to talk about his new album “Being Somewhere” and perform songs from it. Then, young attractive actor Cabin Fevver stops by to make a big announcement. Later, chiropractor Dr. Crack drops by to talk about having the loudest cracks on the internet. Plus, another exciting edition of Would You Rather!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Reggie Watts, Vic Michaelis, Dave Theune | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600046/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Friend of the show Reggie Watts joins Scott to talk about what he’s up to once the Late Late Show is wrapped, attending SatanCon, and his upcoming book about his high school years. Then, superhero Oopsie Spider-Man stops by to talk about wanting to join the Avengers. Plus, soft drink representative Tam Pasture drops by to introduce new flavors of Coca-Cola.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Paul F. Tompkins, Ego Nwodim, Matt Apodaca | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600047/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Podcast co-host Ted Newguy joins Scott to talk about his false crime podcast Murder Was Wrote, Sesame Street, and waterpark buffets. Then, dancer Stormy Kirkland stops by to talk about being a valet dancer. Plus, concerned citizen Ricky Johnson returns to talk about how he got out of his time loop.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jason Woliner, Lily Sullivan, Will Hines, Casey Feigh | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600048/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Director extraordinaire Jason Woliner (Borat Subsequent Moviefilm) joins Scott to talk about his new docuseries Paul T. Goldman that has been 10 years in the making. Then, cruise ship worker Chippy Dipps stops by to talk about her latest cruise line job. Later, coffee impresario Bill Smither drops by to talk about his special cafe experience. Plus, Joey Salsa stops by to share some exciting news.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Allison Williams, Dan Lippert, Erin Keif | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600049/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actress Allison Williams joins Scott to talk about her new film M3GAN, playing Peter Pan in Peter Pan Live!, and her signature scream. Then, NBA legend Bill Walton returns to talk about his new children’s book. Plus, Macy Hannigan stops by to talk about working as a full-time mannequin at Macy’s.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ben Schwartz, Drew Tarver, Mary Holland | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600050/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Backyard Era is back as Ben Schwartz aka The Elegant Mr. S joins Scott for the first CBB episode of 2023! Ben and Scott chat about Paris, vampire teeth, and Ben playing a bad guy in the upcoming film Renfield. Then, inventor Henry Heimlich returns to talk about his latest invention to prevent choking. Later, crafter Barb Nuts drops by to talk about all the crafts she makes out of mason jars.</description></item><item><title>Best of 2022 Part 4 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600051/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Scott and Paul F. Tompkins talk about flashbacks before finally cracking the final TOP 4 episodes of the Best of Comedy Bang! Bang! 2022 countdown as voted by you listeners. Plus, another round of the Snowman Game!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2022 Part 3 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600052/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600052/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s a special Day After Christmas Edition of CBB as Scott and Paul F. Tompkins continue the Best of Comedy Bang! Bang! 2022 countdown with Part 3! On this episode, Scott and Paul talk about the Federal holiday of Christmas before counting down your choices for episodes eight through five. Tune in Thursday to hear which episodes cracked the Top 4!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2022 Part 2 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600053/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Scott and Paul F. Tompkins put the Part 2 in 2022 as they continue the Best of Comedy Bang! Bang! 2022 countdown. On this episode, Scott and Paul talk about babies before counting down your choices for episodes twelve through nine. Tune in Monday for Part 3!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2022 Part 1 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600054/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Best Of&amp;rsquo;s to you and many hamburgers to all from Comedy Bang! Bang! Join Scott and Paul F. Tompkins as they countdown numbers seventeen through thirteen of the Best CBB episodes of 2022 as voted by YOU listeners. Tune in Thursday for Part 2!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Holiday Spectacular 2022 w/ Paul F. Tompkins, Shaun Diston, Jon Gabrus, Lily Sullivan, Carl Tart, Jessica McKenna, Will Hines, Vic Michaelis, Lisa Gilroy, Gil Ozeri | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600055/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join us for that special time of year when Scott invites friends old and new to celebrate the Comedy Bang! Bang! Holiday Spectacular! Expect appearances from Obi Ron Kenobi, McGruff the Crime Dog, intern Gino Lombardo, social media expert Francesca Bolognese, basketball legend Charles Barkley, pop superstar Harry Styles, and so many more! Happy Holidays from CBB!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kristian Bruun, Paul F. Tompkins, Matt Gourley, Lisa Gilroy | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600056/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor/friend of the show Kristian Bruun joins Scott to talk all about his new show The Recruit. Then, Santa Claus returns to talk about changes being made to Christmas. Later, budding artist Teen Giger stops by to talk about learning how to be an artist again. Plus, mythical creature Peonis Pilates drops by to seek help to save his kind from going extinct.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Max Silvestri, Tim Baltz, Lily Sullivan | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600057/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian extraordinaire Max Silvestri joins Scott to talk about the doors that have opened since his legendary 10 minute stand-up set at a festival in Johnny Carson’s honor, growing up driving near a drive-in movie theater, and his new scripted Audible podcast “Past My Bedtime.” Then, celebrity podiatrist Harry Footman stops by to make a confession. Plus, truck enthusiast Kayla Dickie returns to talk about how her town celebrates Ford Rock Hard Eve.</description></item><item><title>Jason Mantzoukas, Seth Morris, Erin Whitehead | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600058/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600058/</guid><description>Podcast Description CBB fave and How Did This Get Made?’s own Jason Mantzoukas joins Scott once again to talk about Halloween, Oklahoma! the musical, and Buzz Lightyear. Then, Scott’s ex-step father Bob Ducca returns to share BuzzFeed headlines he’s created. Later, housefly Stacy Buzzaba stops by to pitch a remake of The Fly. Plus, the exciting return of Would You Rather!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nick Kroll, John Gemberling, Gil Ozeri | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600059/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Big Mouth creator Nick Kroll joins Scott to talk about Danny Elfman at the Hollywood Bowl, season 6 of Big Mouth, and his latest stand-up special “Nick Kroll: Little Big Boy.” Then, Mutty Brickford stops by to talk about his supernatural conundrum. Plus, the world’s busiest man Ned Belanela drops by to talk about tips and tricks on how to manage your time.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Natalie Morales, Jillian Bell, Griffin Newman, Christine Bullen | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600060/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Powerhouse duo Natalie Morales and Jillian Bell join Scott to talk about their new movie “I’m Totally Fine,” performing sketch comedy together for charity, and compete in a Whitney Houston singing competition. Then, YouTube reviewer CJTETHEMAN9888_UNLIMITED stops by to review YouTube for the first time. Plus, writer Piper Adoggy drops by to talk about her unsold holiday movie scripts.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kurt Braunohler, Mike Hanford, Jacob Wysocki | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600061/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian of note Kurt Braunohler joins Scott and co-host John Lennon for a spoOoky episode of Comedy Bang! Bang! After John catches us up on his recent plan to reboot Stranger Things, Kurt talks about his new special “Perfectly Stupid,” being a dad, and putting up an immersive Halloween themed play. Plus, COOTER the supercomputer stops by to try to make Scott’s life easier.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kevin Nealon, Ryan Rosenberg, Dave Theune | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600062/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian, author, and SNL alum Kevin Nealon joins Scott to talk about his new book “I Exaggerate: My Brushes with Fame,” what parts of his body have been replaced, and tries to have a serious conversation. Then, umpire coach Donald Ump stops by to talk about teaching how to ump. Plus, attorney Robby Delmuda returns to talk about being framed for tax evasion.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sharon Horgan, Paul F Tompkins, Casey Feigh | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600063/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Award winning actor/writer/producer Sharon Horgan (Catastrophe, This Way Up) joins Scott to discuss her new Apple TV+ series Bad Sisters, anecdotes about ear biting, and count down the Top 5 protective flaps. Next, Original Fig stops by to talk about his scratch card maladies and set the record straight about The Hogan Family. Then, Weed Seinfeld drops by the studio to test out some new material.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kyle Bornheimer, Dan Lippert, Erin Keif | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600064/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor/friend of the show Kyle Bornheimer joins Scott to talk about Westworld, playing a stepdad on the new show High School, and the second season of Avenue 5. Then, professor Lloyd Garterbelt stops by to talk about recently being fired. Plus, author Matilda Gravyman drops by to read excerpts from her unauthorized biography about Scott.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dan Wilson, Paul Rust, Christine Bullen, Charlie McCrackin | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600065/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Singer-songwriter Dan Wilson joins Scott to talk about his favorite song he’s ever written, 10 Things I Hate About You, and performs songs off his new EP “Dancing on the Moon.” Then, Cecil Sotheby of Sotheby’s Auction House stops by to share a list of celebrity items that are up for auction. Later, recent widow Myrtle McGee drops by to talk about her previous 17 husbands. Plus, Cordwood Pete Bunyan stops by looking for lumberjack work.</description></item><item><title>Rachel Bloom, James Mannion, Matt Apodaca | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600066/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emmy Award winning actress Rachel Bloom joins Scott to talk about her new audiobook Kiss &amp;amp; Tell, acting in the new Hulu series Reboot, and the St. Elsewhere extended universe. Then, postal worker Chris Orchard stops by to talk about his new relationship. Plus, local grocer Albert Roe returns to talk about Kissy’s Grocery store getting into creating content.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Live from The Paramount Theatre, Austin TX 08/06/022 w/ Paul F. Tompkins, Carl Tart, Dan Lippert | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600067/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600067/</guid><description>Podcast Description A live b-b-b-bonus-s-s-s ep?! From The Paramount Theatre in Austin TX, Scott welcomes to the stage Chesley &amp;ldquo;Sully&amp;rdquo; Sullenberger, M.C. Sugarbutt, and Todd Padre! Visit https://www.comedybangbangworld.com for access to all shows from the CB!B! 13th Anniversary Tour!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jason Mantzoukas, Andy Daly, Paul F. Tompkins | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600068/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Old friend of the show Jason Mantzoukas finally returns in-studio and joins Scott to talk about Top Gun, the Nicole Kidman AMC ad, and why the recent How Did This Get Made? tour was cut short. Then, royal watcher Byron Denniston returns to break news regarding The Queen’s passing. Plus, The Griz also returns to break news about The Queen.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jon Hamm, Lily Sullivan, Devin Field | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600069/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Professional actor Jon Hamm joins Scott to talk about his role in Top Gun: Maverick, his new film Confess, Fletch, and performing in a production of Ordinary People at the University of Missouri. Then, diarist Bridget Jones stops by to read some new entries from her diary. Plus, travel guide Steve Spinx drops by to share some travel tips.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Adam Scott, Matt Besser, Monika Smith, Toni Charline | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600070/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Severance star Adam Scott joins Scott for a pre-Emmys check-in as they talk about the making of Severance, his one-of-a-kind tuxedo, and who he will be inviting to the Emmys. Then, Olaf’s Middle Part from Frozen stops by to talk about separating himself from Olaf. Later, TikTok star Harvey the Truth Seeker drops by to tap into everyone’s mind to find hidden meanings. Plus, Martha the medium stops by to communicate with the afterlife.</description></item><item><title>Bridger Winegar, Paul F. Tompkins, Lamar Woods | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600071/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Writer and podcaster Bridger Winegar joins Scott to talk about the gifts he’s received on his podcast I Said No Gifts!, $25 dollar bills, and his favorite app. Then, manager/producer Sprague the Whisperer returns to make a big announcement. Plus, a young player making moves by the name of Dre Wonka stops by to talk about what he’s owed by the Wonka family.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Silversun Pickups, Will Hines, Matt Apodaca, Ele Woods | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600072/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Silversun Pickups join Scott once again to talk about Prince, dispel Wikipedia rumors, and to perform songs off their latest album “Physical Thrills.” Then, punk rocker Keith Keith returns to promote his new album. Later, Officer Marshal Sergeant stops by to shut down the podcast. Plus, opera singer Maximo Tootie drops by to adapt CBB into an opera.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tatiana Maslany, Paul F. Tompkins, Caitlin Reilly | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600073/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Canadian actress Tatiana Maslany joins Scott to talk about becoming green for the new Disney+ series She-Hulk: Attorney at Law, her favorite scene in Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles II: The Secret of the Ooze, and using The Rock’s alarm clock. Then, American citizen Obi Ron Kenobi stops by to talk about his love of nature. Later, Hollywood starlet Lucy Bukater drops by in search of her birth mother.</description></item><item><title>Bob Odenkirk, James Austin Johnson, Carl Tart | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600074/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Scott’s old Mr. Show buddy Bob Odenkirk returns to talk about Comic Relief 8, the finale of Better Call Saul, and his future focusing on himself. Then, celebrity chef Bobby Flay stops by to talk about his new cooking show. Plus, lawyer Italiano Jones returns to fight for Scott in a mock trial.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Patton Oswalt, Suzi Barrett, Dave Theune, Peter Banifaz | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600075/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian and actor Patton Oswalt joins Scott to talk about his new movie I Love My Dad, skipping apps, and his SNL dream cast. Then, scientist Ellen Norton-Simon Harris-Finley Finister stops by to talk about getting kids jazzed about science. Later, Scott’s new neighbor Dean Hormel drops by to invite everyone to his block party. Plus, musician Johnny Scat visits to talk about the scat community.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Paul F. Tompkins, Lauren Lapkus, Mary Holland | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600076/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fellow Threedom co-hosts Paul F. Tompkins and Lauren Lapkus join Scott to talk about simping, The Weeknd, and musical instruments. Then, local reporter Haney Dilf stops by to talk about her recent car accident. Later, Carmine DeLonge arrives to show off his special skill. Plus, fencing instructor Jarles whose trapped in the Earwolf Studios stops by for another #classicjarles appearance!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>13th Anniversary: Dan Lippert, Stars, Paul F. Tompkins, Lily Sullivan, Tim Baltz, Ego Nwodim, Shaun Diston, Will Hines | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600077/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Scott celebrates the 13th Anniversary of Comedy Bang! Bang! with co-host Bill Walton, music by the band Stars, fan favorites, plus newcomers! Special guests dropping by include visual artist Big Chunky Bubbles, social media expert Francesca Bolognese, Richie Castlebaum, Pastor Pasta, Garry the Gardener, and punk rocker Keith Stanley. Thanks for listening to CBB for all these years!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jason Mantzoukas, Andy Daly, Paul F. Tompkins | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600078/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jason Mantzoukas joins Scott once again to talk about the Carolverse, West Side Story, and Thin Lizzy. Then, royal watcher Byron Denniston returns to talk about the plans for The Queen’s Platinum Jubilee. Plus, The Griz returns to challenge Byron to a duel. Who will be victorious? Tune in to find out!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2021 Part 4 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600079/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600079/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s finally time for Scott and Paul F. Tompkins to countdown the TOP 3 EPISODES of the Best of Comedy Bang! Bang! 2021 as voted by YOU listeners. Plus, the climactic conclusion of the Snowman Game!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2021 Part 3 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600080/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Scott and Paul F. Tompkins continue the Best of Comedy Bang! Bang! 2021 as they go countdown numbers seven through four of the Best CBB episodes of this year as voted by YOU listeners. Tune in Thursday for Part 4 to hear which episodes make the Top 3!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2021 Part 2 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600081/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600081/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Best of Comedy Bang! Bang! 2021 countdown continues as Scott and Paul F. Tompkins countdown numbers eleven through eight of the Best CBB episodes of this year as voted by YOU listeners. Tune in next week for Part 3!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2021 Part 1 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600082/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Holidays from Comedy Bang! Bang! Join Scott and Paul F. Tompkins as they countdown numbers fifteen through twelve of the Best CBB episodes of 2021 as voted by YOU listeners. Tune in Thursday for Part 2!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>12th Anniversary: Jason Mantzoukas, Manchester Orchestra, Andy Daly, Paul F. Tompkins, Jessica McKenna, Tim Baltz, Lily Sullivan, Shaun Diston, Jon Gabrus, Carl Tart, Dan Lippert, Ego Nwodim | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600083/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Scott celebrates the 12th Anniversary of Comedy Bang! Bang! with co-host Jason Mantzoukas, music by Manchester Orchestra, fan favorites, plus newcomers! Special guests dropping by include Byron Denniston, The Griz, Margery Kershaw, Randy Snutz &amp;amp; off-and-on girlfriend Carissa, Sprague the Whisperer, intern Gino Lombardo, Charles Barkley, Rabbi Bill Walton, and Charlotte Hornette. Thanks for listening to CBB for all these years!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2020 Part 4 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600084/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy New Year from Comedy Bang! Bang! Scott and Paul F. Tompkins continue the Best of CBB 2020 countdown as they countdown the final FOUR episodes as voted by YOU listeners. Keep smiling!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2020 Part 3 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600085/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600085/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Best of 2020 Comedy Bang! Bang! countdown continues as Scott and Paul F. Tompkins countdown numbers eight through five of the Best CBB episodes of 2020 as voted by YOU listeners. Tune in Thursday for Part 4 to hear which episodes made it to the top!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2020 Part 2 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600086/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Merry Christmas Eve from Comedy Bang! Bang! Join Scott and Paul F. Tompkins as they countdown numbers twelve through nine of the Best CBB episodes of 2020 as voted by YOU listeners. Tune in next week for Part 3 and keep smiling!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2020 Part 1 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600087/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Holidays from Comedy Bang! Bang! Join Scott and Paul F. Tompkins as they countdown numbers sixteen through thirteen of the Best CBB episodes of 2020 as voted by YOU listeners. Tune in Thursday for Part 2!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Comedy Bang! Bang! Presents: We Have To Stop Talking TMNT on CBB | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600088/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to We Have to Stop Talking TMNT on CBB. This podcast is a comprehensive and encyclopedic compendium of all things Turtles. On their debut episode, Sprague the Whisperer and Scott discuss the first Teenage Mutant Ninja movie. To hear them break down every TMNT movie, subscribe to Patreon.com/ShaunDiston!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2019 Pt.4 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600089/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy New Year from Comedy Bang! Bang! Scott and Paul F. Tompkins continue the Best of CBB 2019 countdown as they countdown the final FOUR episodes as voted by YOU listeners.
This episode is brought to you by Dashlane.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2019 Pt.3 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600090/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Scott and Paul F. Tompkins continue the Best of CBB 2019 countdown as they countdown numbers eight through five as voted by YOU listeners. Tune in Thursday for Part 4!
This episode is brought to you by Star Wars Jedi: Fallen Order and Dashlane.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2019 Pt.2 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600091/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Holidays (and Boxing Day) from Comedy Bang! Bang! Join Scott and Paul F. Tompkins as they countdown numbers eleven through ninth of the Best CBB episodes of 2019 as well as the number one LIVE episode as voted by YOU listeners. Tune in next week for Part 3!
This episode is brought to you by Star Wars Jedi: Fallen Order.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2019 Pt.1 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600092/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Holidays from Comedy Bang! Bang! Join Scott and Paul F. Tompkins as they countdown numbers fifteen through twelve of the Best CBB episodes of 2019 as voted by YOU listeners. Tune in Thursday for Part 2!
This episode is brought to you by Squarespace (www.squarespace.com/BANGBANG), Dashlane (www.dashalen.com/bangbang), and Audible.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>10th Anniversary Part 2 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600093/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Scott Aukerman celebrates the 10th Anniversary of Comedy Bang! Bang! by implementing a true open door policy and welcomes fan favorite guests of the show over the last 10 years!
Part Two Featuring:
Thomas Middleditch
Adam Scott
Chelsea Peretti
Nick Kroll
Drew Tarver
&amp;ldquo;Weird Al&amp;rdquo; Yankovic
Paul Rust Neil Campbell
Bobby Moynihan
Mary Holland
Horatio Sanz
Ben Schwartz
Jon Daly
Shaun Diston
Mike Hanford
Will Hines
Brendon Small</description></item><item><title>10th Anniversary Part 1 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600094/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Scott Aukerman celebrates the 10th Anniversary of Comedy Bang! Bang! by implementing a true open door policy and welcomes fan favorite guests of the show over the last 10 years!
Part One Featuring:
Jason Mantzoukas
Andy Daly
Paul F. Tompkins
Seth Morris
Jon Hamm
Lauren Lapkus
Jessica McKenna
Zach Reino
Jon Gabrus
Ego Nwodim
Zeke Nicholson
Carl Tart
Rob Huebel
Thomas Lennon
Matt Besser
Paul Scheer
Tawny Newsome</description></item><item><title>Best of 2018 Pt. 4 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600095/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Scott and Paul F. Tompkins have arrived to the final part of the Best of Comedy Bang! Bang! 2018 countdown with numbers three, two, and one as voted by YOU. Happy New Year!
This episode is brought to you by Squarespace (www.squarespace.com code: BANGBANG) and Hotel Tonight.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2018 Pt. 3 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600096/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Celebrate New Year’s Eve with Scott and Paul F. Tompkins as they continue to countdown the Best of Comedy Bang! Bang! 2018 episodes with numbers six through four. See you next year!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2018 Pt. 2 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600097/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Dec 2018 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Scott and Paul F. Tompkins continue the Best of 2018 Comedy Bang! Bang! countdown with numbers ten through seven. You’re welcome!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2018 Pt. 1 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600098/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2018 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600098/</guid><description>Podcast Description This Christmas Eve Scott and Paul F. Tompkins give you the gift of the Comedy Bang! Bang! Best of Countdown! Join them as they countdown numbers fourteen through eleven of the Best CBB episodes of 2018 as voted by YOU listeners. Tune in Thursday for Part 2!
This episode is brought to you by Squarespace (www.squarespace.com/BANGBANG), Leesa (www.leesa.com/bangbang code: BANGBANG), and Roman (www.getroman.com/BANGBANG).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2017 Pt. 4 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600099/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2018 08:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Scott and Paul F. Tompkins conclude the Best of Comedy Bang! Bang! 2017 as voted by YOU listeners with numbers four through one on the countdown!
This episode is brought to you by Squarespace and Legal Zoom.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2017 Pt. 3 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600100/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy New Year! Scott and Paul F. Tompkins continue the Best of Comedy Bang! Bang! 2017 countdown with numbers eight through five as voted by YOU listeners. Stay tuned for Part 4!
This episode is brought to you by Squarespace (www.squarespace.com code: BANGBANG) and Leesa (www.leesa.com/BANGBANG).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2017 Pt. 2 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600101/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Scott and Paul F. Tompkins continue the Best of Comedy Bang! Bang! 2017 countdown with numbers twelve through nine as voted by YOU listeners. Stay tuned for Part 3!
This episode is brought to you by Audible.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2017 Pt. 1 - Nagada: A Star Wars Story | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600102/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600102/</guid><description>Podcast Description This Christmas Scott and Paul F. Tompkins give you the gift of the Comedy Bang! Bang! Best of Countdown! Join them as they countdown numbers sixteen through thirteen of the Best CBB episodes of 2017 as voted by YOU listeners. Plus, Scott and PFT sing a very special Christmas song!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2016 Pt. 4 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600103/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 08:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Finally, the conclusion of the Best of Comedy Bang! Bang! 2016 countdown with special co-host Paul F. Tompkins is here with your Top 3 episodes of the entire year and your number 1 on the Best of CBB Live 2016. Thanks for listening and Happy New Year!This episode is brought to you by Thursday Boots ( www.thursdayboots.com/bangbang ).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2016 Pt. 3 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600104/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2016 08:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Scott and Paul F. Tompkins continue counting down The Best of Comedy Bang! Bang! 2016 episodes as they go through numbers seven through four on the count down as well as number two on the Best CBB Live episode of 2016 as voted by YOU. You’re welcome!This episode is brought to you by Squarespace ( www.squarespace.com code: BANGBANG), Blue Apron ( www.blueapron.com/CBB ), and Leesa.com ( www.leesa.com/BANGBANG ).</description></item><item><title>Best of 2016 Pt. 2 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600105/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 08:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600105/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Best of Comedy Bang! Bang! 2016 count down continues as Scott and Paul F. Tompkins go through numbers eleven through eight on the count down as well as number three on the Best CBB Live episodes of 2016 as voted by YOU. Plus, a special Christmas surprise for all you precious listeners!This episode is brought to you by HUAWEI (www.huawei.fit/comedybangbang) and Leesa.com (www.leesa.com/BANGBANG).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2016 Pt. 1 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600106/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2016 08:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Another year, another special Comedy Bang! Bang! Best of Countdown with Scott and Paul F. Tompkins. Scott and PFT countdown numbers fifteen through twelve of the Best CBB episodes of 2016 and number four of the Best CBB Live episodes of 2016 as voted by YOU listeners. Stay tuned for Pt. 2!This episode is brought to you by Huawei ( www.huawei.fit/comedybangbang ) and Leesa.com ( www.leesa.com/bangbang ).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2015 Pt. 4 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600107/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2015 08:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600107/</guid><description>Podcast Description At long last, the conclusion of the Best of Comedy Bang! Bang! 2015 countdown with special co-host Paul F. Tompkins is here with your Top 3 episodes of the entire year. Thanks for listening and Happy New Year!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2015 Pt. 3 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600108/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2015 08:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600108/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Best of Comedy Bang! Bang! 2015 countdown continues with Scott and special co-host Paul F. Tompkins as they go through numbers six, five, and four on the list of the best episodes YOU voted for. Please enjoy and we will see you on New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve for the final installment!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2015 Pt. 2 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600109/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2015 08:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600109/</guid><description>Podcast Description The best of Comedy Bang! Bang! 2015 continues with Scott and Paul F. Tompkins as they count down numbers ten through seven of the best episodes YOU voted for! Merry Christmas to you all and we&amp;rsquo;ll see you next week for Pt. 3!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2015 Pt. 1 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600110/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 08:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600110/</guid><description>Podcast Description As we say farewell to another year of Comedy Bang! Bang! we look back at some of the favorite moments of 2015. Joining Scott is Paul F. Tompkins of SPONTANEANATION to countdown numbers fourteen through eleven of the Best CBB episodes of 2015 as voted by YOU the listener. Stay tuned for Pt. 2 dropping on Christmas Eve!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Harris Wittels, Chelsea Peretti, Adam Scott | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600111/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 07:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600111/</guid><description>Podcast Description 4 years ago, maybe the greatest recording in Earwolf history took place. Now, the Farts and Procreation crew aka Harris Wittels, Chelsea Peretti, and Adam Scott return for the fourth time to attempt to recreate the magic. Creak, slam, sit, and chill with the Farts &amp;amp; Pro crew as we hear some gems during Harris’ Foam Corner, an incredible charac from Chelsea, and the hard work (e-mails) that went into making this episode a reality.</description></item><item><title>Best of 2014 Pt 4 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600112/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 07:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600112/</guid><description>Podcast Description The exciting conclusion of the Comedy Bang! Bang! best of 2014 countdown with Paul F. Tompkins is here with numbers three to one of the best CBB eps that YOU have chosen! Happy New Year!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2014 Pt 3 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600113/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2014 08:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600113/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s getting real close to the end with part three of the Comedy Bang! Bang! best of countdown as Scott and special guest Paul F. Tompkins get into the meat of the matter and count down numbers seven through four. Sit tight and look out for the final installment!This episode is sponsored by Squarespace, Audible , and Casper Mattresses . Use offer code BANGBANG at checkout for some great savings!</description></item><item><title>Best of 2014 Pt 2 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600114/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2014 06:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Merry Christmas to you all! The best of Comedy Bang! Bang! countdown 2014 continues with Scott and special guest Paul F. Tompkins as they count down numbers eleven through eight of the best episodes YOU voted for! Come back Monday for Pt 3!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2014 Pt 1 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600115/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2014 08:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Say bye bye to another year but say hello hello to the new year with the best of 2014 episode of Comedy Bang! Bang! One of our faves, Paul F. Tompkins joins Scott to countdown numbers fifteen through twelve of the best CBB eps of 2014 that YOU voted for. Stay tuned for Pt 2 dropping on Christmas day!This episode is sponsored by Club W , and Bonobos .</description></item><item><title>Taran Killam, Paul Brittain | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600116/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedy buds Taran Killam and Paul Brittain are back to chat about how to take compliments, if older people should be driving old cars, and why aren&amp;rsquo;t birds shitting on us all the time. Later, Bever Hopox and Chico Hands aka the Calvins twins gallop into the studio to discuss the ostentatious, hypervacious, dualicacious world of prized horse fighting. It&amp;rsquo;s a flip flopping good time!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2013 Pt 4 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600117/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2014 08:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600117/</guid><description>Podcast Description And now the exciting conclusion to the best of 2013 countdown with special guest Paul F. Tompkins. What will be the number one episode of 2013? You&amp;rsquo;ll have to tune in to find out!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2013 Pt 3 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600118/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2013 08:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600118/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s getting real close to the end with part three of the Comedy Bang! Bang! best of countdown as Scott and special guest Paul F. Tompkins count down numbers six through four as well as some b-b-b-bonus-s-s-s clips. Sit tight and look out for the final installment!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2013 Pt 2 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600119/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2013 08:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600119/</guid><description>Podcast Description The best of Comedy Bang! Bang! countdown continues with Scott and special guest Paul F. Tompkins as they go count down numbers eleven through seven of the best episodes YOU voted for along with additional b-b-b-bonus-s-s-s clips. Much love!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2013 Pt 1 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600120/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2013 08:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600120/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alas, we say farewell to another year but never fear because the best of 2013 episode of Comedy Bang! Bang! is here! There were sooo many good episodes this year that we had to step up the countdown to the next level. Making a rare appearance is special guest Paul F. Tompkins who helps Scott countdown numbers fifteen through twelve of the listener selected episodes of the year and some very special b-b-b-bonus-s-s-s clips.</description></item><item><title>Adam Scott, Harris Wittels, Chelsea Peretti | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600121/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2013 07:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600121/</guid><description>Podcast Description 2 years ago, a momentous recording occurred in the Earwolf studios. Now, all the participants have returned once more to recreate the magic. You asked for it and it’s finally happening, Adam Scott, Harris Wittels, and Chelsea Peretti are here for the Farts &amp;amp; Pro threequel! You won’t believe the amazing characs that they got for us this time around. Creak, slam, sit and be mesmerized by the Farts Crew!</description></item><item><title>Best of 2012 Pt 2 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600122/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2012 08:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600122/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wait no longer as the conclusion of the Comedy Bang Bang Best of 2012 is here! We’re counting down the top five episodes as chosen by the listeners and of course more special b-b-b-bonus clips. Join Scott Aukerman and Paul F. Tompkins to see which episodes went head to head for the number one spot and we’ll see you in 2013!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2012 Pt 1 | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600123/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2012 08:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600123/</guid><description>Podcast Description Another year has flown by, so what better way to celebrate than to revisit some of the best Comedy Bang Bang moments that YOU voted for! Special guest Paul F. Tompkins makes a rare appearance as he helps Scott Aukerman countdown numbers ten through six of the listener selected episodes of the year and some very special b-b-b-bonus clips. Stay tuned for Pt 2 to see which episodes made it to the top of the list!</description></item><item><title>Adam Scott, Harris Wittels, Chelsea Peretti | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600124/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2012 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last year, an episode of Comedy Bang Bang was made that, to put it simply, changed the world. Nearly a year later, can the magic be replicated? We&amp;rsquo;ve brought back Harris Wittels, Adam Scott, and Chelsea Peretti, and they&amp;rsquo;re here for more songs, characters, foam, two-man shows, life advice, and plugs! Is the world ready to be changed again? It better be!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Paul Scheer,Nick Swardson,Brody Stevens | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600125/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600125/</guid><description>Podcast Description How many ingredients are in pizza? Can you high five an orangutan? What does the moon do when we&amp;rsquo;re not looking? The answers to these questions and more can be found in today&amp;rsquo;s Comedy Bang Bang! Nick Swardson finally found his way back to the studio and is joined by two first time guests: Comedian Brody Stevens and Nic Cage stand-in (and brother) Bob Cage. They guess the misheard lyrics, get on their soap boxes, and ponder &amp;ldquo;Would You Rather?</description></item><item><title>Adam Scott,Harris Wittels,Chelsea Peretti | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600126/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2011 07:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600126/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week&amp;rsquo;s episode of Comedy Bang Bang is devoted to all the Parks and Recreation fans in the audience. We&amp;rsquo;ve jam packed the show with Parks and Rec insiders from Chelsea Peretti to Harris Wittels and even Adam Scott! If you like the unique cast of crazies that Pawnee offers, you&amp;rsquo;ll love hearing Chelsea Peretti&amp;rsquo;s brand new characters. Maybe you watch the show for the compelling relationships: Prepare for the deep, meaningful, fascinating relationship between Jack and his brother-in-law Bryan from Carl&amp;rsquo;s Lumber Yard.</description></item><item><title>Natasha Leggero,Harris Wittels,Matt Besser | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600127/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Creak! Slam! Sit down for some Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast! This week&amp;rsquo;s episode has everything you love about the show; the music of Phish and pussy jokes! Natasha Leggero, Harris Wittels, and Harris&amp;rsquo; protege King Henry VI are our guests, along with Natasha and Harris&amp;rsquo; new characters Maude and Jack. Death-Ray fans know Jimmy Stewart to be dismissive, but we&amp;rsquo;ve unearthed some footage that proves that he&amp;rsquo;s also winning.</description></item><item><title>Thomas Lennon, Rob Huebel | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600128/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600128/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast! As is to be expected, the first few episodes are where the show finds its footings, and that it does! Rob Huebel from TV&amp;rsquo;s “Human Giant”, Tom Lennon from TV&amp;rsquo;s “The State”, and Doug Benson from TV&amp;rsquo;s “Last Comic Standing” make Scott&amp;rsquo;s first episode an immediate hit. Hear some music from today&amp;rsquo;s hottest comedy musicians, have your twitter questions answered, and hear an abbreviated version of Doug Loves Movies on this episode.</description></item><item><title>Find Full Archive of Comedy Bang! Bang! on Stitcher Premium | Comedy Bang Bang: The Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7415600129/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2009 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7415600129/</guid><description>Podcast Description Find Full Archive of Comedy Bang! Bang! on Stitcher Premium
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>