<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>KILL TONY on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/kill-tony/</link><description>Recent content in KILL TONY on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 18:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/kill-tony/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>#640 - STAVROS HALKIAS | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stavros Halkias, Kam Patterson, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, William Montgomery, Jon Deas, Matthew Muehling, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Kino Loasis, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 12/04/2023
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
ZIPPIXTOOTHPICKS.COM – CODE: “KILLTONY10” FOR 10% OFF ORDER! — Get $15 off a Skylight Calendar at https://SkylightCal.com/TONY — Support the show by going to https://www.hellofresh.com/ktshowfree and using code KTSHOWFREE — Support the show and download the Gametime app.</description></item><item><title>#639 - TIM DILLON | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tim Dillon, Kam Patterson, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, William Montgomery, Jon Deas, Matthew Muehling, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Kino Loasis, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 11/27/2023
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
ZIPPIXTOOTHPICKS.COM – CODE: “KILLTONY10” FOR 10% OFF ORDER! — Support the show and get 20% off and free shipping at https://www.manscaped.com and use code killtony — Get 50% off of Factor &amp;amp; support the show at https://www.</description></item><item><title>#638- GREG FITZSIMMONS + DAVE SMITH | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Greg Fitzsimmons, Dave Smith, Kam Patterson, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, William Montgomery, Jon Deas, Matthew Muehling, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Kino Loasis, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 11/20/2023
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
Support the show by going to https://www.hellofresh.com/ktshowfree and using code KTSHOWFREE
Support the show and get 10% Off with the code TONY at https://www.TheFreezepipe.com
Get $15 off a Skylight Calendar at https://SkylightCal.</description></item><item><title>#637 - STEVEO + ADRIENNE IAPALUCCI | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290004/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290004/</guid><description>Podcast Description STEVEO, Adrienne Iapalucci, Kam Patterson, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, William Montgomery, Jon Deas, Matthew Muehling, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Kino Loasis, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 11/13/2023
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
Get 20% off your first monthly box when you sign up at https://bespokepost.com/KILLTONY
Support the show by going to https://www.hellofresh.com/ktshowfree and using code KTSHOWFREE
Support the show &amp;amp; get $80 off your first month of therapy at https://www.</description></item><item><title>#636 - RON WHITE + PAULY SHORE | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ron White, Pauly Shore, Kam Patterson, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, William Montgomery, Jon Deas, Matthew Muehling, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Kino Loasis, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 11/06/2023
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
Get $15 off a Skylight Calendar at&amp;nbsp;https://SkylightCal.com/TONYSupport the show by going to&amp;nbsp;https://www.hellofresh.com/ktshowfree
and using code KTSHOWFREE
Support the show and download the Gametime app. Save $20 off your 1st purchase with the code KILLTONY</description></item><item><title>#635 - DUNCAN TRUSSELL + LIL' HOBO | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Duncan Trussell, Lil' Hobo, Kam Patterson, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, William Montgomery, Jon Deas, Matthew Muehling, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Kino Loasis, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 10/30/2023
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
Get 50% off of Factor &amp;amp; support the show at https://www.factormeals.com/KILLTONY50 &amp;amp; use code KILLTONY50
—
Support the show and download the Gametime app. Save $20 off your 1st purchase with the code KILLTONY</description></item><item><title>#634 - YANNIS PAPPAS + RYAN SICKLER + MIKE FEENEY | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290007/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yannis Pappas, Ryan Sickler, Mike Feeney, Kam Patterson, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, William Montgomery, Jon Deas, Matthew Muehling, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 10/23/2023
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
Get 50% off of Factor &amp;amp; support the show at https://www.factormeals.com/KILLTONY50 &amp;amp; use code KILLTONY50
—
Support the show &amp;amp; get $80 off your first month of therapy at https://www.</description></item><item><title>#633 - KAM PATTERSON + DAVID JOLLY | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kam Patterson, David Jolly, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, William Montgomery, Jon Deas, Matthew Muehling, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 10/02/2023
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
Don’t miss out on all the action this week at DraftKings!&amp;nbsp; Download the DraftKings app today! Sign-up using&amp;nbsp;https://dkng.co/killtony&amp;nbsp;or through our promo code KILLTONY
Support the show and get 20% off your order at&amp;nbsp;https://www.liquidiv.com&amp;nbsp;with code TONY</description></item><item><title>#632 - SUGA SEAN O'MALLEY + JOE LIST | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290009/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Suga Sean O'Malley, Joe List, Kam Patterson, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, William Montgomery, Jon Deas, Matthew Muehling, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 09/25/2023
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
Support the show and get 50% off of Hello Fresh plus free shipping by going to https://www.hellofresh.com/50KTshow and using code 50KTshow
Support the show and get 10% Off with the code TONY at https://www.</description></item><item><title>#631 - KIM CONGDON + JAMAR NEIGHBOORS | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jamar Neighbors, Kim Congdon, Kam Patterson, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, William Montgomery, Jon Deas, Matthew Muehling, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 09/18/2023
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
Support the show &amp;amp; secure your online data at https://www.expressvpn.com/killtony
Try Zip Recruiter for free by going to www.ziprecruiter.com/killtony
Get 50% off of Factor &amp;amp; support the show at https://www.factormeals.com/KILLTONY50 &amp;amp; use code KILLTONY50</description></item><item><title>#630 - DR. PHIL (ADAM RAY) + SAM TALLENT | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290011/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Phil (Adam Ray), Sam Tallent, Kam Patterson, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, William Montgomery, Jon Deas, Matthew Muehling, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 09/11/2023
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
KACHAVA – Nutrient-Rich Superfoods – 10% OFF FIRST ORDER – https://www.kachava.com/collections/kill-tony-podcast
—
HELLOFRESH.COM – Go to HELLOFRESH.COM/50KTSHOW and GET 50% off, plus free shipping!
—
ZIPPIXTOOTHPICKS.COM – CODE: “KILLTONY10” FOR 10% OFF ORDER!</description></item><item><title>#629 - RIC FLAIR - SHANE GILLIS - ARI SHAFFIR - MARK NORMAND - LUIS J GOMEZ - ZAC AMICO | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ric Flair, Shane Gillis, Ari Shaffir,&amp;nbsp;Mark Normand, Luis J Gomez, Zac Amico, Kam Patterson, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, William Montgomery, Jon Deas, Matthew Muehling, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 09/04/2023
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
DRAFTKINGS! – Download the DRAFTKINGS app, new users create an account, and use code KILLTONY. Bet $5 and get $200 worth of bonus bets instantly.</description></item><item><title>#628 - H. FOLEY + KEVIN RYAN | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290013/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290013/</guid><description>Podcast Description H. Foley, Kevin Ryan, Jessie Johnson, Kam Patterson, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, William Montgomery, Jon Deas, Matthew Muehling, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 08/21/2023
&amp;nbsp;--
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
DRAFTKINGS! – Download the DRAFTKINGS app, new users create an account, and use code KILLTONY. Bet $5 and get $200 worth of bonus bets instantly. Terms apply. Again, create an account and redeem code KILLTONY.</description></item><item><title>#627 - ROSEANNE + DAVID KOECHNER | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Roseanne, David Koechner, Kam Patterson, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, William Montgomery, Jon Deas, Matthew Muehling, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 08/21/2023
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
DRAFTKINGS! – Download the DRAFTKINGS app, new users create an account, and use code KILLTONY. Bet $5 and get $200 worth of bonus bets instantly. Terms apply. Again, create an account and redeem code KILLTONY.</description></item><item><title>#626 - JOE DEROSA + DAVID LUCAS | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joe DeRosa, David Lucas, Kam Patterson, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, William Montgomery, Jon Deas, Matthew Muehling, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 08/14/2023
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
DRAFTKINGS! – Download the DRAFTKINGS app, new users create an account, and use code KILLTONY. Bet $5 and get $200 worth of bonus bets instantly. Terms apply. Again, create an account and redeem code KILLTONY.</description></item><item><title>#625 - POST MALONE + JOE ROGAN + KURT METZGER | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Post Malone, Joe Rogan, Kurt Metzger, Kam Patterson, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, William Montgomery, Jon Deas, Matthew Muehling, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 08/07/2023
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
GAMETIME! – Download the Gametime app, create an account, and use code KILLTONY for $20 off your first purchase. Terms apply. Again, create an account and redeem code KILLTONY for $20 off.</description></item><item><title>#624 - THAI RIVERA | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Thai Rivera, Kam Patterson, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, William Montgomery, Jon Deas, Matthew Muehling, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 07/30/2023
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
ZIPRECRUITER.COM&amp;nbsp;– TRY IT FOR FREE AT&amp;nbsp;ZIPRECRUITER.COM/KILLTONY
—
GAMETIME! – Download the Gametime app, create an account, and use code KILLTONY for $20 off your first purchase. Terms apply. Again, create an account and redeem code KILLTONY for $20 off.</description></item><item><title>#623 - BRIAN MOSES + MATTHEW BROUSSARD | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290018/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brian Moses, Matthew Broussard, Kam Patterson, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, William Montgomery, Jon Deas, Matthew Muehling, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 07/24/2023
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
MANSCAPED.COM – USE COUPON CODE “KILLTONY” – GET 20% OFF + FREE SHIPPING – VISIT MANSCAPED.COM
—
HELLOFRESH.COM – Go to HELLOFRESH.COM/50KTSHOW and GET 50% off, plus free shipping!</description></item><item><title>#622 - JIM NORTON | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jim Norton, Kam Patterson, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, William Montgomery, Jon Deas, Matthew Muehling, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 07/17/2023
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
LIQUID-IV.COM&amp;nbsp;-GET 25% OFF ANY ORDER WITH PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT:&amp;nbsp;LIQUID-IV.COM
—
EXPRESSVPN.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 3 FREE MONTHS BY GOING TO:&amp;nbsp;EXPRESSVPN.COM/KILLTONY
—
FACTOR! – Head to FACTORMEALS.COM/KILLTONY50 and use code “killtony50” to get 50% off your first box.</description></item><item><title>#621 - DON BARRIS | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Don Barris, Kam Patterson, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, William Montgomery, Jon Deas, Matthew Muehling, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 07/10/2023
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
ZIPRECRUITER.COM&amp;nbsp;– TRY IT FOR FREE AT&amp;nbsp;ZIPRECRUITER.COM/KILLTONY
—
HELLOFRESH.COM – Go to HELLOFRESH.COM/TONY16 and use code “tony50” for 50% off, plus free shipping!
—
CONZURI – On top of 30% off the site, our listeners get an extra exclusive 15% Off Discount at conzuri.</description></item><item><title>#620 - RICH VOS - ADAM RAY | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rich Vos, Adam Ray, Kam Patterson, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, William Montgomery, Jon Deas, Matthew Muehling, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 07/03/2023
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
GAMETIME! – Download the Gametime app, create an account, and use code KILLTONY for $20 off your first purchase. Terms apply. Again, create an account and redeem code KILLTONY for $20 off.</description></item><item><title>#619 - ARI SHAFFIR | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ari Shaffir, Kam Patterson, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, William Montgomery, Jon Deas, Matthew Muehling, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 06/26/2023
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
FACTOR! - Head to FACTORMEALS.COM/KILLTONY50 and use code "killtony50" to get 50% off your first box.--BOX OF AWESOME! - From style and grooming goods, tobarware, cooking tools, and outdoor gear, Box of Awesome hascollections for every part of your life.</description></item><item><title>#618 - TREVOR WALLACE + BRIAN SIMPSON | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trevor Wallace, Brian Simpson, Kam Patterson, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, David Lucas, William Montgomery, Jon Deas, Matthew Muehling, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 06/19/2023
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
EXPRESSVPN.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 3 FREE MONTHS BY GOING TO:&amp;nbsp;EXPRESSVPN.COM/KILLTONY
—
HELLOFRESH.COM – Go to HELLOFRESH.COM/TONY16 and use code “tony16” for 16 free meals plus free shipping!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#617 - ALI SIDDIQ | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290024/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ali Siddiq, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, David Lucas, William Montgomery, Jon Deas, Matthew Muehling, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban - &amp;nbsp;06/12/2023
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#616 - JOE ROGAN + TOM SEGURA [10 YEAR ANNIVERSARY] | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joe Rogan, Tom Segura, Theo Von, Ron White, Brian Holtzman, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, David Lucas, William Montgomery, Jon Deas, Matthew Muehling, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 06/10/2023
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
LIQUID-IV.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 25% OFF ANY ORDER WITH PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT:&amp;nbsp;LIQUID-IV.COM
—
ZIPRECRUITER.COM&amp;nbsp;– TRY IT FOR FREE AT&amp;nbsp;ZIPRECRUITER.COM/KILLTONY&amp;nbsp;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#615 - THEO VON | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290026/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Theo Von, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, David Lucas, William Montgomery, Jon Deas, Matthew Muehling, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 05/29/2023
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
HELLOFRESH.COM – Go to HELLOFRESH.COM/TONY16 and use code “tony16” for 16 free meals plus free shipping!
—
FIRSTLEAF – Sign up at FIRSTLEAF.COM/KILLTONY to get your first SIX bottles of wine for under $8 a bottle.</description></item><item><title>#614 - DAVE ATTELL + JEFF ROSS | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290027/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dave Attell, Jeff Ross, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, David Lucas, William Montgomery, Jon Deas, Matthew Muehling, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 05/29/2023
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
FACTOR! – Head to FACTORMEALS.COM/KILLTONY50 and use code “killtony50” to get 50% off your first box.
—
BOX OF AWESOME! – From style and grooming goods, to
barware, cooking tools, and outdoor gear, Box of Awesome has</description></item><item><title>#613 - ELEANOR KERRIGAN | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290028/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eleanor Kerrigan, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, David Lucas, William Montgomery, Jon Deas, Matthew Muehling, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 05/23/2023
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
EXPRESSVPN.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 3 FREE MONTHS BY GOING TO:&amp;nbsp;EXPRESSVPN.COM/KILLTONY
—
MANSCAPED.COM – USE COUPON CODE “TONY” – GET 20% OFF + FREE SHIPPING – VISIT&amp;nbsp;MANSCAPED.COM
—
HELLOFRESH.COM – Go to HELLOFRESH.COM/TONY16 and use code “tony16” for 16 free meals plus free shipping!</description></item><item><title>#612 - DOUG STANHOPE | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290029/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Doug Stanhope, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, David Lucas, William Montgomery, John Deas, Matthew Muehling, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 05/15/2023
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
ZIPRECRUITER.COM&amp;nbsp;– TRY IT FOR FREE AT&amp;nbsp;ZIPRECRUITER.COM/KILLTONY
—
GAMETIME! – Download the Gametime app at Gametime.co, create an account, and use code KILLTONY for $20 off your first purchase. Terms apply. Again, create an account and redeem code KILLTONY for $20 off.</description></item><item><title>#611 - BRIAN HOLTZMAN + IAN EDWARDS | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290030/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brian Holtzman, Ian Edwards, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, David Lucas, William Montgomery, John Deas, Matthew Muehling, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 05/08/2023
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
LIQUID-IV.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 25% OFF ANY ORDER WITH PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT:&amp;nbsp;LIQUID-IV.COM
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#610 - PAULY SHORE + ERIK GRIFFIN | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290031/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pauly Shore, Erik Griffin, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, David Lucas, William Montgomery, John Deas, Matthew Muehling, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 05/01/2023
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
FACTOR! – Head to FACTORMEALS.COM/KILLTONY50 and use code “killtony50” to get 50% off your first box.—BOX OF AWESOME! – From style and grooming goods, tobarware, cooking tools, and outdoor gear, Box of Awesome hascollections for every part of your life.</description></item><item><title>#609 - IAN FIDANCE + JOY HINCHCLIFFE | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290032/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ian Fidance, Joy Hinchcliffe, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, David Lucas, William Montgomery, John Deas, Matthew Muehling, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 04/24/2023
SPONSORED BY:
HELLOFRESH.COM – Go to HELLOFRESH.COM/TONY16 and use code “tony16” for 16 free meals plus free shipping!
—
ZIPRECRUITER.COM – TRY IT FOR FREE AT ZIPRECRUITER.COM/KILLTONY
—
GAMETIME! – Download the Gametime app at Gametime.</description></item><item><title>#608 - ADAM RAY | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290033/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adam Ray, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, David Lucas, William Montgomery, John Deas, Matthew Muehling, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 04/13/2023
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
HELLOFRESH.COM – Go to HELLOFRESH.COM/TONY16 and use code “tony16” for 16 free meals plus free shipping!
—
SKYLIGHTFRAME.COM – GET $15 OFF YOUR PURCHASE OF A SKY LIGHT FRAME BY USING THE PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT SKYLIGHTFRAME.</description></item><item><title>#607 - SAM TALLENT | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290034/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Tallent, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, David Lucas, William Montgomery, John Deas, Matthew Muehling, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 04/10/2023
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
BOX OF AWESOME! – From style and grooming goods, to
barware, cooking tools, and outdoor gear, Box of Awesome has
collections for every part of your life. – Get 20% off your first monthly box when you sign up</description></item><item><title>#606 - ARI SHAFFIR + BIG JAY OAKERSON | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290035/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Big Jay Oakerson, Ari Shaffir, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, David Lucas, William Montgomery, John Deas, Matthew Muehling, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 04/03/2023
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
LIQUID-IV.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 25% OFF ANY ORDER WITH PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT:&amp;nbsp;LIQUID-IV.COM
—
TALKSPACE! – As a listener of this podcast, you’ll get $100 off of your first month with Talkspace.</description></item><item><title>#605 - KEVIN RYAN + H FOLEY + YANNIS PAPPAS | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290036/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kevin Ryan, H. Foley, Yannis Pappas, Jeremiah Watkins, Joel Jiminez, Jessie Johnson, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, David Lucas, William Montgomery, John Deas, Matthew Muehling, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 03/27/2023
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
MANSCAPED.COM – USE COUPON CODE “TONY” – GET 20% OFF + FREE SHIPPING – VISIT&amp;nbsp;MANSCAPED.COM.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#604 - RON WHITE | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290037/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ron White, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, David Lucas, William Montgomery, John Deas, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 03/20/2023
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
EXPRESSVPN.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 3 FREE MONTHS BY GOING TO:&amp;nbsp;EXPRESSVPN.COM/KILLTONY
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#603 - SHANE GILLIS | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290038/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shane Gillis, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, David Lucas, William Montgomery, John Deas, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 03/19/2023
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
ZIPRECRUITER.COM&amp;nbsp;– TRY IT FOR FREE AT&amp;nbsp;ZIPRECRUITER.COM/KILLTONY
—
FACTOR! – Head to&amp;nbsp;FACTORMEALS.COM/KILLTONY50&amp;nbsp;and use code “killtony50” to get 50% off your first box.
—
GAMETIME! – Download the Gametime app at GAMETIME.CO, create an account, and use code KILLTONY for $20 off your first purchase.</description></item><item><title>#602 - BERT KREISCHER + WHITNEY CUMMINGS + JIM NORTON | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290039/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bert Kreischer, Whitney Cummings, Jim Norton, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, David Lucas, William Montgomery, John Deas, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 03/13/2023
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
LIQUID-IV.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 25% OFF ANY ORDER WITH PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT:&amp;nbsp;LIQUID-IV.COM
—
TALKSPACE! – As a listener of this podcast, you’ll get $100 off of your first month with Talkspace.</description></item><item><title>#601 - TIM DILLON + ROSEANNE | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290040/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tim Dillon, Roseanne Barr, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, David Lucas, William Montgomery, John Deas, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 03/03/2023
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
ZIPRECRUITER.COM&amp;nbsp;– TRY IT FOR FREE AT&amp;nbsp;ZIPRECRUITER.COM/KILLTONY
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#600 - CHRIS DISTEFANO | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290041/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris Distefano, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, David Lucas, William Montgomery, John Deas, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 02/27/2023
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
EXPRESSVPN.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 3 FREE MONTHS BY GOING TO:&amp;nbsp;EXPRESSVPN.COM/KILLTONY
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#599 - ROSEANNE | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290042/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Roseanne Barr, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, David Lucas, William Montgomery, John Deas, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 02/19/2023
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
ZIPRECRUITER.COM&amp;nbsp;– TRY IT FOR FREE AT&amp;nbsp;ZIPRECRUITER.COM/KILLTONY
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#598 - BRIAN MOSES + THAI RIVERA | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290043/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brian Moses, Thai Rivera, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, David Lucas, William Montgomery, John Deas, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 02/12/2023
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
LIQUID-IV.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 25% OFF ANY ORDER WITH PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT:&amp;nbsp;LIQUID-IV.COM
—
TALKSPACE! – As a listener of this podcast, you’ll get $100 off of your first month with Talkspace. To match with a licensed therapist today, go to Talkspace.</description></item><item><title>#597 - JIM FLORENTINE + PUNKIE JOHNSON + EDDIE PEPITONE | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290044/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jim Florentine, Punkie Johnson, Eddie Pepitone, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, David Lucas, William Montgomery, John Deas, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 02/06/2023
FACTOR! – Head to FACTORMEALS.COM/KILLTONY50 and use code
“killtony50” to get 50% off your first box.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#596 - ALI MACOFSKY | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290045/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ali Macofsky, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, David Lucas, William Montgomery, John Deas, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 01/23/2023
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
ZIPRECRUITER.COM&amp;nbsp;– TRY IT FOR FREE AT&amp;nbsp;ZIPRECRUITER.COM/KILLTONY
—
EXPRESSVPN.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 3 FREE MONTHS BY GOING TO:&amp;nbsp;EXPRESSVPN.COM/KILLTONY
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#595 - TOM PAPA | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290046/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tom Papa, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, David Lucas, William Montgomery, John Deas, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 01/23/2023
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#594 - ADAM RAY + JOE DEROSA | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290047/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adam Ray, Joe Derosa, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, David Lucas, William Montgomery, John Deas, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 01/16/2023
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
BOX OF AWESOME! – From style and grooming goods, to
barware, cooking tools, and outdoor gear, Box of Awesome has
collections for every part of your life. – Get 20% off your first monthly box when you sign up</description></item><item><title>#593 - ANDREW SANTINO + IAN EDWARDS + KIM CONGDON + SARAH WEINSHENK | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290048/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andrew Santino, Ian Edwards, Kim Congdon, Sarah Weinshenk, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, David Lucas, William Montgomery, John Deas, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 01/09/2023
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
LIQUID-IV.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 25% OFF ANY ORDER WITH PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT:&amp;nbsp;LIQUID-IV.COM
—
TALKSPACE! – As a listener of this podcast, you’ll get $100 off of your first month with Talkspace.</description></item><item><title>#592 - JOE ROGAN + JESSIE JOHNSON | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290049/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joe Rogan, Jessie Johnson, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, David Lucas, William Montgomery, John Deas, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 01/02/2023
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
HELLOFRESH.COM – Go to&amp;nbsp;HELLOFRESH.COM/TONY22&amp;nbsp;and use code “tony22” for 22 free meals plus free shipping!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#591 - DAVID &amp; LUNA LUCAS | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290050/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290050/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Lucas, Luna Lucas, John Deas, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 12/26/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
EXPRESSVPN.COM – GET 3 FREE MONTHS BY GOING TO: EXPRESSVPN.COM/KILLTONY
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#590 - ADAM EGET | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290051/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adam Eget, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, William Montgomery, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 12/12/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
LIQUID-IV.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 25% OFF ANY ORDER WITH PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT:&amp;nbsp;LIQUID-IV.COM
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#589 - RON WHITE | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290052/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ron White, Michael Lehrer. Paul Deemer, D Madness, David Lucas, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, William Montgomery, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 12/12/2022
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#588 - BRIAN SIMPSON | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290053/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brian Simpson, Paul Deemer, D Madness, David Lucas, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, William Montgomery, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 12/05/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
SKYLIGHTFRAME.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET $15 OFF YOUR PURCHASE OF A SKY LIGHT FRAME BY USING THE PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT&amp;nbsp;SKYLIGHTFRAME.COM
—
BOX OF AWESOME! – From style and grooming goods, to
barware, cooking tools, and outdoor gear, Box of Awesome has</description></item><item><title>KT #587 - KURT METZGER | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290054/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kurt Metzger, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, William Montgomery, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 11/21/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
LIQUID-IV.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 25% OFF ANY ORDER WITH PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT:&amp;nbsp;LIQUID-IV.COM
Transcript</description></item><item><title>KT #586 - DEADMAU5 + GEORGE PEREZ | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290055/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290055/</guid><description>Podcast Description DEADMAU5, George Perez, Michael Lehrer, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, William Montgomery, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 11/14/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
SKYLIGHTFRAME.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET $15 OFF YOUR PURCHASE OF A SKY LIGHT FRAME BY USING THE PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT&amp;nbsp;SKYLIGHTFRAME.COM
Transcript</description></item><item><title>KT #585 - TOM SEGURA | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290056/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tom Segura, Steve-O, Michael Lehrer, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, William Montgomery, David Lucas, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 11/14/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
SKYLIGHTFRAME.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET $10 OFF YOUR PURCHASE OF A SKY LIGHT FRAME BY USING THE PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT&amp;nbsp;SKYLIGHTFRAME.COM
Transcript</description></item><item><title>KT #584 - RYAN LONG + CHRIS FAGA | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290057/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ryan Long, Chris Faga, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Hans Kim, William Montgomery, David Lucas, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 11/07/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
EXPRESSVPN.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 3 FREE MONTHS BY GOING TO:&amp;nbsp;EXPRESSVPN.COM/KILLTONY
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#583 - TIM DILLON | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290058/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 06:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tim Dillon, John Deas, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, David Lucas, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 10/31/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
BOX OF AWESOME! – From style and grooming goods, to
barware, cooking tools, and outdoor gear, Box of Awesome has
collections for every part of your life. – Get 20% off your first monthly box when you sign up</description></item><item><title>#582 - [SKANKFEST VEGAS] - BIG JAY OAKERSON + LUIS J GOMEZ + DAVE SMITH | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290059/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Big Jay Oakerson, Luis J Gomez, Dave Smith, Kim Congdon, Ali Macofsky, Hans Kim, William Montgomery, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 10/16/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
LIQUID-IV.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 25% OFF ANY ORDER WITH PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT:&amp;nbsp;LIQUID-IV.COM
—
Kimpton Hotel Van Zandt – Save on Sunday and Monday nights when you stay at Hotel Van Zandt using this link:&amp;nbsp;CLICK HERE!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#581 - [SKANKFEST VEGAS] DAVE ATTELL + IAN FIDANCE + ERIK GRIFFIN | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290060/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dave Attell, Ian Fidance, Erik Griffin, Ari Shaffir, Sara Weinshenk, Hans Kim, William Montgomery, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 10/16/2022
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#580 - DERIC POSTON + EHSAN AHMAD | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290061/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Deric Poston, Ehsan Ahmad, John Deas, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 10/10/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
LIQUID-IV.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 25% OFF ANY ORDER WITH PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT:&amp;nbsp;LIQUID-IV.COM
—
Kimpton Hotel Van Zandt – Save on Sunday and Monday nights when you stay at Hotel Van Zandt using this link:&amp;nbsp;CLICK HERE!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#579 - HANS KIM + WILLIAM MONTGOMERY + DAVID LUCAS | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290062/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290062/</guid><description>Podcast Description William Montgomery, David Lucas, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 10/03/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
BOX OF AWESOME! – From style and grooming goods, to
barware, cooking tools, and outdoor gear, Box of Awesome has
collections for every part of your life. – Get 20% off your first monthly box when you sign up</description></item><item><title>#578 - DAVE ATTELL + GREG FITZSIMMONS + IAN FIDANCE | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290063/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 08:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dave Attell, Greg Fitzsimmons, Ian Fidance, Nick Swardson, Dr. Drew Pinsky, William Montgomery, David Lucas, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 09/26/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
Kimpton Hotel Van Zandt - Save on Sunday and Monday nights when you stay at Hotel Van Zandt using this link. CLICK HERE!</description></item><item><title>#577 - DUNCAN TRUSSELL | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290064/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Duncan Trussell, William Montgomery, David Lucas, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, Paul Deemer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Joe White, Kristie Nova, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 09/19/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
LIQUID-IV.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 25% OFF ANY ORDER WITH PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT:&amp;nbsp;LIQUID-IV.COM
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#576 - JOSH WOLF + MIKE FEENEY | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290065/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Josh Wolf, Mike Feeney, William Montgomery, David Lucas, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 09/12/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
BOX OF AWESOME! – From style and grooming goods, to
barware, cooking tools, and outdoor gear, Box of Awesome has
collections for every part of your life. – Get 20% off your first monthly box when you sign up</description></item><item><title>#575 - RON WHITE + BRIAN SIMPSON + RYAN LONG | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290066/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ron White, Brian Simpson, Ryan Long, William Montgomery, David Lucas, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 09/05/2022
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#574 - JOE ROGAN + SHANE GILLIS + MARK NORMAND + ARI SHAFFIR | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290067/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 21:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joe Rogan, Shane Gillis, Ari Shaffir, Mark Normand, William Montgomery, David Lucas, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 08/29/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
EXPRESSVPN.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 3 FREE MONTHS BY GOING TO:&amp;nbsp;EXPRESSVPN.COM/KILLTONY
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#573 - JOE ROGAN | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290068/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 20:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joe Rogan, William Montgomery, David Lucas, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 08/15/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
ZIPRECRUITER.COM&amp;nbsp;– TRY IT FOR FREE AT&amp;nbsp;ZIPRECRUITER.COM/KILLTONY
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#572 - IAN FIDANCE + THAI RIVERA | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290069/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ian Fidance, Thai Rivera, William Montgomery, David Lucas, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 08/15/2022
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#571 - JEFF ROSS | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290070/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 21:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff Ross, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 08/08/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
BOX OF AWESOME! – From style and grooming goods, to
barware, cooking tools, and outdoor gear, Box of Awesome has
collections for every part of your life. – Get 20% off your first monthly box when you sign up</description></item><item><title>#570 - ANNIE LEDERMAN | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290071/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 23:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Annie Lederman, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 08/01/2022
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#569 - THEO VON | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290072/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 21:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Theo Von, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 07/25/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
TALKSPACE! – As a listener of this podcast, you’ll get $100 off of your first month with Talkspace. To match with a licensed therapist today, go to Talkspace.com. Make sure to use the code TONY ​to ​get $100 off of your first month​ and show your support for the show.</description></item><item><title>#568 - ERIK GRIFFIN | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290073/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 01:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Erik Griffin, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 07/18/2022
&amp;ndash;THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
Dr. Squatch! – New Dr. Squatch customers will receive 20% off $20 spend or more with code “DSQKILLTONY” HERE – https://bit.ly/3B3KDj9
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#567 - MARY LYNN RAJSKUB | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290074/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 17:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mary Lynn Rajskub, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 07/11/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
BOX OF AWESOME! – From style and grooming goods, to
barware, cooking tools, and outdoor gear, Box of Awesome has
collections for every part of your life. – Get 20% off your first monthly box when you sign up</description></item><item><title>#566- LUIS J GOMEZ + AARON BERG | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290075/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 20:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Luis J Gomez, Aaron Berg, William Montgomery, David Lucas, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 07/04/2022
&amp;ndash;THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
TALKSPACE! – As a listener of this podcast, you’ll get $100 off of your first month with Talkspace. To match with a licensed therapist today, go to Talkspace.com. Make sure to use the code TONY ​to ​get $100 off of your first month​ and show your support for the show.</description></item><item><title>#565 - SHANE GILLIS + MARK NORMAND | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290076/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 19:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shane Gillis, Mark Normand, Michael Lehrer, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni,, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 06/19/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
LIQUID-IV.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 25% OFF ANY ORDER WITH PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT:&amp;nbsp;LIQUID-IV.COM
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#564 - THE MONTGOMERY'S | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290077/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 21:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Larry Montgomery, Francis Montgomery, William Montgomery, Ellis Arch, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Joe White, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 06/12/2022
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#563 - PAULY SHORE | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290078/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 14:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pauly Shore, William Montgomery, Ellis Arch, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Joe White, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 06/06/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
TALKSPACE! – As a listener of this podcast, you’ll get $100 off of your first month with Talkspace. To match with a licensed therapist today, go to Talkspace.com. Make sure to use the code TONY ​to ​get $100 off of your first month​ and show your support for the show.</description></item><item><title>#562 - FAHIM ANWAR | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290079/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 21:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fahim Anwar, William Montgomery, Michael Lehrer, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Joe White, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 05/30/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
BOXOFAWESOME.COM and enter the code “KILLTONY” at checkout.
Fahim Anwar: Hat Trick (Live At The Comedy Store) - Full Special&amp;nbsp;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#561 - ARI SHAFFIR + CHRIS DISTEFANO | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290080/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 21:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ari Shaffir, Chris DiStefano, William Montgomery, Michael Lehrer, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Joe White, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 05/23/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
LIQUID-IV.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 25% OFF ANY ORDER WITH PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT:&amp;nbsp;LIQUID-IV.COM
—
ZIPRECRUITER.COM&amp;nbsp;– TRY IT FOR FREE AT&amp;nbsp;ZIPRECRUITER.COM/KILLTONY
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#560 - DERIC POSTON | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290081/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Deric Poston, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Joe White, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 05/16/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
LIQUID-IV.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 25% OFF ANY ORDER WITH PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT:&amp;nbsp;LIQUID-IV.COM
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#559 - GARY CLARK JR | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290082/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 15:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gary Clark Jr, William Montgomery, Eliis Aych, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Joe White, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 05/09/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
LIQUID-IV.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 25% OFF ANY ORDER WITH PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT:&amp;nbsp;LIQUID-IV.COM
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#558 - DUNCAN TRUSSELL + DOUG STANHOPE + MICHAEL YO | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290083/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Duncan Trussell, Doug Stanhope, Michael Yo, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Joe White, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 05/02/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
LIQUID-IV.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 25% OFF ANY ORDER WITH PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT:&amp;nbsp;LIQUID-IV.COM
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#557 - H. FOLEY + KEVIN RYAN | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290084/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 20:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290084/</guid><description>Podcast Description H. Foley, Kevin Ryan, Michael Lehrer, David Lucas, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Joe White, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 04/25/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
BOX OF AWESOME! – From style and grooming goods, to
barware, cooking tools, and outdoor gear, Box of Awesome has
collections for every part of your life. – Get 20% off your first monthly box when you sign up</description></item><item><title>#556 - JAKE SHIELDS + BRIAN SIMPSON | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290085/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jake Shields, Brian Simpson, Michael Lehrer, Eliis Aych, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Joe White, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 04/18/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
EXPRESSVPN.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 3 FREE MONTHS BY GOING TO:&amp;nbsp;EXPRESSVPN.COM/KILLTONY&amp;nbsp;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#555 - RACHEL WOLFSON + MAT EDGAR | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290086/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 19:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rachel Wolfson, Mat Edgar, Ellis Aych, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Joe White, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 04/11/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
LIQUID-IV.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 25% OFF ANY ORDER WITH PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT:&amp;nbsp;LIQUID-IV.COM
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#554 - MONTY FRANKLIN | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290087/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 19:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Monty Franklin, Ellis Aych, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Joe White, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 03/21/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
SKYLIGHTFRAME.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET $10 OFF YOUR PURCHASE OF A SKY LIGHT FRAME BY USING THE PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT&amp;nbsp;SKYLIGHTFRAME.COM
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#553 - JESSIE JOHNSON | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290088/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 21:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jessie Johnson, David Lucas, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Joe White, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 03/16/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
BOX OF AWESOME! – From style and grooming goods, to
barware, cooking tools, and outdoor gear, Box of Awesome has
collections for every part of your life. – Get 20% off your first monthly box when you sign up</description></item><item><title>#552 - PUNKIE JOHNSON + DICEY | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290089/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 20:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Punkie Johnson, Dicey, David Lucas, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Joe White, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 03/15/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
LIQUID-IV.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 25% OFF ANY ORDER WITH PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT:&amp;nbsp;LIQUID-IV.COM
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#551 - JOSH BARNETT | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290090/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 23:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Josh Barnett, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Joe White, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 03/28/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
LIQUID-IV.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 25% OFF ANY ORDER WITH PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT:&amp;nbsp;LIQUID-IV.COM
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#550 - RICH VOS + WILLIE HUNTER | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290091/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 22:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rich Vos, Willie Hunter, William Montgomery, Ellis Aych, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Joe White, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 03/14/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
Created by and starring Jak Knight, Langston Kerman, Sam Jay and Chris Redd, Bust Down is
inspired by the crew’s real-life chemistry, conversations, and friendship. The result is an
irreverent, offbeat, unpredictable swirl of hijinks and absurdity.</description></item><item><title>#549 - TOM PAPA | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290092/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 00:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tom Papa, William Montgomery, Ellis Aych, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Joe White, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 03/07/2022. –THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
ZIPRECRUITER.COM – TRY IT FOR FREE AT ZIPRECRUITER.COM/KILLTONY
—
LIQUID-IV.COM – GET 25% OFF ANY ORDER WITH PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT: LIQUID-IV.COM
—
Created by and starring Jak Knight, Langston Kerman, Sam Jay and Chris Redd, Bust Down is</description></item><item><title>#548 - JOE ROGAN + FREDDIE GIBBS + BRIAN MOSES | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290093/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 17:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joe Rogan, Freddie Gibbs, Brian Moses, William Montgomery, Ellis Aych, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Joe White, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 02/28/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
BOX OF AWESOME! – From style and grooming goods, to
barware, cooking tools, and outdoor gear, Box of Awesome has
collections for every part of your life. – Get 20% off your first monthly box when you sign up</description></item><item><title>#547 - BRENDON WALSH + MATT FULCHIRON | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290094/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 23:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brendon Walsh, Matt Fulchiron, William Montgomery, David Lucas, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Joe White, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 02/21/2022
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#546 - RON WHITE | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290095/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 21:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ron White, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Joe White, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 02/14/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
LIQUID-IV.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 25% OFF ANY ORDER WITH PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT:&amp;nbsp;LIQUID-IV.COM
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#545 - AKAASH SINGH | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290096/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 20:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Akaash Singh, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, Ellis Aych, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 02/07/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
FITBOD! – Kick the new year off right, and get started on your customized fitness plan from Fitbod!
-Get 25% off a membership when you sign up now at Fitbod.me/KILL
—
BOX OF AWESOME!! Get 20% off your first monthly box when you sign up at BOXOFAWESOME.</description></item><item><title>#544 - DAVE SMITH | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290097/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 20:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dave Smith, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, Ellis Aych, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 01/31/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
DRAFT KINGS! – Download the DraftKings Sportsbook app now, use promo code KILLTONY, and&amp;nbsp;get FIFTY SIX TO ONE ODDS on any NFL team. Bet just FIVE DOLLARS and win&amp;nbsp;TWO HUNDRED EIGHTY IN FREE BETS if your team wins.</description></item><item><title>#543 - TONY HINCHCLIFFE + BRIAN REDBAN | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290098/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 20:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290098/</guid><description>Podcast Description William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, Ellis Aych, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 01/24/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
LIQUID-IV.COM – GET 25% OFF ANY ORDER WITH PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT: LIQUID-IV.COM
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#542 - DANNY BROWN + JPEGMAFIA | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290099/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 21:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Danny Brown, JPEGMAFIA, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, Ellis Aych, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 01/17/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
ZIPRECRUITER.COM&amp;nbsp;– TRY IT FOR FREE AT&amp;nbsp;ZIPRECRUITER.COM/KILLTONY
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#541 - BENJI AFLALO | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290100/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 21:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Benji Aflalo, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, David Lucas, John Deas, William Montgomery, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 01/10/2022
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
FITBOD! – Kick the new year off right, and get started on your customized fitness plan from Fitbod!
-Get 25% off a membership when you sign up now at Fitbod.me/KILL
—
DRAFT KINGS! – Download the DraftKings Sportsbook app now, use promo code KILLTONY, and</description></item><item><title>#540 - EHSAN AHMAD | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290101/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 21:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ehsan Ahmad, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, William Montgomery, &amp;nbsp;John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 01/03/2020
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
EXPRESSVPN.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 3 FREE MONTHS BY GOING TO:&amp;nbsp;EXPRESSVPN.COM/KILLTONY
—
DRAFT KINGS! – Download the DraftKings Sportsbook app now, use promo code KILLTONY, and
get FIFTY SIX TO ONE ODDS on any NFL team. Bet just FIVE DOLLARS and win</description></item><item><title>#539 - RYAN J EBELT | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290102/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 21:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ryan J Ebelt, David Lucas, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 12/27/2021
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
BOX OF AWESOME!! Get 20% off your first monthly box when you sign up at BOXOFAWESOME.COM and enter the code “killtony” at checkout.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#538 - DAVID LUCAS | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290103/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 19:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290103/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Lucas, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, John Deas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 12/20/2021
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
LIQUID-IV.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 25% OFF ANY ORDER WITH PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT:&amp;nbsp;LIQUID-IV.COM
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#537 - DYLAN SULLIVAN | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290104/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 21:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dylan Sullivan, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, David Lucas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, John Deas, Jules Durel, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 12/13/2021
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
LIQUID-IV.COM – GET 25% OFF ANY ORDER WITH PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT: LIQUID-IV.COM
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#536 - WILLIAM MONTGOMERY | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290105/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 18:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290105/</guid><description>Podcast Description William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, Michael Lehrer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 12/06/2021
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
Visit&amp;nbsp;GETROMAN.COM/TONY&amp;nbsp;and if approved, you’ll get fifteen dollars off your first order of ED treatment.
—
MacGruber is back! Based on the iconic Saturday Night Live sketch and cult classic movie, the Peacock Original series stars Will Forte, Kristin Wiig, Ryan Philippe, Sam Elliott, Laurence Fishburne and Billy Zane.</description></item><item><title>#535 - HANS KIM | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290106/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 21:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hans Kim, William Montgomery, Matthew Muehling, Michael Lehrer, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 11/29/2021
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
EXPRESSVPN.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 3 FREE MONTHS BY GOING TO:&amp;nbsp;EXPRESSVPN.COM/KILLTONY
—
LIQUID-IV.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 25% OFF ANY ORDER WITH PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT:&amp;nbsp;LIQUID-IV.COM
—
SKYLIGHTFRAME.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET $10 OFF YOUR PURCHASE OF A SKY LIGHT FRAME BY USING THE PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT&amp;nbsp;SKYLIGHTFRAME.COM
—
Mack Weldon – For 20% off your first order, visit&amp;nbsp;WWW.</description></item><item><title>#534 - CHRIS TELLEZ | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290107/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 23:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris Tellez, William Montgomery, Matthew Muehling, Michael Lehrer, Hans Kim, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 11/22/2021
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
Go to&amp;nbsp;3CHI.COM&amp;nbsp;to shop for Delta 8 edibles, vapes,
tinctures, gummies, and oils that can be used to make your own homemade
edibles. Use code “KILLTONY” at checkout to receive 5% off your order
● Must be 21 to purchase</description></item><item><title>#533 - ARIELLE ISAAC NORMAN | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290108/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 00:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Arielle Isaac Norman, William Montgomery, Matthew Muehling, David Lucas, Hans Kim, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 11/15/2021
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
Visit&amp;nbsp;GETROMAN.COM/TONY&amp;nbsp;and if approved, you’ll get fifteen dollars off your first order of ED treatment.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#532 - RON WHITE | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290109/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 22:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ron White, William Montgomery, Matthew Muehling, Hans Kim, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 11/08/2021
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
Mack Weldon – For 20% off your first order, visit&amp;nbsp;WWW.MACKWELDON.COM/TONY&amp;nbsp;and promo code “TONY” for 20% off! Mack Weldon — get it right this holiday season.
—
Go to&amp;nbsp;3CHI.COM&amp;nbsp;to shop for Delta 8 edibles, vapes,
tinctures, gummies, and oils that can be used to make your own homemade</description></item><item><title>#531 - KIM CONGDON + SARA WEINSHENK | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290110/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 16:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kim Congdon, Sara Weinshenk , William Montgomery, Matthew Muehling, Hans Kim, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 11/01/2021
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
SKYLIGHTFRAME.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET $10 OFF YOUR PURCHASE OF A SKY LIGHT FRAME BY USING THE PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT&amp;nbsp;SKYLIGHTFRAME.COM
—
ZIPRECRUITER.COM&amp;nbsp;– TRY IT FOR FREE AT&amp;nbsp;ZIPRECRUITER.COM/KILLTONY
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#530 - JUSTIN MARTINDALE | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290111/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Justin Martindale, William Montgomery, Matthew Muehling, Hans Kim, David Lucas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 10/11/2021
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
Visit&amp;nbsp;GETROMAN.COM/TONY&amp;nbsp;and if approved, you’ll get fifteen dollars off your first order of ED treatment.
—
LIQUID-IV.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 25% OFF ANY ORDER WITH PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT:&amp;nbsp;LIQUID-IV.COM
—
Go to&amp;nbsp;3CHI.COM&amp;nbsp;to shop for Delta 8 edibles, vapes,
tinctures, gummies, and oils that can be used to make your own homemade</description></item><item><title>#529 - WILLIAM MONTGOMERY | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290112/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 15:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290112/</guid><description>Podcast Description William Montgomery, Matthew Muehling, Hans Kim, David Lucas, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 10/11/2021
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY: ZIPRECRUITER.COM – TRY IT FOR FREE AT ZIPRECRUITER.COM/KILLTONY
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#528 - HANS KIM | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290113/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 21:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hans Kim, William Montgomery, Matthew Muehling, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Jules Durel, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 10/11/2021
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
LIQUID-IV.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 25% OFF ANY ORDER WITH PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT:&amp;nbsp;LIQUID-IV.COM
—
Go to&amp;nbsp;3CHI.COM&amp;nbsp;to shop for Delta 8 edibles, vapes,
tinctures, gummies, and oils that can be used to make your own homemade
edibles. Use code “KILLTONY” at checkout to receive 5% off your order</description></item><item><title>#527 - JAMAR NEIGHBORS + BRIAN MOSES | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290114/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 22:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brian Moses, Jamar Neighbors, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 10/04/2021
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
Visit&amp;nbsp;GETROMAN.COM/TONY&amp;nbsp;and if approved, you’ll get fifteen dollars off your first order of ED treatment.
—
ZIPRECRUITER.COM&amp;nbsp;– TRY IT FOR FREE AT&amp;nbsp;ZIPRECRUITER.COM/KILLTONY
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#526 - JOE ROGAN + BERT KREISCHER + DOM IRERRA | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290115/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 18:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joe Rogan, Bert Kreischer, Dom Irerra, David Lucas, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 09/27/2021
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
EXPRESSVPN.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 3 FREE MONTHS BY GOING TO:&amp;nbsp;EXPRESSVPN.COM/KILLTONY
—
Go to&amp;nbsp;3CHI.COM&amp;nbsp;to shop for Delta 8 edibles, vapes,
tinctures, gummies, and oils that can be used to make your own homemade
edibles. Use code “KILLTONY” at checkout to receive 5% off your order</description></item><item><title>#525 - SHANE GILLIS + MITCH BURROW | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290116/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 20:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shane Gillis, Mitch Burrow, William Montgomery, David Lucas, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Yoni, Jule, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 09/13/2021
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
Get life insurance! Especially term coverage, which is surprisingly affordable. Why not pay a bit each month to protect the ones you love? If you’re asking yourself this question: choose Ladder. GO TO&amp;nbsp;LADDERLIFE.COM/TONY.
—
ZIPRECRUITER.COM&amp;nbsp;– TRY IT FOR FREE AT&amp;nbsp;ZIPRECRUITER.</description></item><item><title>#524 - KYLE DUNNIGAN + KURT METZGER | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290117/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 22:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kyle Dunnigan, Kurt Metzger, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 09/13/2021
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
Visit&amp;nbsp;GETROMAN.COM/TONY&amp;nbsp;and if approved, you’ll get fifteen dollars off your first order of ED treatment.
—
Go to&amp;nbsp;3CHI.COM&amp;nbsp;to shop for Delta 8 edibles, vapes,
tinctures, gummies, and oils that can be used to make your own homemade
edibles. Use code “KILLTONY” at checkout to receive 5% off your order</description></item><item><title>#523- ALEX JONES | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290118/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 23:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290118/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alex Jones, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Davis Lucas, Matthew Muehling, D Madness, Michael A. Gonzales, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 09/06/2021
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
ZIPRECRUITER.COM&amp;nbsp;– TRY IT FOR FREE AT&amp;nbsp;ZIPRECRUITER.COM/KILLTONY
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#522 - CHRISTINA PAZSITZKY | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290119/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 23:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Christina Pazsitzky, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Davis Lucas, Matthew Muehling, Michael A. Gonzales, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 08/30/2021
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
LIQUID-IV.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 25% OFF ANY ORDER WITH PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT:&amp;nbsp;LIQUID-IV.COM
—
Go to&amp;nbsp;3CHI.COM&amp;nbsp;to shop for Delta 8 edibles, vapes,
tinctures, gummies, and oils that can be used to make your own homemade
edibles. Use code “KILLTONY” at checkout to receive 5% off your order</description></item><item><title>#521 - JOE ROGAN + ELEANOR KERRIGAN | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290120/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 01:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290120/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joe Rogan, Eleanor Kerrigan, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Matthew Muehling, Michael Lehrer, Michael A. Gonzales, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 08/23/2021
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
Visit&amp;nbsp;GETROMAN.COM/TONY&amp;nbsp;and if approved, you’ll get fifteen dollars off your first order of ED treatment.
—
ZIPRECRUITER.COM&amp;nbsp;– TRY IT FOR FREE AT&amp;nbsp;ZIPRECRUITER.COM/KILLTONY
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#520 - JIMMY SHUBERT | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290121/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jimmy Shubert, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Michael Lehrer, Matthew Muehling, Michael A. Gonzales, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 08/16/2021
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
Get life insurance! Especially term coverage, which is surprisingly affordable. Why not pay a bit each month to protect the ones you love? If you’re asking yourself this question: choose Ladder. GO TO&amp;nbsp;LADDERLIFE.COM/TONY.
—
Super Speciosa! Try Kratom and get 20% off your entire order – go to&amp;nbsp;GetSuperLeaf.</description></item><item><title>#519 - BRIAN HOLTZMAN | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290122/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 00:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290122/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brian Holtzman, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, David Lucas, Matthew Muehling, Michael A. Gonzales, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 08/09/2021
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
Visit&amp;nbsp;GETROMAN.COM/TONY&amp;nbsp;and if approved, you’ll get fifteen dollars off your first order of ED treatment.
—
ZIPRECRUITER.COM&amp;nbsp;– TRY IT FOR FREE AT&amp;nbsp;ZIPRECRUITER.COM/KILLTONY
—
LIQUID-IV.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 25% OFF ANY ORDER WITH PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT:&amp;nbsp;LIQUID-IV.COM
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#518 - MICHAEL LEHRER | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290123/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 00:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290123/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michael Lehrer, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, David Lucas, Matthew Muehling, Michael A. Gonzales, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 08/02/2021
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
Visit&amp;nbsp;GETROMAN.COM/TONY&amp;nbsp;and if approved, you’ll get fifteen dollars off your first order of ED treatment.
—
Super Speciosa! Try Kratom and get 20% off your entire order – go to&amp;nbsp;GetSuperLeaf.com/tony
and use promo code TONY for 20% off your entire order
—
Go to&amp;nbsp;3CHI.COM&amp;nbsp;to shop for Delta 8 edibles, vapes,</description></item><item><title>#517 - GREG FITZSIMMONS | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290124/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 00:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Greg Fitzsimmons, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Michael Lehrer, Matthew Muehling, Michael A. Gonzales, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 07/26/2021
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
ZIPRECRUITER.COM&amp;nbsp;– TRY IT FOR FREE AT&amp;nbsp;ZIPRECRUITER.COM/KILLTONY
—
EXPRESSVPN.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 3 FREE MONTHS BY GOING TO:&amp;nbsp;EXPRESSVPN.COM/KILLTONY&amp;nbsp;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#516 - PAULY SHORE + JOSH MARTIN | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290125/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 01:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pauly Shore, Josh Martin, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Michael Lehrer, David Lucas, Matthew Muehling, Michael A. Gonzales, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 07/19/2021
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
LIQUID-IV.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 25% OFF ANY ORDER WITH PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT:&amp;nbsp;LIQUID-IV.COM
—
Super Speciosa! Try Kratom and get 20% off your entire order – go to&amp;nbsp;GetSuperLeaf.com/tony
and use promo code TONY for 20% off your entire order
—
Go to&amp;nbsp;3CHI.</description></item><item><title>#515 - SHANE GILLIS | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290126/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 20:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shane Gillis, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Michael Lehrer, David Lucas, Matthew Muehling, Michael A. Gonzales, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 07/12/2021
–THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
Visit&amp;nbsp;GETROMAN.COM/TONY&amp;nbsp;and if approved, you’ll get fifteen dollars off your first order of ED treatment.
—
Credit Karma’s game-changing technology shows you tailored offers for credit cards and
personal loans that you’re more likely to be approved for, so you can apply with more</description></item><item><title>#514 - DAVID LUCAS | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290127/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 20:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290127/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Lucas, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Michael Lehrer, Matthew Muehling, Michael A. Gonzales, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 07/05/2021
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
ZIPRECRUITER.COM&amp;nbsp;– TRY IT FOR FREE AT&amp;nbsp;ZIPRECRUITER.COM/KILLTONY
—
Credit Karma’s game-changing technology shows you tailored offers for credit cards and
personal loans that you’re more likely to be approved for, so you can apply with more
confidence. Apply with confidence today. Go to&amp;nbsp;CREDITKARMA.COM/PODCAST&amp;nbsp;or the Credit Karma app.</description></item><item><title>#513 - WILLIAM MONTGOMERY | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290128/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 23:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290128/</guid><description>Podcast Description William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Zac Bogus, Michael Lehrer, Matthew Muehling, Michael A. Gonzales, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 06/28/2021
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
ZIPRECRUITER.COM&amp;nbsp;– TRY IT FOR FREE AT&amp;nbsp;ZIPRECRUITER.COM/KILLTONY
—
LIQUID-IV.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 25% OFF ANY ORDER WITH PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT:&amp;nbsp;LIQUID-IV.COM
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#512 - RON WHITE | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290129/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 17:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290129/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ron White, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, David Lucas, Zac Bogus, Michael Lehrer, Matthew Muehling, Michael A. Gonzales, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 06/21/2021
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
Visit&amp;nbsp;GETROMAN.COM/TONY&amp;nbsp;and if approved, you’ll get fifteen dollars off your first order of ED treatment.
—
Go to&amp;nbsp;3CHI.COM&amp;nbsp;to shop for Delta 8 edibles, vapes,
tinctures, gummies, and oils that can be used to make your own homemade
edibles. Use code “KILLTONY” at checkout to receive 5% off your order</description></item><item><title>#511- DANNY BROWN | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290130/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 19:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290130/</guid><description>Podcast Description Danny Brown, William Montgomery, Hans Kim, Zac Bogus, Michael Lehrer, Matthew Muehling, Michael A. Gonzales, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 06/14/2021
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
ZIPRECRUITER.COM&amp;nbsp;– TRY IT FOR FREE AT&amp;nbsp;ZIPRECRUITER.COM/KILLTONY
—
Credit Karma’s game-changing technology shows you tailored offers for credit cards and
personal loans that you’re more likely to be approved for, so you can apply with more
confidence. Apply with confidence today. Go to&amp;nbsp;CREDITKARMA.</description></item><item><title>#510 - ALEX JONES | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290131/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 00:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alex Jones, Joe Rogan, Duncan Trussell, William Montgomery, Zac Bogus, Michael Lehrer, Matthew Muehling, Michael A. Gonzales, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 06/07/2021
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
BOX OF AWESOME! – From style and grooming goods, to
barware, cooking tools, and outdoor gear, Box of Awesome has
collections for every part of your life. – Get 20% off your first monthly box when you sign up</description></item><item><title>#509 - LUIS J GOMEZ + ZAC AMICO | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290132/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290132/</guid><description>Podcast Description Luis J Gomez, Zac Amico, David Lucas, William Montgomery, Zac Bogus, Michael Lehrer, Matthew Muehling, Michael A. Gonzales, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 05/31/2021
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
ZIPRECRUITER.COM&amp;nbsp;– TRY IT FOR FREE AT&amp;nbsp;ZIPRECRUITER.COM/KILLTONY
—
Visit&amp;nbsp;GETROMAN.COM/TONY&amp;nbsp;and if approved, you’ll get fifteen dollars off your first order of ED treatment.
—-
EXPRESSVPN.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 3 FREE MONTHS BY GOING TO:&amp;nbsp;EXPRESSVPN.COM/KILLTONY
—
Go to&amp;nbsp;3CHI.COM&amp;nbsp;to shop for Delta 8 edibles, vapes,</description></item><item><title>#508 - RON WHITE + RUSSELL PETERS | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290133/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 23:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ron White, Russell Peters, Zac Bogus, Michael Lehrer, Matthew Muehling, Michael A. Gonzales, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 05/03/2021
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
ZIPRECRUITER.COM&amp;nbsp;– TRY IT FOR FREE AT&amp;nbsp;ZIPRECRUITER.COM/KILLTONY
—
Credit Karma’s game-changing technology shows you tailored offers for credit cards and
personal loans that you’re more likely to be approved for, so you can apply with more
confidence. Apply with confidence today. Go to&amp;nbsp;CREDITKARMA.COM/TONY&amp;nbsp;or the Credit Karma app.</description></item><item><title>#507 - JESSICA MICHELLE SINGLETON | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290134/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 22:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jessica Michelle Singleton, William Montgomery, Zac Bogus, Michael Lehrer, David Lucas, Matthew Muehling, Michael A. Gonzales, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 05/03/2021
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
BOX OF AWESOME! – From style and grooming goods, to
barware, cooking tools, and outdoor gear, Box of Awesome has
collections for every part of your life. – Get 20% off your first monthly box when you sign up&amp;nbsp;at&amp;nbsp;BOXOFAWESOME.COM&amp;nbsp;and enter the code “KILLTONY” at checkout.</description></item><item><title>#506 - BRIAN HOLTZMAN | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290135/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 01:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brian Holtzman, Zac Bogus, Michael Lehrer, David Lucas, Matthew Muehling, Michael A. Gonzales, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 04/26/2021
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
ZIPRECRUITER.COM&amp;nbsp;– TRY IT FOR FREE AT&amp;nbsp;ZIPRECRUITER.COM/KILLTONY
—
Visit&amp;nbsp;GETROMAN.COM/TONY&amp;nbsp;and if approved, you’ll get fifteen dollars off your first order of ED treatment.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#505 - TIM DILLON | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290136/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 18:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290136/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tim Dillon, Jon Keyz, Zac Bogus, Michael Lehrer, David Lucas, Matthew Muehling, Michael A. Gonzales, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 04/19/2021
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#504 - ALI MACOFSKY + MARK NORMAND | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290137/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 21:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ali Macofsky, Mark Normand, Zac Bogus, Michael Lehrer, Matthew Muehling, Michael A. Gonzales, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 04/12/2021
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
Let Sunday take the guesswork out of growing a greener, more beautiful lawn this Spring.
Visit&amp;nbsp;GETSUNDAY.COM/KILLTONY&amp;nbsp;to get $20 off your custom lawn plan at checkout!
—
MUD\WTR is a coffee alternative with 4 adaptogenic mushrooms and
ayurvedic herbs. With 1/7th the caffeine as a cup of coffee, you get energy without the</description></item><item><title>#503 - DERRIC POSTON | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290138/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 20:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290138/</guid><description>Podcast Description Deric Poston, Lorenzo Dwayne Jackson, Zac Bogus, David Lucas, Matthew Muehling, Michael A. Gonzales, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 04/05/2021
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
—
ROMAN ED – Anyone who’s dealt with erectile dysfunction knows how awkward it can be to talk about in
person. Luckily, there’s a simple, convenient solution to get the treatment you need, without
leaving the couch.
Visit&amp;nbsp;GETROMAN.COM/TONY&amp;nbsp;and if approved, you’ll get fifteen dollars off your first order of ED treatment.</description></item><item><title>#502 - ADAM RAY + JADE CATTA-PRETA | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290139/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 23:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adam Ray, Jade Catta-Preta, Lorenzo Dwayne Jackson, Zac Bogus, Matthew Muehling, Michael A. Gonzales, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 03/22/2021
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
Let Sunday take the guesswork out of growing a greener, more beautiful lawn this Spring.
Visit&amp;nbsp;GETSUNDAY.COM/KILLTONY&amp;nbsp;to get $20 off your custom lawn plan at checkout!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#501 - RON WHITE | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290140/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 22:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290140/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ron White, Jon Keyz, Lorenzo Dwayne Jackson, Michael Lehrer, Zac Bogus, Matthew Muehling, David Lucas, Michael A. Gonzales, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 03/22/2021
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
MUD\WTR is a coffee alternative with 4 adaptogenic mushrooms and
ayurvedic herbs. With 1/7th the caffeine as a cup of coffee, you get energy without the
anxiety, jitters, or crash of coffee. GO TO&amp;nbsp;MUDWTR.COM/TONY&amp;nbsp;to support the show and use code “TONY” for $5 off</description></item><item><title>#500 - JOE ROGAN | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290141/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joe Rogan, Jon Keyz, Lorenzo Dwayne Jackson, William Montgomery, Michael Lehrer, Zac Bogus, Matthew Muehling, David Lucas, Michael A. Gonzales, Yoni, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 04/08/2021
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
Visit GETROMAN.COM/TONY and if approved, you’ll get fifteen dollars off your first order of ED treatment.
—
EXPRESSVPN.COM – GET 3 FREE MONTHS BY GOING TO: EXPRESSVPN.COM/KILLTONY
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#499 - DONNELL RAWLINGS | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290142/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 17:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290142/</guid><description>Podcast Description Donnell Rawlings, Jon Keyz, Lorenzo Dwayne Jackson, Michael Lehrer, Zac Bogus, Matthew Muehling, David Lucas, Michael A. Gonzales, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 03/15/2021
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
MUD\WTR is a coffee alternative with 4 adaptogenic mushrooms and
ayurvedic herbs. With 1/7th the caffeine as a cup of coffee, you get energy without the
anxiety, jitters, or crash of coffee. GO TO&amp;nbsp;MUDWTR.COM/TONY&amp;nbsp;to support the show and use code TONY for $5 off</description></item><item><title>#498 - JOE ROGAN + ADAM EGET | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290143/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 23:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290143/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joe Rogan, Adam Eget, Jon Keyz, Lorenzo Dwayne Jackson, Michael Lehrer, Zac Bogus, Matthew Muehling, David Lucas, Michael A. Gonzales, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 03/08/2021
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
LIQUID-IV.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 25% OFF ANY ORDER WITH PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT:&amp;nbsp;LIQUID-IV.COM
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#497 - SARA WEINSHENK + JAMAR NEIGHBORS | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290144/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290144/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sara Weinshenk, Jamar Neighbors, Jon Keyz, Lorenzo Dwayne Jackson, Michael Lehrer, Zac Bogus, Matthew Muehling, David Lucas, Michael A. Gonzales, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 03/01/2021
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
LIQUID-IV.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 25% OFF ANY ORDER WITH PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT:&amp;nbsp;LIQUID-IV.COM
—
HARRYS.COM&amp;nbsp;– New customers can get a Harry’s Starter Set and a FREE Body Wash for just $3 at&amp;nbsp;HARRYS.COM/KILLTONY. That’s over a $16 value for just $3!</description></item><item><title>#496 - MIAMI #2 - JIMMY SHUBERT | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290145/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 23:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290145/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jimmy Shubert, William Montgomery, David Lucas, Michael Lehrer, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 02/27/2021
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
EXPRESSVPN.COM – GET 3 FREE MONTHS BY GOING TO: EXPRESSVPN.COM/KILLTONY
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#495 - MIAMI - BENJI AFLALO | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290146/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 22:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290146/</guid><description>Podcast Description Benji Aflalo, William Montgomery, David Lucas, Michael Lehrer, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 02/26/2021
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
ZIPRECRUITER.COM&amp;nbsp;– TRY IT FOR FREE AT&amp;nbsp;ZIPRECRUITER.COM/KILLTONY
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#494 - JOE ROGAN + BRIAN MOSES | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290147/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 00:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290147/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joe Rogan, Brian Moses, Jon Keyz, Lorenzo Dwayne Jackson, Michael Lehrer, Zac Bogus, Matthew Muehling, Michael A. Gonzales, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 03/01/2021
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
ROMAN ED – Anyone who’s dealt with erectile dysfunction knows how awkward it can be to talk about in
person. Luckily, there’s a simple, convenient solution to get the treatment you need, without
leaving the couch.
Visit&amp;nbsp;GETROMAN.COM/TONY&amp;nbsp;and if approved, you’ll get fifteen dollars off your first order of ED treatment.</description></item><item><title>#493 - BRIAN HOLTZMAN | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290148/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 02:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290148/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brian Holtzman, Jon Keyz, Lorenzo Dwayne Jackson, Michael Lehrer, Zac Bogus, Matthew Muehling, Michael A. Gonzales, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 02/22/2021
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
LIQUID-IV.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 25% OFF ANY ORDER WITH PROMO CODE: “TONY” AT:&amp;nbsp;LIQUID-IV.COM
—
HARRYS.COM&amp;nbsp;– New customers can get a Harry’s Starter Set and a FREE Body Wash for just $3 at&amp;nbsp;HARRYS.COM/KILLTONY. That’s over a $16 value for just $3! You’ll get a 5-blade razor, weighted handle, foaming shave gel, a travel cover, and a travel size body wash.</description></item><item><title>#492 - DUSTIN YBARRA (PHOENIX) | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290149/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 21:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290149/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dustin Ybarra, William Montogmery, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban - Date: 02/05/2021
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
ZIPRECRUITER.COM&amp;nbsp;– TRY IT FOR FREE AT&amp;nbsp;ZIPRECRUITER.COM/KILLTONY
—
EXPRESSVPN.COM&amp;nbsp;– GET 3 FREE MONTHS BY GOING TO:&amp;nbsp;EXPRESSVPN.COM/KILLTONY
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#491 - SHANE GILLIS | KILL TONY</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5167290150/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 11:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5167290150/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shane Gillis, Jon Keyz, Lorenzo Dwayne Jackson, Michael Lehrer, Zac Bogus, David Lucas, Matthew Muehling, Michael A. Gonzales, Janice Min, Tony Hinchcliffe, Brian Redban – 02/08/2021
THIS EPISODE IS SPONSORED BY:
ROMAN ED – Anyone who’s dealt with erectile dysfunction knows how awkward it can be to talk about in
person. Luckily, there’s a simple, convenient solution to get the treatment you need, without
leaving the couch.
Visit&amp;nbsp;GETROMAN.COM/TONY&amp;nbsp;and if approved, you’ll get fifteen dollars off your first order of ED treatment.</description></item></channel></rss>