<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The David McWilliams Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast/</link><description>Recent content in The David McWilliams Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 04:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bitcoin is back, why? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Time to eat humble pie? Despite us saying last year it that Bitcoin was a BS idea, its value has risen over 150% this year! What’s behind the surge? We talk about Notorious B.I.G, Benjamin Franklin, the wisdom of Charlie Munger and the fact that Bitcoin is something, but it ain&amp;rsquo;t money! But where from here? Should we revise our stance on the technology? Joins us to find out!</description></item><item><title>The Paradox of Prudence | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ireland has a massive deficit in public infrastructure and a massive surplus in the public finances. Economists are advising the government to save on the basis that saving is &amp;ldquo;good&amp;rdquo;. But not spending when we have an increasing immigrant population is a recipe for social chaos. This podcast is celebration of spending. Ireland&amp;rsquo;s tax base is set up to generate surplus, so spend the money. Join the gang! https://plus.</description></item><item><title>Putin's Back! | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 04:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Putin&amp;rsquo;s back, swanning around the Gulf visiting Saudi Arabia and the UAE, telling the world that he was never really away. Things are going his way. Meanwhile America, is swamped with recurring geopolitical crises and its role as the global top dog is under enormous pressure as we head into an election year. 2024 could be the year of a global infection point, we set out the issues. Join the gang!</description></item><item><title>Shane MacGowan, the Diaspora and the coming 2nd Irish Republic. | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 04:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660004/</guid><description>Podcast Description We mark the death of Shane MacGowan by looking at the Irish Diaspora, particularly in England and its impact on English popular culture. From there we look at Ireland&amp;rsquo;s relationship with its Tribe abroad and from there, we imagine what a 2nd Irish Republic will look like (which will happen because it&amp;rsquo;s necessary) and the role of the diaspora in this thinking. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Liberal democracy under threat? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 04:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Liberal democracy in the western world is all too often taken for granted. But its enemies, nationalists, theocrats, Marxists and isolationists - are rising. Will Israel become a &amp;ldquo;wedge&amp;rdquo; issue? Also, why we should defend it and what the erosion of commercial liberalism in China is doing to its economic performance. What does 2024 has in store for the best political idea we&amp;rsquo;ve come up with yet, liberal democracy.</description></item><item><title>Riots in Dublin and the Power of Crowds | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660006/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 04:00:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660006/</guid><description>Podcast Description After the riot, the analysis. We look at the power of crowds, why crowds love destruction, why they grow and how they the dissipate. Plus, of course the economics of the Irish far right, we look at the numbers, who are they and why they are here to stay. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What does Argentina’s U-turn mean? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 04:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660007/</guid><description>Podcast Description From tantric sex expert to President, Javier “chainsaw” Melei is a new type of populist - and anarchy-capitalist one! What does this mean, is this guy libertarianism’s answer to Che Guevara? And where will “dollarisation” take this beautiful but profoundly dysfunctional country? Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Economics of the AI Revolution | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660008/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 04:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660008/</guid><description>Podcast Description The board of Chat GPT may be firing its CEO, but that doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean this revolution is slowing down. A whistle wind tour from the dawn of time with Stanley Kubrick, to Gutenberg in 1453, and up to now, we look at the economics of innovation. With AI are we now facing catastrophe or a creative surge? Listen up, as we explore the economics of AI. Join the gang!</description></item><item><title>Why 1923 still Matters | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 04:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Anti-semitism, inflation, threats to democracy, despotic leaders and fragile governments, if you thought it was today, its is - but hold on. It&amp;rsquo;s happened before&amp;hellip; This very month 100 years ago, German hyperinflation peaked, Adolf Hitler announced himself with a putsch and anti-semitism was rife. History is repeating itself, or is it? Join us on this epic journey back in time to see what we can learn and whether we can apply any historical remedies to today&amp;rsquo;s global problems.</description></item><item><title>The World in 2024. The NATO-Sphere | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660010/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 04:00:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we kick-off a new three part series that looks at the state of the big economic blocs in the world. Part one is the state of the US as it enters an election year. Plus we scan the UK and the EU, briefly. We call this world the NATO-sphere for obvious reasons. Next up in this series, we will deal with the impact of AI and third we will look at China the link between economics &amp;amp; liberalism.</description></item><item><title>BiBi Netanyahu - The Most Important Politician in America | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 04:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660011/</guid><description>Podcast Description How is the Israeli tail is wagging the American dog? America&amp;rsquo;s election is exactly one year from now and Joe Biden is in bed with Netanyahu, but his own party, the Democratic Party is deeply divided by his embrace of Israel. He has given Netanyahu his blessing, but he can&amp;rsquo;t influence the outcome in Gaza. This emasculation, combined with the end of the 0% interest rate days where previous &amp;ldquo;stars&amp;rdquo; are falling to earth - WeWork goes bankrupt, NFTs blinds people and SBF gets convicted - and we have a perfect storm, economically and geo-politically, raging.</description></item><item><title>A live podcast straight from Kilkenomics | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660012/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 04:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660012/</guid><description>Podcast Description John and I sat down at the Watergate Theatre in Kilkenny and had a natter, covering all classes of topics from economics, to James Joyce, WB Yeats and a whole host of other topics, focussing on Europe's economic policy dilemmas.&amp;nbsp; We chatting about unconventional thinkers, how the artist &amp;amp; the entrepreneur are much more similar than meets the eye, both being unconventional dissenters.
And If you’d like to hear my full TED talk on unconventional thinking, simply click here: https://www.</description></item><item><title>The roots of the Israel-Palestinian Conflict pt4 | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 04:00:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660013/</guid><description>Podcast Description We go way back to 70 AD before coming bak to today. Demography demands a two state solution, and the Israeli&amp;rsquo;s know this. But a trap has been set for America, into which it is sliding. The Kremlin has its &amp;ldquo;wedge&amp;rsquo; issue and the battle for the West continues, Putin can&amp;rsquo;t believe his luck. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We need to talk about the pay gap | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660014/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 04:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660014/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s not world shattering to announce that there is a pay discrepancy between men and women - but it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that this gap has been maintained despite numerous laws and financial requirements that have been implemented to remove said gap. So why is is still here? Join us as we talk about the underlying issues that laws can&amp;rsquo;t address! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>The Roots of the Israel-Palestinian Conflict pt3 | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 03:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660015/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the third instalment of our series we explain the period of 1993 to the present in the Middle East. Why the peace accords floundered, the impact of 9/11, why the middle ground gave way to the extremes, and the rise of the Israeli tech industry. Don’t miss it! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The impending commercial property crash | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 03:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660016/</guid><description>Podcast Description The commercial property market is struggling to swallow the interest rate hikes aiming to bring down inflation. Can the mass building of the last decade, built on the back of very low interest rate, survive this new economic landscape?&amp;nbsp;
Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The roots of the Israel-Palestinian Conflict pt2 (1967-1993) | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 03:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Part 2 of our overview of the Israel-Palestinian conflict brings us from the Six Day War to the Oslo Accords. Key things here are the change in the image of Isreal in the world imagination from defiant fighter to oppressive bully and the emergence of Iran, fundamentalism, settlers and economic stagnation. We end with Soviet Jewry emigrating to Israel, the Palestinian Intifada, chaos in Lebanon and the road to, a short-lived, peace.</description></item><item><title>When Mantras Replace Hard Thinking: The Case of the Irish Budget | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660018/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 03:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660018/</guid><description>Podcast Description The budget, despite all the posturing, should make you be afraid, very afraid. It reveals a complete lack of Leaving Cert economic thinking. Today we interrogate just one aspect to see if there is any logical and consistent economic heft behind all the political tinkering. We look at housing. Stay tuned for the verdict! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The roots of the Israel-Palestinian Conflict pt1 | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 02:30:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660019/</guid><description>Podcast Description To understand where we are, you have to appreciate the history - economic, political and social - and that’s what we’re setting out to do! Starting in Dorset St Dublin in 1904 with Leopold Bloom in Jame Joyce&amp;rsquo;s Ulysses, we explore the history of Zionism and make our way from Bloom to the 6 Day War 1967. Stay tuned for part 2 next week when try to bring events from then up to the the current catastrophe.</description></item><item><title>US interest rates: What's driving them? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660020/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 03:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660020/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;rsquo;re in North America this week thinking about the US economy. How come the USA is creating so many jobs, why are interest rates not biting, does macroeconomics have to have a massive re-think about monetary policy and if so, what does this all mean for you? Is the Fed flunking it? Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Brexit: the cost of reality | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660021/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 03:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brexit was supposed to be simple, that was the promise! The reality however is a world of complex costs &amp;amp; frictions which has backed the UK into a structural cul-de-sac. Where does it go from here? Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The September Rate Spike - Is it Time to Worry? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660022/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 03:00:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Long term interest rates spiked up in September. This will have an impact. Mortgage rates everywhere are up dramatically. Could it be time for the debt crunch? We know that there’s a delay between raising rates and the impact of those new rates, but no one knows exactly how long - while the economy appears to be doing fine, are we missing something, something big? A day of debt reckoning?</description></item><item><title>Argentina: An economic and now, political car crash. Its worse than you think | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 03:00:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660023/</guid><description>Podcast Description How does one of the richest economy of the 19th century blow it? What are the lessons for the rest of us? As the saying goes, “The road to ruin is shorter than you think”. How does a good country go bad? And now that Argentina has completely come off the rails, can its be saved or is it about to become a &amp;ldquo;failed state&amp;rdquo;? If it does, could the Argentinean virus spread to the rest of Latin America?</description></item><item><title>Why Ireland should copy Vienna | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660024/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 03:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vienna, one of the world’s most liveable city, was created through a strong vision for its future and targeted taxes. Today, housing costs in Vienna are a third of its Irish counter part, we should be taking notes! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Are we at the 4th turning? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660025/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 03:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s episode is a unique discussion with the writer Neil Howe about a completely different way to look at history, in chapters over decades and how history tends to repeat itself over given periods of time… and spoiler alert: Neil thinks we’re about to change chapter VERY soon! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The ECB on Trial | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660026/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 03:00:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660026/</guid><description>Podcast Description The ECB has raised interest rates ten times in two years but the Euro is not getting stronger, it is getting weaker. What does this tell us about the European economy and inconsistency at the heart of European policy making. We head to Frankfurt and put the ECB in the dock. I rest my case! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Swedenomics | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660027/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 03:00:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660027/</guid><description>Podcast Description The euro-tour continues as we dive into what makes Sweden tick - but not before one of our usual tangents on skin differences! Nevertheless, today is about the libertarian/socialist contradiction that is Sweden and how it always manages to punch above its weight. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Crouch, Bind, Set! &amp; G20 economics | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660028/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 03:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660028/</guid><description>Podcast Description What does the latest G20 accord tell us about the new Cold War and speaking of wars, we examine the Rugby World Cup and more interestingly the Economics of Rugby. Will Saudi Arabia do to rugby what it’s trying to do to football, golf, F1 and probably tennis? Imagine Munster owned by a Sheik? Could it happen? As it spends billions in sports-washing, the RWC is surely a shop window event for potential buyers of the game!</description></item><item><title>How India became the coming power | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660029/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 03:00:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660029/</guid><description>Podcast Description With the coming G20 summit in India we take a look at how the rise of india came to be, how it went from colonialism, to socialism and now to capitalism. Now a significant player on the international stage, will India succeed at becoming rich before it becomes old? Join us as we find out how its going to try Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>The tragedy of state outsourcing | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660030/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 03:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660030/</guid><description>Podcast Description If we are to prepare a future that welcomes 10 million people in Ireland, we need take back control of public infrastructure project costs because these runaway costs are hindering our growth and reducing public confidence in the state. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Uncovering Portugal | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660031/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 03:00:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Portugal’s current economic situation can only be explained through its rich &amp;amp; expansive history. As we tease out the various chapters of Portugal we uncover another nation that although is supposed to be rich, feels poor. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ireland is a teenager in a geriatric home | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660032/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 03:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ireland is an outlier within the European demographic, how can it shape it’s growth in a bloc that is going to be managing for an aging population? Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We need to invest now, or face the consequences | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660033/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 03:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660033/</guid><description>Podcast Description The economy has two main levers: fiscal policies &amp;amp; monetary policies. Through these mechanism we have the means to ensure that our infrastructure keeps up with the population growth while simultaneously keeping the “far” parties of politics at bay… if we use them! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The end of the Chinese financial miracle? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660034/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 03:00:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660034/</guid><description>Podcast Description China’s economic growth is far from what it used to be and cracks are currently appearing in a variety of sectors. Has China’s heroic growth in the last decades finally come to an inflection point? Join us as we break down what is currently happening and where it might go. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Poland rising | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660035/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 03:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660035/</guid><description>Podcast Description The European tour continues, next stop: Poland! An extraordinary country that is rapidly evolving - an evolution that might very well pull the axis of European power towards the East. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Easiest Way to Rob a Bank is to Run It | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660036/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660036/</guid><description>Podcast Description As John returns from Washington DC we take a quick state of that nation before coming home to talk about how the Irish banks are actually stealing their customer&amp;rsquo;s money. Interest income is the income of savers not the banks, if the banks don&amp;rsquo;t pass that on, they are stealing customers income. That&amp;rsquo;s what is happening! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>The Reign in Spain | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660037/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Continuing our European tour we arrive in the the Iberian Peninsula. What makes Spain, this most brilliant of countries tick? With many European countries leaning to the right, Spain has been an interesting outlier - the centre has just held! Join us today as we’re joined with Prof Joe Haslam for a “tour de force” on Spain, its economics, politics, industry and future. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Is the DeGrowth Movement the future? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660038/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 03:00:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660038/</guid><description>Podcast Description One of the most talked about global movements is the DeGrowth movement which believes economic growth is the problem and if we can wean ourselves of the economics of growth, lots of good things will flow. Today, we interrogate this notion, is it a brilliant soundbite or a true and practical guideline for a new world? Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>The Economics of Oppenheimer | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660039/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Culture always mirrors, reinforces or leads economics &amp;amp; Oppenheimer has just returned nuclear energy to the center of the energy discussion. Is is the silver bullet to sustainable energy or the next catastrophe waiting to happen? Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sinead, Music and Stone Age Economics | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660040/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660040/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a quick top-up on last week’s Italian episode, we talk about Sinead O&amp;rsquo;Connor before she became Sinead O&amp;rsquo;Connor. From there we explore why music was always much more than entertainment and how the origins of music might have driven Stone Age productivity and the first economy of the cave man! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How Italy became anti-fragile | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660041/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 03:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Italy, the cradle of European civilization often gets a bad rap, which I personally think is completely unjustified. Today&amp;rsquo;s conversation looks at where the country stands but also how it&amp;rsquo;s history gave it so much resilience - it&amp;rsquo;s a fascinating discussion! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Insiders VS Outsiders | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660042/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 03:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660042/</guid><description>Podcast Description How can some countries be doing well on paper but in reality, there is growing frustration and instability from the population, leading to more extremist ideology? The answer is all about insiders VS outsiders… Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Tyranny of Nostalgia | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660043/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 03:00:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660043/</guid><description>Podcast Description The UK is a mess. Investment, productivity and GPD per head is all flatlining. Why? How can a once good country go bad. In today’s conversation we’re joined by economist Russel Jones to explore what happens when a people look backwards not forwards. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Has the FED done the impossible? Is a soft landing coming? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660044/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 03:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660044/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Americans might have engineered the impossible: a soft landing… which would be an absolute anomaly in economic cycles! While we look at how this might be happening, we also investigate the many camps claiming to have been right on the cycle and the outcome. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bastille Day Special: What makes France tick? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660045/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 03:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660045/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the eve of Bastille Day we head to France to explore the French economy. Who really runs France, the technocrats, big business or the political class of the people? How have the recent riots changed the country? More to the point, how closer is the Republic to being run by President LePen and what would that mean for Europe? Fascinating one this, hope you like it. Join the gang!</description></item><item><title>The Recession that Isn't Happening | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660046/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 03:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660046/</guid><description>Podcast Description We explore why the world is not in a recession despite everything. The US economy simply refuses to buckle under the pressure of high interest rates. A key difference between 2008 and now is that that this time around, the people are not in desperate debt but corporate America is. Companies with lots of debt will struggle. Which big company might go bust first? Look at Twitter and shudder!</description></item><item><title>What's happening in Germany | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660047/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 03:00:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Germany, Europe&amp;rsquo;s most important economy, is at a turning point. It is now a massive industrial economy with no energy. For over one hundred years, Germany has managed this dilemma. But now without Russian gas, and after closing off its nuclear industry, how will Germany power itself? Plus, can its political system handle this transition without a lurch to the extreme? Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>Fiscal Incontinence! | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660048/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 03:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660048/</guid><description>Podcast Description What a scandal at the Irish national broadcaster tells us about how the country became the most expensive place to live in Europe. It&amp;rsquo;s all about value for money and how the government&amp;rsquo;s inability to keep down costs, seeps into the wider economy, pushing up all prices, making everyone feel poorer despite having more money than ever. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>European evolution, train tales and the history of mathematics | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660049/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 03:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660049/</guid><description>Podcast Description From a train journey to Ishango bones we talk about Europe’s complicated relationship with Africa before turning our sights (and your ears) to Maths - and how Math has shaped society as we know it! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Russian Revolution? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660050/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 03:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660050/</guid><description>Podcast Description The whole world learned the name Prigozhin over the weekend as the warlord threatened Putin and plotted a course for Moscow. With this failed coup now behind us, let’s analyze what this means for the Putin regime. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Searching for America with David Brooks | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660051/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660051/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this intimate conversation, we discuss America - from&amp;nbsp;a political, personal &amp;amp; cultural point of view to understand this land where decisions and policies ripple across the world.
Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why modern cities need to look at the 19th century for inspiration | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660052/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Urban living is nothing new, but some decades did it better than others! Let’s look at how people designed cities before the advent of cars and what we can be inspired by as we look ahead. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Unionist strategy against Irish Unity: Poverty | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660053/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 03:00:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brexit was supposed to drive a wedge between the two jurisdictions of Ireland. In reality it has built a bridge: There&amp;rsquo;s far more trade between the North and the South now. Demography is only going one way and the reaction of the Unionists is immiseration. How else can we interpret the Unionist default position of “the south can’t afford us” other than a strategy to stay poor so that the bill of unity might be too steep for Irish taxpayers?</description></item><item><title>The Economics of Football seen through the eyes of Logan Roy | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660054/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 03:00:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Love Football? Love Succession? You&amp;rsquo;re gonna love this one in which we explain the economics of football as Logan Roy would explain it to Shiv, Kendal, Roman and Conor. The game&amp;rsquo;s business model is completely dumb: relegation guarantees bankruptcy and clubs are nothing more than dick waving trophies for bored Princelings. No holding back here, stay tuned to find out more! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>The opioid crisis in America is coming to Europe | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660055/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 03:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660055/</guid><description>Podcast Description America has been fighting through a series of drug epidemics in the last few years, and those drugs are now poised to cross the pond. Today we take a look at what is going on and why Europe should be worried at what&amp;rsquo;s coming from the USA. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why more interest rate hikes are coming and Irish census revelations | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660056/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 03:00:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660056/</guid><description>Podcast Description We start in America, breaking down the impact of the debt ceiling deal &amp;amp; why more bank fallouts are likely on the way before moving to the Irish census to talk about what we can learn from this amazing “day in the life” view of the Irish population Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Follow the money | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660057/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 03:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660057/</guid><description>Podcast Description All criminal enterprises are enterprises, meaning they are businesses…and like every business they leave a money trail. Today we talk to the man who is suing the Wagner Group, hitting them in their deep pocket. Jason McCue has successfully prosecuted the IRA and HAMAS, now he’s going after Wagner. Fascinating stuff! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why the Federal Reserve is stuck in a "cul de sac", and what it means for you. | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660058/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 03:00:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660058/</guid><description>Podcast Description The American economy refuses to obey the Federal Reserve and things are going to break. We examine the monetary bind facing the world&amp;rsquo;s premier central bank and what it all means. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What you know about Western civilization is wrong | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660059/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 03:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660059/</guid><description>Podcast Description The saying goes that there’s a straight line from Plato to Nato - but actually, it’s much more complicated than that. Today we explain why we repeat a story that we know to be untrue and what the real story is. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Coming Great Crash? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660060/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 03:00:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660060/</guid><description>Podcast Description They say that history doesn’t repeat itself, but it rhymes. Today’s discussion is all about what we can take from history as we navigate this slow grinding bank crisis, many years of easy money and still elevated asset prices - all in a time of rising, not falling interest rates Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>This is the most important week in the Ukraine war - and global geo-politics as a whole | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660061/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 03:00:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660061/</guid><description>Podcast Description The counter-offensive might be underway but the outcomes are still very much up in the air. Let’s look at what’s going on and how the outcomes in Ukraine will ripple across the world Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Coming US Default? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660062/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 03:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is the US about to manufacture a debt crisis? Don&amp;rsquo;t rule it out. There are enough nut-jobs knocking around Capitol Hill for whom shutting down government is a victory not a catastrophe. And once we’re finished with the Lunes on the Hill, we explains what any Irish sovereign wealth fund (PS: we’re delighted the government is listening to our ideas!) ought to be focussed on. Incidentally, paying down debt is actually the worst use of money possible.</description></item><item><title>American Bank Carnage part 2 | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660063/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 03:00:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660063/</guid><description>Podcast Description The American banking system is experiencing a slow grinding crisis. We explore, why this is happening, why now and why the Fed adopted a completely different attitude to the 2023 banking crisis than the 2008 crisis and what this all means for the economy and the way we distribute money around the 21st century economy. And further out, could Apple - the great disrupter - be poised to disrupt Wall Street?</description></item><item><title>How does the UK recover financially? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660064/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 03:00:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660064/</guid><description>Podcast Description The UK is what happens when economic growth stops. So on the week of the coronation let’s look at what is happening in the country and what it takes to right the wrongs of the last few years. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Dream Economy | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660065/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 03:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Arts and culture are associated with many things, but rarely is economic impact cited. This is right, culture is not a spread sheet, but nor too is economics. The economy is a highly sensitive ecosystem of which arts and culture are part. We examine the role of culture in the economy, plus in a special detour, we look at the economics one of Ireland&amp;rsquo;s great revolutionary heroes, Wolf Tone.</description></item><item><title>Civilization and the planet | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660066/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 03:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660066/</guid><description>Podcast Description We seldom hear how the environment affected the growth and collapse of civilizations across the world and history. More than any other factor, the environment has been a defining factor to where we live, how we organize and what we consume. Today we’re joined by the great Peter Frankopan for a masterclass in this untold story. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>The Paradox of Prudence | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660067/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 03:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Having money is only half the battle, deploying it well is the other half. We look at Ireland&amp;rsquo;s financial balance sheet: we&amp;rsquo;re saving far too much! By saving too much, both at the State and the punter level, we are hiding behind the sanctimonious veil of savings rather than involving ourselves in hard thinking, which is what economics is all about. Economists have a bias towards prudence and prudence only, this is highly costly and is an abdication of responsibility.</description></item><item><title>Feed your Brain | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660068/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 03:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660068/</guid><description>Podcast Description I’ve just come back from giving a TED talk in Vancouver. Brilliant experience, lots of amazing speakers, top notch presentations ;which more than anything reveal to us the stories that nations tell themselves. Today we also announce the line up for the Dalkey Book Festival, showing that as a nation of storytellers, we Irish are still second to none. Hope to see you at Dalkey which kicks of with a live podcast!</description></item><item><title>Biden, Relationships VS interests &amp; Contemplations from TED | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660069/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 03:00:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Countries don&amp;rsquo;t have relationships, they have interests - this notion guides us as we reflect on the coverage of Biden&amp;rsquo;s visit to Ireland before tackling the current economic landscape of Canada from my vantage point in Vancouver where I&amp;rsquo;m preparing to give a TED talk Friday! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The benefits of longterm thinking in the TikTok age | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660070/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 03:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Future citizens have, by definition, no voice but someone needs to speak on their behalf if we’re meant to build a longterm society. The solution to the global housing crisis requires longterm thinking, creating solutions that will sustain us for at least the next 100 years, not just the next election cycle… and it’s much more affordable than you might think! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>Why negativity took over the news cycle | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660071/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 11:46:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Communicating the bad before the good is an evolutionary trait that has helped us survive - but in today’s world, our ancestral instincts and the need to sell media has created a vicious circle that we need to expose and change. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Global Irish Soft Power | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660072/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 03:00:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660072/</guid><description>Podcast Description What does Ireland do for the Irish Diaspora? Here&amp;rsquo;s an idea: why not use Ireland as the re-charging battery for the Irishness of the Global Irish Tribe? Let&amp;rsquo;s use Biden’s visit to Ireland this week to think about how we harness the soft power of Ireland&amp;rsquo;s greatest and unique asset: the tens of millions people around the world who identify as Irish. Soft power is the power of imagination, and in the future a country&amp;rsquo;s soft power will become much more important for our economy.</description></item><item><title>It's Easter, Ramadan, Passover take your pick! We head to Jerusalem, spiritual home of all three religions. | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660073/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 03:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660073/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s Easter, Ramadan and Passover, so let&amp;rsquo;s go to the centre of the three Abrahamic religions, Jerusalem. Many years ago I spent time living and working in Israel which gave me a first hand impression of the country - both good and bad. This week we talk Israel - a country of 9 million people - as that country erupts in anti-government demonstrations, while some in that government talk openly about annexing the West Bank.</description></item><item><title>Why a country can be rich on paper, but feel poor in reality | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660074/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 03:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660074/</guid><description>Podcast Description You&amp;rsquo;ve never had it so good, but you ain&amp;rsquo;t feeling it. Sound familiar? We explain this dilemma at the heart of a society - in this case Ireland - but its can be applied to many countries. It is one of the reason why politics seems so unstable even in countries where economic data appears robust. Unless economic figures percolate down to how people are experiencing the economy, they are not only unhelpful but worse, they are antagonising.</description></item><item><title>China plays chess, while Russia plays poker | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660075/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 03:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Putin has managed to turn Russia into a vassal state of China, a fact confirmed by Xi’s visit to Russia. The Sino/Russo alliance against the West is solidified between them but the alliance is not one of equals. Russia is China’s petrol station, while China provides Russia with manufacturing goods. This is China&amp;rsquo;s moment. This week we discuss politics, geo-strategy and the enduring appeal, despite its failings, of the West.</description></item><item><title>The Next Global Banking Crisis is Here | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660076/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 03:00:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660076/</guid><description>Podcast Description The easiest way to rob a bank is to run it. Banks go bad from the inside out. When interest rates shift upward, lots of mistakes and dodgy practices are revealed. We break down where we’re at globally and what comes next - spoiler alert: it ain&amp;rsquo;t pretty. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Apartment Living Cures Housing Viruses | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660077/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 04:00:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660077/</guid><description>Podcast Description The global housing crisis is significantly worse in countries that speak English. Why? Is it because far few English speakers live in flats? Flats are cheaper to build, creating more dense communities and apartment dwellers object far less than those who live in houses. We explore the joy of apartments today with the expert help of John Burn-Murdoch Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Bank Carnage | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660078/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 03:00:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660078/</guid><description>Podcast Description You wait for bank failures for years then&amp;hellip; three come in a week, one in the home of banking, Switzerland,. This presents central banks with a dilemma. Central banks have two key mandates. One is controlling inflation which, right now, demands higher interest rates, the other preserving the banking system, which right now requires lower interest rates. What gives? Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>On St Patricks Day, a US State of the Nation special with Bernie Sanders | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660079/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 03:00:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660079/</guid><description>Podcast Description On St Patrick&amp;rsquo;s Day we go to the US, home to thirty five million Irish/Americans - there are only 7 million of us on the island. In the country that, more than any other, has been shaped by Irish immigrants, we take the pulse of the US with Brooklyn&amp;rsquo;s finest, Bernie Sanders. We chat about the deep problems that exist in the US, but also the way America can be renewed.</description></item><item><title>SVB Bank Run. Is 2023 a re-run of 2008? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660080/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 03:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660080/</guid><description>Podcast Description We explain why SVB went bust, why yield curves matter and what comes next. Banks go bad from the inside out, but is this the first or the last bank crash of 2023? Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The UK is stuck in a political, economical and social cul de sac is there a way out? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660081/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 04:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660081/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we visited the richest and poorest parts of the UK and it didn&amp;rsquo;t feel right. London, so long the dynamo for productivity, growth and taxation is spluttering and stagnating, while up the road in Northern Ireland; the poorest people now have a healthy life expectancy on par with Sierra Leone. Something has to give. What are Britain&amp;rsquo;s options, will it take them or is the national decline now endemic and irreversible?</description></item><item><title>The end of economists | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660082/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 04:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660082/</guid><description>Podcast Description AI has really come into its own in 2023 with the mainstream use of ChatGPT - but beyond the headlines and the initial curiosities, what does the ascent of AI mean for our economy and our society? Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Russia - A Giant Hostage Situation? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660083/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 04:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660083/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the mindset of the West, Russia is a big, significant, military power with significant resources, but is this perception based in reality? Is the reality that Russia is a decrepit state that has failed its people and ransacked its resources? Have the Russians done what they&amp;rsquo;ve done for years, which is lie and spin about its real potential, taking hostages and threatening all around them? In truth it&amp;rsquo;s a large, leaky petrol station with nukes.</description></item><item><title>Addressing land capture and the new face of the world bank | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660084/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 04:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660084/</guid><description>Podcast Description The way out of the housing crisis, both in Ireland and abroad is going to require us to think as a collective and reject individualistic, speculative instincts. Let’s look at what can be done to create better cities and communities, it’s actually pretty simple. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>In defence of Democracy | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660085/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 04:00:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660085/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the eve of the invasion of Ukraine, we examine how fragile this idea of liberal democracy, where the individual is valued and protected, has become. Yes it has its problems and yes, on a number of fronts, it has not delivered for all, but would you change the combination of liberal democracy and capitalism? There are alternatives out there, I&amp;rsquo;m not sure I&amp;rsquo;d like to live in any.</description></item><item><title>The housing fix might be here - if we hold strong | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660086/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 04:00:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660086/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s finally happening, the government is going to tax vacant land! Or at least, they’re thinking about it. As a listener to the podcast, you&amp;rsquo;ll be aware that taxing land to bring it into use has been a cornerstone of what is necessary to bring about a more efficient use of land. Not surprisingly, those with most to lose - major landowners/speculators are pushing back. This fight is the future of housing in Ireland (and everywhere).</description></item><item><title>The great China/USA breakup | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660087/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 04:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660087/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week&amp;rsquo;s Chinese balloons are only the latest sign of tension between the two superpowers. The relationship between China and the US has deteriorated drastically in the last decade - what happened? Today we explore how China transformed itself from a simple producer to a high-tech producer, how that impacts their relationships on the global stage and why microchips are the epicentre of a trade and technology war that will define the coming decades.</description></item><item><title>Immigration Part 2: Is immigration a class issue? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660088/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 04:00:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660088/</guid><description>Podcast Description On last week’s episode we discussed the fact that immigration is good for the economy in the aggregate, but is it good for everyone? As with most things, poorer people and richer people experience life and its challenges differently. Poorer people compete with new immigrants in the housing and jobs market, as well as for public services. This creates tensions. We examine these social tensions, and look for some solutions.</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode: Why prices fluctuate - the impact of interest rates on our lives | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660089/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660089/</guid><description>Podcast Description This bonus episode is brought to you by Done Deal Motors.
Price and value don't exist in isolation - everything is relative. Join us for this bonus episode as we look at our social lens on value and the profound impact of interest rates on our lives
Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why are some countries more successful than others? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660090/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 04:58:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Economic growth is not distributed evenly. Why are some societies richer than others? What is the impact of economic growth? let&amp;rsquo;s look at the very essence of economics today and explain how successful economic growth has a profound impact on our daily lives. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The case for immigration | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660091/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 04:00:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Immigrants are used to having it hard, both in life an in the public eye where they are often vilified. This lambasting though is based on nothing more than lies - the truth is that immigrants helps society grow and prosper. It’s time to set the record straight. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Creating a new Currency | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660092/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 04:00:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Argentina and Brazil are currently undertaking the herculean task of creating a new currency based on the Euro model. Let’s discuss why they’re attempting this and how the Euro, the model they are following, came to be. The currency is the most important price in most economics, so getting this right is hugely important. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>In Praise of Cathedral Thinking | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660093/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 04:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660093/</guid><description>Podcast Description The people who build Europe&amp;rsquo;s gothic cathedrals knew that they wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be around to see them completed. They were building for people yet to be born. This is what we need to build liveable cities right now. Looking at John Gray the 19th century architect of Dublin&amp;rsquo;s water system, we apply Gray&amp;rsquo;s thinking and planning to the of the biggest urban dilemma of the 21st century: housing and urban planning.</description></item><item><title>Things Learnt Half way up the Alps | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660094/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 04:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Davos’s World Economic Forum, although often maligned for it’s ultra-wealthy attendees - and understandably so - is still an event that outlines, and in some cases, shapes the economic priorities of the world for the year ahead. Today we go right to the source to understand what is on the mind of this year’s speakers. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Around the world, 30 year olds are getting screwed | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660095/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 04:00:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660095/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s never been more expensive to be 30 something. The old social contract used to be, work hard, study, get a degree, keep your beak clean and soon enough your income will rise and you will end up richer than your parents. That&amp;rsquo;s no longer the case. The conveyor belt of upward social mobility has stalled. The Millennials are falling behind, while their parents are surging ahead. And what about the generation coming behind them?</description></item><item><title>The view from Kyiv - Part 2 | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660096/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 04:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Listen to the view of the region from my travelling companion to Ukraine, Sasha Kabanovsky, born and bred in Kyiv. We covered a lot of ground, historic, political, social and economic. Hope you enjoy it. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Letter from Kyiv | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660097/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 04:00:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660097/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a student I first went to the Soviet Union in 1987. Then spent months in the Russian countryside trying to learn the language in 1991. Since then, I have worked and travelled in both Russian and Ukraine. I was first in Kyiv in 1998, working in the Ukrainian economy. So I&amp;rsquo;ve spent many years in that part of the world and have friends from both countries. Last week, I went back to Kyiv with an old Ukrainian mate.</description></item><item><title>Unmasking cryptocurrency from both a financial and technological standpoint | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660098/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 04:00:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660098/</guid><description>Podcast Description 2022 saw many ups and downs - and one notable &amp;ldquo;down&amp;rdquo; was the fall of crypto-mania. While the madness feels behind us, most still don&amp;rsquo;t understand this &amp;ldquo;currency&amp;rdquo; that is shrouded in myths and lore - today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to make sense of it all. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The story of money | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660099/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 04:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Like fire, money has profoundly impacted our species. So much so that it’s development has shaped how we organize together, how the world was discovered and who innovated first (and best!). Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Reframing the housing crisis | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660100/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 04:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Let&amp;rsquo;s start the new year with a fresh perspective on housing - because looking at it differently can create new ideas to solve the problem! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A hard look at the return of Inflation - and why it hasn't been transitory | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660101/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 04:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660101/</guid><description>Podcast Description With inflation still very much present at the end of the year and various unions fighting to maintain their real world wages, some through strikes, let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at why inflation hasn&amp;rsquo;t been transitionary and how China has been able to hold it at bay for so long. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Irish Argentine | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660102/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 04:00:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Messi apart, the player that caught most people&amp;rsquo;s eye was Alexis McAlister. But how did his Irish family end up in the Pampas? Today we tell the story of the Irish Argentineans. More than 500,000 Argentineans are Irish-Argentineans, who are they and when did they leave Ireland. The most famous of course is Che Guevara Lynch. In February 1889, the largest single transport ship of immigrants ever to dock in Argentina was &amp;ldquo;The City of Dresden&amp;rdquo; and it came from Cork.</description></item><item><title>The UK’s transformation in 2022 | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660103/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 04:00:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660103/</guid><description>Podcast Description This year has been a turbulent one, across Europe, one of the countries that has felt this the most is the UK: 3 prime ministers in a year, a bank crisis and rising Scottish nationalism. Let’s explore how we got there and what might come next Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode: The economics of movies | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660104/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 05:06:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660104/</guid><description>Podcast Description This bonus episode is brought to you by NOW.
Where did movies come from? What costs and expenses are involved in making them? How has streaming platforms changed the types of movies being made? All this and more answered in this episode!
Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ukraine economics - Before &amp; after the war | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660105/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 04:05:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The new phase of the economy and short trading explained | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660106/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 04:00:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660106/</guid><description>Podcast Description With the latest macro-economic cycle coming to an end, let’s look at what’s next on the horizon and how to spot companies that are over-value with the help of the legend himself: Jim Chanos Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The end of competence | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660107/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 04:00:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660107/</guid><description>Podcast Description As we near the end of 2022 let’s look at the year that’s been, identify takeaways of what has passed and have a chat about what might be on the horizon for 2023 Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Adam Smith was wrong: we need to diversify, not specialize | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660108/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 04:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660108/</guid><description>Podcast Description The crazy things about economics is that so much of what we’re taught growing up is actually wrong. Today we take a look at the myth about specialization by talking about Fitzcarraldo, biology and the impact that diversification has had on Ireland Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The End of a 14-year Bull Market | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660109/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 04:00:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660109/</guid><description>Podcast Description The credit cycle is an unforgiving master, as interest rates rise, different questions are asked about both companies and investments. We examine the new world of positive interest rates and what it means for the global economy. With more than $3.4 trillion wiped off the value of tech companies, far more than the entire GDP of the UK, we assess the impact. Are you ready for the next phase of this cycle?</description></item><item><title>Finding Russia’s Remote Killers | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660110/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 04:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660110/</guid><description>Podcast Description As the war between Russia and Ukraine grinds into winter, Putin&amp;rsquo;s new strategy is to destroy Ukrainian infrastructure. What it couldn&amp;rsquo;t achieve on the battle field Russia aims to achieve in the living room, by trying to freeze ordinary Ukrainians. Today we have a fascinating chat with European Investigative Journalist of the Year Christo Grozev of Bellingcat on how he identified the poisoners of Alexi Navalny and how, using the same techniques, he has identified the Russia&amp;rsquo;s remote killers, the civilian men and women, computer programmers, software engineers and data specialists living normal lives in Russia, who actually push the buttons and program the missiles raining down on Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>The great crypto collapse | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660111/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 04:00:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660111/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;rsquo;ve always been &amp;ldquo;Doomcoiners&amp;rdquo; - yes, you guessed it, not fans of crypto. Now you know why. A passing understanding of monetary economics and monetary history would have warned anyone to be very careful. One of the biggest crypto exchange has filled for bankruptcy and across the board crypto currency valuation is in free fall - How did we end up here? And more critically, what sort of frauds will be unearthed when the dust settles.</description></item><item><title>Planning for 10 Million people | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660112/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 04:00:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ireland&amp;rsquo;s population is set to grow rapidly. Like a parent buying a-size-too-big-clothes for a teenagers, the State needs to be building infrastructure for an island population of 10 million. We explore this critical issue, plus musings of Toto Schilacci, the economic equivalent of playing keepy-uppies with Maradona and lots more. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The nature of money | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660113/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 14:51:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join us on this wide ranging conversation on the nature of money that might change. the way you look at central banks, investments, spending and much more! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Letter from America | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660114/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 04:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660114/</guid><description>Podcast Description I&amp;rsquo;m in NYC this week and caught up with Jeff Goldberg, editor of The Atlantic magazine. With the American midterm elections, the collapse of FTX exchange and Ukraine&amp;rsquo;s victories in the field, we discuss the State of the Union, the American mindset as revealed in the elections, and America&amp;rsquo;s role in the world. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tech Feudalism with Yanis Varoufakis | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660115/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is Capitalism dead? There’s a new media and retail ecosystem that is controlled by a select few who use algorithms to curate what we consume and how we shop… sounds like Feudalism! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How the world changes with interest rates - Live from Kilkenomics | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660116/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 04:00:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Taking a look at the long-term economics shifts we breakdown how everything has changed since the pandemics - from international allies to cost of living crisis, it’s all here! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is Ukraine a distraction for a Taiwan takeover? - With Angelica Oung | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660117/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 04:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660117/</guid><description>Podcast Description With the world’s eyes turned to the conflict between Ukraine and Russia - are the Chinese about to make a move on Taiwan while the world is distracted? Today we’re joined by angelica Oung to talk about increased tensions between China and the island. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Housing market shifts and tech stock carnage - With Katie Martin | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660118/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 04:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660118/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is a buyer’s panic being followed by a seller’s panic in the housing market? Plus, what is happening in the tech sector? This week, the market valuation of tech stock went down by almost a Trillion dollars - let’s figure out what’s happening. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode: How to thrive in these turbulent times | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660119/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 03:00:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660119/</guid><description>Podcast Description This bonus episode is brought to you by Square.
Retail has been changing drastically over the last few years, on this pod we take a look at the history of trade, the current disruptions from Covid and Ecommerce and where it might go next!
Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The house price horror show - With Vinjeru Mkandawire | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660120/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 03:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660120/</guid><description>Podcast Description There’s a wind of change in the air, globally house prices are falling by double digits? What’s happening? Why now? We’re joined by The Economist’s global property correspondent: Vinjeru Mkandawire to answer all that and more! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The UK’s fall from grace, it's not about politicians, it's about policy. | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660121/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 03:00:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Economic stability is no laughing matter - and quite a bit more fragile than people believe. The UK may have a new PM but does it have a new vision? What’s its business model? And critically how does it address the economic, political, social and regional inequalities? Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We might already be in World War 3 - it’s just not what you thought it would look like - With Pippa Malmgren | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660122/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 03:00:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660122/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pippa joins us today to talk about about the state of global geopolitics and makes a case for the world being in a third global war - just not on land but rather at sea and in space. It’s fascinating stuff and might change the way you see the world! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>London Calling! - With Mark Blyth | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660123/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 03:00:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660123/</guid><description>Podcast Description The UK is in a mess, how did it get there and how does it get out, or can it? It&amp;rsquo;s much more than Truss. It&amp;rsquo;s a decade of shite decisions. Lots going on in this episode, chatting to the brilliant Mark Blyth but the upshot is what is happening in London can happen anywhere and if the UK, for years the global centre of finance, can&amp;rsquo;t stabilise its markets, what hope for the rest?</description></item><item><title>Why central bankers want higher unemployment | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660124/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 02:00:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660124/</guid><description>Podcast Description When your mate loses his job it&amp;rsquo;s a downturn, when you lose your&amp;rsquo;s, its a recession. And you know what, the world&amp;rsquo;s central bankers will not juts be cheering you losing your job, they&amp;rsquo;ll be causing it. Economic policy all over the world is now aimed and bringing about a recession to bring down inflation. What this means in plain English is job losses, leading to widespread unemployment. Tighten your belt.</description></item><item><title>The new energy reality | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660125/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 02:30:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660125/</guid><description>Podcast Description OPEC+ has announced that it will reduce its production quota by 2 Million barrels per day - something the west has seen as OPEC+ siding with the Kremlin. What does that mean for. your life? For our economy and cost of living? Join us as we talk all about it Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>UK experiments &amp; Irish stability | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660126/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 02:00:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660126/</guid><description>Podcast Description When the Tories lose the trust of the financial markets you know that something has gone incredibly wrong. History tells us that people need to trust the governments for them to succeed - let’s look at what Germany did post WW2, what Ireland is doing and what’s going on over in the UK Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The crucial link between the planet and your pension | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660127/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 02:30:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660127/</guid><description>Podcast Description In partnership with Irish Life , we bring you: The crucial link between the planet and your pension - because making the right investments can end up being more environmentally friendly than taking the bus! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>UK chaos and bond doom loop | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660128/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 02:30:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660128/</guid><description>Podcast Description The global financial markets, particularly the bond markets are in bad shape, and the UK was the first to show how bad it can get, but this is not a UK problem - its a global problem. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Endgame for Putin? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660129/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 01:30:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660129/</guid><description>Podcast Description With the &amp;ldquo;mobilization&amp;rdquo; Putin reveals that he is running out of road. He is doing what he always does, escalating. To make sense of this escalation, and living with this regime, we talk to a Russian insider to guide us through these new developments. If you are interested in Russia, don&amp;rsquo;t miss this. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is Liz Truss the leader of a Doomsday Cult? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660130/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 01:30:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660130/</guid><description>Podcast Description The UK, already the most unequal country in Western Europe, just got more unequal. We start by breaking through the internet noise with tangible facts about inequality and standard of living, comparing Ireland, UK. US and Norway. Then we examine the madness of the UK&amp;rsquo;s budget, Sterling collapsing, gilts tanking and a country unhinged over there, before settling down to the predictable stability and calm of the Irish budget!</description></item><item><title>Populism might not be what you think | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660131/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 01:30:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Populism is often vilified - but it’s origin is far more noble than you might think - and we might all need a bit more populism moving forward! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>With interest rates going up, housing market is heading down | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660132/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 01:30:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660132/</guid><description>Podcast Description Housing is a global asset class now and now that rates are rising, lots of leveraged property funds are likely to go bust. How is this going to play out and what does it all mean? Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How inflation in the 1970s brought us to our current situation - and what we can do about it | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660133/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 02:30:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660133/</guid><description>Podcast Description The economy is full of unintended consequences - and those ripple through time for decades. How the world stopped inflation in 1970 brought on our current world view - but this time we’re fighting inflation radically differently… Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Queen is dead. What now for her kingdom? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660134/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 02:30:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660134/</guid><description>Podcast Description A few months back we talked about 1922 being the year the 20th actually began, in terms of modernism, ideology, politics and economics. We mused whether the same would be said of 2022, that this momentous year -with everything that is happening - would be the year the 21st century actually begins. There is nothing more 20th century than the British Empire and their monarchy. Is this the end of that road and what does that mean for the UK?</description></item><item><title>Lizz Truss: Friend or Foe? And the state of the UK nation | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660135/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 02:30:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660135/</guid><description>Podcast Description The rotating cast of Torie leaders continues, this time it’s Lizz Truss’s time in the spotlight. What exactly is going on in the UK, and where is the nation headed? Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How it all came down: The story of the last leader of the USSR | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660136/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 02:30:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660136/</guid><description>Podcast Description More than a few years back, I got the chance to sit down and chat to the most consequential politician of my life, Mikhail Gorbachev, the last President of the USSR - the very antithesis to Vladimir Putin in every way, politically, intellectually and emotionally. We look back at his life and a leader who drastically changed the course of the world. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>The Chinese property bubble has just burst, here’s what you need to know | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660137/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 02:30:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Many in China have stopped paying their mortgages - what happened to this once golden goose of investment? And perhaps more importantly: how does this end? Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>With Euro/dollar below parity, lets talk exchange rates | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660138/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 02:30:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660138/</guid><description>Podcast Description Within the Euro, given the vastly different economic structures and stage of economic development, some countries, like Ireland, have undervalued exchange rates and others, like Croatia/Italy/Greece have overvalued exchange rates. This means that Ireland experiences massive supply problems, in housing, transport, too much inward investment etc, while the others experience severe deficient demand problems, unemployment, emigration etc. This represents a permanent flaw at the heart of the system; will it be fixed in the next crisis?</description></item><item><title>Weedenomics | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660139/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 02:30:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660139/</guid><description>Podcast Description The war on drugs has failed and the public perception of marijuana is changing rapidly, here&amp;rsquo;s some numbers that underscore why legalization is long overdue! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Financing a Revolution: The economics of Michael Collins | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660140/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 02:30:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660140/</guid><description>Podcast Description New countries start with no money. The departing colonists take everything with them, including capital. Like all former colonies, the New Ireland had no money. Micheal Collins, revolutionary leader and Minister of Finance, as well as head of the army, laid out a plan. From crowd-funding the 1916-1921 revolution, to setting up a national bank and a new national insurance company, designed to stop capital flowing to London, from marketing Ireland abroad, to rejecting state socialism and focusing on investment both national and foreign, Collins&amp;rsquo; economic vision for Ireland was the direct opposite to either the conservatism of the first 1920s governments or twisted radicalism of De Valera.</description></item><item><title>The Economics of Music | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660141/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 02:30:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today an Irish artist needs to get around 4000 streams an hour or about 300,000 per month to earn the minimum wage which we know is far below what is needed to pay the rent. How can someone survive trying to be a musician? Today we explore the &amp;ldquo;new&amp;rdquo; economics of music, what is the financial reality for young and not so young musicians, the history of the music industry and why the economic of our old friend Joseph Schumpeter is behind it all.</description></item><item><title>Why the housing crisis can undo 30 years of economic growth | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660142/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 02:30:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660142/</guid><description>Podcast Description All over the world rent prices are skyrocketing and bringing unbearable pressure on the young and the most vulnerable. let’s talk about how this comes about and what can be done to fix it. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How behavioural economics and personalization shapes your life | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660143/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660143/</guid><description>Podcast Description In partnership with Liberty Insurance, we bring you: Nudges, choices and personalization - today&amp;rsquo;s episode is all about the countless small decisions we make everyday and how those choices are being influenced in new &amp;amp; various ways. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Return of Malthus? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660144/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660144/</guid><description>Podcast Description Droughts in Europe, resource-wars and global warming got us thinking about Thomas Malthus and his observations about population. Can we square the world&amp;rsquo;s finite resources with the demands of 7 billion wannabe consumers? We talk positive checks, why hunter gathers were taller and ate better than the first farmers, plus the big Malthusian warning from the past, the Irish Famine. In the past two hundred years ,the world prized itself free of the Malthusian Trap via technology; could we be about to fall back into the grip of Malthus?</description></item><item><title>Taiwan and the Global Economy (With Angelica Oung) | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660145/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660145/</guid><description>Podcast Description Taiwan was all over the news this week. We explore why this small island will be the most sensitive geo-strategic location for the coming showdown between the USA and China. The global economy can survive a conflict with Russia, with China all bets are off. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is Putin winning? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660146/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 02:30:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660146/</guid><description>Podcast Description The War in Ukraine is entering its 6th month, many predicted it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t last 6 days. As time drags on and Russia&amp;rsquo;s energy strategy begins to pay off, can the West remain united? What does phase 2 of the war look like - and who is the most likely winner? Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why Manufacturing Matters | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660147/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 02:00:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660147/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ireland is a manufacturing powerhouse, producing half as much as the UK per year, despite having a population that is 13 times smaller. With 1% of EU&amp;rsquo;s population, Ireland produces 5% of total EU industrial output. 30 years ago, Ireland had practically no manufacturing base to speak of. How was this transformation achieved? Can it be sustained? Can a strong manufacturing base explain a countries political and social outlook and what else can developed from manufacturing prowess?</description></item><item><title>Why the Italian government crumbled | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660148/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 02:30:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660148/</guid><description>Podcast Description Draghi is out and the Italian government is heading for yet another election - what is happening with this country that seems to be in constant political turmoil? Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How &amp; why recessions happen | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660149/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 02:30:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660149/</guid><description>Podcast Description Starting with a Chinese example before moving to Ireland, we breakdown how exactly recessions happen, how one person’s behaviour spreads through society and what the current signals are saying about the winter to come Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Coming Currency Crises. Are you safe? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660150/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 02:30:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660150/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bit of a macroeconomic-fest this one. We examine currency crises and why currency collapses could become contagious. We are heading into strange economic times, expect far more currency crises than the mainstream expects. Watch this space in the Autumn. Expect debt forgiveness ahead. Plus this week we have a new slot: my answers to your questions on Patreon. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>What China’s shock recession means for you! | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660151/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 02:30:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660151/</guid><description>Podcast Description China is hurtling towards recession. This is a dramatic shift in the global economy which will have huge unforeseen consequence for the economy. Plus, last week Sony Kapoor outlined why the economically, financially and politically next ten years won’t be any like the last two or three decades. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The new financial era is here for a coming world where there will be more Nigerians than Europeans | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660152/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 02:30:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660152/</guid><description>Podcast Description For financial markets, the last three decades of easy money is officially over. Sony Kapoor joins us to tease out the world economy at this inflection point. Fascinating, wide ranging, optimistic and urgent. You&amp;rsquo;ll love this one! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The end of Boris Johnson and the British Inconsistent Triplet | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660153/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 02:30:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660153/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s finally happening! The &amp;ldquo;chaos monkey&amp;rdquo; is gone, but the chaos remains. We look at the trilemma facing the next British leader or as I prefer to call it the &amp;ldquo;inconsistent triplet&amp;rdquo; at the heart of UK policy making. What comes next for the UK? Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>In conversation with Gary Shteyngard | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660154/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 02:30:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660154/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s pod is going to be slightly eccentric, we’re going to look at the world’s big events of the last year through the eyes of one of the world’s best satirist: Gary Shteyngard. In this wide ranging interview we’ll cover everything from Russia to Covid - and everything in between! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>People have the Power | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660155/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 02:30:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660155/</guid><description>Podcast Description As Patti Smith sang, People have the Power. The economic pendulum is swinging from capital to labor, from profits to wages, and these shifts never happen smoothly, markets - previously priced profits -freak out, central banks no longer support companies&amp;rsquo; P/L and we are in for a tumultuous few months, as the world digest what is happening. Economies, demographics, realpolitik &amp;amp; technology always change the face of our society, so are we now at the moment where the worker reclaims his and her pricing power?</description></item><item><title>The future of the internet with Tim O’Reilly | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660156/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 02:30:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660156/</guid><description>Podcast Description Metaverse, web 3.0 and NFTs have been appearing everywhere online in the last year - but what exactly are they? And perhaps more importantly, what do their arrival mean for our daily lives? Today we try to simplify it all with the help of Tim O’Reilly Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The transformation of Ireland and what comes next | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660157/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 02:30:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660157/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s episode looks at the long &amp;amp; the short of Ireland’s transformation. Through a series of choices we have carved a unique place within Europe - where do we go next? Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We don’t know ourselves - A conversation with Fintan O’Toole | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660158/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 02:30:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660158/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have things really changed? Is Ireland really that different than it was? What are the personalities that have marked our history? Through a wide ranging conversation with Fintan O’Toole we explore these topics to bring the spirit of Ireland to life in an unexpected way. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The future of the internet economy with Stripe co-founder: John Collison | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660159/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 02:30:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660159/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we’re bringing you a unique conversation that I had with John Collison over the weekend where I got to ask him a wide variety of questions covering innovation, crypto, macro-trends for the internet and even flying cars! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The 2nd Atomic Age | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660160/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 02:30:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660160/</guid><description>Podcast Description With markets gyrating all over the shop, it&amp;rsquo;s easy to forget the big picture. The price of energy is the foundational price in any economy. Right now it&amp;rsquo;s too high, but it will come down. And, getting it down, plus achieving net zero on carbon emissions are two of the most critical objectives for the entire globe. So how do we get enough clean energy to power the world, and bring down pollution?</description></item><item><title>Inflation returns (kinda), what would James Joyce think? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660161/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 02:30:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660161/</guid><description>Podcast Description Inflation is back. Don&amp;rsquo;t panic&amp;hellip;.unless you bought Bitcoin in the past year. Inflation will abate as the policy and the economy adjust, but it may take a bit of time. Plus Bloomonomics - the economics of Ulysses and it&amp;rsquo;s hero Leopold Bloom - what it tells us about creating and fostering civic, mixed living cities - which are the font of most innovation, and economic growth. Join the gang!</description></item><item><title>Platinum Jubilee, Sordid Slavery | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660162/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 02:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660162/</guid><description>Podcast Description As the UK celebrates the Queen Elizabeth&amp;rsquo;s Jubilee, we forget that monarchies have historically sat on top of an economic system with slaves, colonies and extractive settlements, the objective of which was to steal wholesale from the colonised countries and peoples. The legacy of the colonialism runs deep in many parts of the world. This week we focus on the Caribbean, its traumatic legacy and how the money taken from there fuelled the capital markets of the 18th century and the industrial revolution.</description></item><item><title>What hairdressers and Lobster Thermidor tell us about the economy, employment and inflation | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660163/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 02:30:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660163/</guid><description>Podcast Description The economy is changing rapidly, we are seeing challenges everywhere, almost all have to do with an excess of demand and deficient supply. This is, in the context of the past hundred years economic history, a brilliant to place to be! is But we might be looking at big developments, not just for policy, but for the coming conflict between public sectors and the governments - everywhere. Join the gang!</description></item><item><title>Putin and the long game against the West | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660164/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 02:30:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660164/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last week president Zelensky addressed Davos asking the WEF to help Ukraine rebuild, we talk being at Davos, and why in many ways Davos Man has been involved with Russia long before the Ukraine war came along. We also hear from Bill Browder about the nature of dealing with Putin and question as to whether the West will hold strong against Putin&amp;rsquo;s long game. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.</description></item><item><title>Brexiternity - the only way the Tories to stay in power | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660165/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 02:30:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660165/</guid><description>Podcast Description We focus on our closet neighbour the UK today as it turns its back on the metric system. Yes, true, you believe it? We explore why the Tories have to keep Brexit going. It&amp;rsquo;s their only electoral meal ticket. Expect more &amp;ldquo;false flag&amp;rdquo; operations, more weaponizing of Northern Ireland and more jingoistic nonsense about imperial weights, miles, furlongs and the like. You never know, if we wait long enough decimalization might be gone and they&amp;rsquo;ll be back to the half-crown, farthing and shilling!</description></item><item><title>There's great dryin' in that wind! | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660166/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 02:30:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660166/</guid><description>Podcast Description Economics is energy and energy is economics. Imagine a country blessed with renewable energy, able to power itself and export electricity, faced with the opportunity to completely transform its economy and society and contribute positively to eliminating carbon emissions? That country is Ireland; and outcrop in the north Atlantic buffeted by maritime winds. When Mammy said there&amp;rsquo;s great drying in that wind, she was talking about the transformative opportunity that living in a constant gale affords.</description></item><item><title>A Global Perfect Storm | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660167/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 02:30:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660167/</guid><description>Podcast Description Markets are suffering from global contagion. Stock markets are down 22% this year. Bonds are tanking too. There are at least four if not five proximate reasons as the global economy heads towards coordinated recession. China (17% of the global economy) is at a stand still due to zero covid, the US is fighting inflation. Europe&amp;rsquo;s real incomes have been squeezed by &amp;ldquo;Putinflation&amp;rdquo; and emerging markets are running out of dollars.</description></item><item><title>Living with inflation, the story of Turkey | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660168/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 02:30:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660168/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s episode is going to be exploring the intersection between Turkey and inflation, a country that has been living for many years with what traditional metrics would call “out of control” inflation for the last few years. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Coins and Crypto Carnage | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660169/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 02:30:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660169/</guid><description>Podcast Description Digital assets are crashing across the board, something that we’ve warned about across various episodes. Today’s chat is about what is happening &amp;amp; why its happening - is this going to be like the .com crash or like the sub-prime crisis (much worse). Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Scandinavian Models | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660170/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 02:30:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660170/</guid><description>Podcast Description Swanneying around Gothenburg this week, the thought stuck me how do these people do it? Why do the Scandinavians do this so well economically, from income, to health, to women feeling safe walking alone at night, Scandinavian countries lead the way, why? Starting from a car wash analogy, we interrogate wage equality, why higher wages at the lower-end are critical to innovation and creating a more fair society - something the Scandinavian countries seem to have figured out ahead of everyone else!</description></item><item><title>The coming interest rate crusade against inflation? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660171/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 02:30:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660171/</guid><description>Podcast Description Imagine mortgage rates at 8%, inconceivable possibly but when you think about it not completely out of the question. Historically we&amp;rsquo;ve been here before. We examine the last time the interest/inflation cycle turned, what happened, who paid most and what were the long-term consequences? Buckle up for the ride. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Death of Distance - direct from Inis Meain | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660172/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 02:30:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660172/</guid><description>Podcast Description This one’s a special one: we’re coming to you from Inis Meain, the middle island of the three Aran islands to discuss how Covid and connectivity has enhanced our ability to thrive in remote locations, how going upmarket is the way forward and how this small Irish-speaking community is preserving its (and our) roots while at the same time, adjusting to this new modern reality. Ultimately we are witnessing the death of distance, and, in the future, the more distant you are, the more you will benefit.</description></item><item><title>What can the Reformation tell us about Twitter, Martin Luther, Elon Musk and Vladimir Putin? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660173/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 02:30:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660173/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is power? How is it acquired and who owns it? We look at the economics of power, the power of networks and the &amp;ldquo;strength of weak ties&amp;rdquo; and the constant historic tension between vertical power, the type deployed by Putin, and horizontal power the type sought by Musk. Plus we explore what they can both learn from the master &amp;ldquo;influencer&amp;rdquo; of the early 16th century, Martin Luther. Join the gang!</description></item><item><title>The Biggest Question in Economics - How exactly does and economy grow or contract? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660174/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 02:30:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660174/</guid><description>Podcast Description Economies weren’t always focused on growth, as weird as that might sound now, growth, is a relatively new concept. Today we’re joined by one of the greats: Mark Blyth, who talks to us about past &amp;amp; future growth rates… and how the planet plays into it. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The centre just held in France, but with houses prices out of control, will it here? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660175/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 02:30:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660175/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s episode covers a wide range of economic headlines, from the Inis Meain 10k, the critical roll of credit unions, Macron&amp;rsquo;s win, to Irish housing and what the dysfunctional markets for cars in Cuba can tell us about the equally dysfunctional Irish housing market. Hope you enjoy it&amp;hellip;if that&amp;rsquo;s the word! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The third world debt crisis is going to affect you | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660176/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 02:30:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660176/</guid><description>Podcast Description One continent has been missing from the headlines lately - Africa: they’re going through a severe debt crisis and with the current state of globalization, what happens there is going to ripple here. Join us as we break it down with David McNair Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>231 - Germany's dreadful choice &amp; Elon Musk's “Chaos monkey” moment | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660177/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 02:30:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660177/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s episode is split in two - we start by looking at what German cowardice &amp;amp; its refusal to sanction Russian gas means for both the war and the western alliance. Then we talk Twitter with Mark Little who helps us breakdown the issues thrown up by Musk&amp;rsquo;s bid to take over Twitter and what it tells us about the economics of the internet. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.</description></item><item><title>230 - How to save democracy | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660178/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 02:30:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660178/</guid><description>Podcast Description Democracy is often accepted as a given - but it is anything but. Today we tackle the myths about democracy and immigrants to hopefully lay the blueprints for a more resilient society. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>229 - Pipes, Pumps and Putin. The Energy Crisis is here. | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660179/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 02:30:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660179/</guid><description>Podcast Description Europe usually has a 14 day supply of diesel, which is currently down to 4 days. In the coming days Russia might cut off Europe or Europe might decide to stop buying from Russia - what happens then? Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>228 - The uncomfortable reality of our energy future | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660180/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 02:30:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we’re joined by Doomberg to talk about the way out of our energy crisis - because energy is quite literally life.
The way out of this mess might necessitate us coming to grips with the fact that we’re going to have some imperfect allies to survive.
Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>227 - Crunch Time for Energy | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660181/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 02:30:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660181/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week is all about energy - Putin’s betting Europe won&amp;rsquo;t stand firm, if diesel begins to run out. The next few weeks will be crucial. We&amp;rsquo;ve have not seen an energy crisis like this since 1973. With inflation set to rise further and output slumping due to our ill-conceived dependence on Russian energy, it&amp;rsquo;s crunch time for Europe! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>226 - REITs and the possible end of Russia | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660182/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 02:30:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660182/</guid><description>Podcast Description We start with a breakdown of what exactly is a REIT before the conversation turns to Russia - and more specifically the multi-faceted population of Russia. Are we nearing the point where the population reminds Moscow that it doesn’t speak for the whole country? Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>225 - The economics of energy | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660183/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 02:30:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660183/</guid><description>Podcast Description Economics has always been about energy. When the price of energy rises, everything follows. We go to the Gulf to understand the politics of energy and Putin&amp;rsquo;s calculation that an energy war will cause a Western recession, just like 1973, may well come off. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>224 - The Resurgence of the Liberal order | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660184/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 02:33:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660184/</guid><description>Podcast Description Putin has weaponized global capital and because of that action I believe that we will see investment flow towards liberal democracies, which is a massive economic opportunity for the countries that will present themselves as a safe place to use business - but we have to get inflation under control! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>223 - China at a tipping point | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660185/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 03:30:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660185/</guid><description>Podcast Description China looks to have made its choice for now, and it is with Russia. This might be the most consequential decision for the world economy since the fall of the Berlin wall. Globalization is in the balance and a bipolar world of us and them, now looks likely. Why would China risk everything to bail out Putin? Thats the question. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>222 - Odessa - the vibrant symbol of urban irreverence and why it irritates Putin so much. | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660186/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 03:30:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660186/</guid><description>Podcast Description As the war in Ukraine continues, we focus on an extraordinary city which could well be the next Russian target, Odessa. A product of commerce and an effervescent example of urban economics, Odessa is cosmopolitan, tolerant, self-reinventing, brimming of various ethnicities, home to Russian intellectual greats Pushkin, Babel, Eisenstein and Jabotinsky. Today this great city is on the frontline. We explore its economy and history, and why destroying this city is akin to destroying an idea, which is why it will be impossible.</description></item><item><title>221 - Why climate change is an investment, not a cost | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660187/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660187/</guid><description>Podcast Description To reach the global climate goals in 2030, we need to half our emissions, so speed is the name of the game! Join us as Eric Lonergan &amp;amp; Corinne Sawers talk about the steps and mindset that we need to adopt to save the planet. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>220 - Russian sanctions explained with Sony Kapoor | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660188/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 04:30:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660188/</guid><description>Podcast Description Let&amp;rsquo;s look at the next stage of sanctions, how they&amp;rsquo;re designed and how the whole world is reacting to their implementation. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>219 - Women in economics | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660189/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 01:30:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660189/</guid><description>Podcast Description The celebrate international women’s day we ask why are women still so underrepresented in economics? Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>218 - Russian sanctions &amp; Wartime speculations | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660190/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 02:30:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660190/</guid><description>Podcast Description The west is fighting a new type of war - an economic war instead of a ground war. Let’s investigate what is going on &amp;amp; wether or not its going to work. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>217 - The Economics of the War | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660191/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660191/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we frame the invasion of Ukraine as a war against the &amp;ldquo;idea&amp;rdquo; of the EU. For Putin, Ukraine is only the start. The big prize is destabilizing the EU. So far he has miscalculated, but it&amp;rsquo;s early days. We examine the Ukrainian economy, who will stand up to Putin and we chat to the brilliant Norwegian economist, Martin Sandbu of the Financial Times. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.</description></item><item><title>216 - Russia/Ukraine and where we go next | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660192/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 02:00:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660192/</guid><description>Podcast Description Russia has amputated a chunk of Ukraine. War is now looming in Europe. How did we end up here? Where did diplomacy go wrong? What is coming next? Today’s episode aims to simply explain the whole situation and provide some thoughts about what might happen next. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>215 - Are interest rates the solution to inflation? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660193/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 03:30:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660193/</guid><description>Podcast Description The most talked about solution to fight off inflation is interest rates - but is that blunt instrument really going to fix such a complex problem? Join us as we bring in Dario Perkins to give us his point of view. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>214 - Are the central banks working for you? Or big money? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660194/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 03:30:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660194/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s episode is a fascinating interview with Christoper Leonard who walks us through his latest book and brings to life how the FED and central banks around the world have rarely been on the side of the little guy. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>213 - How do we solve the inflation problem? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660195/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 03:30:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660195/</guid><description>Podcast Description All around the world people are feeling their purchasing power shrink: as inflation rises the cost of living - and indeed your real wealth - goes down. What is causing this? Is this going to continue? How do we make it go away? All that &amp;amp; more in today’s episode. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>212 - The full shilling? The case for crypto as a speculative asset - but a currency, eh no! | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660196/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 03:30:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660196/</guid><description>Podcast Description Crypto has captured the imagination of many as way to get rich quick - but few are able to agree or even explain what it actually is. In today’s conversation we are joined by Michael Saylor, one of the biggest bitcoin holder, to explain what it is and how you might be using it - spoiler alert: he doesn’t think it’s a currency either! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.</description></item><item><title>211 - Understanding inflation through the man behind the FED in America | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660197/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 03:30:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660197/</guid><description>Podcast Description Behind every decision is human beings, who they are, how they act &amp;amp; where they’re from is critical to understanding the context in which any given decision is taken. In light of the announced interest rate hikes we attempt to pull back the curtain and understand who is Jerome Powell (besides the chair of the federal reserve of the United States) - because his actions in the coming year will ripple across the world Join the gang!</description></item><item><title>210 - Russian tensions explained &amp; pub economics | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660198/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 03:30:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660198/</guid><description>Podcast Description Russia has been dominating headlines as of late and clickbait titles want you to believe that World War 3 is on the horizon - What is really happening in Russia? Join us as we hear from people living there what news they are hearing and how they see this large scale posturing play out. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>209 - If global warming is the question, free public transport is the answer | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660199/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 03:30:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660199/</guid><description>Podcast Description With the return to office happening all around the world, we’re seeing old problems come back; namely, traffic and congestion in cities. This is something we can, and should, solve - join us as we look at how we make it work for everyone. Plus on the 100th anniversary of the publication of Ulysses, what would Leopold Bloom have to say about traffic, land tax and urban economics. Join the gang!</description></item><item><title>208 - Breaking down the metaverse &amp; why we we need to disconnect | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660200/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 03:30:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660200/</guid><description>Podcast Description There’s massive amounts of money being thrown around by people who are trying to invest in the metaverse… so what exactly is it? And perhaps more importantly: is it a necessary or even a desirable future that these companies are setting up for us. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>207 - What's happening in finance, why all the crashing? Plus, the key to unlocking the Irish economy | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660201/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 03:30:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660201/</guid><description>Podcast Description We breakdown what is happening with the falling stocks in the tech sector by talking about bonds, inflation and returns on investment before looking at the state of the Irish economy as we emerge from lockdown. Spoiler alert: Housing is involved! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>206 - Is it Last call for Boris Johnson? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660202/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 03:30:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660202/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today is about the UK: as Boris Johnson fights for his political life we breakdown the timeline of events that brought us here, when &amp;amp; how this all might end and finally: what is legacy might be. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>205 - Can the centre hold? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660203/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 03:30:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660203/</guid><description>Podcast Description WB Yeats in his poem &amp;ldquo;The Second Coming&amp;rdquo;, described a world, 100 odd years ago, where the forces of economics and politics meant that &amp;ldquo;things fall apart&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;the centre cannot hold&amp;rdquo;. In many ways he was right. In 1922, the centre didn&amp;rsquo;t hold, not in Ireland, not anywhere. Things did fall apart. Today we look at the complexion of Irish society as it is, not as sloganeers might want it to be and ask the same question.</description></item><item><title>204 - The Origin of Covid. Where precisely did it come from? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660204/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 03:30:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660204/</guid><description>Podcast Description Where exactly did Covid come from? Today’s episode tackles the origin of Covid, where did it come from, the food chain or a lab leak? A lab leak opens the door to all sorts of questions, geo-political, scientific and ethical. In fact, its one of the most important questions surrounding the pandemic and yet, it is the question few have asked? Conventional wisdom says it jumped from bats to animals in a Wuhan market, what it this is not true?</description></item><item><title>203 - Is this the year crypto crashes? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660205/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 03:30:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660205/</guid><description>Podcast Description I&amp;rsquo;ve no idea whether crypto and Bitcoin in particular will crash, double or stay where it is. No one does. In economic terms, cryptocurrency is definitely SOMETHING, but at this stage, it is patently not money. Join us as we explain how Bitcoin is clearly an asset, but its is definitely not money. Why a good way to look at money is to imagine it is like language and why money is a technology not a commodity.</description></item><item><title>202 - The Washington Putsch - One Year on | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660206/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 03:30:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660206/</guid><description>Podcast Description Let&amp;rsquo;s talk America one year to the day after storming of Capitol Hill. Some warn the US is moving towards civil war, certainly the place is divided, what of the early Biden optimism and just when you though it was safe to dream again, he&amp;rsquo;s back, more orange than ever. All this a discussion on productivity, wages and growth in Ireland. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>201 - The World at a Tipping Point | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660207/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 03:30:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660207/</guid><description>Podcast Description The New Year and a new credit cycle. In 2021 the world was awash with money, but will this continue in 2022? If not what will it mean for the economy, for you, and for confidence? All credit cycles follow similar paths, we trace these cycles. Also what about European and Irish tech in the next 12 months and how John is becoming a drummer. Join the gang! https://plus.</description></item><item><title>200 - The economics of Nighttime. Why we need more not less, socializing! | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660208/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 03:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660208/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Christmas! Hope you had a good one! Weird that this week we are talking about more boozing, more socializing, more venues, more events, more late nights, more entertainment just when things are closing down, but the best gift we can give the social economy, is open up everything, no more Victorian licences, and embrace the night time economy. For a city to live, it has to be 24 hours, for those who want to go out, where they like, when they like.</description></item><item><title>199 - the Central banks have spoken… what does it mean? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660209/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 03:30:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660209/</guid><description>Podcast Description Around the world the central banks have announced their vision for what 2022 will look like - How will these announcements affect your Daily budget and your ability to make biggest purchases? Join us to find out! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>198 - The economics of Football | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660210/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660210/</guid><description>Podcast Description There&amp;rsquo;s an extra episode this week!Thanks to the folks at NOW we&amp;rsquo;re bringing you the economics of football to understand clubs really work, what are the incentives driving their behaviors and how in many ways they mirror our broader economy as a whole. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>197 - The changing political landscape in Ireland &amp; the UK | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660211/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660211/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today is all about politics as Kevin Cunningham joins us to breakdown the latest numbers for Ireland and the UK Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>196 - The Russian crisis that nobody saw coming | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660212/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660212/</guid><description>Podcast Description The rising tensions between Russian and Ukraine has flared up faster than anyone could have predicted and we&amp;rsquo;re now at the edge of what could be the biggest story of the year - so let&amp;rsquo;s break down exactly what is happening and more importantly, WHY its happening Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>195: The economics that made America | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660213/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660213/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s episode we get all historical and look at economics of Alexander Hamilton, the man who forged America and got murdered for his troubles. Through his eyes we tackle hyper-inflation, financing revolution, central banking, government borrowing and trade and wonder why it all still feels so contemporary. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>194 - What happens now? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660214/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660214/</guid><description>Podcast Description As we go into another quasi-lockdown, what does it mean for the economy. What as Covid done to our understanding of the economy, why is this so different and what is likely to happen to the economy and in financial markets which are already expensive. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>193 - Comparing innovation between the US and Europe with Michael Fertik | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660215/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660215/</guid><description>Podcast Description As we begin to take stock of the year we’re looking at how the pandemic has changed the working landscape through the lens of innovations and entrepreneurship. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>192 - Movement: markets, people and viruses | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660216/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660216/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the span of a single week, a bright outlook for 2022 is now starting to look quite bleak as the new South African Covid variant enters our communities &amp;amp; media cycles. Today’s episode is all about how movement works, across people, financial markets &amp;amp; of course… COVID Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>191 - China and America's latest Sputnik moment | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660217/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660217/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we talk about China: its growth, its dominance and perhaps most importantly; its future Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>190 - The housing crisis solution is going to be imperfect | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660218/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660218/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s start is about the way out of the global housing crisis, how some well intentioned ideas have unfortunate unexpected consequence and why the way out of this problem is going to require us to accept some imperfect solutions. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>189 - When money dies: Notes on hyperinflation, currency manipulation and Ponzi schemes, plus who is with who in the new Middle East | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660219/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660219/</guid><description>Podcast Description We explain precisely how exchange rate, interest rate and monetary policy actually interact and work - all within the first 30 mins! While inflation is grabbing headlines across the world whats hiding behind the headlines is fragile currencies: today we look at Beirut to understand what lessons we can take from a country when money dies. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>188 - Lessons from Oslo: How to create green innovation | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660220/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660220/</guid><description>Podcast Description Following last week’s conversations on climate change we wanted to talk about the real, tangible ways that we can create this better, greener future through public initiatives. The race to 2030 is on - and the finish line is closer than we might think! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>187 - The return of inflation | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660221/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660221/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s no secret that we’ve been living in inflationary times, but inflation is always the harbinger of higher interest rates and if they were to go up, what happens? Lessons from Zillow, the problem of tomorrow&amp;rsquo;s big data, yesterday&amp;rsquo;s invented barter, and the amount of debt out there and a central banks that gets spooked. Fascinating stuff. Its all about inflation, transitory or temporary? Today we’re joined by Rob Armstrong in New York to explore.</description></item><item><title>186 - The myths of dereliction - and how to fight back | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660222/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660222/</guid><description>Podcast Description When it comes to dereliction there&amp;rsquo;s many myths that people tell to accept the status quo - &amp;ldquo;that&amp;rsquo;s just the way it is&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;the council is doing its best &amp;quot; - &amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s a problem with planning permission&amp;rdquo;. To put it bluntly: most of these are simply not true. Let&amp;rsquo;s break them down and talk about what we can do to create a better future. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.</description></item><item><title>185 - Inflation, leverage and the ecological warning from the vikings | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660223/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660223/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s episode explores two topics: we begin by looking at what the market thinks of potential interest rate increases - is there a bear market coming? Then we continue to focus on climate change through a warning from the Vikings regarding how civilizations choose to collapse. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>184 - The Climate Change Opportunity | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660224/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660224/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are running out of time, it&amp;rsquo;s now or never. The world needs to stop burning fossil fuels. That&amp;rsquo;s the challenge. It’s not all doom &amp;amp; gloom. We explore about the massive economic opportunities of renewables for those who are ready to seize them! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>183 - What’s next for Germany and why it matters; plus the life of journalist Robert Fisk | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660225/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660225/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s podcast is split in two: we explore the changing of the guard in Germany and a massive undocumented shift in German policy, before exploring the legacy of a great journalist and writer: Robert Fisk Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>182 - Why now is the time to go for a wage rise! | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660226/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660226/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why now is the time to strike for a higher wage. Wages are going up, don&amp;rsquo;t get left behind. Also, a quick follow-up on last week’s chats on inflation &amp;amp; crypto, we ask the question what does crypto/Bitcoin do in a crisis? The Great Depression was caused by dumb-ass attachment to the gold standard, why would digital gold be any different in another slump? Plus wages, the Great Resignation and what it means for your job &amp;amp; your salary?</description></item><item><title>181 - Is Cryptocurrency the silver bullet to inflation? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660227/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660227/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re continuing our conversation on inflation, this time through the lens of cryptocurrency to understand if it actually is the safe haven to inflation that many seem to think it is Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>180 - Money and inflation - What to make of the current rising costs | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660228/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660228/</guid><description>Podcast Description From the Greek Goddess Maia, to the Roman God Mercury, and the Lord Edward Pub in Dublin, this week&amp;rsquo;s chat on inflation takes an eclectic turn. We’re seeing price increases across various aspects of our lives - how worried should you be? Today we breakdown how these price increases came to be and how long they might last. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>179 - The crossroad between a Mad Max or a Star Trek Future | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660229/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660229/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we connect with Alec Ross, the author of the Raging 2020s to talk about the fight for our future, how share-holders rose to power and the way that society can take back control for a better future for all. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>178 - Tinder for ideas and the new corporate tax rate implications | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660230/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660230/</guid><description>Podcast Description We kick off the week with the launch of our new international trade and money course which aims to bring economics to everyone! We start the chat with a quick overview of the course before talking about the new corporate tax rate, what&amp;rsquo;s happening and how we can use this new reality to make Ireland a more entrepreneurial place for our youth. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>177 - Is China the new Japan? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660231/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660231/</guid><description>Podcast Description We examine the similarities between China in 2022 and Japan in 1990. The trajectory of huge export-led growth, dragging Japan in the 1950s, 60s, 70s out of the post-WW2 morass, and China in the 1990s, Noughties and Teens out of the post-Mao torpor, leading to an internal domestic bubble, fuelled by property, real estate speculation and excessive bank lending. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>176 - Britain's coming Winter of Discontent | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660232/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660232/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;ldquo;A spectre is haunting Britain—the spectre of stagflation&amp;rdquo;. It&amp;rsquo;s not always the podcast paraphrases Karl Marx, but when it comes to ideology, there are few better examples of &amp;ldquo;the one size fits all&amp;rdquo; trap as Marxism or Brexit. Now the consequences of Brexit and the end of the pandemic are pushing the UK, one of the most inherently inflationary economy in the West, towards stagflation where growth slows at the same time as prices rise.</description></item><item><title>175 - Conversation with the brilliant behavioural economist Dan Ariely | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660233/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660233/</guid><description>Podcast Description From the experience economy, to the economics of meaning, the psychology of Covid deniers, what happens when you are too committed to on idea, the perils of Facebook, the economics of internet bullying and what happens when we don&amp;rsquo;t see the downside of our own bad behaviour. Brilliant stuff, fascinating insights. I think you will enjoy it. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>174 - The Housing Price Theory of Everything | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660234/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660234/</guid><description>Podcast Description We kick off with a jammy deal in Dublin and why it tells you everything you need to know about what&amp;rsquo;s wrong with Ireland&amp;rsquo;s housing market. Plus the hidden costs of house price increases everything from obesity, climate change, wealth inequality and even fertility! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>173 - Evergrande implosion and the economics of Colonialism | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660235/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660235/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we start in China to talk about Evergrande, the real estate empire that is on the brink of collapse before talking about the history of colonialism and linking it to current day economics Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>172 - The Economics of Casement, Carson, Congo and Colonialism | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660236/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660236/</guid><description>Podcast Description As Michael D Higgins, Ireland’s President gets into a scrap, we have a hot take on rubber booms, Apocalypse Now, Roger Casement, King Leopold and Oscar Wilde! Enjoy! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>171 - Inflation: why it's personal | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660237/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660237/</guid><description>Podcast Description With headlines around the world talking about rising inflation its well worth the time to break down what it is, why yours might not be like anyone else’s and why, in time, this too shall pass. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>170 - A few thoughts from Dubai and what Sally Rooney and the points race can tell us about the elite and elite overproduction? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660238/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660238/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, we&amp;rsquo;re in Dubai, giving a quick run down of what the region looks like to the visitor, then we head back to Europe in order to look at the dilemma of elite overproduction, how our new meritocracy is turning sour an what it means for the economics, politics and society. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>169 - The great Chinese closedown | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660239/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660239/</guid><description>Podcast Description China has been making huge policy changes in the last few weeks - it’s laying out a clear vision for what it wants the country to look like for the decades to come. We join Angelica Oung in Taiwan to help us breakdown the latest events Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>168 - Thoughts on the new Irish housing plan | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660240/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660240/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Irish governments has finally laid out a vision to tackle the ongoing housing crisis and while it’s far from perfect, it is a step in the right direction. Join us as we go over what was proposed and what kind of impact it might have. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>167 - Education for the brave new world | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660241/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660241/</guid><description>Podcast Description As the 4th industrial revolution has converged with a global pandemic creating seismic shifts in various aspects of our lives, how will the future of work look like? Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>166 - Taliban Tremors | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660242/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660242/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is the implication of the Taliban&amp;rsquo;s takeover of Kabul? The author of &amp;ldquo;The Silk Roads&amp;rdquo;, Peter Frankopan shares his wisdom with us, and explains what all this means for the region and the globe. Plus, the odd riff on August, Louis Walsh and Jimmy Carter. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>165 - Afghanistan, from the perspective of people who are &amp; have been there with Nelofer Pazira Fisk | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660243/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660243/</guid><description>Podcast Description Afghanistan is unraveling in front of our eyes, and while many stories are making headlines, few talk about what it currently feels like for the regular folks living there. We’re bringing you a unique perspective from real Afghans about what it feels like right now as well as what might come next. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>164 - Russia after Putin with political dissident Mikhail Khodorkovsky | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660244/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660244/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s not always you get to chat to a man who survived 10 years in a Siberian Gulag, Mikhail Khodorkovsky is such a man, so this is a real treat. Who better to discuss Putin than the man Putin was so afraid of that he put him in prison? The handover from the Putin regime will be an huge geo-political event and it has the potency to go very badly wrong.</description></item><item><title>163 - The Edge &amp; Brian Cox go beyond the music | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660245/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660245/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today&amp;rsquo;s episode is a unique blend of music, creativity &amp;amp; quantum physics between two masters of their respective fields. From Brian Cox&amp;rsquo;s early brushings with music to tips on being a good ancestor - this is one you don&amp;rsquo;t want to miss! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>162 - The politics of catastrophe with Niall Ferguson | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660246/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660246/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re bringing you another conversation from the Dalkey Book Festival where we explore nationality, sports, history, the pandemic, and most importantly why the incentives to implement preventive measures are non-existent in our society!! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>161 - Sitting down with Bernie Sanders | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660247/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660247/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we want to bring you a great conversation that I had with Bernie Sanders at the Dalkey Book Festival a few weeks ago. Senator Sanders touches on the current economic climate of politics in the states, the Biden agenda and where he wants to push the budget committee. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>160 - The economics of love (Best of) | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660248/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660248/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s August - We&amp;rsquo;re taking a moment to go through our archives and surface a few &amp;ldquo;best of&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo; to keep you company on your summer holidays. This week we&amp;rsquo;re revisiting one of our all-time favourites: the economics of love! Hope you enjoy! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>159 - Dante and the economics of the 14th century | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660249/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660249/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we dive back into Florence and Dante to explore how this extraordinary writer’s lessons and insights are still as relevant today as the day they were written Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>158 - Economics at a crossroad with Mark Blyth &amp; Eric Lonergan | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660250/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660250/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eric &amp;amp; Mark walk us through the vacuums in politics and the different types of anger that has brought on the rise of populism globally and how they’ve used this anger to create a new economic framework Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>157 - Mid-year review with Paul Donovan | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660251/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660251/</guid><description>Podcast Description Everyone has tried to make the year that’s passed fit into classic boom/bust models but the truth is that there’s nothing classical about 2020 - so let’s assess what really happened to the economy and what we’re heading into now. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>156 - Get on board with ESG or else! | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660252/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660252/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brands spend millions to represent something that consumers want to be associated with. The tricky part is that culture is always changing, always evolving. The latest cultural change is the rise of ESG in people’s decision making - not understanding this shift can significantly impact bottom lines! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>155 - Is Cuba in the middle of a regime change | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660253/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660253/</guid><description>Podcast Description There is a wind of change in the Cuban air. The Castro family is no longer running the country and there are whispers among the locals that this might be a tipping point for the country. Let’s breakdown the current situation &amp;amp; the different ways that this can play out. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>154- The economics of climate change, the coming resource wars and what we can do about it. | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660254/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660254/</guid><description>Podcast Description Economists are dangerous, so says this week&amp;rsquo;s guest iconoclastic economist,Professor Steve Keen and this is particularly the case if we think about climate change. What can we do to avoid a climate catastrophe? Carbon credits could be the answer, but we have to act quickly. Plus, why Ireland could be to renewable energy what Saudi Arabia is to petrol and thrifty five years after Chernobyl, why the return of nuclear is on the cards.</description></item><item><title>153 - Follow the Money: Why is the government selling the Bank of Ireland cheaply and why now? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660255/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660255/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Irish government is trying to sell its stake in the Bank of Ireland at a half price. Selling cheap and buying expensive is never good business. We head back to the West Lower to explore the nexus between selling Bank of Ireland cheaply and the dreaded Davy Stockbrokers, that entity that is under investigation by the State. Could there be a link? If so what does it say about corporate culture in Ireland?</description></item><item><title>152 - The NYtimes is wrong - Ireland is not a tax haven | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660256/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660256/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last week the New York Times took a swipe at Ireland by calling it a tax haven - which it most definitely is not. Using taxes is central to any nation&amp;rsquo;s economic policy. A tax haven is understood to be a place where a company puts a brass plate up, has few if any employees and proceeds to wash money through this shell company. That is not what is happening in Ireland.</description></item><item><title>151 - Reimagining cities post COVID | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660257/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660257/</guid><description>Podcast Description The world is changing and nowhere is that more apparent than in urban areas around the world. Today’s episode looks at the transformations happening in our podcast home of Dun Laoghaire and use it as a template to discuss what might happen around the world. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>150 - Rich Man/Poor Man with Stephanie Kelton &amp; Marla Dukharan | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660258/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660258/</guid><description>Podcast Description Up here, in what used to be called the &amp;ldquo;1st World&amp;rdquo;, the pandemic has focused economists&amp;rsquo; minds on what can be done to change our thinking after Covid has passed. M.M.T. sets out new economic opportunities available, for example, to the the US. But not all countries have the luxury of this approach built up over decades of wealth and stability. Countries in what is now termed the &amp;ldquo;Global South&amp;rdquo; do not have these possibilities.</description></item><item><title>149 - Let’s talk Pride, is there a gay economy? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660259/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660259/</guid><description>Podcast Description When I was a kid, being inclusive or accepting of gay people was regarded as the death knell of commerce. Today it’s an essential attribute of a successful economy or company. This week we talk about the change Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>148 - Is the political centre back? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660260/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660260/</guid><description>Podcast Description We examine recent political trends and ask the question: is the centre, written off by the extremes, back in the game &amp;amp; And if so, what does it mean? Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>147 - The housing market by the numbers | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660261/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660261/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;rsquo;re slowly but surely coming to the boiling point of the housing market, but as we do so it&amp;rsquo;s important to step back and understand the magnitude of the mess we&amp;rsquo;re in. Join us this week as we quantify the booms &amp;amp; busts of the last 2 generations in Ireland. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>146 - The Great Caste War | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660262/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660262/</guid><description>Podcast Description Elections all over the world are now power struggles between &amp;ldquo;castes&amp;rdquo;, not so much classes, ideologies or even economics. We look at economic history as being one on going struggle between three castes, the priests, the warriors and the merchants. Each traditional caste has evolved from their historical origins, but they are essentially unchanged in the modern. Today&amp;rsquo;s politics is still dominated by this fascinating three-way struggle, economics is also determined by the winners of this battle.</description></item><item><title>145 - Kamikaze Kapitalism | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660263/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660263/</guid><description>Podcast Description History is a great teacher - so this week we turn to the 1980s in Japan to learn how one country who had seemingly figured it all out - lost its way! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>144 - What is Money? With Eric Lonergan | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660264/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660264/</guid><description>Podcast Description Money is so deeply engrained in our lives that we sometimes forget to think about it at all. With the rise of alternative currencies it&amp;rsquo;s worth taking a step back and thinking about what exactly is money? Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>143 - G7, global corporate taxes &amp; Disrupting the building sector | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660265/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660265/</guid><description>Podcast Description Every country has the right to use the tools at their disposable to make the lives of its citizens more prosperous - even the tax code. With the G7 underway and it’s headlines about a common tax rate we’re going to explore what that could mean for Ireland before moving to another key global issue: Disrupting the construction industry to achieve affordable housing. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>142 - Value is created in the mind with Rory Sutherland | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660266/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660266/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why gold may have started with prostitution, why wine makers take the mickey, why economists only see half the picture and what Naomi Osaka tell us about decision-making and why the so-called hard sciences are actually easy and the soft one, hard. We’ve always opened the podcast by saying that you need to understand human nature to understand the economy, so today instead of interrogating a specific topic, we look at value &amp;amp; value creation - because economics has to be more open to marketing &amp;amp; psychology to see the big picture and be materially better at creating a better future.</description></item><item><title>141 - Is Bitcoin a bubble or the currency of the future - or can it be both? Part.2 | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660267/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660267/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bitcoin’s value has gone from 10 000 USD to a whopping 60 000 USD in the last 6 month - before going down to about 35 000 USD now. But what is it? Is it money or an asset? Can a currency so volatile be a reliable replacement to fiat money? Is it even a currency? Or something else entirely? This week we’re doing a 2 part series that aims to untangle all the noise around coins and cryptocurrency.</description></item><item><title>140 - Is Bitcoin a bubble or the currency of the future - or can it be both? Part.1 | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660268/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660268/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bitcoin’s value has gone from 10 000 USD to a whopping 60 000 USD in the last 6 month - before going down to about 35 000 USD now. But what is it? Is it money or an asset? Can a currency so volatile be a reliable replacement to fiat money? Is it even a currency? Or something else entirely? This week we’re doing a 2 part series that aims to untangle all the noise around coins and cryptocurrency.</description></item><item><title>139 - Boring but radical: How Biden is getting it done | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660269/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660269/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a quick hit on Bitcoin we join Harvard economist Megan Greene for a deep dive on why MMT is rising in America, how Biden is embracing this new vision of monetary policy and what he’s trying to achieve with these massive infrastructure plans - all while watching out for the inflation risk! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>139 - The UK’s new economic approach | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660270/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660270/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brexit has created a new economic environment for the UK. Robert Lind joins us to untangle what the new business model might be moving forward, how it might diversify the UK economy &amp;amp; how it might affect London and beyond. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>138 - Global panic buying &amp; inflation | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660271/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660271/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you know anyone in their 20s or 30s, no matter where in the world you are, you’ve been talking about housing. By all accounts the pandemic has turned an underlying condition into a fatal diagnostic for most millennials. Today we look at how the world’s housing markets in a variety of countries before moving onto the return of inflation - its always important to keep things in perspective Join the gang!</description></item><item><title>137 - Israel and Palestine, explained, put into perspective and hopefully made more clear with Tom Friedman | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660272/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660272/</guid><description>Podcast Description Through a unique Broadway analogy, the fascinating three times Pulitzer Prize winner, New York columnist Times Tom Friedman helps us navigate the bigger picture behind the terrible headlines that we&amp;rsquo;ve been reading for the last week regarding the conflict in the Israel, Gaza, Jerusalem and the West Bank. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>136 - What the Pope told Mack! | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660273/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660273/</guid><description>Podcast Description As wages stagnate but house prices rise, a new class will emerge, beneficiaries of the housing boom, an inheritance class. As the younger generation falls behind, they will become more dependent on inheriting wealth, normally via parent&amp;rsquo;s houses. This will create a drone class without the get up an go of previous strivers. We are already seeing it in some countries: you can go backwards. Also a conversation I had with the Pope, yes Francis himself about exactly this!</description></item><item><title>135 - Vultures, cuckoos, pigeons - what's with all these avian funds? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660274/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660274/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can you feel it in the air? The wind is changing for property funds in Ireland, people are realizing how rigged the system is against them and they’re deciding to do something about it. The first step of any battle is to understand what you’re up against. This week we’ll try to breakdown these funds to better understand what they are &amp;amp; how we got here. Join the gang!</description></item><item><title>134 - Lessons from the Great Depression | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660275/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660275/</guid><description>Podcast Description Those who cannot remember the past are condemned to repeat it - or so the saying goes. This week, with the help of IG, we’re looking at what happened in the Great Depression and comparing it with Biden’s current economic approach to see if we’ve learned anything from the past economic cycles… Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>133 - The beauty of discovering numbers | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660276/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660276/</guid><description>Podcast Description Some argue that great civilized societies are measured by culture, literature or art but what about the idea that real sophistication is statistics? Truly self-confident societies reveal, expose, shine a light and measure. Calculation is purity. Data matters and to fully understand anything it’s often essential to understand numbers. Why do we use a base 12 for months? 60 for seconds? How do we make sense of the latest political stats?</description></item><item><title>132 - Pulling up the drawbridge | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660277/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660277/</guid><description>Podcast Description The biggest barrier to progress is the contented class, driven by their C.A.V.E philosophy: Citizens Against Virtually Everything, they want things to slow down now that they have risen up. they object to almost everything, gumming up the planning process, driving up house costs and house prices. These Cavemen, consumed by the anti-social behavior of serial objecting, are lifting the ladder behind them it in an attempt to further their economic status at the expense of the next generation.</description></item><item><title>131 - What will your Spotify Moment look like? Learning from the music industry | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660278/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 06:06:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660278/</guid><description>Podcast Description The music industry has been the most iconic example of disruption in the modern age, but if Will Page is right (former chief economist of Spotify) - it might only be the tip of the iceberg for what’s to come. Join us as we explore what happened to the music industry and how the same disruption is coming for many more categories, maybe including your own! Join the gang!</description></item><item><title>130 - The end of Neo-Liberalism &amp; economic super-cycles explained with Dario Perkins | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660279/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660279/</guid><description>Podcast Description Through the super-league we look at what might be the impending end of neo-liberalism: it&amp;rsquo;s all about the background noise!. From there we tease out what economic super-cycles are, why they might be a breath of fresh air for the next generation and how we’ve come to an inflection point in macroeconomic thinking Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>129 - No one is safe until everyone is safe | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660280/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660280/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yesterday was the worst day to day for new cases of COVID 19 globally since the pandemic started. WE may feel safer, but the world is a dangerous as ever. To combat it, and any future variants, we must respond as a united planet: the reality is we can only open if rich countries pay for the vaccines of poor countries. In 1918 after WW1 we had the League of Nations, in 1948, after WW2 the UN, World Bank, Marshall Plan and the WHO.</description></item><item><title>128 - Clinging to power, what's the next move? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660281/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660281/</guid><description>Podcast Description We head down the West Lower to look at the fallout from the KBC move to leave Ireland, plus in the week that the new more muscular USA slaps sanctions on Russia, we look at the geo-strategic options for Russia, including a tacit alliance with the USA against China in Siberia. Also, there&amp;rsquo;s a Russian/American summit coming up, why doesn&amp;rsquo;t Ireland host it and use out neutrality actively? Join the gang!</description></item><item><title>127 - By 2030 there will be more female millionaires in the world than men. Change is coming. | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660282/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660282/</guid><description>Podcast Description One of the most significant changes influencing our world is the feminization of the economy. It&amp;rsquo;s been a long time coming, and the fruits of many battles- contraception, free and inclusive education, divorce, abortion. Finally, in the West, woman are catching up with men, in income and wealth. This trend will profoundly affect the society and the economy. Candice Bushnell, writer of Sex in the City, remarked that, &amp;ldquo;Women with money is a notion that our society is uncomfortable with&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>126 - The end of the road for the Irish corporate tax advantage? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660283/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660283/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over the last few decades Ireland has been growing by leaps &amp;amp; bounds, catching up with most of our European neighbours in almost every measurements, social and economic. Part of that story has been the dramatic improvement in the countries&amp;rsquo; capital base as a result of US MNC investment. Ireland has received more US corporate investment that China, Russia, India and Brazil combined! Now the Biden administration wants to harmonize global corporation tax - do we need to come up with a new strategy?</description></item><item><title>125 - When China flexes. Is Taiwan Asia's Berlin wall? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660284/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660284/</guid><description>Podcast Description China is changing. Relations with the US have plummeted Taiwan is the ground zero for the new China. What happens in Taiwan will affect the global economy for decades to come. We head to Taipei for an explosive local view of regional and global. Also what doe the US&amp;rsquo;s new 20% corporation tax mean for Ireland and the world economy. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>124 - Where is the "lockdown dividend"? Joe Biden the economic revolutionary - plus its Vespa time! | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660285/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660285/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ireland has been in lockdown for 231 days - by far the most stringent lockdown in the EU, so where&amp;rsquo;s the dividend? Could 1950s/60s Irish emigration to the UK explain far more about Ireland and Covid than we care to admit? Plus, it&amp;rsquo;s all changed in the USA. Paul McCulley talks about the tectonic shift in economic policies that is shaking up the United States - how Biden calls time on Reagan&amp;rsquo;s economics and why we are looking at a bear market for bonds.</description></item><item><title>123 - Our hyper-integrated world. Suez canal, supply chain fragility &amp; the death of traditional recessions! | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660286/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 06:38:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660286/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yes, the canal is unblocked, but the ramifications of the events should not be understated: the fragility of our global supply chain has been exposed and people are starting to awaken to the inter-connectivity of our global lives. Join us as we talk with the brilliant historian Mr Silk Roads himself, Peter Frankopan about what all this will mean for the future of globalization. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.</description></item><item><title>122 - Its time for a buyer’s strike | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660287/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660287/</guid><description>Podcast Description Any free trade has 2 sides: a buyer &amp;amp; a seller. After today’s conversation with one of our Patreon: Ciaran Mulqueen - who runs the crazy house prices instagram page it seems that buyers are going to start taking major steps to change the course of the housing market, in Ireland and globally! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>121 - The Psychology of the Far Right | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660288/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 07:06:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660288/</guid><description>Podcast Description All European countries have seen increases in far-right parties in the last decade. This political affiliation will not just disappear as most people hope it will. This week we look the far-right straight in the eyes and try to understand the underlying sentiments &amp;amp; motives behind the political affiliation. History has shown us the risk of letting it run free. Withe the help of Kevin Cunningham we don&amp;rsquo;t just look at economics and social issue, but personality types &amp;amp; deep human characteristics, inherited from our hundreds of thousands of years as hunter gatherers which unwittingly dictate how we see the world.</description></item><item><title>120 - Cease and desist. Get out of the housing market right now, plus the 5 fundamental ways cities are changing | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660289/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660289/</guid><description>Podcast Description The global seller’s market for housing is hitting new levels of madness - its time for buyers to take a stand and decide that they’re not going to take part in this madness - at least until the supply comes back to its pre-pandemic levels. In the same vein, it’s important to consider how the world is changing as people look to buy new homes. We break down five major urban trends with Simon Kuper.</description></item><item><title>119 - The Economic Revolution is here | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660290/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660290/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joe Biden unveils a $1.9 trillion package and is saying he will spend more. This is a massive change - almost a revolution against economic orthodoxy - and we are on our way to MMT (Modern Monetary Theory). We talk to the main proponent of MMT: Professor Stephanie Kelton about this brave new world. We are in a transformative age. Welcome to the future! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.</description></item><item><title>118 - If you tolerate this, then your country will be next | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660291/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660291/</guid><description>Podcast Description Financial scandal in Ireland, what would an American bank regulator and prosecutor do? We talk to Professor Bill Black, former US banking regulator and lead investigator in the US &amp;ldquo;Savings and Loans&amp;rdquo; scandal of the early 1990s. Some hard truths. Also, on the week Stripe - run by two software engineers - invest big time in Ireland, we look at why countries that favour innovators over rent-seekers, grow faster.</description></item><item><title>117 - Learning from the master innovator Johannes Gutenberg | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660292/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 07:19:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660292/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learning used to be hands-on, trail and error, mentors, mistakes &amp;amp; real world experience. Gutenberg is the model. Could going back to the old ways be the key to unlocking the innovators within our youth? Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>116 - White collar crime, why vaccines are destiny, &amp; the miraculous resurrection of Boris Johnson | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660293/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660293/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why vaccine is the only game in town. What Michael should say to Joe on St Patricks Day, plus crimes in the “West lower”&amp;hellip;.. then off the London talking with Robert Shrimsley of the Financial Times on Boris Johnson’s surprising resurgence in popularity Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>115 - The War on Drugs has failed, stop it. | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660294/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660294/</guid><description>Podcast Description The War in Drugs is a spectacular failure. It is time to end it and begin to have an adult conversation about legalizing drugs. If you went out to set up a better way to enrich a violent criminal class, it would be impossible to find a better way. We explain the economic case for the legalization of drugs, tax them and use the proceeds to help those small amount of recreational drug takers who become addicts.</description></item><item><title>114 - Building back better | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660295/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660295/</guid><description>Podcast Description The markets are getting their knickers in a twist over inflation and maybe even deficits, we explain why the economics of the 1990s no longer applies and the big shift in global policy is the bias now is towards inflation not deflation for the first time since the 1970s. Plus, the brilliant economist Noah Smith from San Fransisco on three brilliantly practical ideas to make housing work better for everyone.</description></item><item><title>113 - Bidenomics, why we should not worry about inflation and embracing economic heres | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660296/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660296/</guid><description>Podcast Description The USA is embarking on the biggest change in economic policy in decades. Biden is using the economics of the 1930s to avoid the 1930s. This is a big deal. We speak to renowned economic heretic and former Fed economist, Claudia Sahm about Biden&amp;rsquo;s New Deal, being bullied by 1970&amp;rsquo;s thinking and America creating 10 million new jobs. Also, we talk about economic heresy. When only one Federal Reserve economist out of 406 is black, economics has a problem.</description></item><item><title>112 - How Ireland really works! | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660297/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660297/</guid><description>Podcast Description The upcoming sale of Ulster Bank will reveal how Ireland actually works. We give you the &amp;ldquo;collars up&amp;rdquo; view from the West Lower Stand at the Aviva stadium - where deals are done. This corporate finance 101 podcast breaks down the likely carve-up of Ulster Bank amongst the Insiders, and explains why as long as the banking system is joined at the hip to the property market, Ireland will always be a boom/bust economy driving up mortgage rates and down competition.</description></item><item><title>111 - The future of the City | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660298/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660298/</guid><description>Podcast Description What will our cities look like after Covid? We talk to renowned urbanist Richard Florida, the man behind the concept of the Creative Class and Creative Cities about what next for our cities. We also outline three &amp;ldquo;must do&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rdquo; for cities. The first is a directly-elected Mayor with proper taxation/spending powers, second a tax on land hoarding to make land useful again and third, cities need to issue municipal bonds to finance everything, from housing to great public works, with the aim of making our cities beautiful, livable and magnificent.</description></item><item><title>110 - Going Dutch, London's Brexit losses and what's the story with Bitcoin? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660299/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660299/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hundreds of years ago, the Dutch were Europe&amp;rsquo;s moneymen and it looks as if they are at it again. We look at new alliances &amp;amp; digital trade routes emerging in the post-Brexit era. Looking at Hindu parables, what&amp;rsquo;s the elephant in the room? What&amp;rsquo;s the story with Bitcoin, digital Gold or digital Tulips, plus the logic in Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s big bet. If Bitcoin is a hedge against catastrophe, are we missing something?</description></item><item><title>109 - The fallout from economic mania &amp; the conventional thinking trap with Tom Bergin | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660300/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660300/</guid><description>Podcast Description we start off by taking a look at the fallout of the Gamestop fiasco before tackling the bigger issue: Conventional thinking. In many ways the world is still pushing “zombie” ideas - ideas that have been proven to be false but that are still being pushed as policies. With the help of Tom Bergin we look at a few conventional ideas and explain why they’re nothing more than a popular myth.</description></item><item><title>108 - How to fix the housing market | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660301/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660301/</guid><description>Podcast Description Public housing should be addressed with the same urgency as public health. If we can close down the economy, borrow billions, furlough millions and stop the world in the name of public health, we should be able to tear up the rule book when it comes to housing. The property market in Ireland and the rest of the English speaking world is a scam, rigged to push prices upwards, indenturing working families and exacerbating the wealth divide.</description></item><item><title>107 - Wall Street and the Short Selling Revolution Part 2 | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660302/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660302/</guid><description>Podcast Description We take another look at the &amp;ldquo;day-trading&amp;rdquo; insurrectionists to examine who is actually in control, what human emotions are unleashed by the markets and what it all means for politics and economics. We are joined by the authors of the wonderful book Angrynomics political scientist Mark Blyth and hedge fund manger Eric Lonergan. Things are rarely as they seem to be! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>106 - Wall Street, Game Stop and the Short Squeeze Revolutionaries! | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660303/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660303/</guid><description>Podcast Description Something unusual is happening in the stock market: the little guy - or in this case, guys - are beating up the big multi-billionaire hedge-fund managers. This is in stark contrast to the usual market hegemony and might signal a deep change: the little guy is slowly recognizing their power in numbers. If short selling, margin calls, put options, short squeezes are all Double Dutch to you, fret now we have you covered.</description></item><item><title>105 - The Rentier Economy | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660304/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 07:14:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660304/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ireland, like many economies is hostage to the rentiers, companies that sidle up to governments to get a licence to provide some product or service that the government used to provide. This is a licence to print money, because the rentier company has a monopoly to hoover up rent rather than make anything. They dominate the property market, utilities and have led to the infantilization of the public sector.</description></item><item><title>104 - Doughnut Economics | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660305/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660305/</guid><description>Podcast Description The arrival of Joe Biden has led to a profound change in tone, with America quickly re-signing back up to the Paris Accord. The planet is back on the agenda and the mantra of growth at all costs irrespective of the environmental costs, is being reappraised. We talk to Kat Raworth, author of &amp;ldquo;Doughnut Economics&amp;rdquo; about a different way of looking at the world, the economy and how we understand our relationship to the world around us, our priorities and the need to re-frame economics for the 21st century.</description></item><item><title>103 - Doc Martins, the financialization of the global economy, IPO's, inequality and Joe Biden's political agenda | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660306/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660306/</guid><description>Podcast Description We explain by way of the SFX and Doc Martins how financial markets create inequality. Late stage financial capitalism generates super normal profits for owners of capital and debt by way of IPOs, and forces wage moderation on ordinary workers. We explain how understanding the credit cycle is key to understand the modern economy through the prism of the glorious Doc Martin, focusing on trickle down economy, opportunism and leveraged profits and market booms and busts.</description></item><item><title>102 - The last day of Trump | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660307/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660307/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trump is gone but what next for Trumpism? The saga is far from over. While the armed Boogaloo boys are mobilizing across the United States we talk with Professor William Black to get a thorough understanding of what’s going on in America and what the future holds for Donald J. Trump. Also a quick hit on how China has emerged unassailable from both Trump and Covid, plus America&amp;rsquo;s first internal rebellion and the vision of Alexander Hamilton.</description></item><item><title>101 - How to end this Lockdown for good! | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660308/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660308/</guid><description>Podcast Description We still have time to do a New Zealand, with the vaccine roll out going so slowly, can we do a Taiwan and be out and about my St Patrick&amp;rsquo;s Day? We talk zero Covid with Prof Aoife McLyset: How we can administer an economic vaccine while we wait with a bit of imagination, plus what the new biotech revolution - ushered in by the mRNA vaccine - means for all of us.</description></item><item><title>100 - American Carnage and its radicalized Middle | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660309/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660309/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trump is over, Trumpism is not. The great American experiment is only starting, as the Republicans become the party of the anxious while, the Democrats - the party of the satisfied. As the world&amp;rsquo;s economic power shifts to Asia, we should try to understand people&amp;rsquo;s real fears. Also, why the world need fewer &amp;ldquo;blackboard&amp;rdquo; economists and more &amp;ldquo;kitchen table&amp;rdquo; economists and will America&amp;rsquo;s next president, Joe Biden lead the charge of change?</description></item><item><title>The Brexit Dividend - for everyone bar Britain! | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660310/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660310/</guid><description>Podcast Description Interesting times! As the US is engulfed by a culture war, we look at a culture war closer to home. Here’s why Brexit provides a once in a generation opportunity and how we can seize it. Brexit is a change and change is the one thing that is constant. Embrace it. Economically, there’s huge upside. Politically, it makes constitutional change on this island more likely. We are chatting to Andrea Catherwood on the future of Ireland, how to avoid our own culture war and how we best negotiate it from here.</description></item><item><title>Every Day is Crucial! | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660311/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660311/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome back to the podcast 2021! During the height of the civil rights campaign when people were dying needlessly, Martin Luther King deployed this expression “the extreme urgency of now” to describe the urgency of achieving civil rights immediately, not sometime in the future. Precisely the same can be said about the vaccine. Every day is crucial and the roll out of the vaccine will be the litmus test for how serious your country is!</description></item><item><title>Christmas Podcast | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660312/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660312/</guid><description>Podcast Description Thanks for your support all year. This week we take stock of Ireland after the year we’ve just had and how your view on COVID actually tells much more about who you are and what you think than you might originally think. Happy Christmas!! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Investor or Speculation? Tech, market madness &amp; the cost of mistakes | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660313/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660313/</guid><description>Podcast Description Technology changes the world - but not everyone who bets on technology wins. With the recent boom in tech IPOs we take a look at what the market with the help of FT’s John Thornhilll and explore a short history of market mania, from AirBnB, to canals, railways, Irish Navies, Homer Simpson plus a cameo from Ken Clarke late night in bar in Hong Kong Halloween night 1997. A few thoughts on global monetary policy too!</description></item><item><title>When Scotland Rises | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660314/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660314/</guid><description>Podcast Description The first casualty of Brexit will be Britain. Scotland is on its own path for the first time since 1707. When Scotland becomes independent, it will trigger enormous economic and political changes up here in the North West Atlantic. Mark Blyth, Professor at Brown University helps us to tease out the economics of Scottish Independence and what’s ahead for Scotland, Ireland and England. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Beyond Brexit. What does the post-Brexit world look like? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660315/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660315/</guid><description>Podcast Description The British are gone - well almost - and the EU will change. The face of that change is likely to be Emmanuel Macron. So we examine France, by way of a small tour of European monetary history, French diplomacy, a quick trip to Paris, a bit of Albert Camus, the Cure, Algeria, Sudenten Germany and Ireland’s coming “Viking Alliance” with Scandinavia. Lots to marinade on. Join the gang!</description></item><item><title>Meritocracy - Scourge or Salvation | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660316/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 06:09:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660316/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we review our Tuesday conversation with Andy Haldane and go through some of the most interesting aspects of the discussion, including the merits and pitfalls of meritocracy. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Brexit and much more with Andy Haldane, Chief Economist of the Bank of England | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660317/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660317/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s Brexit week, last throw of the dice allegedly, so what better week to talk to the man from the Bank of England - an institution that will have to deal with the economic, financial and political fallout of leaving Britain’s leaving the EU? You will love this chat with Andy, talking about Brexit, inequality, the tyranny of meritocracy, why banks fail, crypto currency, Roy Keane’s man management skills and the future of Sunderland FC!</description></item><item><title>The end of the car park | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660318/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 07:58:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660318/</guid><description>Podcast Description Not all ideas are timeless - this week we look at how we can take dead space and turn it into living spaces through economic incentives Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Hand of pod" - The Maradona Generation | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660319/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660319/</guid><description>Podcast Description We go to Argentina to gauge the reaction to the death of the Diego. Plus we explore with the former economics minister of Argentina, Martin Lousteau, what went wrong in Argentina - a country that was once the richest in the world to now being the 77th richest. Its a cautionary lesson on how good countries can go bad, how strong economies can become enfeebled and ultimately why good economics matters!</description></item><item><title>The World in 2021 | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660320/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660320/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Thanksgiving, with the Dow hitting 30,000 and Janet Yellan taking over at the US Treasury, we examine the short and medium terms health of the US economy with David Rosenberg - Warning: it doesn’t look too pretty. We also look further out to assess the demographic, budget and debt arithmetic for the US and the West and how China goes from strength to strength. All this, plus a bit of Leviticus and Deuteronomy if you are feeling all biblical!</description></item><item><title>the fallout from COVID | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660321/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660321/</guid><description>Podcast Description There’s light at the end of the tunnel - for the first time it seems that people are starting to see the end of this mess. As we look to the return of some level of normality, we know that the new normal won’t look like the old normal: both companies &amp;amp; cities will have to adapt to the end of business travelling. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Show me the money | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660322/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660322/</guid><description>Podcast Description Optics and execution are two profoundly different things. All over the world politicians talk and entrepreneurs walk. Small businesses have been promised help by people who have never taken a risk in their lives, who don&amp;rsquo;t understand the game because they’ve never had skin in the game. The result is a mess, good firms will shut, their loans bought by vulture funds and the process of the financialization of our economy, governed by spreadsheet spivs will take one further big step forward.</description></item><item><title>“Don’t cry for me Great-Brit-Annia” - to be sung imagining Boris Johnson channelling his inner Elaine Page | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660323/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660323/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Is Boris Johnson England’s Eva Peron? All through my wild days, my mad existence…..and all that stuff, anyway we get to this point following an amazing conversation with economist Adam Posen about the USA. imperial delusions, NASCAR and the commercial fairytale that is Brexit.&amp;nbsp;There’s lots in here from economic gravity, the “Great Patriot/Shit Citizen” dilemma &amp;amp; Northern Irish football melodies to a bit of Picasso, Joyce &amp;amp; early 20th century modernism.</description></item><item><title>Lets talk about unemployment | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660324/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660324/</guid><description>Podcast Description Behind every statistic is a person and a family. As unemployment sky-rockets, we need to put employment front and centre for the economy in 2021. We look a trends in employment, what type of companies are creating jobs and why the rise long term unemployment in the middle aged and older workers could support populism here. Plus lots more! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Outside it’s America! | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660325/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660325/</guid><description>Podcast Description What Joe Biden’s victory means and what it does not. We examine the US economy with a former US cabinet member and Chairman of the Council of Economic Advisors. Plus what can be done and what won’t - why the Democrats have won the popular vote in six out of the last seven elections but have more or less shared the Presidency with the Republicans! Join the gang! https://plus.</description></item><item><title>Orange is the new Red | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660326/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 08:21:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660326/</guid><description>Podcast Description Biden just about, but Orange is the new Red. The Trump family business has taken over the GOP. What does this mean? Why the Democrats need to find their inner Roosevelt and why pollsters give economists a good name. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Good Day to hide Bad News! | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660327/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660327/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re avoiding America, (well mostly) today as we can’t add much more. We’re going all Covid. There might not be a right answer for how to tackle the pandemic, but there’s certainly a wide array of approaches. We head to Israel, who are about seven weeks ahead of Western Europe, just lifting a successful Lockdown and Sweden, a country that has had no Lockdown at all! Two countries, two scientists, two different conclusions.</description></item><item><title>Market &amp; Politics - Why Who Wins Matters &amp; Why It Doesn’t | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660328/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660328/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this special episode, we look at the relationship between politics and money through the lens of the US elections.&amp;nbsp;
We try to make sense of what you should be looking out for and what each candidate is signalling - hope you enjoy!
The episode is brought to you in partnership with IG.
Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Skin in the Game | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660329/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660329/</guid><description>Podcast Description 3 Mile Pubs, why public servants don’t get business, why cashflow is King, the Grantocracy, Hydraulic economics, and what Flann O’ Brien had to say about PhDs Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Funeral of Austerity &amp; the Return of Brexit, plus when an Opel Jersey walked into the Tate Gallery! | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660330/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660330/</guid><description>Podcast Description This was the week austerity died. We explore the timely end of a bad idea and look forward to a new era for economics. Plus what the Modh Coinníollach tells us about economics . Also, an in-depth conversation on what the latest Brexit drama means (spoiler alert: there will ALWAYS be a deal), plus uncomfortable jockeys and lots more! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>A gem of a Letter from America with the brilliant Tom Frank | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660331/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 02:30:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660331/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why dereliction is vandalism in Ireland and then off to Kansas with the author of NYT’s mega best-seller, “What’s the Matter with Kansas”, American journalist and historian Thomas Frank. This conversation is critical if you want to understand the American culture war and how the Republicans and Democrats flipped sides, delivered with great humour and humanity. Speaking of humour an humanity, Oscar Wilde and George Bernard Shaw, and why Wilde told Shaw that socialism will never catch on!</description></item><item><title>How will Trump getting Covid affect the campaign, and why Ireland’s youth should determine the budget. | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660332/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660332/</guid><description>Podcast Description The legend that is Professor Bill Black on the USA. This is the man who put more white collar criminals behind bars than any other. He’s an economist, lawyer and criminal psychologist and he brings this laser-like clarity to the US, four weeks from the election. We talk economics, Proud Boys, abortion and the culture war. Plus, back home why Ireland should use the budget to build houses, show vision and understand that we have the highest young population in the EU, make the budget about them.</description></item><item><title>Economics at a tipping point | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660333/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660333/</guid><description>Podcast Description Economics is at a tipping point, as we lockdown again, how can we remain solvent, avoid national and international bankruptcy and deploy all the possible economics tools at our disposal. We are facing a 1930s style Depression and need 1930s style policies to get us out. Listen to one of the best macroeconomists in the world: Paul McCulley navigate the path to prosperity. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>How the UK breaks up….lessons from the Balkans, plus Trump’s possible road to victory | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660334/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2020 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660334/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s been a monumental week - with the help of American policy analyst Pippa Malmgren - we look at what might be the unintended consequences of Boris Johnson’s action and why all eyes are on African American women for a second Trump term. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Back to Brexit | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660335/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660335/</guid><description>Podcast Description Once again the British government uses Ireland as a hostage in its Brexit theatre with the EU. The record is on repeat. Brexit has now returned and this time its even more mental. We breakdown the latest carryon, talk about the implications for the future. Just when you thought it couldn’t get any weirder, it does! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>The American divide and the Vaticanization of the ECB | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660336/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660336/</guid><description>Podcast Description Less than 2 months away from what will inevitably be a historic election we take a look at the American landscape - how we got there and what might happen depending on election results. We then move on to talk about Eurozone, and how the rising tensions between Germany and Italy could potential reshape the fundamentals of how the zone operates. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>Cryptocurrency &amp; the future of money | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660337/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660337/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we tackle one of the most requested topics: Cryptocurrency. We’re going to try and explain what Bitcoin is, where it came from and what it might mean for the future of money. To help get to the bottom of this topic, we enrolled the help of Peter McCormack, host of the podcast “what bitcoin did” to guide us on some of the more technical aspects of this new monetary movement.</description></item><item><title>How history shapes current policies | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660338/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660338/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we ignore the political shenanigans in Ireland (as it’s so pathetic) and look at what we can learn from ancient Mesopotamia and its approach to pandemics. Plus, staying in the region: how to make sense of the Middle East by understanding a coup in Iran in 1953 and how it set the tone for everything that came after! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>The 15 minute city | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660339/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660339/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cities are at a crossroads. The decisions we take now will dictate a new urban future. The office as we know it is over and its main enemy is not COVID, it’s Zoom. This can lead to a renaissance of our urban centres and a repopulation of our rural towns - the choice is ours! Hope you enjoy! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Angrynomics - Why its okay to be mad about the current economic crisis and what we can do about it | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660340/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660340/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we talk with two brilliant economists Mark Blyth and Eric Lonergan on this fantastic new book - Angrynomics. We analyze why people are angry, how it&amp;rsquo;s affecting economics and politics and what we can do about it. There are some obvious solutions and this conversation sets them out. You’ll love it! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How bonds not bombs liberated Ireland | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660341/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660341/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we mark the death of John Hume, a great Irish patriot. We explore one of his unheralded achievements, the Credit Unions and how these small “community banks” transformed Ireland and led to the success of the Derry punk band the Undertones. However, in using financial innovation, Hume was part of a long tradition in Ireland of financing social and political reform. We explore the “magic of the bond market” in making the impossible, possible.</description></item><item><title>Living in interesting times and how best to think of it | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660342/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660342/</guid><description>Podcast Description Four massive economic changes are going on right now under our noses, yet we are unaware of their magnitude because we increasingly value short-term thinking at the cost of long-term thinking. Today we explore those changes, make a case for thinking long-term and tease out how we can escape “the tyranny of now” with the help of Roman Krznaric, Author of: “The Good Ancestor”. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.</description></item><item><title>Taxes, urine &amp; wealth creation | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660343/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660343/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we take a rather unconventional look at the Apple ruling - taking the time to look at the many ways that countries around the world have created wealth. We follow that chat with another conversation with Luke O’Neill who gives us a breakdown of the medical breakthroughs that COVID has accelerated and a quick update on what might be on the horizon from a vaccine point of view Join the gang!</description></item><item><title>From "the craic economy" to the annexation of the West Bank | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660344/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660344/</guid><description>Podcast Description Another week, another episode where we look at the world and try to make sense of it. This week we explore how language evolves, the idea of &amp;ldquo;the craic economy&amp;rdquo; and have a chat with Stav Shaffir, the leader of the green party in Israel Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Black Swans &amp; Black lists | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660345/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660345/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we explore black swans and black lists. First, we explain why the economy behaves more like a complex adaptive system rather than a giant machine. This means we, in the West are exposed to “black swan” events which disrupt the economy. From black swans we move on black lists and black lives with Trinidadian economist Marla Dukharan talking about EU racism, neo-colonialism, bullying and double standards when dealing with small, largely non-white countries.</description></item><item><title>The enormous potential of free money and the illusion of a V shaped recovery | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660346/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660346/</guid><description>Podcast Description How the ECB is turning into the Fed. What Austria issuing a 100 year bond means for Irish economy policy. Why a new EU philosophy is changing the rules of the game! We also talk with Harvard economist Megan Greene about the United State’s future, outlook and why a V shaped recovery might not be on the horizon! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Addressing generational wealth inequality | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660347/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660347/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we talk about the youth &amp;amp; money - because if you lose the youth, you lose the future - something our new government doesn’t seem to be giving much thought to. We also have a chat with renowned international diplomat and former Under Secretary-General of the UN Shashi Tharoor about Ireland winning a seat on the Security Council Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>Skin deep | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660348/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660348/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we discuss options for a New Ireland, building sovereign wealth finders to underwrite a start up nation and why the evolutionary battle between two vitamins explains a lot! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tribal voices | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660349/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660349/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dispatches from a Pulitzer Prize winner on the LA frontline, why the 1980s ain’t coming back, who are ’The Jews who Booze”, why networks matter more than guns and how the economy could recover quickly. This one’s got you covered! Enjoy it. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>America burns, Ireland’s potential reset and the end of Fianna Fáil? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660350/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660350/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Rappers deploy the language of Presidents and Presidents deploy the language of Rappers, you know America is in trouble. Plus, why commercial property is over, Fianna Fails slow demise and a new election in Ireland? Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Unconventional thinking: its enemies &amp; why it is important | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660351/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660351/</guid><description>Podcast Description While it seems that the peak of the cases are now behind us we’re still facing its economic repercussions. The Pandession is here. This week we talk about the social economy, and crucially why it is critical to think unconventionally in times of crisis…..plus lots more, including where the expression “not worth a continental” comes from! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>We are living through a Pandession | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660352/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660352/</guid><description>Podcast Description Language is important, in fact its is essential. If you can’t describe it, you don’t understand it. So, today we coin the expression a “Pandession” - a recession brought about by a pandemic. Plus, how in the new Cold War between America and China, the economic theatre of battle will be supply chains and why Ireland can benefit. Plus, what next for the EU? Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.</description></item><item><title>Leaving Cert - the Irish equivalent of national service. Covid in the Caribbeans &amp; what Judy Garland tells you about monetary economics. | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660353/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660353/</guid><description>Podcast Description From Leaving Cert cancellation to understanding the impact of COVID 19 in other countries and wrapping things up by reframing what you thought about the Wizard of Oz, plus the economic origin of the expression Dixie for the South of the USA - and why its all relevant to the world in 2020. Jam packed episode this week. Hope you enjoy! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>The extreme urgency of now | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660354/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660354/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, why Corona will spark huge changes in economic thinking. We explore the coming a revolution in monetary economics with the woman who may well be the most important economist in the USA in the 2020s, Professor Stephanie Kelton. Also, why small businesses are the beginning, middle and end of the economy and the small matter of how we save the economy now. Plus, we have our first winner of our Schumpeter Slot!</description></item><item><title>Why economics is not a cult, negative oil prices, Newcastle United, Altar boys, America’s reckoning and gay hit men! Whats not to love? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660355/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660355/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we cover a wide array of subjects: from new Irish government to possible recession fixes (no disinfectant involved) and then talking to Frank Kane to get to the bottom of negative oil prices. All this and some history and craic along the way, hope you enjoy! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What’s Next? Lessons from the Great Depression, avoiding bad economics, reading the markets’ tea leaves &amp; the youth surge. | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660356/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660356/</guid><description>Podcast Description These are the times when change happens - not incremental change, drastic changes - the type that can completely change the face of a nation. In this week’s episode we talk about how monetary policy is the key to what happens next. Hope you enjoy! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What’s Next? The frugal four, antibody testing and post-COVID changes | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660357/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660357/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s been another packed week. On this week’s episode we talk about what’s next for the economy, we talk to Prof Luke O’Neill on the next science steps, and anti-body testing; and the short and longer term economic and geo-political consequences of COVID. Plus, we tell you about a time when the Irish were accused of being plague carriers. Take care of yourself. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>The Anatomy of a Pandemic | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660358/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660358/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we explore what’s happening in Ireland and Europe’s crucial reaction, plus we focus on the catastrophe enveloping the developing world. We explore why COVID 19 will change global relations between rich and poor, why we need a new Bretton Woods and an optimistic lesson from the Black Death of 1347! All this, and thoughts on the economics of washing machine, Italia 90 and learning economics in the lockdown.</description></item><item><title>Macroeconomics for a Globalized World | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660359/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 08:26:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660359/</guid><description>Podcast Description Now that we all have more time on our hands, why not use this time to learn economics? I&amp;rsquo;ve devised a new macro economics course based largely on the course I teach in Trinity College Dublin. The audio course comes with detailed notes and reading lists. Here&amp;rsquo;s the introduction free. Join me on Patreon.com/davidmcwilliams for weekly classes and let&amp;rsquo;s master economics, together. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>The economics of the possible | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660360/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 02:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660360/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are looking at the complete rethinking of economics. So much is possible, from mortgage rates plummeting here immediately, to ensuring that taxes never have to rise to pay for our corona spending. All this and what Rihanna can tell you about the long term, unforeseen consequences of pandemics. Also, why not use the lockdown to learn economics with me over the next few weeks? Lets do it together!</description></item><item><title>Beyond money - Why livelihoods matter most | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660361/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660361/</guid><description>Podcast Description Capitalism as we know it has been suspended. The most important thing now is to minimize unemployment and see beyond the crisis. Unemployment isn’t just economical, it’s psychological and emotional. We have an economic vaccine, we explain what it is and how it can be used. But we need to move fast. Take care, stay apart, stay safe and be strong. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>Lockdown, Herd immunity &amp; helicopter money | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660362/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660362/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy St Patrick&amp;rsquo;s Day. The strangest, most eerie one I&amp;rsquo;ve ever experienced. Make no mistake about it, this Coronavirus will change our world profoundly. Nothing, not economics, not politics, not sociology will be the same again. This week we focus on the path of the disease and what central banks should do about it. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Corona goes Global | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660363/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660363/</guid><description>Podcast Description With markets collapsing, oil prices plummeting and the West about to be put in lockdown, we examine the dramatic consequences of Corona for economics and politics. Plus in geo-politics what the showdown between Saudi Arabia and Russia over oil means for all of us. Hope you enjoy it Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Got you face mask yet? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660364/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660364/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we talk viruses with the brilliant Professor Luke O’Neill and as I’m in New York - and no one does panic better than this shower- we explore the similarities between pandemics, financial markets, manias and investor freak-outs! Enjoy and don’t panic!!! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Germany is changing - and Europe should take notice | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660365/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660365/</guid><description>Podcast Description Germany is going through a fundamental change - the alt-right is rising, Angela Merkel’s reign is coming to an end and Germans are aging… how will the steady hand of Europe’s metamorphosis impact the EU and the world? Join us and find out!
Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The battle for the soul of Fianna Fail (if there is such a thing) and are we witnessing China’s Chernobyl? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660366/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660366/</guid><description>Podcast Description Napoleon once said “to govern is to choose”, Fianna Fail has to make a choice, will it be SF or FG in coalition? Plus as the Corona Virus spreads are we witnessing China’s Chernobyl, a tipping point moment after with the Middle Kingdom will never look the same again - and are the financial markets pricing this in? Hope you enjoy! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>Storm Shinner | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660367/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660367/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vladimir Lenin once said “there are decades when nothing happens and there are weeks when decades happen” - this was one of those weeks. We explain what has happened, we explain what the Sinn Fein vote is not, and what it is. Why it could be positive and what are the possible pitfalls, what it means for NI and whether the shift to the Left is permanent or temporary.</description></item><item><title>Stats, polls &amp; elections | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660368/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660368/</guid><description>Podcast Description A leap in the dark or the bright shining light of change? SF - for the first time ever - lead the polls. We welcome Kevin Cunningham - the sharpest pollster in the country - to the podcast in order to help us get a reading on the upcoming Irish elections from a statistical point of view - discussing the pitfalls and opportunities with stats and polling along the way.</description></item><item><title>The Giant Global Housing Swindle | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660369/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660369/</guid><description>Podcast Description From Davos to balance sheet recession this week is all about economics. Join us as we explain how the wealthy get rich in bust economies and how regular people become poor in boom economies Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why traffic is like gas, not liquid | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660370/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660370/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we tackle the problem facing many cities: congestion. We look at why historical thinking isn&amp;rsquo;t working and what could be a possible way forward. Hope you enjoy! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Irish elections and the differences between Fine Gael &amp; Fianna Fáil | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660371/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660371/</guid><description>Podcast Description With an election coming and the RIC debate still raging, we examine the deep differences between FF and FG, what our grandfathers did in 1920, the class basis for 1916, Leinster Rugby and the Christian Brothers Revolutionaries and why Irish politics might be more sophisticated than you imagine. Hope you like it!! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>USA, IRAN and the 3 M’s that precede wars | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660372/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660372/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week has been dominated by news of the rapidly escalating conflict between Iran and the United States - today we breakdown where it came from, what it means and what might be coming in the future - including the 3 M’s that usually precede wars
Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Special episode: Welcome to the Third Decade of the 21st century | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660373/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660373/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re going to be taking a look at our 2019 episodes, trying to find out what you liked best and touch on what is coming from the podcast in 2020 Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The economics of love | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660374/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660374/</guid><description>Podcast Description Money, assets, yield and dividends - all table stakes of economics, but what if there was something underlying all these? This week we talk about the crucial but all too often overlooked aspect of economics: love
Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Boris Johnson, the last PM of the UK? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660375/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660375/</guid><description>Podcast Description The elections are over, Boris Johnson has won a massive and the UK is changed utterly. What does it all mean for all of us, where are we now heading and could Boris Johnson be the last PM of the UK? This week we invite the brilliant economist Diane Coyle, to tease out the issues. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why the British election is about so much more than who will be the next PM. It’s about the very fabric of British society - explained with FT chief political commentator Robert Shrimsley - one is the sharpest political minds covering the UK right now | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660376/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660376/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Thursday the United Kingdom will vote once again - and its choice will have a drastic impact on the future of the country, most notably with Brexit hanging in the balance. Robert Shrimsley joins us to demystify what lies ahead and then we look at how Argentina can teach us lessons about bad management and how those lessons can be applied to the UK
Join the gang! https://plus.</description></item><item><title>Populism and the evolution of Ireland - Live From Vicar street | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660377/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660377/</guid><description>Podcast Description Here it is! Our first ever live show tackling the rise of populism around the world, the evolution of Ireland and so much more, hope you enjoy! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Impeachment explained and the polarization of US politics with professor Bill Black | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660378/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660378/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week in a break from tradition, John and David are joined from the States by Prof Bill Black, scourge of the white collar criminal, to explore impeachment, where might it end and the fractured nature of American society and politics Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A hard look at the human impact of the housing crisis | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660379/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660379/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rising housing costs are not new news - but all too often the human element of the problem is overlooked. Today we discuss the very real human aspect of the problem, how it has impacted society and where it might go from here. Hope you enjoy! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Economics and the law of unintended consequences | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660380/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660380/</guid><description>Podcast Description Economics rarely behaves the way decision makers intended it to - From the Berlin wall to the rise of populism we look at the unintended consequences of economic and political decisions that have impacted history and that are occurring as we speak
Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What does a post-meat world means for society and the economy? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660381/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660381/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Burger King goes veggie - you know something whopper is stirring. This week we take a look at the rapid shift in global meat consumption, how different areas of the world are reacting and the deep ramifications that our eating habits have on the economy. Hope you enjoy! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is the age of the job over? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660382/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660382/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week’s episode is a rollicking Joycean trip around the world from Morocco to Buffalo, focusing on why great artists like James Joyce and great business people are the same sorts, generating commercial and intellectual energy through curiosity and their own skin in the game; in addition, why openness, tolerance and liberalism, are the key to a dynamic economy. Plus Hemingway, Bloom, the Erie Canal and the Ice Age!</description></item><item><title>Brexit - are we there yet? Plus, how the map of the Mid East has been redrawn in the week - all brought to you from the Atlas Mountains in Morocco. | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660383/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660383/</guid><description>Podcast Description This weeks podcast brought to you from high up in the Atlas Mountains in Morocco aims to explain the latest Brexit Boloxology and from the Arab world, how lines in the sand written by colonialists one hundred years ago continue to haunt the Kurds, Iraqis, Turks and the Irish!
Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Brexit endgame: a plot summary | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660384/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660384/</guid><description>Podcast Description What have Coleen Rooney, Boris Johnson and Leo Varadkar all got in common? Tales from the Brexit end game, a bit of economics and the political twilight for the 400 year old Project Britain Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We need to fix the root problem: wealth inequality | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660385/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660385/</guid><description>Podcast Description Here’s the latest episode on the overarching political/social/economic issue of our day, wealth inequality. How has it happened, why is it profoundly worrying and how we can solve it - enjoy Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to get ready for globalization 3.0 | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660386/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660386/</guid><description>Podcast Description Small countries live and die by the quality of their strategic thinking. This week’s podcast focuses on how small countries can truly transform themselves, clutching victory from the jaws of defeat, by completely re-thinking the relationship with multinational companies. Globalization 3.0 here we come! Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Out of Africa | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660387/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660387/</guid><description>Podcast Description I’ve just come back from Kenya, this week we are discussing poverty, relentless entrepreneurialism, the role of technology in transforming Africa and why it will be the site of the next battle between America and China Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A future warning from past cities! | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660388/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660388/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we tackle the matter of future cities - as urban living becomes financially impossible for the middle class around the world how can we find a way forward that accommodates everyone? Through the lens of history we try to make sense of it all and propose a path forward Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Boris Johnson is not a politician, he’s a gambler | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660389/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2019 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660389/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we analyse why Boris Johnson is not a politician, how different societies react to democratic struggles and why bottom-up societies is a better way forward than the traditional top-down structures many of us have today. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Curious minds - Discussing Turkey and losing democracy with Ece Temelkuran | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660390/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 04:30:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660390/</guid><description>Podcast Description For this month&amp;rsquo;s curious minds episode we talk with Ece Temelkuran, one of Turkey’s best-known journalists and political commentators about her latest book- How to Lose a Country: The 7 Steps from Democracy to Dictatorship, her own personal experience in Turkey and what the world should understand from it. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Fragility of democracy and why winner takes all economics has led to the rise of populism | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660391/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660391/</guid><description>Podcast Description Democracy is often taken for granted and many countries are currently testing its resilience right before our eyes. On this episode we break down how we ended up in this political/economic/social mess
Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trade wars, amazon fires &amp; the unexpected consequences of economics | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660392/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660392/</guid><description>Podcast Description Economic decisions impact many facets of our lives - often in unexpected ways. This week we connect the dots between seemingly unrelated events and explain how economics decisions are at the core of it all. Plus why countries need to grieve and learn how to adapt from loss of power &amp;amp; influence Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ireland, Brexit and the Great British Breakoff, from Britsplaing to Explaining and lots more in between!! Enjoy | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660393/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660393/</guid><description>Podcast Description As Brexit moves towards the endgame and the UK government’s new policy appears to centre on inflicting as much economic damage as possible on Ireland to change the “backstop”, we explore why the Brexiteers are so ignorant about Ireland, how come Ireland is now considerably richer than the UK, more globalized and more resilient. In short, when so-called “Global Britain” exports 1.5 times more to “little” Ireland than it does to China, you know the Brexiteers are living in an economic la la land!</description></item><item><title>Are we heading towards a global economic slowdown? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660394/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660394/</guid><description>Podcast Description With the central bank cutting interest rates last week we thought it would be a good idea to analyze the current market signals and try to breakdown what might be looming in the future for the global economy
Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trying to untangle Iran and the Middle East relationships | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660395/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660395/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we dive into the Middle East as tension have currently been ramping up between the United States and Iran - How did we get here, what do we need to know to understand the middle east and why is Turkey the wildcard? That’s what we’re going to attempt to explain. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Curious minds - Discussing the evolution of journalism and technology with Tom Friedman | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660396/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660396/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we’re introducing a new monthly segment to the podcast that I’m calling curious minds. These are going to be a series of 1-on-1 conversations with various personalities offering unique viewpoints that I want to share with you. I’m kicking things off with the legendary American correspondent Tom Friedman, 3 times Pulitzer winner and New York Times columnist talking about the evolution of journalism, the position of the United States and technology’s impact on all of us.</description></item><item><title>China's unique approach to foreign influence | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660397/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660397/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2100 four out of ten people on the plant will be African. What does that mean for economics, politics and geo-political relations. While the West hasn&amp;rsquo;t been looking, China has made a huge bet on Africa, lending billions to African countries. Will this bet come off and if it does, what will it mean for all of us Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>The next phase of Brexit through its history, its psychology and its economics | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660398/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660398/</guid><description>Podcast Description Boris Johnson's rise to MP marks a new chapter for Brexit. As we enter this next phase, we tease out how we got here: Looking at where the movement started. Attempting to understand what are the driving forces of Brexit (its not economics!). And finally, looking at what the future holds for the UK’s economy if Brexit goes the way Boris Johnson wants (and why Leo Varadkar has Johnson by the balls)</description></item><item><title>Why healthy economies are inherently unstable not inherently stable! | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660399/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660399/</guid><description>Podcast Description What do you get when you cross Donna Summer, David Bowie, Bitcoin, Joseph Schumpeter, creativity and innovation? You get the essence of the modern capitalist economy, something called “creative destruction” - the most potent force in economics. In this podcast ,we explore the role of disruption in the economy from 1970s disco beats to 21st century blockchain technology. Hope you enjoy it and tell us about what you thought!</description></item><item><title>The failed war on drugs | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660400/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660400/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s time to face the facts - the war on drugs has been a failed experiment. Anyone with a basic knowledge of economics and supply and demand will know that prohibition drives prices upwards, drive profits into the hands of criminal gangs and those very profit coaxes more gangs into the business, leading to more and more violence. It&amp;rsquo;s time to call time on the war on drugs and apply common sense economics to this global issue.</description></item><item><title>Understanding China's trade wars, Brexit and Tianammen Square through the lens of Japanese history | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660401/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660401/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, we examine today’s geo-politics, the China vs America showdown and related economic threats through lessons from Japan’s Meji Restoration, plus Soviet and Chinese history. Remember, those who forget their economic history are condemned to repeat it. Enjoy Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A guide to understanding Germany | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660402/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660402/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why has Germany, the most important country in Europe, not had the political sway that matches its economic dominance and how that might change in the future. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why it’s time to move Dublin Port | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660403/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660403/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dublin Port is 600 acres of prime residential land, beside the sea, close to all transport links and it should be developed in a new city on the water. The rest of the world is moving their ports, even Cork is, yet in Dublin, the legacy of a time when ports had to be at the mouths of rivers because rivers were a country’s key transport links, dominates our urban thinking.</description></item><item><title>International property cycles | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660404/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660404/</guid><description>Podcast Description The global markets have never been so connected, and economies tend to be cyclical - what does that mean for Ireland as we face the real possibility of a global economic slowdown? Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trump’s tariffs explained &amp; the new tech cold war | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660405/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660405/</guid><description>Podcast Description As Trump lands in Ireland this week, we examine his trade war with China, his tariff policy and who it really hurts, plus why China and the US are heading for a major conflict and why the new Cold War is in truth a tech Cold War which the US believes it has to win and the implications of all this for politics, Silicon Valley and the world economy.</description></item><item><title>Exploring the ramifications of a united Ireland | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660406/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 09:50:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660406/</guid><description>Podcast Description There's a wind of change in the air and its nationalism, you can feel it - it's in France, in the UK and even in Ireland. For the first time in a long time, Brexit and demographics in Northern Ireland have opened a real possibility of a united Ireland. But what would it mean, culturally, politically and economically?
Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Special episode: A sit down with Bernie Sanders | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660407/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 20:53:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660407/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is going to be a bit of a different one - back in 2017 I had a chance to sit down with Bernie Sanders for a wonderful conversation - and as some of the topics discussed then are still making headlines now, we wanted to share this amazing conversation with you. Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>US politics, the fed, AOC &amp; quantitative easing | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660408/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 05:35:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660408/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s time to join the dots. We explore why the shift to the left from younger voters is simply a logical reaction to policies that were put in place to save the baby boomer’s way of life, what that means for politics &amp; for the economy now, and in the future.
Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Shadow banks &amp; Dublin's crane epidemic | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660409/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 05:35:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660409/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is Dublin about to experience a commercial property crash? For some, the skyline with swarms of cranes signals prosperity, to others it signals risk. Which one will it be? Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Black Irish &amp; European elections | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660410/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 08:10:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660410/</guid><description>Podcast Description They say history repeats itself. Economic history certainly does. In this podcast, we are going to look at the upcoming European elections and in particular, the rise of populist parties, through the lens of Irish history and specifically, what happened in American politics in reaction to 1000 Irish emigrants a day arriving, poor and destitute into New York in the 1840s and 1850s. The story the Irish in the ghettos of New York and “nativist” political reaction to mass migration will help us understand what is going on in Europe right now.</description></item><item><title>Is Brexit good or bad for Ireland? | The David McWilliams Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9916660411/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 14:49:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9916660411/</guid><description>Podcast Description How can Ireland make the best of Brexit? Join us as we explore the potential benefits and pitfalls of Brexit through soccer anecdotes, comparisons with Yugoslavia, and childhood bar stories to outline Ireland's path to success post-Brexit
Join the gang! https://plus.acast.com/s/the-david-mcwilliams-podcast.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>