<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>I've Had It on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/ive-had-it/</link><description>Recent content in I've Had It on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 22:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/ive-had-it/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Live Laugh Love with Gigi Goode | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are joined today by the queen, Gigi Goode. Gigi has had it with all the BS that comes with adulting, inspirational quotes and loud talkers on public transit. Gigi gives the girls some tea on Mormons at the gay bars and rats on herself by admitting that she&amp;rsquo;s an axe murderer. Jennifer identifies a new red flag in the corporate world that all of us at the I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It &amp;ldquo;family&amp;rsquo; need to watch out for.</description></item><item><title>My Heart and Legs are Open | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps get real kinky in today&amp;rsquo;s episode. Jennifer does a dramatic reading of a recent article detailing the BDSM world of Conservatives and Liberals. The girls also listen to your voice memos covering topics from the toothpicking pants-hiking chili-eating old men that call waitresses “darlin” to the gay couples out there that continuously get asked if they’re siblings.
Come see I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It live on the Hot Sh*t Tour!</description></item><item><title>What in the Caucasian Hell | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are here today to deliver some of the most ridiculous news stories on the World Wide Web today. From &amp;lsquo;break-up photoshoots&amp;rsquo; to man-handling live opossums in a Christmas tree. We also layout our new business plan for 2024 - Karens For Hire LLC -where we redirect karenism for the greater good, led by our very own repurposed karen, Judge Judy Diana.
Come see I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It live on the Hot Sh*t Tour!</description></item><item><title>An ATM Machine of Great Ideas with Symone | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680004/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are joined today by the award-winning drag queen Symone. The three have had it with bare feet in the airport, daylight savings and obnoxious little blue text messages. Pumps has had it with women taking too long in the bathroom and Jen has had it with Pumps’ and her most recent yak-mouthing offense.
Come see I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It live on the Hot Sh*t Tour! More info &amp;amp; tickets available at https://linktr.</description></item><item><title>Un-American Cheese with Matt Bellassai | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Matt Bellassai dropped by the studio today to do some top tier sh*t talking with Jennifer and Pumps, in person. The three have had it with the &amp;lsquo;is it cake?&amp;rsquo; trend, American cheese (the worst cheese ever) and the scam artists we call dentists. Jennifer tells Matt and the listeners about the time we attempted to do man-on-the-street interviews in New York City and Pumps cracks up at an A+ blow job joke.</description></item><item><title>Everybody Here Hates Me with Taylor Strecker | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are joined today by Taylor Strecker, host of the Taste of Taylor podcast. The three discuss an issue which Jen has appropriately named &amp;lsquo;vaginasplaining&amp;rsquo; - Taylor has to take an L when the girls come for her and her bad grocery store behavior. Jennifer has had it with black and white thinkers and Pumps brings the receipts on the stupidest vanity plates (aka douche tags) that have crossed her path this week.</description></item><item><title>A Skunk at the Garden Party with Michael Kosta | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are joined by comedian and The Daily Show correspondent, Michael Kosta. Michael has had it with non-engaged listeners, a &amp;ldquo;white trash sport&amp;rdquo; taking over the country and Jennifer&amp;rsquo;s boyfriend Rafael Nadal. Jennifer and Pumps also do a fantasy interview with Melania Trump, asking all the hard-hitting and extremely inappropriate questions that we all want to know the answers to.
Come see I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It live on the Hot Sh*t Tour!</description></item><item><title>A Gaytheist with Ginger Minj | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are joined today by Drag Race all-star, Ginger Minj. These three have had it with the negativity toward drag in this country, modern skin care and crazy family members. Ginger opens up about their childhood and finding their confidence through the art of drag. Pumps has had with stupid questions during a movie and Jennifer has had it with the &amp;ldquo;Jet Bridge Hogs&amp;rdquo; at the airport.</description></item><item><title>Anti-Bucket List with Rennae Stubbs | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are joined by a tennis legend (and Pump&amp;rsquo;s new crush) Rennae Stubbs. The three bond over their shared hatred for all-inclusive cruises, Ron &amp;lsquo;Kitten Heels&amp;rsquo; DeSantis and sh**ty bathroom ettiequte - pun intended. Pumps has had it with selfish communicators and Jennifer does a dramatic reading of a very alarming new disease sweeping the nation.
Come see I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It live on the Hot Sh*t Tour!</description></item><item><title>I Forget I'm Famous with Meghan Trainor | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680010/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pumps is FINALLY not the most famous person on the podcast today because the girls are joined by global superstar, Meghan Trainor. The three discuss IBS, homeschooling and gender reveal parties. Meghan also gets vulnerable and opens up about her recent comments regarding teachers. Jen is worried about Ben Affleck and Pumps works through some role play with Dr. Jennifer Welch (who is not a licensed therapist nor does she play one on TV) that might help her draw some boundaries next time she&amp;rsquo;s in an airport.</description></item><item><title>Who's Your Momma? | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680011/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are fired up today. They have had it with the new Speaker of the House and his Jill Duggar-esque wife &amp;amp; the girls both go on the permanent record with some very disturbing choices in s*x partners. We also play listener voice memos which end up calling out Jen and Pumps as offenders of a few of your grievances.
Come see I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It live on the Hot Sh*t Tour!</description></item><item><title>Thirst Trapping Moms with Elle Duncan | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680012/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are joined today by Elle Duncan, ESPN anchor and host of the Elle Duncan Show. The three discuss the myth that it is the work-life balance and what Elle hopes the future for black women in journalism can look like. Pumps and Elle bond over a common love of softball while Jennifer gets absolutely railed for her “sport” of choice.
Come see I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It live on the Hot Sh*t Tour!</description></item><item><title>Good Not Great with Josh Peck &amp; Ben Soffer | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680038/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are joined by two of our favorite podcasters, Josh Peck &amp;amp; Ben Soffer, the hosts of the Good Guys Podcast. Josh has had it with yoga instructors who think they&amp;rsquo;re now some kind of &amp;ldquo;spiritual giant&amp;rdquo; and Ben has had it with the insanity of tipping culture - ESPECIALLY at a self-checkout. Jennifer puts the boys on the spot with a salacious Had It or Hit It question that leads to Pumps revealing a very scandalous answer.</description></item><item><title>Blasphemous Naughty Nuns | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680039/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Halloween Titty Babies! The two naughtiest nuns in the podcasting business are back with a very blasphemous halloween episode. Jennifer (who is not a centrist) and Pumps (also not a centrist) listen to some hilarious voice memos hand-picked by Kiley (a faith and flag conservative). The girls also recap their trip to the halloween costume shop that ended in an attempt at forced philanthropy and baby talking.</description></item><item><title>Asked and Answered with Jonathan Van Ness | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680040/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are officially hot sh*t because THE Jonathan Van Ness has stopped by to talk about all the things they&amp;rsquo;ve had it with. Judge Judy Diana teaches JVN some hot legal terms that lead to a round of role play and Jennifer stumps Jonathan in an incredibly difficult game of had it or hit it.
Come see I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It live on the Hot Sh*t Tour! More info &amp;amp; tickets available at https://linktr.</description></item><item><title>I Love Rehab with Margaret Cho | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680041/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are joined by comedian and actress, Margaret Cho. Margaret has had it with scammers using her love of cats against her and geriatric politicians refusing to retire. Two things she hasn&amp;rsquo;t had it with? Rehab and funerals. Pumps brings down the IQ of the episode by once again giving out her personal information willy-nilly and Jennifer (the bony one) is decreed the Patron Saint of Podcasting.</description></item><item><title>What the Hell Is Wrong With You? | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680042/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps will never be the same after listening to your voice memos today. From SAHM scrub abuse to grandparents not accepting their gay canine grandchildren, this episode drives the girls to pure insanity -because if you can&amp;rsquo;t beat &amp;rsquo;em, join &amp;rsquo;em. And make sure to be on the look out for new I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast Scrubs, soon to be available at a Walmart near you!</description></item><item><title>Different Strokes with Bianca Del Rio | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680043/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps have finally met their match - Bianca Del Rio joins the pod today and shows the girls what a PHD in hating really looks like. Bianca believes we need to stop using paper straws because how else will the turtles do blow? She&amp;rsquo;s also had it with idiots at the airport, Elton John&amp;rsquo;s wig and drag queens who don&amp;rsquo;t wear earrings. Jennifer has had it with true religion jean wearing youth pastors and Pumps has had it with influencers in the wild.</description></item><item><title>My Crazy Uncle with Mary Trump | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680044/</guid><description>Podcast Description We all have a crazy uncle, but todays guest has the craziest one of them all. Jennifer and Pumps are joined by Mary Trump to talk about the insanity that is Donald Trump. The girls ask all the hard-hitting questions, like: &amp;ldquo;Does he even believe in God?&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Is he really not an alcoholic?&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Have you ever seen him without the comb-over?&amp;rdquo; and Mary answers them all. Pumps has had it with ti**y baby football players who can&amp;rsquo;t hold their own water bottle and Jennifer whips a few of her famous dramatic readings of some of our idiotic hate comments.</description></item><item><title>I Don't Dilly &amp; I Refuse to Dally with Ross Mathews | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680045/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are joined by the hilarious Ross Mathews for one extremely &amp;ldquo;sh*tty&amp;rdquo; conversation - from the Delta flyer incident to the time Pumps took a dump in styrofoam cup on the highway. Jennifer brings up a rather barbaric childhood trend and Pumps has had it with scam calls and their sneaky new tricks.
Come see I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It live on the Hot Sh*t Tour! More info &amp;amp; tickets available at https://linktr.</description></item><item><title>Confronting Our F*** Ups with Josh Welch | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680046/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer, Pumps and Josh get vulnerable in todays episode. You may be familiar with the infamous five rehab stints but today Josh joins to talk in-depth about his struggles and how Jennifer, Pumps and his two boys stuck by him through it all. Pumps opens up for the first time about her own struggles with sobriety and Jennifer delivers some very exciting news about Josh with the listeners.</description></item><item><title>The HBIC with Suze Orman | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680047/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps sit down with the OG head b**** in charge, Suze Orman. Suze has had it with people spending money they don&amp;rsquo;t have to impress people they don&amp;rsquo;t even like and gives the listeners some advice that&amp;rsquo;ll change their life. The three also discuss the issue that is Forced Capitalism. Pumps gets a little too excited performing an ear extraction on Kiley and Jennifer finally clears the air about the sexual tension between her and Pumps.</description></item><item><title>This is So Unladylike with Ashley Longshore | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680048/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps couldn&amp;rsquo;t visit New York City without hitting up the hilarious and talented, Ashley Longshore. Ashley explains how she is metaphorically &amp;lsquo;keeping things equal&amp;rsquo; with the patriarchy, talks about her newly opened NYC showroom and shares a first-time experience she had on Fire Island. Jennifer enlists Ashley to help further the gaslighting of Pumps sexuality and Pumps finds out she may or may not have voluntarily chloroformed herself.</description></item><item><title>Stupid Straight People Stuff with Katya | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680049/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Three biological women, Jennifer, Pumps and Katya, gather to discuss everything they&amp;rsquo;ve had it with. Katya has HAD IT with the Pope, cordless vacuums and body hair. Jennifer gets convinced to do a rather scandalous photoshoot and Pumps has had it with the disturbing twend of moms who wear matching outfits with their poor poor kids.
Come see I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It live on the Hot Sh*t Tour! More info &amp;amp; tickets available at https://linktr.</description></item><item><title>Listen Up Tight Tits with Deux Moi | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680050/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680050/</guid><description>Podcast Description The queen of celebrity news, @DeuxMoi, anonymously joins Jennifer and Pumps today for a hilarious and insightful sh*t-talking session. Deux has had with celebs that call the paparazzi on themselves and those that post annoying cryptic quotes on Instagram. Jennifer has had with airport bathroom abuse, Pumps calls out Jennifer over her lack of chivalry and Kiley preaches the benefits of staying dehydrated on purpose.
Come see I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It live on the Hot Sh*t Tour!</description></item><item><title>All Hat No Cattle | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680051/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps aren&amp;rsquo;t holding back on todays episode. Pumps has had it with the a**holes that leave only one square of toilet paper on the roll and Jennifer has had it with the prick tease known as Hasan Piker. The girls also discuss adult-only flights, dingleberries at waxing appointments and ding-dongs that wear their Apple Watches during sex.
Come see I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It live on the Hot Sh*t Tour!</description></item><item><title>An Exit-Only Hole for Me | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680052/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680052/</guid><description>Podcast Description We all know Jennifer and Pumps love a good dramatic reading and this time we’re taking our talents to the review section of Amazon. From depressing cookbooks for one, jumping the gun on a bulk order of condoms and a great gift idea if you’re looking to get rid of your in-laws, Amazon has it all. Pumps also has a shocking revelation about what’s really going on with a***** bleaching.</description></item><item><title>Love Yourself Less with Jared Freid | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680053/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps missed this guest so much they had to bring him back a second time. Jared Freid joins the girls for a full on sh*t-talking session, from long-winded Instagram captions to CYA photo sessions on bachelor parties. Jennifer does a dramatic reading of a fantastic one star review and Pumps claims that while she is receiving mail from AARP (because she&amp;rsquo;s much much older than Jennifer) she is standing strong and refusing to give in to it.</description></item><item><title>A Manscaping Metrosexual with Josh Welch | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680054/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680054/</guid><description>Podcast Description When you think about trying manscaping for the first time, where’s the first place you go? Obviously Best Buy. Jennifer and Pumps have the famous Josh Welch back in the hot seat to talk about all the things he’s had it with - From take-out order tomfoolery to bad group chat ettiquete. Josh also finally opens about the Italy “Speedogate” incident and how it led him to a very “ballsy” conversation with a Best Buy employee.</description></item><item><title>Soaked in the Devil with Zachariah Porter | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680055/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are joined in studio by the hilarious Zachariah Porter. The three have had it with wedding culture, domestic terrorism via public restroom and the ridiculous removal of smoking sections on airplanes. Zachariah also whips out his famous East Coast mom impression that we all know and love.
Come see I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It live on the Hot Sh*t Tour! More info &amp;amp; tickets available at https://linktr.ee/ivehaditpodcast</description></item><item><title>Pumps' Algorithm Boyfriend with Ben Meiselas | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680056/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer is making dreams come true today. She has invited Pumps&amp;rsquo; algorithm boyfriend, the co-founder of MeidasTouch Ben Meiselas, on the pod today. Ben talks about his time representing Colin Kaepernick versus the NFL and all the things he&amp;rsquo;s had it with regarding the new Republican Party. Jennifer has had it with the obnoxious nervous leg bounce and Pumps is finally thinking about setting some boundaries with her adult children.</description></item><item><title>Raw Doggin in Florida | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680057/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are raw doggin it solo today. Pumps has had it with delivery truck drivers blocking everybody in and Jennifer has had it with conveyor belt hogs at the airport. We play some hilarious listener voice memos - one submission in particular makes it into the I’ve Had It hall of fame.
Come see I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It live on the Hot Sh*t Tour! More info &amp;amp; tickets available at https://linktr.</description></item><item><title>Nefarious Neighbors | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680058/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps cannot get enough of the f**kery going on in the Nextdoor App. From feline self-defense classes to &amp;lsquo;abdocating&amp;rsquo; for dogs on death row, we&amp;rsquo;ve got it all. The girls also give a detailed &amp;ldquo;how to&amp;rdquo; course on looking your very best for school pick-up and drop-off and when/if it is appropriate to only wear a robe.
Come see I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It live on the Hot Sh*t Tour!</description></item><item><title>An Opinionated Homosexual with Cody Rigsby | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680059/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are joined by Cody Rigsby, Peloton Superstar and author of XOXO, Cody: An Opinionated Homosexual&amp;rsquo;s Guide to Self-Love, Relationships, and Tactful Pettiness. The three discuss wardrobe fraud, if kitten heels can be considered sexy and the intricacies of marrying for money. Pumps has had it with &amp;lsquo;Boundary Abuse&amp;rsquo; and Jennifer calls out parking spot squatters.
Come see I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It live on the Hot Sh*t Tour!</description></item><item><title>Single Mom Uber Driver with Yolanda Fister | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680060/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps called up their favorite Uber driver, Yolanda Fister, to talk about all the philanthropic good-deeds the girls have done. From saving a listener from an armed robber to giving dying dogs mouth-to-mouth resuscitation. Pumps may or may not have secretly gotten laid and Jennifer may or may not crash her car into the front of Pumps&amp;rsquo; house.
Come see I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It live on the Hot Sh*t Tour!</description></item><item><title>The Lesbian National Anthem with Kristin Key | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680061/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are joined in studio by the hilarious Kristin Key. The three discuss bad pets, Pump&amp;rsquo;s bald gay husky and how Jennifer allegedly looks just like a hairless cat. Kristin closes the show out by serenading Jen and Pumps with an original song.
Come see I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It live on the Hot Sh*t Tour! More info &amp;amp; tickets available at https://linktr.ee/ivehaditpodcast
Thank you to our sponsors:</description></item><item><title>Smooth as a Ken Doll | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680062/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are back for a listener submission episode - but before they could even get to your hilarious voice memos they had to address the manic meltdowns that are happening over the Barbie movie - Ben Shapiro we&amp;rsquo;re lookin&amp;rsquo; at you bub. Pumps can&amp;rsquo;t stop thinking about 600lb sex lives and Jennifer has had it with &amp;ldquo;secreting grandstanders.&amp;rdquo;
Come see I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It live on the Hot Sh*t Tour!</description></item><item><title>Hashtag Pinch Me with Watch What Crappens | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680063/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are joined by podcast legends, Ben Mandelker &amp;amp; Ronnie Karam, the hosts of Watch What Crappens. The group has had it with mens deodorant scents such as Alpha Male and Manly Musk. Pumps has had it with waiting at the doctors office and Jennifer calls out Instagram influencers pretending to be obsessed with nature, when the truth is they&amp;rsquo;re just obsessed with themselves. Some listeners did a deep dive on MizzWelch&amp;rsquo;s instagram and demand explanation to some questionable caption choices&amp;hellip;.</description></item><item><title>I Actually Don't Like You Anymore with Liza Treyger | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680064/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps have HAD IT and so has comedian Liza Treyger. The three discuss high maintenance friendships, the downfall of the once great toilet paper holder and titty baby billionaires. Jen and Pumps also get called ‘lazy twats’ by their ‘number one fan.’
Come see I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It live on the Hot Sh*t Tour! More info &amp;amp; tickets available at https://linktr.ee/ivehaditpodcast
Thank you to our sponsors:
SimpliSafe: Listeners get a special 20% off any SimpliSafe system when you sign up for Fast Protect Monitoring.</description></item><item><title>Beautiful, Systemic and Seamless Trolling | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680065/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680065/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s a freeballin&amp;rsquo; kind of day, Listener. Jennifer and Pumps catch up after a two week separation and they have A LOT to discuss. From their appearance on the Today Show to some top-notch, inject it straight into our veins Internet Trolling from single mom uber driver, Yolanda Fister - the girls leave no stone unturned. Pumps expresses the utter shock she felt from an unsettling speedo sighting, Jennifer recalls a disturbing story regarding the Saggin&amp;rsquo; Dragons and Kiley plays some A+ listener submissions for the girls.</description></item><item><title>Death is a Total Racket with Trixie Mattel | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680066/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pull out the permanent record because Jennifer and Pumps are officially hot shit. Trixie Mattel joins the girls and she has had it with her niece, the fake mall cops that we call the TSA and open casket funerals. Pumps wants everyone to stop trying to find their purpose in life and Jennifer has had it with all the faux philosophers plaguing social media.
The Hot Sh*t Tour is heading to Atlanta, Philly and D.</description></item><item><title>Is Ozempic Gluten-Free? with Keltie Knight | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680067/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are joined by Keltie Knight, host of Superfan and the LadyGang podcast. The three discuss what kind of things we might find on different celebrity For You Pages. Keltie has had it with babies (unless they happen to embody the soul of an 84-year-old.) Pumps tries to figure out the psychology behind women that fall in love with convicted murderers in prison and Jennifer does a dramatic reading of a very enduring love letter.</description></item><item><title>I Didn't Raise Y'all Like That | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680068/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are back with a very special episode. Pumps continues to prove why she is a horrible pet owner (Scout if you&amp;rsquo;re reading this, we hope you&amp;rsquo;re okay) and Jennifer brings on her new favorite TikToker, Brittani Mfn Monique. Brittani and Jennifer bond over their intense love for their &amp;ldquo;biological children&amp;rdquo; and try their best to inspire Pumps to be a better dog mom.
The Hot Sh*t Tour is heading to Atlanta, Philly and D.</description></item><item><title>We Are SUCH Good People with Nikki Glaser | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680069/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nikki Glaser joins Jennifer and Pumps to share her many, many grievances. These three believe that people should &amp;lsquo;flaunt it if you got it, but especially if you bought it.&amp;rsquo; J-Lo hates our guts and hopes we all stay ugly. Pumps tells the listener about her unfortunate Ozempic journey thus far &amp;amp; Jennifer pays tribute to the brave men and women of the skies, the only group of people rejecting the &amp;ldquo;customer is always right&amp;rsquo; mindset.</description></item><item><title>The Princess Diana of Probiotics | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680070/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Empower yourself to take control of your health and become your own advocate for yourself and your families. Stay on top of the advancements in health to live longer, healthier lives.
If you’re ready to take control of constipation, bloat and stress and live your healthiest life yet, you can get 20% off your first 90-day bottle of Just Calm and Just Thrive Probiotic today. Visit JustThriveHealth.com and use promo code: HADIT.</description></item><item><title>The Dumbest MFers on the World Wide Web | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680071/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are diving into the nefarious world of the Nextdoor app. Nextdoor is an endless scroll of absolutely psychotic neighbors - Self-reporting peeping toms? you betchya. A cat with the biggest set of balls you&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen? absolutely. A possible Gary Busey cult sighting? no brainer. Join us as we attempt to unpack the utter idiocy of nosy neighbors.
The Hot Sh*t Tour is heading to Atlanta, Philly and D.</description></item><item><title>I Don’t Have Time to Pee with Hannah Berner | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680072/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps have a very special guest in-studio today - comedian and podcast host, Hannah Berner. The three destroy the oversized beverage community, which obviously is a direct attack on the star of the show. Pumps gets real and opens up about her dehydration journey and quick shots in the bedroom finally get the praise they deserve.
The Hot Sh*t Tour is heading to Atlanta, Philly and D.</description></item><item><title>Bored to Death | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680073/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Josh Welch is back and better than ever. Jennifer, Pumps and Josh take turns sharing their grievances, most of which come back to Pumps and her lesbian arc. The three end the episode with listener submissions, one of which confirms Josh’s main complaint of the day…
The Hot Sh*t Tour is heading to Atlanta, Philly and D.C in August! more info &amp;amp; tickets available at https://linktr.ee/ivehaditpodcast
Thank you to our sponsors:</description></item><item><title>Birthdays Are Narcissistic with Nick Viall | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680074/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are joined by host of the &amp;lsquo;Viall Files&amp;rsquo; and king of the shirtless selfie, Nick Viall. The three discuss the narcissists who celebrate birthday months and Jennifer and Nick disagree on dating advice. Pumps owns up to an embarrassing dust up at a strip club and Jennifer tells us about the time pretended to be the &amp;ldquo;Granola Joan of Ark&amp;rdquo; for a man.
The Hot Sh*t Tour is heading to Atlanta, Philly and D.</description></item><item><title>That's Your Moment to Shut Up | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680075/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps, better known as La Capitana and the Princess of Podcasting, are back for more listener submissions. In this episode we get into witchcraft, freezing to death and &amp;ldquo;life narrators&amp;rdquo; who don&amp;rsquo;t know when to shut the f*** up. Jennifer campaigns against using the weather to make unnecessary chit chat and Pumps defends her morgue-like living situation.
The Hot Sh*t Tour is heading to Atlanta, Philly and D.</description></item><item><title>Venmo for Jesus with Laci Mosley | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680076/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Listen up, listeners!! We&amp;rsquo;re taking this show on the road. The Hot Shit Tour is heading to Atlanta, Philly and D.C in August - more info &amp;amp; tickets available at linktr.ee/ivehaditpodcast
Jennifer and Pumps are joined by the Scam Goddess, Laci Mosley, today to discuss a few of our favorite scam artists: Hilaria Baldwin the cucumber queen, Elizabeth &amp;rsquo;too pretty for prison&amp;rsquo; Holmes and the almighty Hillsong Church debacle.</description></item><item><title>Eye Roll City | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680077/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are back with another listener submission episode and you all did not disappoint. The two butt heads over long fake eyelashes but find themselves in agreeance over the monstrosity that was Josh&amp;rsquo;s man bun. One caller in particular delivers a catch-phrase so good, it may have changed Jennifers life forever.
Thank you to our sponsors:
CareOf: This episode is sponsored by CareOf, visit takecareof.com and use code &amp;lsquo;hadit50&amp;rsquo; for 50% off your first order.</description></item><item><title>Queen of Gaslighting with Kelly Osbourne | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680078/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are joined by Kelly Osbourne in a special New York City episode. Kelly has had it with know-it-alls, Americans pronouncing &amp;rsquo;twat&amp;rsquo; incorrectly and she also delivers some very strong opinions on the Royal Family. Jen and Pumps swap stories from rehab family week and Kelly opens up about her family&amp;rsquo;s experience with addiction.
Thank you to our sponsors:
CareOf: This episode is sponsored by CareOf, visit takecareof.</description></item><item><title>The Vanderpump Bump with Alex Baskin | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680079/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 22:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680079/</guid><description>Podcast Description You filthy Vanderpump obsessed animals finally wore the girls down. Jennifer and Pumps called up their old friend Alex Baskin, who happens to be the Executive Producer of Vanderpump Rules, to get all the dirty details on everything #Scandoval. The girls ask the hard hitting questions of what REALLY went down, what to expect next season and how the hell production didn&amp;rsquo;t know what was going on the entire time.</description></item><item><title>Sunny With a Chance of Orgasms with Emily Morse | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680080/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 22:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are joined by Dr. Emily Morse to talk about all things SEX. The three discuss the societal shame surrounding sex and Jennifer teaches Pumps a few new moves. Thank you to our sponsor: Apartments.com - the place to find a place.
Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast
Follow Us:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast: @Ivehaditpodcast
Jennifer Welch: @mizzwelch
Angie &amp;ldquo;Pumps&amp;rdquo; Sullivan: @pumpspumpspumps
Special Guest:
Dr. Emily Morse: @sexwithemily</description></item><item><title>Is It Still Mansplaining if You’re in Drag? with Delta Work | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680081/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 22:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps sit down with a fellow sht talking queen, Delta Work. The three talk about the lack of autonomy other human beings have when they step out into the world. Pumps makes Delta choose between an impossible FMK (spoiler: Mike Pence is probably a freak in the sheets) and Jennifer gives some advice on proper dck pic procedure.
Thank you to our sponsors:
Lume: Control body odor, ANYWHERE with @lumedeodorant and $5 off of your Starter Pack (that&amp;rsquo;s over 40% off) with promo code HADIT at lumedeodorant.</description></item><item><title>Deadlines Are Dead to Me with The Pioneer Woman | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680082/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 22:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are joined in-studio by a very special guest today&amp;hellip;. The Pioneer Woman, Ree Drummond, sits down with the girls to air out her long list of &amp;lsquo;had its&amp;rsquo; and she did not disappoint. From couples who claim their spouse is their best friend to your kids making you look like an a**hole in front of the school guidance counselor. Pumps happily hands out her social security number to a scammer and Jennifer is putting a stop to the ridiculous amount of unnecessary and unearned graduation ceremonies.</description></item><item><title>She's Really Let Herself Go | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680083/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 22:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps loop in the listeners for half an hour of debauchery. The girls listen to hilarious submissions covering topics that range from spouses calling 15 times a day to the Instagram influencers who claim to have just “woken up in paradise.” Jen and Pumps also get validation from a Floridian that wants to help the girls annex the state off the planet.
Thank you to our sponsors:</description></item><item><title>Poodles Are Really Getting Laid with Heather McMahan | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680084/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 22:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today Jennifer and Pumps are joined by the hilarious, actress and comedian Heather McMahan. Heather has had it with &amp;ldquo;limp dick&amp;rdquo; handshakes, Jennifer gets hoodwinked into being a good person on a recent flight to New York and Pumps drops some dirty details from a divorce drama.
Thank you to our sponsors:
Bright Cellars: For a limited time, listeners get $100 off their first six bottle box by going to Brightcellars.</description></item><item><title>Mommy's Going to Federal Prison | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680085/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 22:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Thursday, Listeners. Jennifer and Pumps kick off this episode with a hot take on a cold criminal. We then embark on the journey through your many &amp;lsquo;had its&amp;rsquo;. Our listeners had a lot to get off their chests - from the friends that always reject your invitation only to then get mad if you stop inviting them to the blanketed baby photoshoots for every single month milestone on instagram.</description></item><item><title>Queer Eye for All Y'all with Bobby Berk | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680086/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 22:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are feeling like hot sh*t because our guest this week is a really big deal. Design expert and Emmy-nominated host of Netflix&amp;rsquo;s Queer Eye, Bobby Berk, joins the girls. The three discuss everything from getting the cops called on you in a road rage incident to what it was like growing up gay in a highly religious environment. Pre-order Bobbys upcoming book &amp;lsquo;Right at Home: How Good Design is Good for the Mind&amp;rsquo; at bobbyberk.</description></item><item><title>Beacons of Mental Health | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680087/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 22:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we have a very special episode, diving into the many mental health issues from which Jennifer and Pumps suffer. We are joined by acclaimed psychotherapist and author Terri Cole, who has no problem laying down a diagnoses on the two psychopaths we call our hosts. From committing full-on therapist assault to being the cover models for co-dependency, Jennifer and Pumps bare all.
Thank you to our sponsors:</description></item><item><title>You Can't Babysit Your Own Kids | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680088/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 22:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps go down the rabbit hole of Boomer Facebook, reading all the hilarious and highly unsuccessful attempts the generation makes at using the platform. The girls also listen to your submissions, which leave Jessica and Pumps tearing up in laughter. Thank you to our sponsors:
Jenni Kayne:
Find your forever pieces @jennikayne and get 15% off with promo code HADIT at jennikayne.com! #jennikaynepartner
Hint Water:
Visit hintwater.</description></item><item><title>I Hope You Get a Flat Tire and Don’t Have Triple A | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680089/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 22:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680089/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s our favorite time of the week, Listener, because Jennifer and Pumps get to sit down and hear what you all have had it with. From the hot-shot grandstander that tries to slip in during heavy traffic to the extreme judgment from others when you don&amp;rsquo;t want to &amp;ldquo;donate a dollar&amp;rdquo; at the Walgreens check-out counter. Want to be featured on the show? Send us a voice memo on Instagram telling us what you&amp;rsquo;ve &amp;ldquo;had it&amp;rdquo; with.</description></item><item><title>Homeschool Energy with Jared Freid | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680090/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 22:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are joined today by the hilarious comedian and podcast host, Jared Freid. In light of his upcoming European tour, Jennifer gives Jared the rundown of all the things Europeans can&amp;rsquo;t stand about Americans. Jared shares stories of his mother, who he affectionately refers to as the Navy Seal of Body Shaming and the three play a very eye-opening game of Marry, F*ck, Kill.
Thank you to our sponsors:</description></item><item><title>Hate Thy Neighbor | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680091/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever had a neighbor leave a two page long, single-spaced manifesto taped to your door? Pumps has. Jennifer and Pumps dive into your listener submissions and take turns swapping next-door neighbor horror stories. The two also get into it over an &amp;ldquo;alleged&amp;rdquo; lack of punctuality.
Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast
Follow Us:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast: @Ivehaditpodcast
Jennifer Welch: @mizzwelch
Angie &amp;ldquo;Pumps&amp;rdquo; Sullivan: @pumpspumpspumps
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sad Fishing with Heather McDonald | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680092/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are joined by special guest and host of Juicy Scoop, Heather McDonald. The three discuss sadfishing, pageant queens and Heathers recent return from the dead. Jennifer also tells a titillating tale of one married mans attempt to whisk her away on a crazy train ride..
Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast
Follow Us:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast: @Ivehaditpodcast
Jennifer Welch: @mizzwelch
Angie &amp;ldquo;Pumps&amp;rdquo; Sullivan: @pumpspumpspumps
Special Guest: Heather McDonald: @heathermcdonald Check out: @JuicyScoop Transcript</description></item><item><title>Attention Sneezing Personality Disorder | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680093/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680093/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s Jennifer and Pumps&amp;rsquo; favorite day of the week, where they get to listen to all of your petty grievances. Jennifer delivers a powerful manifesto defending the rights of canines everywhere and one submission about &amp;ldquo;c*nty capitalism&amp;rdquo; has both Jen and Pumps absolutely losing it.
Thank you to our sponsors:
BetterHelp:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It is brought to you by BetterHelp, visit Betterhelp.com/hadit today to get 10% off your first month.</description></item><item><title>A Highly Strange Episode with Payne Lindsey | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680094/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are joined in studio with prolific podcaster and host of High Strange, Payne Lindsey. The three discuss all things extra-terresterial and answer the hard hitting questions like &amp;ldquo;Are UFOs real?&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Would you hook up with an alien if they were hot?&amp;rdquo; Spoiler alert: The answer to both is YES. Thank you to our sponsors:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It is brought to you by BetterHelp, visit Betterhelp.</description></item><item><title>Are Gender Reveals Attempted Murder? | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680095/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps finally unleash one of their biggest &amp;ldquo;Had It&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rdquo; with the help of comedian Robyn Schall - the annoying and honestly quite dangerous Gender Reveal Party. The girls discuss all of the ridiculous fuckery that couples have caused the past few years with this mediocre celebration and the trail of damage that follows it. Robyn also tells a wild first date story that almost ended in murder&amp;hellip;.</description></item><item><title>Karens Gone Wild | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680096/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are joined by TikTok stars (and hosts of the new podcast &amp;ldquo;The Social Dose&amp;rdquo;) Paris Nicholson and Michael Judson Berry to talk about what the hell is going on on the internet - or as Jennifer calls it: &amp;rsquo;the World Wide Web.&amp;rsquo; Kiley defends her hashtag usage and also reads the girls some of the hilarious hate comments they&amp;rsquo;ve received online. The duo also cannot get enough of all the ass play pumps has been getting in the U.</description></item><item><title>That's Some Jeffrey Dahmer Shit | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680097/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps get to hear what you all have absolutely HAD IT with. From rejecting modern medicine by popping out babies in the bathtub to getting dicked over in a drive thru pay-it-forward train, the girls couldn&amp;rsquo;t agree more. Kiley also poses a question that sends Jen and Pumps into a conversation on modern day cannibalism&amp;hellip;.
Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast
Follow Us:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast: @Ivehaditpodcast</description></item><item><title>I’m Content with My Content with Alex Bennett | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680098/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps take the low road when reunited with Alex Bennett, host of the Mean Girl pod. The three reminisce about when Alex worked for Jennifer and all the shenanigans that ensued. Pumps excitedly labels Jennifer the &amp;ldquo;Worlds Oldest Bridesmaid&amp;rdquo; and Alex opens up about some drama going on over at Barstool. Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast
Follow Us:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast: @Ivehaditpodcast
Jennifer Welch: @mizzwelch</description></item><item><title>Are We the Yak Mouths? | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680099/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps sit down to listen to what you all have had it with and get a surprise submission from one of their own children. The girls cover everything from the long manifesto&amp;rsquo;s you find before every recipe to unwanted guests inviting themselves to your party. Every single grievance on this episode came down to one universal issue: Yak Mouths.
Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast
Follow Us:</description></item><item><title>What Doesn’t Kill You Makes You Trailer Trash with Adam Rippon | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680100/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are joined by olympic figure skater and the self-proclaimed American sweetheart, Adam Rippon. The three talk about how Tanya Harding had absolutely HAD IT with Nancy Kerrigan, Adam&amp;rsquo;s run-in with the boogeyman and how Pumps believes she has to get bangs at age sixty. Jennifer expresses her deep distain for inspirational quotes and the whole gang plays a hilarious round of &amp;ldquo;Had It or Hit It?</description></item><item><title>Boom, There’s My Ex-Wife | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680101/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680101/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s an extra special Thursday because Jennifer and Pumps are joined in-studio by luxury rug designer and personal friend, Kyle Bunting. Kyle dives into the post-divorce dating world, running into exes on Bumble and the phenomenon of the dine-and-dash dater. Jennifer continues to brow-beat Stanley Cup abuse and Pumps has HAD IT with personal space invaders. Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast
Follow Us:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast: @Ivehaditpodcast</description></item><item><title>Little Dick David | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680102/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680102/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week&amp;rsquo;s extra special episode, Jennifer and Pumps tell Florida to leave the Statue of David and his micro-penis alone. They also listen to some &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It&amp;rdquo; submissions from our followers and discuss a very titillating dream from our hottest host. This episode is so good, you will literally die.
Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast
Follow Us:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast: @Ivehaditpodcast
Jennifer Welch: @mizzwelch
Angie &amp;ldquo;Pumps&amp;rdquo; Sullivan: @pumpspumpspumps</description></item><item><title>You’re Not a #GirlBoss | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680103/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps let the listeners in on their weekly therapy sessions, airing out the many grievances. From angry adult women attempting to recruit you into their multi-level marketing scheme to the overzealous grocery store clerk. However, the real highlight of the episode goes to the brave listener that declared they&amp;rsquo;ve &amp;lsquo;had it&amp;rsquo; with one of our beloved hosts&amp;hellip;..
Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast
Follow Us: I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast: @Ivehaditpodcast</description></item><item><title>Dark Side of the Spoon with Jackie Schimmel | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680104/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are joined by self-proclaimed professional asshole and host of The Bitch Bible, Jackie Schimmel. The girls swap pregnancy horror stories and DIY self-grooming mishaps. Schimmel gets the inside scoop on how to handle a very shitty post-pregnancy problem and Jennifer gets called out for her accessory of choice - the Apple Watch. Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast
Follow Us:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast: @Ivehaditpodcast
Jennifer Welch: @mizzwelch</description></item><item><title>Low and Loose | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680105/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps take on more listener submissions, ranging from insane wedding registry requests to almost throat-punching a person that won&amp;rsquo;t let you escape a conversation. Jennifer also leads an on-air Kegel exercise class for all to partake in - free of charge. Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast
Follow Us:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast: @Ivehaditpodcast
Jennifer Welch: @mizzwelch
Angie &amp;ldquo;Pumps&amp;rdquo; Sullivan: @pumpspumpspumps
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Unhappy Occasions and Happy-Endings | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680106/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are joined by comedienne Kristin Key. The three discuss everything that is wrong with baby showers, baby sprinkles and the wretched Mammogram. The girls relive the time Pumps got Jennifer pregnant using Josh as a sperm donor and the not-so-happy-ending massage experience in Mexico. Kristin closes the show out performing an original song about one very NASTY grandma&amp;hellip;
Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast
Follow Us:</description></item><item><title>We Manifested This Episode | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps play new listener submissions and according to Jen we may have found the &amp;ldquo;creme de la creme&amp;rdquo; of all had it&amp;rsquo;s. From manifesting to mini-vans, this episode will take you on quite the journey
Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast
Follow Us:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast: @Ivehaditpodcast
Jennifer Welch: @mizzwelch
Angie &amp;ldquo;Pumps&amp;rdquo; Sullivan: @pumpspumpspumps
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mediocrity is Trending with Amanda Hirsch | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680014/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are joined by Amanda Hirsch, host of Not Skinny But Not Fat @notskinnybutnotfat. Amanda teaches the girls about the influencer phenomenon that is GRWM&amp;rsquo;s. Don&amp;rsquo;t know what that stands for? Neither does Pumps. The three also express their downright hatred of the snail mail Christmas card tradition. PSA: Nobody cares about your matching pajama family photoshoot, all it does it take up space in our trashcans.</description></item><item><title>The Josh Welch Shotgun Method | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are joined by the highly-requested and self-proclaimed stunner, Josh Welch. The three dig into the unnecessary and excruciating social interactions we all deal with every day. The solution to avoiding these? The Josh Welch Shotgun Method.
Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast Follow Us:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast: @Ivehaditpodcast
Jennifer Welch: @mizzwelch
Angie &amp;ldquo;Pumps&amp;rdquo; Sullivan: @pumpspumpspumps
Special Guest:
Josh Welch: @joshwelch_
Transcript</description></item><item><title>You’ve Got to Be Culting Me with Sarah Edmondson | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are joined by Sarah Edmondson, former member-turned-whistleblower of NXIVM, featured on HBO&amp;rsquo;s The Vow and the co-host of A Little Bit Culty. It&amp;rsquo;s decided that Pumps is the ideal candidate for cult recruitment and Jennifer may or may not already be in one. Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast
Follow Us:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast: @Ivehaditpodcast Jennifer Welch: @mizzwelch
Angie &amp;ldquo;Pumps&amp;rdquo; Sullivan: @pumpspumpspumps
Special Guest:
Sarah Edmondson: @sarahedmondson</description></item><item><title>Ninja Lesbians | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps sit down to hear about all the things you&amp;rsquo;ve had it with and they were NOT disappointed. Pumps dives into her inability to correctly handle a simple stop-sign situation and Jennifer admits she&amp;rsquo;s guilty of being a fitness influencer. Send us a voice memo on Instagram with what you&amp;rsquo;ve had it with for a chance to be featured on upcoming bonus episodes! Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Public Displays of Assholery with Heather Dubrow | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680018/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever accidentally attended a swingers dinner party? Pumps has. On this episode Jennifer and Pumps are joined by RHOC star and Podcast host, Heather Dubrow. They discuss what makes a horrible party guest and how to avoid being one yourself. Also, if you&amp;rsquo;re reading this: Please stop inviting Jennifer to parties, there&amp;rsquo;s nothing less she would rather do.
Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast
Follow Us:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast: @Ivehaditpodcast</description></item><item><title>The Slobification of America | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps have had it with most things, but your listener submissions aren&amp;rsquo;t one of them. From your love/hate relationship with old people and their cellphones to cyclists in spandex hogging the roads. Pumps drops a hot dating tip on how to pick up men - binoculars required. Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast
Follow Us:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast: @Ivehaditpodcast
Jennifer Welch: @mizzwelch
Angie &amp;ldquo;Pumps&amp;rdquo; Sullivan: @pumpspumpspumps</description></item><item><title>Self-Yelp Seminar | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680020/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps are joined by Christine &amp;amp; Xandy Shiefer, the hosts of Beach Too Sandy, Water Too Wet. They dive deep into the world of Yelp and it&amp;rsquo;s many horrendous and hilarious reviews. Jennifer also teaches Pumps a thing or two about what really goes on inside a strip club. Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast
Follow Us:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast: @Ivehaditpodcast
Jennifer Welch: @mizzwelch
Angie &amp;ldquo;Pumps&amp;rdquo; Sullivan: @pumpspumpspumps</description></item><item><title>Stick Figure Families | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680021/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps dive into what you all have had it with, ranging from the insane way people spell their children&amp;rsquo;s names to the stupid bumper stickers we are all subjected to each and every day. Jennifer also outs Josh Welch as a psycho-sports parent, who may or may not deserve to have his ass kicked. Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast
Follow Us:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast: @Ivehaditpodcast</description></item><item><title>Private Eyes, Public Places | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680022/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps welcome Private Investigators Bari Kroll and Jen Rosant, who impart advice on what to do when you see a red flag in your spouse. Meanwhile, Jennifer has had it with Pharmaceutical commercials.
Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast
Follow Us:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast: @Ivehaditpodcast
Jennifer Welch: @mizzwelch
Angie &amp;ldquo;Pumps&amp;rdquo; Sullivan: @pumpspumpspumps
Special Guest: @blaureninvestigations &amp;amp; @jenrene_rosant
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Stupid People, Stupid Questions | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps listen to your &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rdquo; ranging from pharmacist woes to the annoying acronyms we have to Google every single day. Jennifer also tells us about an unforgettable trip to the gynecologist with Pumps. IYKYK. Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast
Follow Us:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast: @Ivehaditpodcast
Jennifer Welch: @mizzwelch
Angie &amp;ldquo;Pumps&amp;rdquo; Sullivan: @pumpspumpspumps
Transcript</description></item><item><title>BJ’s for PJ’s with Ashley Longshore | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680024/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer, Pumps and renowned artist Ashley Longshore try to connect the dots between self-diagnosed food allergies and not being able to shut up about it. Also, what would you endure to be able to have your own Gulfstream? Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast
Follow Us:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast: @Ivehaditpodcast
Jennifer Welch: @mizzwelch
Angie &amp;ldquo;Pumps&amp;rdquo; Sullivan: @pumpspumpspumps
Special Guest: @ashleylongshoreart
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Time to Wean off the Tit | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680025/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps listen to your I&amp;rsquo;ve Had Its. From stupid Facebook comments and breastfeeding eight-year-olds to how best to handle the ex-husband&amp;rsquo;s new wife - they&amp;rsquo;ve had it with all of it. Pumps also drops a bomb on Jennifer after 20 years of friendship. Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast
Follow Us:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast: @Ivehaditpodcast
Jennifer Welch: @mizzwelch
Angie &amp;ldquo;Pumps&amp;rdquo; Sullivan: @pumpspumpspumps
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Purity Culture Club | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680026/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer, Pumps and special guest Kate Casey take a deep dive into the abstinence movement, including purity rings and born-again virginity. Meanwhile, Jennifer is offended by the terrible architecture of mega churches.
Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast
Follow Us:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast: @Ivehaditpodcast
Jennifer Welch: @mizzwelch
Angie &amp;ldquo;Pumps&amp;rdquo; Sullivan: @pumpspumpspumps
Special Guest: @katecaseyca
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Male Vanity and Green Text Bubbles | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680027/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pumps has had it with Jennifer&amp;rsquo;s psycho-dialing and Josh Welch stops by the studio to discuss sea salt spray, eye serum and frankly, how he&amp;rsquo;s never looked better. Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast
Follow Us:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast: @Ivehaditpodcast
Jennifer Welch: @mizzwelch
Angie &amp;ldquo;Pumps&amp;rdquo; Sullivan: @pumpspumpspumps
Special Guest:
Josh Welch: @joshwelch_
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Weather Woodies and Rain Curtains | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680028/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 19:30:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps welcome Jake and Matt from the Reality Gays podcast and they&amp;rsquo;ve HAD IT with getting duped by weather forecasters. Pumps also begs the question: is there no limit to Jennifer&amp;rsquo;s controlling nature? Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast
Follow Us:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast: @Ivehaditpodcast
Jennifer Welch: @mizzwelch
Angie &amp;ldquo;Pumps&amp;rdquo; Sullivan: @pumpspumpspumps
Special Guest:
@realitygayspodcast
@themattmarr
@jakeitorfakeit
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Brunch is a Drag | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680029/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Special guest Mara Davis joins the ladies to take a swing at Sunday Funday and Jennifer has a beef with Pump&amp;rsquo;s phone etiquette.
Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast
Follow Us:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast: @Ivehaditpodcast
Jennifer Welch: @mizzwelch
Angie &amp;ldquo;Pumps&amp;rdquo; Sullivan: @pumpspumpspump
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Freeballin’ | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680030/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pumps and Jennifer recap the year with a laundry list of things they&amp;rsquo;ve had it with. Producer Nilly phones-in a friend who is a super-griper of the utmost kind. Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast
Follow Us:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast: @Ivehaditpodcast
Jennifer Welch: @mizzwelch
Angie &amp;ldquo;Pumps&amp;rdquo; Sullivan: @pumpspumpspumps
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Back to Burning Man | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680031/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer and Pumps drag out the dead horse to beat the Burning Man out of it. Some familiar faces return to give a recap of Black Rock City 2022. Meanwhile, Pumps gets swindled by Instagram ads. Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast Follow Us:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast: @Ivehaditpodcast
Jennifer Welch: @mizzwelch
Angie &amp;ldquo;Pumps&amp;rdquo; Sullivan: @pumpspumpspump
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Pickleball Cult | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680032/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer is deep in the Pickleball Cult and Pumps is worried that Jennifer&amp;rsquo;s next step is drinking the Kool-Aid. Additionally, the ladies have had it with gated community and online security. Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast
Follow Us:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast: @Ivehaditpodcast
Jennifer Welch: @mizzwelch
Angie &amp;ldquo;Pumps&amp;rdquo; Sullivan: @pumpspumpspump
Special Guest:
clubleftisttennis.substack.com
clubleftisttennis.bigcartel.com
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bad Travelers | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680033/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 06:27:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer, Pumps and guest Becca Tobin take on everything from airport attire, personal pillows on planes and those who clap upon landing. Also, Jennifer dissects why the adults she loves the most all have digestive issues. Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast Follow Us:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast: @Ivehaditpodcast
Jennifer Welch: @mizzwelch
Angie &amp;ldquo;Pumps&amp;rdquo; Sullivan: @pumpspumpspump
Check out @theladygang
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Men Who Skirt the System | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680034/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Viagra and big bank accounts allow undesirable men to reel in 25 year olds, Pumps turns out to be quite the case cracker and Jennifer has a reason for wearing all black. Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast
Follow Us:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast: @Ivehaditpodcast
Jennifer Welch: @mizzwelch
Angie &amp;ldquo;Pumps&amp;rdquo; Sullivan: @pumpspumpspump
Special Thank to Director, Cinematographer &amp;amp; Photographer Jonathon Narducci - www.jnarducci.com
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Armpits, Feet and Butt Play | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680035/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680035/</guid><description>Podcast Description The ladies welcome bare knuckle boxer, drag queen, and artist Diego Garijo. Jennifer is crying over spilled breast milk and Pumps is floored by a revelation from their sound engineer. Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast
Follow Us:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast: @Ivehaditpodcast
Jennifer Welch: @mizzwelch
Angie &amp;ldquo;Pumps&amp;rdquo; Sullivan: @pumpspumpspumps
Special Guest:
Diego Garijo - @Diegogarijo
Photography of Diego by @lunaferoxphotography
Transcript</description></item><item><title>You’re Not a Pisces, You’re a Schmuck | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680036/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yack mouths ruined a historic tennis match for Jennifer while Pumps recalls a 25-old tarot card warning she should have heeded. Sounds like Mercury was in retrograde. Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast
Follow Us:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast: @Ivehaditpodcast
Jennifer Welch: @mizzwelch
Angie &amp;ldquo;Pumps&amp;rdquo; Sullivan: @pumpspumpspumps
Special Guest: Kate Wolff - @thekatewolff
Transcript</description></item><item><title>National Everything Day | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680037/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer gets blindsided by &amp;ldquo;National Sons Day&amp;rdquo; and finds herself scrambling to post glowing reviews about her boys on social media. Pumps doesn&amp;rsquo;t post at all because she&amp;rsquo;s fuming about being hijacked by yack mouth gas station attendants.
Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast
Follow Us:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast: @Ivehaditpodcast
Jennifer Welch: @mizzwelch
Angie &amp;ldquo;Pumps&amp;rdquo; Sullivan: @pumpspumpspumps
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Burning Man | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680107/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680107/</guid><description>Podcast Description What&amp;rsquo;s worse? Hot yoga or a hot week in the desert at Burning Man? As if Jennifer isn&amp;rsquo;t appalled enough, the reality of cuddle puddles and peeing in a bucket sends her through the roof. Pumps, however, stays grounded so she can flirt with this week&amp;rsquo;s guest. Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast Follow Us:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast: @Ivehaditpodcast
Jennifer Welch: @mizzwelch
Angie &amp;ldquo;Pumps&amp;rdquo; Sullivan: @pumpspumpspumps
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Toddlers are Assholes | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680108/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Toddlers are assholes&amp;hellip;what&amp;rsquo;s wrong with saying it? Jennifer and Pumps are gonna say it after they get to the bottom of which fruit is the universal sign for swingers. Subscribe to our Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IveHadItPodcast Follow Us:
I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It Podcast: @Ivehaditpodcast
Jennifer Welch: @mizzwelch
Angie &amp;ldquo;Pumps&amp;rdquo; Sullivan: @pumpspumpspumps
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jennifer Welch and Angie ”Pumps” Sullivan | I've Had It</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2571680109/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 05:55:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2571680109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over the past two decades, former television personalities Jennifer Welch and Angie &amp;ldquo;Pumps&amp;rdquo; Sullivan have been amassing a list of things they&amp;rsquo;ve HAD IT with and it&amp;rsquo;s a hilarious slant on power moms, over-talkers, men who skirt the system and people who blame bad behavior on their astrological signs. Join the ladies and their special guests on &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It&amp;rdquo; and let this comedic, feel-good podcast expose you to all the things you didn&amp;rsquo;t know you&amp;rsquo;ve had it with!</description></item></channel></rss>