<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Dan Carlin&#39;s Hardcore History: Addendum on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/categories/dan-carlins-hardcore-history-addendum/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Dan Carlin&#39;s Hardcore History: Addendum on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 16:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/categories/dan-carlins-hardcore-history-addendum/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Dan Carlin&#39;s Hardcore History: Addendum - EP25 The Long View</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307900025/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307900025/</guid>
        <description>It&amp;rsquo;s Hardcore History.
Attention.
I hear from many of you that say,
just turn on the microphone and talk,
and it&amp;rsquo;ll be a good show, and we&amp;rsquo;ll be glad to get it.
So today will perhaps be a test of this theory&amp;rsquo;s validity.
What&amp;rsquo;s held up today&amp;rsquo;s show for a while now
is probably some old training in the news business
that doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist anymore.
Um, where, as a youngster learning the ropes,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Dan Carlin&#39;s Hardcore History: Addendum - Manifesting the Muse with Rick</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307900024/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307900024/</guid>
        <description>It&amp;rsquo;s Hardcore History.
Attention.
I have always loved the quote from Mozart, and I think it&amp;rsquo;s abbreviated.
I think it&amp;rsquo;s a couple of different sentences cut out, but the quote as put together is
wonderful and it&amp;rsquo;s symbolic of something we&amp;rsquo;re going to talk about today.
And the quote is, when I am completely myself, entirely alone, or during the night when I
cannot sleep, it is on such occasions that my ideas flow best and most abundantly.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Dan Carlin&#39;s Hardcore History: Addendum - Boxing with Ghosts</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307900023/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307900023/</guid>
        <description>♪♪
It&amp;rsquo;s Hardcore History Addendum.
♪♪
I have threatened for a long time
to introduce a bunch of sort of niche subjects
into the Hardcore History Addendum feed.
That&amp;rsquo;s why we established this alternative,
uh, feed to begin with, right?
So instead of having to have a show that could,
you know, hold one&amp;rsquo;s attention for four or five hours
or multi-parts in a series,
something we could just do as a throwaway&amp;hellip;</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Dan Carlin&#39;s Hardcore History: Addendum - The Fabulous Bill Barrett</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307900022/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307900022/</guid>
        <description>And now, the show with the most handsome voice talent
working today, It&amp;rsquo;s Common Sense with Bill Barrett,
hosted by that Dan Carlin guy.
That voice that you heard just there in the introduction
as he said himself, was Bill Barrett.
The number one choice that I would have had
if somebody had said to me in 2005,
when we started podcasting, that you could have any&amp;hellip;
sort of big voice announcer in the entire world,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Dan Carlin&#39;s Hardcore History: Addendum - Hollandansandbrook</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307900021/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307900021/</guid>
        <description>♪♪
It&amp;rsquo;s Hardcore History.
ATTENTION.
♪♪
So, the conversation that you&amp;rsquo;re about to listen to
was done through a format that I ripped off
from the people that we&amp;rsquo;re talking with,
because I was on their podcast not that long ago,
and I remember thinking that the way
that they put it together structurally
was fantastic for three people,
because when you have three people in a conversation,
it can get unwieldy sometimes.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Dan Carlin&#39;s Hardcore History: Addendum - A Republic Lost at Sea</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307900020/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307900020/</guid>
        <description>It&amp;rsquo;s Hardcore History.
Attention.
So, like most of you, I have my historical pet peeves.
And one of them is when sort of the lightweight media program here or there, I&amp;rsquo;ll be listening
and they will confuse the Roman Empire and the Roman Republic.
They mean the Roman Republic, but they say the Roman Empire, right?
So it&amp;rsquo;s the fall of the Roman Empire or whatever.
So, you know, that gets under my skin in a way that is totally out of proportion to the</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Dan Carlin&#39;s Hardcore History: Addendum - Asymmetrical Perspectives</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307900019/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307900019/</guid>
        <description>♪♪
It&amp;rsquo;s Hardcore History.
Attention.
♪♪
So, the origin story for the conversation
you&amp;rsquo;re about to hear is that I was on a panel
with the upcoming guest,
and as we were departing the panel,
he leans in and whispers in my ear,
we should talk about asymmetrical warfare
sometime on your show.
And as many of you know, I&amp;rsquo;m a sucker
for romantic talk like that.
So, we set it up, and we had the conversation,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Dan Carlin&#39;s Hardcore History: Addendum - Iranian Interconnections</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307900018/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307900018/</guid>
        <description>♪♪
It&amp;rsquo;s Hardcore History.
Attentum.
♪♪
The guest we&amp;rsquo;re gonna have on today
is talking about a subject that is near and dear to my heart.
I first fell in love with what I would&amp;rsquo;ve called
Persian civilization as a teenager,
um, by studying ancient history.
And the Persians are in one of their&amp;hellip;
You know, perhaps their greatest period,
it depends on how you define greatest,
but perhaps the greatest period in their history.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Dan Carlin&#39;s Hardcore History: Addendum - Engineering Victory with Elon</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307900017/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307900017/</guid>
        <description>It&amp;rsquo;s Hardcore History.
Attention.
So my apologies if today&amp;rsquo;s show sounds a little like you&amp;rsquo;re joining a conversation that&amp;rsquo;s
already in progress, but this has happened with me before where I&amp;rsquo;ll be talking with
someone about something, usually over a long period of time, messaging back and forth or
whatever it might be, and I&amp;rsquo;ll think to myself, usually a little too late in the game, wow,
you know, should have thought about making this a podcast.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Dan Carlin&#39;s Hardcore History: Addendum - Powers Thrones and Dan Jones</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307900016/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307900016/</guid>
        <description>♪♪
It&amp;rsquo;s Hardcore History.
Attention.
♪♪
So, I am a Dan Jones fan,
and many of you are, too, no doubt.
He&amp;rsquo;s one of our finest writers of history
for the period in the Middle Ages,
you know, the fall of Rome to the Renaissance.
A lot of stuff that made up
what a lot of us grew up with loving.
I mean, if you had&amp;hellip;
Knights in shining armor, Crusades, Norman Saxons,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Dan Carlin&#39;s Hardcore History: Addendum - The Supernova Coda</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307900015/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307900015/</guid>
        <description>It&amp;rsquo;s Hardcore History.
ATTENTION.
There&amp;rsquo;s an interesting sort of phenomenon,
I guess you could call it, that happens after we get
a Hardcore History series finished.
You begin to hear from people that are connected
with the subject matter, and you get opportunities,
for example, to talk to them or to interview them.
And the upside is, um&amp;hellip;
they&amp;rsquo;re usually people that you would really like to talk to.
The downside is, you&amp;rsquo;ve just finished up, usually,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Dan Carlin&#39;s Hardcore History: Addendum - The Game of War</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307900014/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307900014/</guid>
        <description>It&amp;rsquo;s Hardcore History.
Attention.
I imagine given the subject matter
that I talk about on this program,
that there are quite a few people in the audience
that have played strategy and tactic wargaming type, um,
games on their computer or video console
or what have you over the years.
If that&amp;rsquo;s a subject that interests you,
gonna have an interview on this program
where we talk to one of the founders of a company</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Dan Carlin&#39;s Hardcore History: Addendum - Gladwell and the Bomber Mafia</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307900013/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307900013/</guid>
        <description>It&amp;rsquo;s Hardcore History Addendum.
Well, it is way past time, isn&amp;rsquo;t it? For just about any content from us. Hardcore History
Addendum shows long overdue. I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on tying up the loose ends that develop over
a six-part multi-year long, is that even right, series on the Second World War. So, sorry
patience required on that front, but when we wrap that up, we&amp;rsquo;ll be done with the Second</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Dan Carlin&#39;s Hardcore History: Addendum - Wolf Pack Hunting with Hanks</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307900012/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307900012/</guid>
        <description>It&amp;rsquo;s Hardcore History Addendum.
We told you when we first unveiled the Hardcore History Addendum feed that this was going
to be the everything else feed.
Anything that didn&amp;rsquo;t belong in the main Hardcore History feed for one reason or another will
end up here.
We knew there would be interview shows because compared to what we normally do, the big Hardcore
History shows, interview shows are simple, so we knew that there&amp;rsquo;d be quite a few of</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Dan Carlin&#39;s Hardcore History: Addendum - Toronto Redux</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307900011/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307900011/</guid>
        <description>It&amp;rsquo;s Hardcore History, Attention!
So last October 2019, right around Halloween, I was in Toronto to do a promotional event
for The End is Always Near, the book I got out last year.
And I went to the theater and I met the guy who was going to be the interviewer, it was
a Q&amp;amp;A set up, which works really well in these kinds of environments.
And I sat down and just had the best time for a little while before the actual event,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Dan Carlin&#39;s Hardcore History: Addendum - Strangelove Whisperings</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307900010/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307900010/</guid>
        <description>Today&amp;rsquo;s show is sponsored by the multi-academy award-winning first world war themed film
1917 which is available to own starting March 10th on digital streaming and on March 24th on 4k ultra HD and blu-ray
More on what&amp;rsquo;s available then at the end of our upcoming interview with Fred Kaplan
It&amp;rsquo;s hardcore history
You may not be interested in war the war is interested in you
That is a wonderful quote by</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Dan Carlin&#39;s Hardcore History: Addendum - Glimpses of Olympias</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307900009/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307900009/</guid>
        <description>It&amp;rsquo;s Hardcore History.
Attentum.
I keep reading in all of the entertainment stories how desperate the entertainment industry
is for new ideas and new concepts and subject matter and all this stuff and I read one the
other day that says this is the reason why you keep seeing like Teenage Mutant Ninja
Turtles 47 and every cartoon you grew up with as a kid made into a live action movie.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Dan Carlin&#39;s Hardcore History: Addendum - Caesar at Hastings</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307900008/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307900008/</guid>
        <description>It&amp;rsquo;s Hardcore History, Addendum.
So we&amp;rsquo;re finally getting enough of these Hardcore History Addendum shows out
so that a little bit of the pattern, I think,
is starting to establish itself in terms of what it was going to be,
because we said at the outset I was hoping to use it
as a subsidiary feed for things that just didn&amp;rsquo;t really fit
into the big Hardcore History experience, should we say.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Dan Carlin&#39;s Hardcore History: Addendum - Hardcore History on Fire</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307900007/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307900007/</guid>
        <description>It&amp;rsquo;s Hardcore History Addendum.
So, in this Hardcore History Addendum,
we&amp;rsquo;re going to have a friend of mine on the program,
and it&amp;rsquo;s gonna be kind of a cross-cast
between his show and mine.
And I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll pardon me, I have a cold right now,
so things are a little&amp;hellip;
-&amp;hellip;less than perfect. Um, his name is Daniele Bolelli,
by the way, and you may know him
because he&amp;rsquo;s a famous history podcaster.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Dan Carlin&#39;s Hardcore History: Addendum - On The Vietnam War with Sir Max</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307900006/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307900006/</guid>
        <description>♪♪
It&amp;rsquo;s Hardcore History.
Attention.
♪♪
I&amp;rsquo;ve always said some of the best things
we do around here are apologies.
And so, I want to apologize if it seems as though
our subject matter and, um,
and the stuff we&amp;rsquo;re talking about lately
all kind of falls into a narrow sort of,
uh, subject matter or a, you know, historical period.
It&amp;rsquo;s mostly been 20th century stuff.
It&amp;rsquo;s not by design, but I don&amp;rsquo;t work by design.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Dan Carlin&#39;s Hardcore History: Addendum - Nightmares of Indianapolis</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307900005/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307900005/</guid>
        <description>Today&amp;rsquo;s show is sponsored by audible. Go to audible.com slash
Carlin that&amp;rsquo;s audible.com slash Carlin or text Carlin to 500500
to get started.
I&amp;rsquo;ve just heard the audio that you&amp;rsquo;re about to hear and this is
my own critique of the audio that you&amp;rsquo;re about to hear and
it&amp;rsquo;s a little redundant only because I actually start off the
program with a little bit of that sort of talk too. So I</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Dan Carlin&#39;s Hardcore History: Addendum - Exposing the Hart of The Great War</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307900004/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307900004/</guid>
        <description>Today&amp;rsquo;s show is sponsored by audible audible is offering our listeners a free audiobook with a 30-day trial membership
Just go to audible.com forward slash Carlin and browse the unmatched selection of audio programs
Download a title free and start listening. It&amp;rsquo;s that easy
Go to audible.com slash Carlin or text Carlin to 500-500 and get started today
It&amp;rsquo;s hardcore history
Attention
I&amp;rsquo;ve said before that one of the wonderful side benefits of a gig like this is the chance to speak to people whose work</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Dan Carlin&#39;s Hardcore History: Addendum - A Four-Star Conversation</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307900003/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307900003/</guid>
        <description>It&amp;rsquo;s Hardcore History Addendum.
When I was designing this Hardcore History Addendum format, I knew that we were going
to want to do interviews.
It&amp;rsquo;s a good way for us to get out content quickly that&amp;rsquo;s interesting and that it involves
other people, other voices, people that you might want to know more about.
And I knew that we would have authors on because there&amp;rsquo;s always a lot of good people writing</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Dan Carlin&#39;s Hardcore History: Addendum - Rome Through Duncan&#39;s Eyes</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307900002/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307900002/</guid>
        <description>It&amp;rsquo;s Hardcore History.
Attention.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been podcasting since like the Stone Age, 2005.
And way back then and for a long time afterwards, I kind of considered all the other people
who were podcasting as my colleagues.
We&amp;rsquo;re not really in the sort of industry where you say, yes, my colleagues, and we publish
papers or whatever the normal idea of what you might consider a colleague to be.
But it really felt the same, right?</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Dan Carlin&#39;s Hardcore History: Addendum - Imperial Germany vs Nazi Germany</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1307900001/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1307900001/</guid>
        <description>It&amp;rsquo;s Hardcore History.
Attentum.
Which military was superior?
The First World War military of the German Imperial State or the Second World War military
of Nazi Germany?
I know that sounds like a random question, but it&amp;rsquo;s actually something that I get asked
about all the time.
All the time.
It&amp;rsquo;s not so random either because these people are not just asking me that question out of
thin air.
They are asking me to elaborate on a statement that I once made, kind of a throwaway line</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
