<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Normal Gossip on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/normal-gossip/</link><description>Recent content in Normal Gossip on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/normal-gossip/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Getting Frisky at the Black Rose with Erika Casupanan | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Survivor 41 winner Erika Casupanan joins us this week for a story about the perils of gossiping at work.
Listen to Erika's podcast, Happy to See Me!
Sign up to hear Normal Gossip's next secret here.
Support Radiotopia's fall fundraiser!
You can support Normal Gossip directly by buying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.com.
Our merch shop is run by Dan McQuade. You can also find all kinds of info about us and how to submit gossip on our Komi page: https://normalgossip.</description></item><item><title>Dog Salon Divas with Hayes Brown | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hayes Brown joins us to learn just how deranged the world of upscale dog grooming can be.
Follow Hayes on Twitter @HayesBrown.
Sign up to hear Normal Gossip's next secret here.
Support Radiotopia's fall fundraiser!
You can support Normal Gossip directly by buying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.com.
Our merch shop is run by Dan McQuade. You can also find all kinds of info about us and how to submit gossip on our Komi page: https://normalgossip.</description></item><item><title>Rich Mom Razzle Dazzle with Maitreyi Anantharaman | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our Defector colleague Maitreyi Anantharaman joins us for a story about private school moms taking a theater performance — and "urban dance" classes — too seriously.
Follow Maitreyi on Twitter @maitreyiaa.
Support Radiotopia's fall fundraiser!
You can support Normal Gossip directly by buying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.com.
Our merch shop is run by Dan McQuade. You can also find all kinds of info about us and how to submit gossip on our Komi page: https://normalgossip.</description></item><item><title>Weedsgiving with Zakiya Gibbons | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260004/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, our pal Zakiya Gibbons joins us for a story about a Thanksgiving home rental gone horribly, horribly wrong.
Zakiya is the host and editor of Hang Up, a new reality dating podcast from Radiotopia! We are obsessed. Check it out!
Speaking of Radiotopia....support Radiotopia's fall fundraiser!
You can support Normal Gossip directly by buying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.com.
Our merch shop is run by Dan McQuade.</description></item><item><title>"Emily in Paris" Meets "Parasite" with Amanda Montell | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260005/</guid><description>Podcast Description We're going abroad for a long-awaited au pair adventure with writer and podcast host Amanda Montell!
Follow Amanda on Instagram @amanda_montell and make sure to pre-order her book, The Age of Magical Overthinking.
You can support Normal Gossip directly by buying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.com.
Our merch shop is run by Dan McQuade. You can also find all kinds of info about us and how to submit gossip on our Komi page: https://normalgossip.</description></item><item><title>Should've Said No to the Ceviche with Sarah-Violet Bliss | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260006/</guid><description>Podcast Description TV writer and showrunner Sarah-Violet Bliss joins us for an evening of moral quandaries and infinite amounts of ceviche.
You can support Normal Gossip directly by buying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.com.
Our merch shop is run by Dan McQuade. You can also find all kinds of info about us and how to submit gossip on our Komi page: https://normalgossip.komi.io/
Episode transcript here.</description></item><item><title>25 Bridesmaids and an Empath with Jasmine Ellis | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Jasmine Ellis joins us for a tale about an absurdly large bachelorette party involving sardines, adult jocks, and an empathetic queen.
Follow Jasmine on Instagram at @jasmineelliscomedy.
You can support Normal Gossip directly by buying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.com.
Our merch shop is run by Dan McQuade. You can also find all kinds of info about us and how to submit gossip on our Komi page: https://normalgossip.</description></item><item><title>Teenage Cop Camp with Josie Duffy Rice | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260008/</guid><description>Podcast Description What happens when you send a manic pixie dream girl to CSI summer camp? Journalist, writer, law school graduate, and podcast host Josie Duffy Rice joins us to find out 👀
Check out Josie's podcast: Unreformed: the Story of the Alabama Industrial School for Negro Children.
You can support Normal Gossip directly by buying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.com.
Our merch shop is run by Dan McQuade.</description></item><item><title>Vodka Sommelier Bullshit with Katie Barnes | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260009/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are BACK for our fifth season! Get ready for 10 episodes of drama, scandal, and pettiness. This week, sports journalist Katie Barnes joins us for a story that brings us back to our high school days.
Buy Katie's book, Fair Play: How Sports Shape the Gender Debates, and follow them on Twitter @katie_barnes3.
You can support Normal Gossip directly by buying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode: Sexy Hide-And-Seek at the Shakespeare Festival with Brydie Lee-Kennedy | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260010/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260010/</guid><description>Podcast Description We're releasing an episode from our secret feed vault to give you a taste of what you can get each month as a Friend or Friend-of-a-Friend subscriber. Our guest, Brydie Lee-Kennedy, is a Friend-level subscriber who joined Kelsey on the secret feed last November to tell a harrowing story about a game of sexy hide-and-seek gone wrong.
If you loved Brydie's story, make sure to check out her novel, Go Lightly!</description></item><item><title>Surprise! The Plant Story 🪴 | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260011/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy summer! We’re popping in with a little summer surprise: the recording from our December 2022 live show in Washington, D.C., with Brittany Luse! This is a different story than the one we’re telling on our tour this summer. If you want to get tickets to the tour, there are still seats available! You can support Normal Gossip directly by buying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.</description></item><item><title>Family Mealworms with Patrick Redford | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Friend of the show and fellow Defector comrade Patrick Redford is on the public feed for the first time! This week, we're talking about ~intentional living communities and their alternative sources of protein.
Follow Patrick on IG @patrickredford
PSA: This is the season four FINALE! We're going to take a quick break to tour around the country (see you there?!) and then we'll be back for season 5.</description></item><item><title>'Til Deb Do Us Part with Caroline Moss and Sally Tamarkin | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260013/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sally Tamarkin and Caroline Moss get extremely triggered in this episode about a chill bride and her blissfully oblivious wedding weekend.
PSA: This is the ninth of ten episodes this season! Get ready babes!!!!
Follow Sally on Twitter @sallyt and follow Caroline on IG @geethanksjustboughtitpod
You can support Normal Gossip directly by buying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.com. Our merch shop is run by Dan McQuade.</description></item><item><title>Murder Binders and Unthinkable Burgers with Mariah Smith | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mariah Smith joins us for a true crime adventure.
PSA: This is the EIGHTH of ten episodes this season!
Get your tickets to the Normal Gossip live tour here.
Follow Mariah on IG @mariahmariahmariah
You can support Normal Gossip directly by buying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.com. Our merch shop is run by Dan McQuade. You can also find all kinds of info about us and how to submit gossip on our Komi page: https://normalgossip.</description></item><item><title>The CHAIR SAGA with Hannah Giorgis | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260015/</guid><description>Podcast Description The esteemed Hannah Giorgis returns for a tale about what happens when your cousin is too rich for your own good.
Many of you will remember Hannah from our D.C. live shows last winter! Follow Hannah on IG @hannahgiorgis
PSA: This is the SEVENTH of ten episodes this season!
You can support Normal Gossip directly by buying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.com. Our merch shop is run by Dan McQuade.</description></item><item><title>Vigilante Renovation with Jasmine Guillory | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jasmine Guillory joins us for a tough lesson in bro friendships.
PSA: This is the sixth of ten episodes this season!
Get your tickets to the Normal Gossip live tour here.
Follow Jasmine on IG @jasminepics
You can support Normal Gossip directly by buying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.com. Our merch shop is run by Dan McQuade. You can also find all kinds of info about us and how to submit gossip on our Komi page: https://normalgossip.</description></item><item><title>Processing Our Michael Phelps Trauma with B.A. Parker | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260017/</guid><description>Podcast Description B.A. Parker takes a trip back in time to a community pool in the South that has some major logistical issues.
Parker is a freelance writer and the host of NPR's Code Switch podcast! Follow Parker on Twitter @aparkusfarce.
PSA: This is the FIFTH of ten episodes this season! We're halfway, baby!
Get your tickets to the Normal Gossip live tour here.
You can support Normal Gossip directly by buying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.</description></item><item><title>Is Mythology Just Gossip? With Liv Albert | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Liv Albert joins us to ponder the age-old question: follow your dreams, or follow the money?
Liv is the host of the podcast Let's Talk About Myths, Baby! and the author of the books Greek Mythology and Nectar of the Gods.
PSA: This is the fourth of ten episodes this season!
Get your tickets to the Normal Gossip live tour here.
Follow Liv on IG @livalbert.
You can support Normal Gossip directly by buying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.</description></item><item><title>I Love All Corgis with Dr. Eve L. Ewing | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260019/</guid><description>Podcast Description One of you monsters made Dr. Eve L. Ewing cry by sending us a curséd PowerPoint presentation from a dog Facebook group.
PSA: This is the third of ten episodes this season!
Get your tickets to the Normal Gossip live tour here.
Follow Eve on IG @eve.ewing. This is the New Yorker article we talked about by Rachel Aviv.
You can support Normal Gossip directly by buying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.</description></item><item><title>The Only Single Girl at Disney with Blythe Roberson | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Blythe Roberson joins us for a story about how wrong a group text can go at Disney World.
Blythe's new book America the Beautiful? is out next week!
This is the second of ten episodes this season, which will release every Wednesday for the next nine weeks!
Follow Blythe on IG @blythelikehappy.
Get your tickets to the Normal Gossip live tour here.
You can support Normal Gossip directly by buying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.</description></item><item><title>Every Peach is a Miracle with Samin Nosrat | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260021/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260021/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are back for season 4! Samin Nosrat (author of Salt Fat Acid Heat and host of Home Cooking) joins us for a tale about fruit, #vanlife, and forbidden love.
This is the first of ten episodes this season, which will release every Wednesday for the next nine weeks!
Follow Samin on IG @ciaosamin.
You can support Normal Gossip directly by buying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.</description></item><item><title>S3 Ep9: Big Business Announcement Episode (new partner and new season!!!) | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260022/</guid><description>Podcast Description We're back with some big announcements and answers to your questions, like: Where have you been?
Who is your new partner?
What does it mean that you have a new partner? What will change about the podcast?
Will you please have a live show in my city pleasseee?
WHEN ARE YOU COMING BACK
You can support Normal Gossip directly by buying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.</description></item><item><title>S3 Ep8: Steampunk-Ass Murder Mystery with Tuck Woodstock | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gender Reveal host and producer Tuck Woodstock joins us for an epic love story from another time .... the early aughts. Follow Tuck on Twitter @tuckwoodstock. Get your tickets to our live show in D.C. at Sixth &amp;amp; I here! You can support Normal Gossip directly bybuying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.com. Episode transcript here. Follow the show on Instagram @normalgossip, and if you have gossip, email us at normalgossip@defector.</description></item><item><title>S3 Ep7: The Science Behind Gossip with Eshin Jolly | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Eshin Jolly joins us this week to teach us about the science of gossiping!!! Eshin is a post-doctoral researcher in the Computational Social Affective Neuroscience Laboratory at Dartmouth College. Follow Eshin on Twitter @Eshjolly. You can support Normal Gossip directly bybuying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.com. Episode transcript here. Follow the show on Instagram @normalgossip, and if you have gossip, email us at normalgossip@defector.</description></item><item><title>S3 Ep6: In Defense of Children with Youngmi Mayer | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260025/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian and host of Feeling Asian and Hairy Butthole Youngmi Mayer joins us to get to the bottom of a decades-old crime haunting one family: WHO flushed the hot dog down the toilet? Follow Youngmi on Instagram @ymmayer. You can support Normal Gossip directly bybuying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.com. Episode transcript here. Follow the show on Instagram @normalgossip, and if you have gossip, email us at normalgossip@defector.</description></item><item><title>S3 Ep5: You Can't Fight with Heiress Tongue with Matt Bellassai | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260026/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian, writer, and host of Unhappy Hour Matt Bellassai joins us for sojourn into the messy world of queer kickball leagues! Follow Matt on Instagram @mattbellassai. You can support Normal Gossip directly bybuying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.com. Episode transcript here.
Follow the show on Instagram @normalgossip, and if you have gossip, email us at normalgossip@defector.com or leave us a voicemail at 26-79-GOSSIP. Normal Gossip is hosted by Kelsey McKinney (@mckinneykelsey) and produced by Alex Sujong Laughlin (@alexlaughs).</description></item><item><title>S3 Ep4: Christmas is Cancelled with Laurel Bristow | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260027/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260027/</guid><description>Podcast Description We're thrilled to welcome everyone’s favorite guide to infectious diseases, Laurel Bristow. She's the program director for Emory’s TB Research Advancement Center and she's the first Laurel to be on the show! Follow Laurel on Instagram @laurel__bristow. You can support Normal Gossip directly bybuying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.com. Episode transcript here.
Follow the show on Instagram @normalgossip, and if you have gossip, email us at normalgossip@defector.</description></item><item><title>S3 Ep3: Loud Cats and Thin Walls with Sabrina Imbler | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Defector staff writer and creature correspondent Sabrina Imbler joins us for a story about the lives we lead on the other sides of extremely thin apartment walls. Follow Sabrina on Twitter @aznfusion and pre-order their book, How Far the Light Reaches! You can support Normal Gossip directly bybuying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.com. Episode transcript here. Follow the show on Instagram @normalgossip, and if you have gossip, email us at normalgossip@defector.</description></item><item><title>S3 Ep2: The Adventures of Flat Margaret with Jessica Goodman | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260029/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Writer Jessica Goodman joins us for a tale of a One Direction concert weekend gone wrong. Follow Jessica on Instagram @jessicagoodman and buy her books! You can support Normal Gossip directly bybuying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.com. Episode transcript here. Follow the show on Instagram @normalgossip, and if you have gossip, email us at normalgossip@defector.com or leave us a voicemail at 26-79-GOSSIP. Normal Gossip is hosted by Kelsey McKinney (@mckinneykelsey) and produced by Alex Sujong Laughlin (@alexlaughs).</description></item><item><title>S3 Ep1: Righteous Lesbian Energy with Samantha Irby | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260030/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to season 3! We're kicking it off with writer and comedian Samantha Irby for a story about a misguided move to the South and a rogue HOA president. You can support Normal Gossip directly bybuying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.com. Episode transcript here. Follow the show on Instagram @normalgossip, and if you have gossip, email us at normalgossip@defector.com or leave us a voicemail at 26-79-GOSSIP.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep10: Poledancing, book clubs, and gay men's chorus: Your niche gossip | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260031/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260031/</guid><description>Podcast Description We've been waiting for your niche gossip all season, and you delivered! Five stories of clubs, communities, and small towns, just for you. Content warning: We always say that no animals are harmed in our stories, but Alex was tired when she picked these and didn't realize that there are actually two harmed animals in these stories -- one dog who dies (off-screen) and one cat who dies. Please forgive, we will learn from our mistakes.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep9: Telephone Game with Alex and Justin | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260032/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alex and Justin spent season 2 playing a little game of telephone with the guests....and kept Kelsey out of the loop. Join us to hear how much one gossip story can change from person to person. You can support Normal Gossip directly bybuying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.com. Episode transcript here. Follow the show on Instagram @normalgossip, and if you have gossip, email us at normalgossip@defector.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep8: Conflict Archaeology with Julia Furlan | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260033/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Julia Furlan joins us for a pandemic wedding saga. You can support Normal Gossip directly bybuying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.com. Episode transcript here. Follow the show on Instagram @normalgossip, and if you have gossip, email us at normalgossip@defector.com or leave us a voicemail at 26-79-GOSSIP.
Normal Gossip is hosted by Kelsey McKinney (@mckinneykelsey) and produced by Alex Sujong Laughlin (@alexlaughs). Transcript</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep7: Dishing in the Confessional with Emma Eun-joo Choi | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260034/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian, writer, and host of NPR's Everyone &amp;amp; Their Mom, Emma Eun-joo Choi, joins us for a story about teenage love that went on way, way too long. You can support Normal Gossip directly bybuying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.com. Episode transcript here. Follow the show on Instagram @normalgossip, and if you have gossip, email us at normalgossip@defector.com or leave us a voicemail at 26-79-GOSSIP.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep6: Podcast Famous with Brian Park | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260035/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian and host of Feeling Asian Brian Park makes the case for just sending that risky DM already. You can support Normal Gossip directly bybuying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.com. Episode transcript here.
Follow the show on Instagram @normalgossip, and if you have gossip, email us at normalgossip@defector.com or leave us a voicemail at 26-79-GOSSIP. Normal Gossip is hosted by Kelsey McKinney (@mckinneykelsey) and produced by Alex Sujong Laughlin (@alexlaughs).</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep5: Personality of a Tan Wall with Tobin Low | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260036/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tobin Low (Nancy, This American Life, Radiolab) joins us for a romantic (?) tale about hourly work and spilled milk. You can support Normal Gossip directly bybuying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.com.
Episode transcript here.
Follow the show on Instagram @normalgossip, and if you have gossip, email us at normalgossip@defector.com or leave us a voicemail at 26-79-GOSSIP.
Normal Gossip is hosted by Kelsey McKinney (@mckinneykelsey) and produced by Alex Sujong Laughlin (@alexlaughs).</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep4: Short King of East Texas with Lindsey Weber and Bobby Finger | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260037/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who Weekly's Lindsey Weber and Bobby Finger join us for a story about a dad's mid-life crisis and the friends he meets along the way. You can support Normal Gossip directly bybuying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.com. Episode transcript here.
Follow the show on Instagram @normalgossip, and if you have gossip, email us at normalgossip@defector.com or leave us a voicemail at 26-79-GOSSIP.
Normal Gossip is hosted by Kelsey McKinney (@mckinneykelsey) and produced by Alex Sujong Laughlin (@alexlaughs).</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep3: Squirrel Enthusiast with Tracy Clayton | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260038/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tracy Clayton joins us this week to affirm her hatred of squirrels, and also to judge who is truly the villain in a group of busybody preschool parents. You can support Normal Gossip directly by buying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.com. Episode transcript here. Follow the show on Instagram @normalgossip, and if you have gossip, email us at normalgossip@defector.com or leave us a voicemail at 26-79-GOSSIP.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep2: The Not-Quite-Magicians with Kalyn Kahler | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Defector’s Kalyn Kahler decides whether this week’s story is about a benevolent business owner with boundary issues — or a cult. You can support Normal Gossip directly by buying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.com. Episode transcript here. Follow the show on Instagram @normalgossip, and if you have gossip, email us at normalgossip@defector.com or leave us a voicemail at 26-79-GOSSIP.Normal Gossip is hosted by Kelsey McKinney (@mckinneykelsey) and produced by Alex Sujong Laughlin (@alexlaughs).</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep1: Grandma's 'Best Friend' Dot with Danielle Henderson | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260040/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to season 2! This week, Danielle Henderson joins us for a prime piece of vintage gossip that will knock your wayfarers off. Get tickets to the Normal Gossip live show at Caveat in NYC on June 1 here! You can support Normal Gossip directly by buying merch or becoming a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.com. Episode transcript here. Follow the show on Instagram @normalgossip, and if you have gossip, email us at normalgossip@defector.</description></item><item><title>S1 Ep10: Bonus #2: Your FAQ + Some BIG Announcements! | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260041/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kelsey and Alex answer your most burning questions: How do we make the show? Why did we take a break? WHEN IS SEASON 2 STARTING? Plus, some big announcements! Become a Friend or a Friend-of-Friend at supportnormalgossip.com . Episode transcript here. Follow the show on Instagram @normalgossip, and if you have gossip, email us at normalgossip@defector.com or leave us a voicemail at 26-79-GOSSIP. Normal Gossip is hosted by Kelsey McKinney (@mckinneykelsey) and produced by Alex Sujong Laughlin (@alexlaughs).</description></item><item><title>S1 Ep9: Season 1 BONUS: Your Family Gossip | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260042/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260042/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re back with a special gossip treat for you! Kelsey is joined by Normal Gossip producer Alex Sujong Laughlin to react to YOUR family gossip stories. Episode transcript here. Follow the show on Instagram @normalgossip, and if you have gossip, email us at normalgossip@defector.com or leave us a voicemail at 26-79-GOSSIP. Normal Gossip is hosted by Kelsey McKinney (@mckinneykelsey) and produced by Alex Sujong Laughlin (@alexlaughs).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>S1 Ep8: Spot the Scammer with Claire Fallon and Emma Gray | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260043/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Claire Fallon and Emma Gray join us for our season 1 finale to hear about a girls trip gone horribly wrong. Follow Claire on Twitter @ClaireEFallon and follow Emma @emmaladyrose. Episode transcript here. Follow the show on Instagram @normalgossip, and if you have gossip, email us at normalgossip@defector.com or leave us a voicemail at 26-79-GOSSIP. And don't forget to send us your FAMILY GOSSIP for our special between-season bonus episode.</description></item><item><title>S1 Ep7: No One Tells Josh Gondelman the Good Gossip | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260044/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, comedian Josh Gondelman loves the gossip story we told him so much he compared it to O. Henry and Poe. Follow Josh on Twitter @joshgondelman. Episode transcript here. Follow the show on Instagram @normalgossip, and if you have gossip, email us at normalgossip@defector.com or leave us a voicemail at 26-79-GOSSIP. Normal Gossip is hosted by Kelsey McKinney (@mckinneykelsey) and produced by Alex Sujong Laughlin (@alexlaughs). Subscribe to Defector Media and get your first month for 99 cents at defector.</description></item><item><title>S1 Ep6: Nemesis by Proxy, with Delia Cai | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260045/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Senior Vanity Fair correspondent Delia Cai joins us to break down some real John Tucker Must Die shit. Follow Delia on Twitter @delia_cai. Episode transcript here. Follow the show on Instagram @normalgossip, and if you have gossip, email us at normalgossip@defector.com or leave us a voicemail at 26-79-GOSSIP. Normal Gossip is hosted by Kelsey McKinney (@mckinneykelsey) and produced by Alex Sujong Laughlin (@alexlaughs). Subscribe to Defector Media and get your first month for 99 cents at defector.</description></item><item><title>S1 Ep5: Leave ‘em a Little Bit Broke, a Little Bit Mad with Laci Mosley | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260046/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260046/</guid><description>Podcast Description THE Scam Goddess, Laci Mosley, joins us in an adventure to the South where a group of sorority sisters teach us the first rule of Gossip Fight Club: never text your mess. Follow Laci on Twitter @DivaLaci and subscribe to Scam Goddess! Episode transcript available here. Follow the show on Instagram @normalgossip, and if you have gossip, email us at normalgossip@defector.com or leave us a voicemail at 26-79-GOSSIP. Normal Gossip is hosted by Kelsey McKinney (@mckinneykelsey) and produced by Alex Sujong Laughlin (@alexlaughs).</description></item><item><title>S1 Ep4: Always Google Your Neighbors with Megan Greenwell | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260047/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Megan Greenwell dishes some upstate woods gossip and we tell her about a mysterious, entrepreneurial neighbor.
Follow Megan on Twitter at @megreenwell
Episode transcript available here.
Follow the show on Instagram @normalgossip, and if you have gossip, email us at normalgossip@defector.com or leave us a voicemail at 26-79-GOSSIP.
Normal Gossip is hosted by Kelsey McKinney (@mckinneykelsey) and produced by Alex Sujong Laughlin (@alexlaughs).
Subscribe to Defector Media and get your first month for 99 cents at defector.</description></item><item><title>S1 Ep3: Can I Say Something Bitchy? With Rachelle Hampton | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260048/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rachelle Hampton, host of Slate’s ICYMI podcast, joins us to unravel the scandal brewing in a neighborhood knitting circle! Listen to ICYMI and follow Rachelle on Twitter at @heyydnae. Episode transcript available here. Follow the show on Instagram @normalgossip, and if you have gossip, email us at normalgossip@defector.com or leave us a voicemail at 26-79-GOSSIP. Normal Gossip is hosted by Kelsey McKinney (@mckinneykelsey) and produced by Alex Sujong Laughlin (@alexlaughs).</description></item><item><title>S1 Ep2: Dickmatized with Sam Sanders | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260049/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Sanders, Correspondent and host of NPR's "It's Been a Minute," joins us for our second episode! Join us as we hear a story good enough that it forced Sam to reveal that, "the first rule of fight club is never date a tall, cute bartender." Check outSam Sanders' "It's Been a Minute" here, and follow him on social media @samsanders. Episode transcript available here. Follow the show on Instagram @normalgossip, and if you have gossip, email us at normalgossip@defector.</description></item><item><title>S1 Ep1: Gossiptonin with Virgie Tovar | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260050/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Author, activist, and podcast host Virgie Tovar joins us for our first ever gossip story! Join us as we revel in a messy grad school cohort and go on a camping trip with a dog named Pancake. Check out Virgie’s podcast Rebel Eater’s Club and pre-order her new book, The Body Positive Journal. Episode transcript available here. Follow the show on Instagram @normalgossip, and if you have gossip, email us at normalgossip@defector.</description></item><item><title>S1: You didn't hear this from me | Normal Gossip</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1495260051/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 22:27:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1495260051/</guid><description>Podcast Description After two years where gossip has been hard to find, we decided it was finally time to create a space for the silly, strange, banal gossip we all know and love. This is Normal Gossip, a podcast from Defector Media. Check back here January 5, 2022 for episode 1.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>