<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Irish History Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/irish-history-podcast/</link><description>Recent content in Irish History Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 04:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/irish-history-podcast/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Forgotten: The Irish in the American West | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 04:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350001/</guid><description>Podcast Description New York, Boston, and Chicago dominate the history of Irish migration to the United States. However by 1900 one of the most Irish cities in the US was Butte Montana. Situated high in the Rocky mountains, Butte was just one of hundreds of Irish communities dotted across the American West.&amp;nbsp;
Beginning back in the California Goldrush of the 1850s,&amp;nbsp;tens of thousands of Irish immigrants ventured into the American West.</description></item><item><title>Taking the world by storm – a history of podcasting 2/2 | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 04:30:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350002/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the past decade, podcasting has taken the world by storm. The advent of smartphones and the ground-breaking podcast 'Serial' would see podcasting surge in popularity.
In 2020 alone over a million new shows were launched. But does it have a future? Some are not convinced.
In the second and final part of my series on the history of podcasting I look at how podcasting became so popular and where it’s heading.</description></item><item><title>Are you in a cult? A history of podcasting 1/2 | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350003/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 13:49:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350003/</guid><description>Podcast Description ‘You might not be a revolutionary, but you are living through a revolution.’&amp;nbsp;
Podcasting is much older than you might imagine. A decade before the true crime show Serial took the world by storm, creators were making some of the earliest shows. &amp;nbsp;
This podcast is a nostalgic trip through the early days of the internet in Ireland when podcasting emerged. Brian Greene who was making shows in the mid 2000s shares his memories of the early days of podcasting.</description></item><item><title>Assassinated: A Story of Vengeance &amp; Murder in the Great Hunger | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 04:30:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350004/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s a dark evening in early November 1847.
A carriage makes it's way through lawless starving countryside in North Roscommon.
A gun shot rings out, a man falls dead.
A family mourns but a community rejoices.
While the Great Hunger of the 1840s resulted in one million deaths, this one murder encapsulated the stark choices facing that generation of Irish people in a one gripping story. It is retold in this episode.</description></item><item><title>The Irish in Andersonville 'the deadliest place in America' | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 04:30:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350005/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the mid 1860s, Andersonville became one of the most feared places in America.
This sleepy corner of Georgia gained notoriety in the later stages of the US Civil War when the Confederacy opened a prison camp there. Nearly one third of all prisoners who entered Andersonville never left.&amp;nbsp;
Among their number were hundreds of Irish men. This podcast tells their stories.
I am joined by historian Damian Shiels who runs the Andersonville Irish project.</description></item><item><title>Rose McKenna &amp; Sydney Arnold – Rebels With A Secret History | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 04:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Writing histories of people who led secret lives is difficult because they leave few records. Yet that is precisely what my guest in today’s show has done. In this podcast, Dr Maurice Casey, shares the fascinating history of Rose McKenna and Sydney Arnold and how he uncovered their secret lives.
In the early 20th century, this Latvian-Irish couple participated in two revolutions in Ireland and Russia. While Rose tried to arms for the IRA in London, they were also contemporaries of Ho Chi Minh when they lived in Moscow.</description></item><item><title>A History of the Supernatural in Ireland | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 03:30:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350007/</guid><description>Podcast Description As we prepare to celebrate Halloween, this episode is a timely exploration of the history of the supernatural in Ireland.
Ghosts have long played an important role in Irish history and culture. In this podcast I am joined by Dr Clodagh Tait, a historian of the supernatural. Our conversation focuses on a specific type of ghost referred to as a crisis apparition. These usually appeared far from home, often informing an emigrant about an imminent death in their family.</description></item><item><title>A History of Ireland's Deaf Community [From the archives] | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 03:30:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350008/</guid><description>Podcast Description I have come down with a cold so rather than subject you to me coughing and spluttering through a show I have selected a classic from the archives.&amp;nbsp;
As I explain, I recently listened back to this episode after a chance meeting with my guest Cormac Leonard. The episode on the history of the Deaf community is the definition of forgotten history. Until recently the community was largely ignored by historians.</description></item><item><title>Anti-Irish Racism in 1930s Britain | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 03:30:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350009/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the 1920s and 30s Irish emigrants in Britain faced widespread racism and discrimination. Labelled drunks, subversives, and a threat to society, right wing politicians whipped up fear and hatred against the community.This podcast tells the forgotten stories of these emigrants.
The episode begins with humorous story of Martin King whose drunken escapades after downing half a bottle of whiskey revealed the racism at the heart of British society.</description></item><item><title>The Arigna Soviet | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350010/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 03:30:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350010/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1923 as the Irish revolution came to an end, large parts of the North Roscommon town of Arigna lay in ruins. While war and revolution had swept across Ireland over the previous years few places shared Arigna’s unique experience. When workers occupied local coalmines demanding better working conditions this began years of intense and bitter conflict with the authorities. This is the story of the Arigna Soviet You can find Oisín Ó Drisceoil's essay on the Arigna Soviet in Labour HIstory in Irish History here.</description></item><item><title>Addiction in Irish History | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350011/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 03:30:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350011/</guid><description>Podcast Description At the turn of the 20th century alcoholism was a major problem in Irish society. The island had 17,300 pubs while around 40% of all prison sentences were alcohol related. There was a general sense alcohol addiction was out of control. The stereotype of the happy-go-lucky drunk certainly masked the reality of the Irish alcoholism.
In this podcast I explore addiction in Ireland at the turn of the 20th century by focusing on the life of one woman - the Sligo native Sarah Garvey.</description></item><item><title>The Origin Story of 'A Lethal Legacy' | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 00:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Every book has an origin story. My new book ‘A Lethal Legacy – A History of Ireland in 18 Murders’ is no different. While the book goes on sale today, the origin story goes back to 2015 when I found a trove of old letters belonging to a grandmother I never knew.
Tune in to find out more.
THE BOOK LAUNCH IS ON TONIGHT (SEP 14) AT 6P.M. IN HODGES FIGGIS BOOKSHOP ON DAWSON ST.</description></item><item><title>The Cork tsunami &amp; other historic natural disasters | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350013/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 16:38:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350013/</guid><description>Podcast Description This podcast looks at forgotten story of the tsunami that hit Cork in 1755, the volcanic winter of 1816 and a meteor that was way to close for comfort in 1908. Although they dont feature prominently in history, they had huge impact at the time.
Articles referenced in the show A seismic tsunami in the Irish annals, recorded at Iona in October 720 https://arxiv.org/abs/2211.05224
Folklore about the Cork tsunami http://www.</description></item><item><title>The First Modern Royal Visit to Ireland | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 03:30:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350014/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1821 George IV was the first British monarch to visit Ireland in modern times. It was a historic occasion for multiple reasons. Not only was he the first king to set foot on Irish soil since the 17th century but he was the first to do so without an army.
Many held out hope the king's arrival might usher in a new era in Irish history.
However George himself had other ideas.</description></item><item><title>A Broken People: The Survivors of the Great Hunger | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 03:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350015/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Great Hunger left deep scars on the Irish society. Many of those who survived the 1840s never fully survived the harrowing ordeal they had endured. They were traumatised in body and spirit. For the rest of their lives, they carried the physical and psychological injuries the Great Hunger inflicted on them.
This podcast follows the life one of the last survivors in Dublin - Catherine Mulhern.
This podcast was included in an early draft of my upcoming book A Lethal Legacy – A History of Ireland in 18 Murders.</description></item><item><title>The Brighton Bombing - the attempt to kill Margaret Thatcher | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 03:30:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350016/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1984, the Conservative Party, lead by the British Prime Minister Margaret Thatcher, gathered in the seaside town of Brighton for their annual conference. In the early hours of October 12th a bomb ripped through the Grand Hotel where Thatcher and several other conservative leaders were staying. The following day the Provisional IRA would claim responsibility for the attack. This triggered one of the largest manhunts in history. While the plan was audacious, the police operation to catch the IRA team that planted the bomb was extraordinary.</description></item><item><title>A Deep, Dark History. Bunmahon &amp; the Copper Rush of the 19th Century | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 03:30:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bunmahon is an idyllic seaside town in Co Waterford but it has a deep dark history. It's a story that begins in an abandoned mine and ends in a search for a lost town...
Need I say more?
You can find out more about Bunmahon at the local visitor centre.
My upcoming book 'A Lethal Legacy - A History of Ireland in 18 Murders' will be released on September 14th 2023.</description></item><item><title>Jack the Ripper: Irish Connections [From the Archives] | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 03:30:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350018/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode was originally released in 2019. Over the past week I was recording the audio version of 'A Lethal Legacy - A History of Ireland in 18 Murders' so I didnt have time to prepare a new episode but this is worth a relisten! Normal service resumes next week.“In the later half 1888 London was gripped by fear when five women were murdered within a few months of each other in the East End of the city.</description></item><item><title>Taking the Hard Road - Edward O’Rourke &amp; opposing Hitler | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 07:25:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350019/</guid><description>Podcast Description As I mention in the episode I am recording the audio version of A Lethal Legacy - A History of Ireland in 18 Murders this week! Don't forget to pre-order at Easons and use the code FD10 to get 10% off!Edward O’Rourke is not a name you expect to encounter in the history of Eastern Europe, yet he is a celebrated figure in the Polish city of Gdansk for the role he played in opposing the&amp;nbsp;rise of the Nazis in the city in the 1930s.</description></item><item><title>The Road to War - How the Irish Civil War Started | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 03:30:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350020/</guid><description>Podcast Description 'The Road to War' is the first episode in a five part Irish History Podcast production on the Irish Civil War. The full series, exclusively available for supporters, features the leading Irish historian Dr Brian Hanley from Trinity College Dublin. Over the five episodes the series covers the full story of the Irish Civil War from the National Army assault on the Four Courts through to the IRA order to dump arms in 1923.</description></item><item><title>The Irish Women Who Fought the Nazis in World War II (The French Resistance Part II) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350021/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 05:56:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350021/</guid><description>Podcast Description **This is the second of two episodes on the story of Irish people who fought in the French Resistance. Part I was released last week.**
Few Irish people recognise the names Sr Katherine Anne McCarthy or Patricia O'Sullivan. However during the Second World War II they were among the dozens of Irish women who fought in the underground war against the Nazi occupation of France. The stories of these women are unbelievable.</description></item><item><title>Irish Volunteers in the French Resistance Part I | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350022/</guid><description>Podcast Description The struggle of the French Resistance against the Nazi Occupation of France remains one of the most famous chapters in World War II history. It has been immortalized in numerous film and books. However the story of the dozens of Irish people who served in the Resistance has been almost completely forgotten. In this podcast I interview Dr David Murphy from Maynoooth University who has researched the Irish people who served in the Resistance.</description></item><item><title>Rotten Prod - The Life of James Baird | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 03:30:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350023/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode needs a bit of an introduction. While the term Rotten Prod, short for Rotten Protestant, sounds like a sectarian slur, the phrase has a very different and fascinating history. It actually originated within the Protestant community in Ulster to describe a person considered disloyal to Unionism. At the turn of the 20th century, the majority of Ulster Protestants were Unionists, meaning they supported Ireland remaining in the United Kingdom.</description></item><item><title>A Lethal Legacy - A History of Ireland in 18 Murders (A New Book from Fin Dwyer) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 03:30:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350024/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is short, but has a big reveal! For nearly two years I have been working on a new book and I can finally tell you all about it. Published by Harper Collins, it's called 'A Lethal Legacy - A History of Ireland in 18 Murders.' In this podcast I explain what you can expect from the book, how it was shaped by you and, most importantly, how you can get your hands on a copy.</description></item><item><title>Sights, Sounds &amp; Smells: Life in Dublin on the Eve of the 1916 Rising [from the archives] | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350025/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 03:30:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350025/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 1916 Rising is one of the most famous events in Irish history but it’s easy to forget it took place in a city that 300,000 people called home. In this podcast (originally released over three years ago) I explore Dublin on eve of the rising&amp;nbsp;revealing what the city was like in the early 20th century. You will hear the sounds of Dublin, what the city looked like, even how it smelled by following the city coroner Dr Louis A Byrne.</description></item><item><title>Oliver Cromwell - Still Notorious, But Why? | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350026/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 03:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350026/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Cromwellian Conquest of Ireland took place over 370 years ago. Despite the passage of time the man who led that conquest remains one of the most reviled figures in Irish history. In this podcast I look at why he, above others, is so reviled in Ireland.
****Get tickets for my new walking tour mentioned in the episode are available here.****
The episode is recorded in the ruins of Dunhill Castle.</description></item><item><title>A Journey to the Gates of Hell | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350027/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 03:30:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350027/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1397 Ramón de Perellós left the city of Avignon in the Kingdom of France, setting out on a 2,000 km journey to Ireland. His ultimate destination was a fabled gateway to the afterlife on Station Island, Lough Derg, Co Donegal.&amp;nbsp;In this episode you will follow in the footsteps of de Perellós on this medieval pilgrimage.&amp;nbsp;Forget the problems of the modern world and prepare yourself for a gruelling journey by land and sea through medieval Europe.</description></item><item><title>Belfast and the Slave Trade | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 03:30:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350028/</guid><description>Podcast Description The history of Belfast has been dominated by the Troubles of the late 20th century and the longer history of sectarian conflict in the city. However Belfast holds a lesser-known yet significant chapter in its past—it's connections to the slave trade. In this episode, I am joined by Tom Thorpe who uncovers Belfast's complex ties to slavery in the United States.&amp;nbsp;
Join us as Tom sheds light on how Belfast's economy became intertwined with the slave trade and explores the emergence of a radical anti-slavery movement within the city.</description></item><item><title>The Parnell Divorce Case - a story that shocked the Victorian world | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350029/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 03:30:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350029/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the 1880s Charles Stewart Parnell was the most famous Irish politician of his generation. Dubbed 'the uncrowned king of Ireland' he was respected and admired across the political spectrum.
However 1890 he was embroiled in a sensational scandal that rocked the Victorian world when it emerged he had been in a decade long relationship with a married woman. In this episode I am joined by Dr Lloyd (Meadhbh) Houston.</description></item><item><title>Disert - A Place Where Mythology and History Meets | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350030/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 03:30:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Disert is a remote townland in the Bluestack Mountains in Co Donegal. For reasons that are not entirely clear, our ancestors have been drawn here for thousands of years. There is no question it is a special place.
Located in the shade of a sacred mountain - Carnaween - it was a site of pagan worship associated with some of the most famous figures in Irish mythology. There are stories relating to Finn MacCumhail (McCool), Diarmaid and Grainne in the surrounding area.</description></item><item><title>The Lingaun – Exploring Ireland's Oldest Frontier Part II | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350031/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 03:30:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350031/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Neil Jackman and myself continue our journey down the Lingaun Valley, one of Ireland’s oldest frontiers. As we move closer to the present day we explore an 800 year old church, a castle and a battlefield from the 1798 rebellion looking at how this once contested frontier fell into obscurity after thousands of year.
Support the show at&amp;nbsp;patreon.com/irishpodcast
Check out Neil’s episodes 26 and 28 of Neil’s Podcast Amplify Archaeology which cover topics related the Lingaun.</description></item><item><title>The Lingaun – Exploring Ireland's Oldest Frontier Part I | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350032/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 03:30:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350032/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Lingaun Valley is a little known valley that forms the border between Co Kilkenny and Co Tipperary. However for thousands of years this small river formed one of the most important frontiers in Ireland.
While the societies and kingdoms that fought and died over this valley are long vanished the region is littered with their remains in the tombs, religious sites, castles and battlefields.
A few weeks ago I met up with archaeologist Neil Jackman, an expert in the region and we spent a morning exploring the valley.</description></item><item><title>Heroes or Villains? How To Trace Your Ancestors... | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350033/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 03:30:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever wondered about your ancestors and who they were were? Were they on the right side of history? Maybe you’re curious to find out if your family have dark secrets?&amp;nbsp;
In this podcast genealogist Martin Costello gives you a step by step guide to tracing your family. Over the episode I follow Martin’s steps and trace my ancestors back to the Great Hunger. Along the way I found out a few secrets my great grandparents would prefer had remained in the 19th century!</description></item><item><title>Bad Bridget: When American Dreams became Nightmares | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350034/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 03:30:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emigration has been one of the defining features of Irish life since the Great Hunger. Generations have been drawn to the United States in the hope of finding a better life across the Atlantic. Many succeeded but for some these dreams became nightmares.&amp;nbsp;
Over the last few years The Bad Bridget Project in Queens University Belfast by Dr Elaine Farrell and Dr Leanne McCormick has focused on criminal and deviant Irish women in North America.</description></item><item><title>Burned Alive: The Burning of Bridget Cleary | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350035/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 04:30:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350035/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1895 Bridget Cleary was a confident independent woman in a rapidly changing Ireland. This brought her into conflict with dark and sinister figures in her own community.&amp;nbsp;
After being labelled a 'changeling' (a fairy who had taken the place of the real person) Bridget was tortured in a brutal ritual. This podcast, based in an original episode released in 2016, explores Cleary's life and why those closest to her ultimately murdered her.</description></item><item><title>Women on Trial - The Alice Morton Divorce Case of 1920 | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350036/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 04:30:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Until 1981 a woman was considered the property of her husband under Irish law. A husband could even sue another man for damaging his property if he had an affair with his wife. Referred to as 'criminal conversation’ these trials were demeaning and humiliating for the women involved. 'Women on trial looks' looks at the story of Alice Morton. When her marriage fell apart in 1919, she found herself at the centre of a sensational divorce and criminal conversation trial.</description></item><item><title>The Mystery of Henry Wilson’s Assassination | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350037/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 04:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350037/</guid><description>Podcast Description On June 22nd 1922, the British Field Marshall, Henry Wilson was shot dead in London. The assassination sparked a major political crisis in Ireland. The British government blamed the killing on a faction of the IRA opposed to the recent Anglo-Irish Treaty. When they demanded action be taken against them, Michael Collins oversaw an attack on an IRA unit occupying the Four Courts in Dublin. This sparked the Irish Civil War.</description></item><item><title>Ireland's Alcatraz - the Story of Spike Island | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350038/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 14:14:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Spike Island in Cork Harbour is often referred to as 'Ireland’s Alcatraz'. While this famous island prison began life as a monastery it was transformed into a fortress during the American Revolutionary War. However Spike island gained it's notorious reputation during the Great Hunger of the 1840s when a prison was opened in the fort. This episode recorded on Spike island tells the story of Ireland’s Alcatraz…
I would like to thank the team on Spike Island for facilitating the recording of this episode.</description></item><item><title>How the Famine Irish built New York | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350039/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 13:17:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Between 1840 and 1860 the population of New York almost trebled growing from 300,000 to 800,000. This influx of migrants from Europe gave birth to modern Manhattan. At the heart of this story were the 250,000 Irish people who made the city their home in the aftermath of the Great Hunger.&amp;nbsp;
This is the story of the Famine Irish in New York.
In this episode I interview Dr Tyler Anbinder from George Washington University.</description></item><item><title>The Myth of Irish Neutrality in World War II | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350040/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 04:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Five days after the end of the Second World War, Winston Churchill launched into a blistering critique of Irish neutrality on the BBC World Service. He would famously claim the government of Éamon de Valera had frolicked with German representatives in Dublin while Britain fought the Nazis.&amp;nbsp;
The reality of Irish neutrality in the World War II was somewhat more complicated. To discuss the story of Irish neutrality I am joined by the Dr Donal Ó Drisceoil from the History of Department of University College Cork.</description></item><item><title>The Story of Irish Coffin Ships Continued... | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350041/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 04:30:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350041/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode continues the story of emigration and Irish Coffin Ships during the Great Famine. Dr Cian T. McMahon, the author of The Coffin Ship - Life and Death at Sea during the Great Famine discusses The death rate onboard coffin ships What factors determined whether someone lived or died.How Irish Famine emigrants adjusted to life in the U.S.You can get a copy of The Coffin Ship - Life and Death at Sea here If you want listen to more stories form the Great Hunger my 30 part podcast series is available here.</description></item><item><title>The Story of Irish Coffin Ships Part I | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350042/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 04:30:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Between 1845 - 1855 over two million people left Ireland to escape hunger, poverty and disease during the Great Hunger. The experience of these emigrants was often harrowing. The term Coffin Ship has became synonymous with their journeys across the Atlantic.&amp;nbsp;
While the term conveys misery, what was the experience actually like?
In the first of two podcasts on the subject, I am joined by Dr Cian T. McMahon author of The Coffin Ship - Life and Death at Sea during the Great Famine.</description></item><item><title>How will 2022 be remembered in history? | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350043/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 04:30:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are we living through historic times? The Russian Invasion of Ukraine, the Queen's death, Liz Truss and Elon Musk have all dominated the headlines in 2022. However headlines don't always make history. Will the events of our lifetime be remembered in the future?
In this episode I look at how the last twelve months might be remembered by future historians.
Become a supporter at https://patreon.com/irishpodcast
Become a member at https://plus.</description></item><item><title>A Slum City - Life &amp; Death in Late Victorian Dublin | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 04:30:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Life in Dublin at the turn of the 20th century was difficult to say the least. Working Class Dubliners were lucky if they reached 50. In those five or so decades, they worked dangerous jobs and lived in appalling conditions. In this episode I am joined by Dr Ciara Breathnach. Ciara has spent several years researching the records of Dublin's Coroners Court for her book 'Ordinary Lives, Death, and Social Class: Dublin City Coroner's Court, 1876-1902'.</description></item><item><title>A lost town in the Wicklow Mountains | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350045/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 04:30:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Castlekevin was once a thriving settlement deep in the Wicklow Mountains. However in the 14th century after decades of warfare the historical record fell silent.&amp;nbsp;
Over the past year the Roundwood &amp;amp; District Historical &amp;amp; Folklore Society have been working with a team of archaeologists to uncover the story of this lost town and castle. Using ground penetrating radar, drones and ecological surveys the team have started to unlock the lost story of this forgotten town.</description></item><item><title>The Black Death in Ireland | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350046/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 04:30:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350046/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Black Death changed Europe and Ireland forever. This disease which swept across the continent through 1348 carried off around 40% of the population. Its aftermath was no less sensational as social upheavel, wars and revolts broke out across Europe. Ireland was no different, indeed it was arguably affected in more profound ways than most of the continent. Over last few months I have produced a new hour three hour audio feature on the Black Death in Ireland based on my 2016 book 1348: A Medieval Apocalypse.</description></item><item><title>Contraception in Ireland | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350047/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 04:30:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Believe it or not, it was a crime to sell contraception in Ireland between 1935 and 1979. The Irish government also banned all literature on family planning for decades as well. This had a profound impact on life in Ireland. Couples couldn't plan families or engage in recreational sex without fear of pregnancy. This devastated relationships and left many people with a very limited understanding of sex and pregnancy.</description></item><item><title>The Hunt for Nazi Spies in World War II | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350048/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 03:30:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350048/</guid><description>Podcast Description While Ireland remained neutral in the Second World War several Nazi agents were smuggled into the country. Their aims varied, some sought to establish contact with the IRA while others were spies. In this episode, I interview historian Marc McMenamin about the attempts of Irish Military Intelligence's to catch these spies and agents. Marc also explains the attitude of the IRA towards these individuals &amp;amp; the forgotten Irish code breakers in the war.</description></item><item><title>Exploring A Medieval Fortress - Conwy Castle | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350049/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 03:30:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350049/</guid><description>Podcast Description There is a photo essay to accompany this episode here&amp;nbsp;Conwy castle in Wales in one of Europe's most spectacular medieval castles. Built in the 1280s by Edward I the castle has withstood sieges and the ravages of time. On Sat October 8th I organised a supporters trip to the castle. Early the following morning, as the sun rose over the medieval town I recorded this episode. Using the acoustics of the castle and the walls I explain the history, what the castle looks like today and how its elaborate and lethal defences worked in the middle ages.</description></item><item><title>[Ep 3/3] Ireland's Last Aristocrat - The Life of Olive Packenham Mahon | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350050/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 03:30:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350050/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this final episode of Ireland's Last Aristocrat, you will hear how Olive Packenham Mahon adjusted to life in Ireland after the War of Independence. This follows her story through the chaotic early days of the Irish Free State, her futile attempts to budget as money ran out and how she would end up an eccentric living in a mansion that crumbled around her.&amp;nbsp;
There will be a bonus episode of recordings from Strokestown Park House for supporters at www.</description></item><item><title>[Ep 2/3] Ireland's Last Aristocrat - The Life of Olive Packenham Mahon | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350051/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 03:30:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Olive's unpublished diary and letters reveal a story of war, revolution and scandalous relationships in Ireland during the War of Independence.
After being raised in splendour with servants taking care of her every need (see part I), this episode follows Olive Packenham Mahon through the Irish revolutionary era. After the outbreak of World War I everything changed.&amp;nbsp;
The Packenham Mahons and other aristocrats found themselves on the wrong side of history as revolution swept through Ireland.</description></item><item><title>[Ep 1/3] Ireland's Last Aristocrat - The Life of Olive Packenham Mahon | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350052/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Olive Packenham Mahon was born into wealth and privilege in 1894, but the legacy of a secret funeral and the spectre of war and revolution defined her life.&amp;nbsp;
She was no ordinary aristocrat - Olive was the last of her kind...
A special thanks to Oisin O'Driscoll, Martin Fagan &amp;amp; Tony Aspel and all the team at Strokestown Park House for their time.
Olive Packenham Mahon's home Strokestown Park House is open to the public.</description></item><item><title>[Coming Weds 21st] Ireland's Last Aristocrat - the Life of Olive Pakenham Mahon | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350053/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 23:30:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Olive Pakenham Mahon was one of Ireland's last Aristocrats. Haunted by a secret funeral in her families past, revolution and war defined her life. She was anything but normal...
Subscribe to the Irish History Podcast where you listen to podcasts https://linktr.ee/irishhistory
Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/irishhistory.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Who was Bridget O’Donnel? AKA The Most Famous Irish Woman in History | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350054/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 03:30:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350054/</guid><description>Podcast Description You may not recognise the name Bridget O’Donnel, but she is one of the most recognisable women in Irish history. In December 1849 her image (pictured in the episode artwork and here) appeared in The Illustrated London News. Over the following decades she became the face of the Great Famine. Today she is one of the most recognisable women in Irish history, but who was Bridget O’Donnel?
Is it possible she never existed but was the creation of an artist called James Mahony?</description></item><item><title>From Ancient Ireland to Westeros: A History of Dragons | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350055/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 03:30:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350055/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this special episode brought to you by NOW, I look into why humans are fascinated with dragons. Did you know mythology around dragons is older than organised religion and spiritual beliefs of any kind? Meanwhile images of dragons has been found on all continents in societies from ancient Ireland to China.&amp;nbsp;In this podcast I look at why dragon myths are so old, where did this mythology came from and what does it mean?</description></item><item><title>15 Minutes in Medieval Dublin [From the Archives] | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350056/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 03:30:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350056/</guid><description>Podcast Description 2022 has been stressful so this episode treats you to 15 minutes of escapism. It brings you back to Dublin in 1320 in a soundscape of the medieval city. Reconstructed by trawling through 700 year old records for distinctive sounds; it was originally released back in 2014 but is definitely worth another listen.&amp;nbsp;
I am currently binge editing audio for an upcoming series but I will be back next week with a fresh episode!</description></item><item><title>Was the Great Famine a Genocide? [From the Archives] | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350057/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 04:00:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over the next two weeks I will be busy writing and editing an upcoming series called Ireland's Last Aristocrat. In the meantime I have dusted down two episodes I thought you might enjoy diving back into. This podcast was released in 2019. It's one of was the most listened to and generated the most feedback! It asks if the Great Hunger was a genocide.
Become a supporter and join me on the trip to Conwy - https://www.</description></item><item><title>From Newgrange to D-Day: A History of Weather Forecasting | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350058/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 03:30:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Since the dawn of history humans have been intrigued by the weather. However while it has the potential to sustain or destroy life, our ability to accurately forecast it is very recent. In this podcast I am joined by meteorologists Evelyn Cusack and Noel Fitzpatrick to explain the fascinating history of weather forecasting. Our desire to predict the weather is a story driven by war, natural disasters, human ingenuity and super computers.</description></item><item><title>‘No Irish, No Blacks, No Dogs’ - The Irish in London | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350059/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 03:30:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350059/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 1950s were a dismal time in Ireland. While the economy tanked, the catholic church, at the height of its power, maintained strict control over social life. Desperate to find a better life, nearly 500,000 Irish people emigrated. This staggering figure was equivalent to 80% of those born in the Free State between 1931 and 1941. This was a level of emigration unseen since the days of the Great Hunger of the 1840s.</description></item><item><title>A voicenote from Fin | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350060/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 04:00:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey folks, I have a few important announcements for you:
🎙️🎙️Starting in September supporters (at the $5 tier or more) will receive an exclusive series on the Civil War with Dr Brian Hanley from Trinity College Dublin. You can hear more on this above. Become a supporter to get the series
Patreon - Patreon.com/irishpodcast
Acast+ - https://plus.acast.com/s/irishhistory
🛥️🏰I am delighted to invite announce my a supporters' trip to Wales to visit the stunning Conwy Castle.</description></item><item><title>Murder at Mother Mountain 5/5 - Redemption? | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350061/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 03:30:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350061/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the series finale 'Redemption', we follow Ellen's life in Australia where a strange and unexpected redemption awaits.
Support the show:
Patreon https://patreon.com/Irishpodcast
Acast+ https://plus.acast.com/s/irishhistory
This week's special supporters are:
Z Hamming
R Downes
E Zimmer
G Hickey
R Hurley
M Nutty
E Rushe
P Kopf
C Wilson
J Guth
K McNamara
M Kelly
L Rosewood
D Gleason
C Stapleton
MJ Brodie
G Robertson
Become a member at https://plus.</description></item><item><title>Murder at Murder Mountain 4/5 - The Punishment | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350062/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 03:30:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350062/</guid><description>Podcast Description The trials are over, the sentences have been passed down and there is nothing left but the punishment. However as we have seen in the story so far, this is story is if anything unpredictable.
Support the show:
Patreon https://patreon.com/Irishpodcast Acast+ https://plus.acast.com/s/irishhistory
This week's special supporters are
StephenA
M Mulhern
B Donohoe
K Connolly
S Wall
G Browne
D Healy
B Cleary
P Lynch
L Anderson
K L Mayer</description></item><item><title>[Deep Dive] Behind the scenes of a victorian murder investigation | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350063/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 03:30:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Given the popularity of true crime genre, we are increasingly familiar with how murder investigations work in the 21st century. However they were quite different in the 19th century. In the third deep dive of Murder at Mother Mountain I am joined by Dr Niamh Howlin to explain how murder investigations &amp;amp; trials worked in the 1840s. Niamh is an expert on 19th century law and she explains how the process worked before DNA, forensics or even the concept of a trial by a jury of our peers existed!</description></item><item><title>Murder at Mother Mountain 3/5 - The Trial | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350064/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 03:30:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350064/</guid><description>Podcast Description The trial begins in Nenagh Courthouse in August 1846. What lies ahead for the accused is more uncertain than ever - murder in 19th century Ireland carries the death sentence.
Get add free early access to the next episode and help fund the show Patreon https://patreon.com/Irishpodcast Acast+ https://plus.acast.com/s/irishhistory
This week's special supporters&amp;nbsp;are&amp;nbsp;
B Flaherty
E Fogarty
H Lewis
C Rowland
D Browne
P Foran
P Hurley
C Wright&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>Murder at Mother Mountain Part 2/5 - The Crime | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350065/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 03:30:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350065/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part 2 of Murder at Mother Mountain Ellen’s life changes forever on March 10th 1846 when the violence that overshadowed her life finally comes to her door...
Support the show
www.patreon.com/irishpodcast
https://plus.acast.com/s/irishhistory
This week's special supporters are&amp;nbsp;
M Renee
D Mosier&amp;nbsp;
A Dacy
A O'Brien&amp;nbsp;
M Kelly
J A C McGowan
K L. Daly&amp;nbsp;
E Laurent
B Walsh
D Hill&amp;nbsp;
C Bleakley
M Lynch
A Jameson
G B.</description></item><item><title>[Deep Dive] Religion in Ireland before the Famine | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350066/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 09:48:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350066/</guid><description>Podcast Description To accompany Murder at Murder Mountain, I am releasing five deep dive episodes which delve into the history of the early 19th century Ireland in greater detail. These will be released between the main episodes.&amp;nbsp;
This is deep dive looks at the pre-Famine catholic church. While religion was very important during Ellen Kennedy's childhood, the catholic church emerging from centuries of repression was a very different organsation than it is today.</description></item><item><title>Murder at Mother Mountain 1/5 - Nurtured by Violence | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350067/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 03:30:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ellen Kennedy was born into in Western Tipperary in 1803. Her youth was one nurtured by violence. Hunger and food shortages were common. The stark inequalities lead to frequent outbreaks of violence. In this deeply unequal society young women like Ellen faced the threat of abduction and forced marriage.
Ellen however was far from average...
Support the show and get early access to the next episode. Patreon http://patreon.com/irishpodcast Acast+ https://play.</description></item><item><title>New Series - Murder at Mother Mountain Coming June 20th | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350068/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 03:30:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ellen Kennedy was born into in Western Tipperary in 1803. Her youth was one nurtured by violence…
Listen to an exclusive preview of episode 1 now at https://patreon.com/irishpodcast or Acast+https://plus.acast.com/s/irishhistory
Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/irishhistory.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>175 years on - Does Black '47 &amp; the Great Hunger still matter? | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350069/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 04:00:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over the last decade there has been countless events to mark the centenary of the Irish Revolution. However 2022 is also the 175th anniversary of Black ‘47, one of worst years of the Great Hunger. This has received little or no attention.&amp;nbsp;This begs the question does the Great Famine matter anymore or is it fading in to the distant past?
In this podcast I looked at the impact of the Great Famine, asking what if any meaning it has for day to day life in the 21st century.</description></item><item><title>From Bastardstown to Slutsend: A History of Irish Place Names | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350070/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 04:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ireland has some very strange place names. They range from the perplexing – Skeoghvosteen in Kilkenny, to the scandalous - Slutsend in Dublin and Bastardstown in Co Wexford. But where do these names come from and what do they tell us about our history? Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/irishhistory.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Violent History of Fun - Having the Craic in Medieval Ireland 50/16 | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350071/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 03:00:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350071/</guid><description>Podcast Description When you think of the Middle Ages what springs to mind? Medieval battles, warfare and general hardship? Certainly not fun. However while medieval Ireland was a violent place by any standard people were still able to enjoy themselves. In this episode I explore what our medieval ancestors did for fun. From football to archery, poetry to the pub they knew how to have a good time! Become a member at https://plus.</description></item><item><title>'From the Backwoods to the Motorway' A History of Traditional Irish Music | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350072/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 03:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Traditional music is central to Irish culture and identity in the 21st century. Contrary to what we might think, this is a relatively recent development. As late as the 1960s Trad was perceived as unfashionable and musicians were not allowed to play in pubs.&amp;nbsp;
60 years later it has become extremely popular and recognised the world over. So what happen?
Last weekend I sat down with Tom Mulligan, a legend in Trad scene to talk about the history of Trad over the century.</description></item><item><title>Cocaine, Murder &amp; Inquests: A night on the town in Victorian Waterford [Live from Katty Barry’s] 50/14 | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350073/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350073/</guid><description>Podcast Description This live podcast pokes in to the darker corners of the past looking at life in Victorian Waterford. Recorded live in Katty Barry’s in Waterford, it's a strange journey through macabre inquests that took place in pubs through to dentists who peddled cocaine!
The second half of the podcast looks at a bizarre murder involving a veteran of the Famine.
Support your history
www.patreon.com/irishpodcast
This week's special supporters are</description></item><item><title>Hitler, Copperfaced Jack &amp; Bodysnatching - The real history of Stephens Green. 50/13 | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350074/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 02:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stephen’s Green is one of Dublin’s well known areas. Located in the heart of the city centre, the Green is home to several prestigous instiutions and businesses including the Royal College of Surgeons, the Department of Foreign Affairs and the Shelbourne Hotel.&amp;nbsp;
It's history however is very different. Originally a swampy marshland, it was home to numerous brothels and the city gallows. In this&amp;nbsp;podcast I am joined by historian Frank Hopkins to explore the history of St Stephen's Green.</description></item><item><title>Nazi Propaganda in Ireland - the story of Irland Redaktion (50/12) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350075/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 04:00:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Irland Redaktion was a Nazi radio station established during the Second World War. It's sole purpose was to shape and influence Irish public opinion in favour of the Nazis. In this episode I am joined by William Quinlan, the winner of the Irish History Summit RSR competition. William, a stuident in St Jospeph's College Borrisoleigh, wrote his R.S.R. (Research Study Report) on Irland Redaktion. In this podcast he details the fascinating story of this little known station, explaining why it was initially broadcast in Irish, what the Nazis hoped to achieve and if it was successful.</description></item><item><title>Getting Dirty in a Digital Archive | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350076/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 04:00:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350076/</guid><description>Podcast Description What did Dublin look like before the authorities demolished the medieval city?&amp;nbsp;
How did Irish people address Queen Victoria during the Famine?
The answers to these questions lie in documents stored in Dublin City Library's archives which chronicles 800 years of life in the city. Until now the only way to access the archive and it's fascinating stories was to go in person to Pearse Street Library.&amp;nbsp;
That is all about to change.</description></item><item><title>A Human History of Forests and Woodlands in Ireland | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350077/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 05:00:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Its National Tree Week! In this special episode brought to you by Wolfgang Reforest, I investigate the history of Ireland's woodlands and forests. The show begins by looking what an actual native Irish woodland because woodlands and forests looked very different in the past. Then we embark on a journery through 12,500 years of our history. From the distant past when 80% of the island was covered with forests through to the 1920s when there was scarcely a single tree in the Irish landscape, the story of our woodlands and forests is interwoven with the history of humans on the island.</description></item><item><title>'Riding the Lartigue' Ireland's only Monorail | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350078/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 05:00:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350078/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1888 Ireland's most unusual railway, the Lartigue monorail, opened for business. Although largely forgotten, the story of this unique train is intriguing. Operating between the 1880s and the 1920s, it carried everything from tourists to livestock.
This show (recorded in Listowel, Co Kerry) explains how this train inspired by camels in the Sahara went onto support an early form of mass tourism in the west of Ireland.&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>Grace O'Malley, an Irish 'Pirate Queen' | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350079/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 05:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Grace O'Malley or Granuaile is an iconic name in Irish history. Born in 1530, she emerged as a powerful leader in the West of Ireland in ruthless and violent era as the Tudor reconquest of the Island was in full swing. Grace is often called a pirate queen, a chieftain or even in some tellings&amp;nbsp;a queen of the west. In this episode I interview her biographer Anne Chambers about the real woman and her remarkable life.</description></item><item><title>The War of Independence Finale (Endgame III) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350080/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 05:00:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350080/</guid><description>Podcast Description We've made it! This is the final episode in the War of Independence series. The episode begins as Michael Collins and an Irish negotiating team lock horns with Lloyd George and Winston Churchill in London. When a controversial treaty is agreed we return to Dublin to see how it is received. The show also includes extensive recreations of the famous Treaty debates from Aidan and Therese.
I hope you enjoy the show.</description></item><item><title>Endgame II | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350081/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 05:00:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350081/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the second last episode in the War of Independence series. In this podcast we travel to Belfast in the summer of 1921. Despite major violence, the city was preparing for what was only its third visit from a reigning monarch since 1690.
With George V due to arrive on June 22nd over 10,000 troops&amp;nbsp;were drafted into Belfast in a massive security operation. What unfolded was unquestionably the most significant royal visit to Ireland since the 17th century.</description></item><item><title>Endgame Part I | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350082/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350082/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the first of three episodes which will be released over the next 8 days to conclude the War of Independence Series. Endgame I is a fast moving show that takes you back to Cork in the opening weeks of 1921. The war develops a new ferocity with the declaration of martial law. The episode is based around one of the enduring controversies of the war - the kidnapping of the widow Maria Lindsay.</description></item><item><title>From Kerry to Antarctica - The Life of Tom Crean | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350083/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 05:00:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tom Crean was born outside Anascaul, Co. Kerry in 1877. One of eleven children from a small farming family, Crean grew up in a world where Antarctica was still a largely unknown continent.
Although overlooked by history, Crean went on to become one of the most distinguished Antarctic explorers of his age. Over the course of his life he would play a key role in several attempts to reach the South Pole.</description></item><item><title>Radio News from Black 47 | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350084/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 05:00:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Imagine radio had existed during the Great Famine. What would it sound like if you could go to an archive and listen to news reports from 1847?
To mark the 150th Anniversary of the Great Hunger in 1997, BBC Merseyside created news reports as if their journalists were reporting live from 1847. With the permission of BBC Merseyside I am delighted to share some of these reports with you in this special episode.</description></item><item><title>Nixie Boran - An Underground Rebel | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350085/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 05:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350085/</guid><description>Podcast Description The life of Nicholas Boran was extraordinary. Known as 'Nixie', he was born outside Castlecomer in Co Kilkenny in 1904. At the age of 18 he fought in the Civil War alongside Dan Breen in Tipperary. The harrowing violence he witnessed in the conflict permanently scarred him and challenges the romanticised myths that often surround the life of Dan Breen. While this had an enduring legacy, Nixie would gain a national reputation for his actions following the Civil War.</description></item><item><title>Inside the Vault - Behind the Scenes in the National Museum | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350086/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 05:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350086/</guid><description>Podcast Description One of the most important buildings in terms of Irish history or archaeology is located in North County Dublin. Strange as it may sound, this building is not very old. It actually only dates from the later 20th century and it was originally an electronics factory.&amp;nbsp;
However it is now owned by the National Museum of Ireland and houses millions of artifacts amassed over the decades.&amp;nbsp;This fascinating complex, which measures over 200,000 sq feet, is not open to the public.</description></item><item><title>The Mary Celeste of Medieval Ireland | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350087/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 05:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350087/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Mary Celeste is one of the great mysteries of modern times. The ship was found abandoned in the Atlantic in 1872 and the ten people who had been onboard the vessel were missing. However everything else appeared normal. It has never been satisfactorily explained what provoked the crew to abandon the ship in mid winter far from any coast.
This episode is recorded in a very Irish unusual castle with echoes of the Mary Celeste - Ballymoon Castle.</description></item><item><title>The Ladies of Llangollen | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350088/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 05:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350088/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Irish women Eleanor Butler and Sarah Ponsonby are known to history as the Ladies of Llangollen. In 1780 the two aristocrats caused controversy when they rang away together. They would spend the rest of their lives in Llangollen, a town in north Wales.
For nearly 250 years their relationship has been the source of intense speculation. Some claim they were&amp;nbsp;Ireland’s first openly lesbian couple. Others insist they just kindred spirits.</description></item><item><title>Growing up Black &amp; Irish - A personal history of Liverpool | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350089/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 05:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last month I recorded a show at the Liverpool Irish Festival with Teresa Hill. Teresa is really passionate about her fascinating family history. Her father from was from Freetown in Sierra Leone while her mother's family were from Ireland.&amp;nbsp;
In this interview Teresa spoke candidly about her life. She grew up in a Liverpool where racism was common and many Irish families ostracised mixed race family members. However her grandfather Luke Bernard was very different as Teresa explains he was 'a forward thinking man'.</description></item><item><title>Reprisals, Concentration Camps or ‘Indian measures’ - British paths to victory in 1921? (The War of Independence Part XXII) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350090/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 05:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Following on from the collapse of the Clune Peace talks in December 1920, the British Government adopted an even more aggressive attitude to the war.&amp;nbsp;
However as they prepared to escalate the conflict in 1921 some leading figures in the British military and political establishment suggested extreme measures. This episode reveals what were deeply alarming debates taking place about how the war should be escalated.
To this end we hear from men who would go on to become some of the most famous British generals of the 20th century - Bernard Montgomery and Arthur Percival both of whom served in Ireland in 1921.</description></item><item><title>Peace, Partition &amp; Christmas 1920 (The War of Independence Part XXI) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350091/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over the last three episodes of the War of Independence Series, we saw the Republican movement demonstrate an ability and willingness to fight on despite recent setbacks. This episode looks at how the British authorities reacted to these developments. While the immediate reaction was to declare martial law across the South West, there was also murmurings of peace.
While indirect talks between republican leaders and the British Authorities started in early December these faced huge challenges.</description></item><item><title>The Irish History Summit January 2022 – Cultivating Ireland’s Historians of the Future | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350092/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350092/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Irish History Summit returns! Taking place on Saturday January 15th 2022 we have a great line up of historians and educational experts to prepare students for the Leaving Cert history exams. Headlining this year is the journalist and historian Leo Enright. He will be joined by Dr Sarah Anne Buckley, Dr Brian Hanley and Liz Gillis. We are also delighted to welcome our first international guest - Dr Dieter Reinisch from the University of Vienna.</description></item><item><title>The Kilmichael Ambush &amp; the Burning of Cork (The War of Independence XX) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350093/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kilmichael is remembered as one of the most important and controversial battles in the War of Independence. This episodes explains what actually happened in this remote valley in Cork in late November 1920.&amp;nbsp;
The podcast also continues the wider story of the war through one of the most turbulent periods of the conflict. Beginning with dramatic attacks in Liverpool, the shows carries the story through to the burning of Cork City in mid December.</description></item><item><title>Bloody Sunday (The War of Independence part XIX) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350094/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350094/</guid><description>Podcast Description November 21st, 1920 was one of the most violent days in the War of Independence. It has gone down in history as 'Bloody Sunday'. While this episode explains the days events, it also introduces the man who was arguably the most important republican in the conflict - the IRA director of Intelligence, Michael Collins.
Get your tickets for my live show in Kikenny November 6th https://www.eventbrite.com/e/irish-history-podcast-live-show-tickets-190958380657 or historyshow.eventbrite.com</description></item><item><title>The Fernside Raid &amp; the Execution of Kevin Barry (The War of Independence XVIII) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350095/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350095/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the first of three back-to-back episodes that will take us through one of the most critical periods of the war. The Autumn of 1920 witnessed an intensification of the conflict as&amp;nbsp;British Crown forces began to get the upper hand on the IRA. This lead to two key events in Dublin - the Fernside Raid &amp;amp; the Execution of Kevin Barry.&amp;nbsp;While these set the stage for the pivotal events of Bloody Sunday, the Fernside Raid and the bloody gun battles that followed were a key moment in the war.</description></item><item><title>The IRA Campaign in Britain (The War of Independence Part XVII) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350096/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Although frequently overlooked, the IRA and the wider republican movement in Britain played an important role during the War of Independence. While they were actively involved in gun running and several high profile jail breaks, their operations included some of the most controversial IRA actions during the war.
In this episode I interview Sam McGrath on the IRA campaign in Britain. Sam, who has been working on the series has also conducted in-depth research into the IRA in Britain, particularly Manchester.</description></item><item><title>Revolutionary Justice (The War of Independence Part XVI) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350097/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350097/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode introduces two forgotten but remarkable revolutionaries -&amp;nbsp;Margaret and Rose Quinn. These two sisters operated a secret IRA prison from their home in a Dublin suburb. This was part of wider attempts to solve the problem of growing lawlessness in Ireland by the summer of 1920.
As British authority disintegrated in rural areas someone had to maintain law and order. This would see a revolutionary justice system established, however it raised fundamental questions for the revolutionaries - where did crime end and revolutionary activity begin.</description></item><item><title>The War of Independence (Part XV) - Daily Life during the War | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350098/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350098/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a break of three months, the War of Independence Series finally returns! This episode takes you back to Ireland in the grip of war in 1920. Given it has been a while since the last War of Independence episode, this show eases you back into the story.&amp;nbsp;
Rather than recap previously covered material, the show looks at what wider life was like for those not directly involved in the conflict.</description></item><item><title>Human Skulls and Pagan Idols - The story of a sacred bog | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350099/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Until recently few people had heard of Gortnacranagh in Co Roscommon. Then, in early August, archaeologists announced they had made startling discoveries during an excavation of what appears to have been a prehistoric sacred bog in the area.&amp;nbsp;
These included a large wooden pagan idol, human bones and animal depositions. While post excavation analysis has yet to be completed,&amp;nbsp;Dr Eve Campbell, who lead the dig, joins me for an exclusive interview.</description></item><item><title>History off the beaten track - Ireland's top heritage sites (you've never heard of) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350100/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ireland has literally thousands of amazing historic and archaeological sites that stretch back thousands of years. Many of the best of these are off the beaten track and do not feature on tourist trails.
A few weeks ago archaeologist Neil Jackman took me to one of these - the vast sprawling ruins of Athassel priory in South Tipperary. In a wide ranging interview, Neil explained the history of this 800 year old building.</description></item><item><title>Passage East - A Medieval D-Day on Ireland's Omaha beach | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350101/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do beaches have a history? They very rarely feature in history books, however some of the most important chapters in our past began on beaches.
This episode was recorded at Passage East in Co Waterford. This beach is arguably one of the most important historic landscapes on the island. The Norman Invasion began here as both Strongbow and Henry II made landfall at Passage East.
In this episode I look at the history of beaches, why they are often overlooked by historians and the fascainting story of how the Norman Invasion began at Passage East .</description></item><item><title>The History of the Knights Templar in Ireland | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350102/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350102/</guid><description>Podcast Description You've probably heard of the Knights but did you know they had a long history in Ireland lasting nearly two centuries?
In this podcast I interview Maeve Callan, an expert on the history of the Templars in Ireland. Maeve details this intriguing story from their first arrival in the early 12th century through to their dramatic and sensational downfall in the early 14th century.
This is part of a much longer interview available for listeners who sign up on Acast+.</description></item><item><title>Kylemore Abbey - Life in a Victorian Mansion in Connemara | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350103/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350103/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode you will step back a century to experience life in a Victorian mansion.
Kylemore Abbey is a stunning mansion located in the wilds of Connemara in the West of Ireland. While it hugs the shoreline of the remote Pollacappul lake, this stately home could rival any great house in Ireland. With over seventy rooms including a ballroom, the house frequently entertained high profile visitors from England.</description></item><item><title>Sieges, Luxury and Servitude - A Day in a 500 Year Old Castle | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350104/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350104/</guid><description>Podcast Description What was it like to it live in a castle? Were they luxurious? How similar were they to modern houses?&amp;nbsp;
Last week I visited Clara Castle and recorded an episode inside this 500 year old building. From&amp;nbsp;toilets to secret chambers - castle living is not what we often think it was.&amp;nbsp;
Tune in to find out more...
Copies of my book Life in Medieval Ireland are available here https://irishhistory.</description></item><item><title>The Black Death vs Covid-19: A Social History of the Pandemic | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350105/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350105/</guid><description>Podcast Description 673 years ago in Kilkenny, a Franciscan Friar John Clyn wrote one of the most famous accounts of the Black Death in Ireland. In this episode I am joined by D.J. Walsh and Eoin Tabb, the hosts of the podcast Snugcast, to see how this account shapes up against our experiences of the Black Death.&amp;nbsp;
While the Black Death was far more deadly, some of our reactions to Covid-19 are surprisingly similar to how our medieval ancestors reacted to the plague.</description></item><item><title>5000 Year Old Tombs, Writers Block &amp; Graveyards of Inspiration | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350106/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350106/</guid><description>Podcast Description I have writers block again, so I went on a hunt for inspiration in historic locations around Kilkenny. I ended up at a tomb that's over 5,000 years old where our ancestors did very very strange things....
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts
Patreon www.patreon.com/irishpodcast
Acast https://plus.acast.com/s/irishhistory
📢June 2023 Update - New Walking Tour 📢
I am thrilled to announce my brand new walking tour in Ireland's oldest city, Waterford.</description></item><item><title>Terence MacSwiney's Hunger-Strike (The War of Independence XIV) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350107/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Through 1920 Terence MacSwiney became the most well known Irish republican across the world. Elected as Lord Mayor of Cork in March, he was arrested in August and began the longest hunger-strike in Irish history at the time.&amp;nbsp;The story of this battle of wills between MacSwiney and the British Authorities proved a crucial moment in the war and is an extraordinary story.
Additional research was by the archivist and historian Sam McGrath, sound was by Jason Looney, additional narrations are by Aidan Crowe and Therese Murray and the artwork for the series is by Keith Hynes.</description></item><item><title>The Rebel County (the War of independence Part XIII) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350108/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cork is known as the rebel county. From late 1919 it earned this adage as some of the most bitter fighting in the War of Independence took place in Cork city and county.&amp;nbsp;This episode begins with the story of Eilis MacCurtain whose husband Tomas was Cork's first republican Lord Mayor and the Commander of the Cork No.1 Brigade of the IRA.&amp;nbsp;
In the second part of the show we head to West Cork and the mountainous terrain of the Beara Peninsula where the crown forces faced relentless opposition from the republican movement.</description></item><item><title>Belfast, Derry &amp; The War in the North (the War of Independence XII) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350109/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350109/</guid><description>Podcast Description The story of the War of Independence in the North of Ireland is often overlooked. This obscures the fact that Belfast was the most violent place in Ireland during the conflict. However it was a very different war when compared to the experience of other parts of the island.&amp;nbsp;
This podcast explains the war in the north and why, contrary to popular misconceptions, the IRA were not the force they were elsewhere.</description></item><item><title>Women &amp; the Irish Revolution - The War of Independence Part XI | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350110/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350110/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the latest installment of the War of Independence series I am joined by historian Liz Gills to talk about women and the Irish revolution. While numerous Irish women from revolutionaries to unionists have been covered in the series to date, in this fascinating interview, Liz provides wider context to their involvement in the conflict.
She explains how women were pivotal in establishing Ireland’s revolutionary movement and how many women although often overlooked in later histories played essential roles in the conflict.</description></item><item><title>The IRA on the Offensive - Easter 1920 (the War of Independence Part X) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350111/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350111/</guid><description>Podcast Description As Easter approached in 1920 many politicians in Britain feared a major uprising in Ireland along the lines of the 1916 Rising. While the IRA had a major operation planned it was one that took the authorities off guard. Indeed the Spring of 1920 saw a surge in republican activity as prisoners across Ireland and Britain went on hunger strike which in turn lead to a general strike. Meanwhile the scale of individual IRA attacks increased.</description></item><item><title>An Empire in Crisis (The War of Independence Part IX) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350112/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350112/</guid><description>Podcast Description To date the War of Independence series has focused largely on the republican movement. This episode however looks at how the British government and their representatives in Ireland viewed the conflict.&amp;nbsp;
While the show follows those in the highest office in the land, this is&amp;nbsp;not stuffy office politics. By December 1919 the IRA were preparing an attack on the most powerful British figure on the island - the Viceroy - Lord John French.</description></item><item><title>The Fermoy Army Riots (The War of Independence VIII) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350113/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350113/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode we move south to the Cork town of Fermoy. While most clashes in the war to date have seen the IRA pitted against police constables, this episode will see British Army soldiers enter the fray. These battle hardened veterans from the First World War pose a very different threat to Royal Irish Constabulary.&amp;nbsp;The show also introduces some famous figures including Liam Lynch arguably one of the most influential IRA commander during the war and also Winston Churchill.</description></item><item><title>The Knocklong Ambush (The War of Independence Part VII) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350114/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350114/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode returns to the story of Seumus Robinson, Dan Breen, Sean Hogan and Sean Treacy. Known as the Big Four, these IRA volunteers had come to prominence after playing a leading role in the Soloheadbeg Ambush often considered the opening shots of the war.&amp;nbsp;After five months on the run, the police captured Sean Hogan. Given the eighteen year old almost certainly faced a death sentence, Robinson, Breen and Treacy resolved to free him.</description></item><item><title>The Podcast Has Run Aground in The Suez Canal | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350115/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 07:22:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350115/</guid><description>Podcast Description There was no episode this week and here's why....
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts
Patreon www.patreon.com/irishpodcast
Acast https://plus.acast.com/s/irishhistory
📢June 2023 Update - New Walking Tour 📢
I am thrilled to announce my brand new walking tour in Ireland's oldest city, Waterford. Join me and explore 1,000 years of history from the Vikings to Cromwell &amp;amp; Strongbow to the Irish Revolution.&amp;nbsp; Enhanced by wireless headsets 🎧 you will hear the sounds of the city through the ages and the words of the people who made history in Waterford.</description></item><item><title>The Limerick Soviet and The Russian Revolution (The War of Independence VI) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350116/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350116/</guid><description>Podcast Description *There was an audio issue on an early version of this episode. This was resolved and a new issue was uploaded on Monday 15 March at 21:00 - Fin*.
In April 1919 the focus of the War of Independence shifted to the city of Limerick. In response to an IRA raid, the British Army effectively besieged the city for over a week leading trade unions to launch a general strike.</description></item><item><title>The Escape from Lincoln Jail (The War of Independence V) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350117/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last weeks episode looked at the story of the Soloheadbeg Ambush, often considered the opening shots of the war. A few weeks later one of the most audacious IRA operations of the entire war took place in England. This saw three high profile republican prisoners attempt a daring escape from Lincoln Jail . Following on from the Soloheadbeg ambush if successful it would serve as&amp;nbsp;a stunning propaganda coup for the republican movement.</description></item><item><title>The Soloheadbeg Ambush &amp; the First Dáil (the War of Independence IV) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350118/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350118/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the latest installment of the War of Independence series we look at the famous 1918 election from the perspective of a forgotten Sligo woman Sarah Garvey who started a riot on election day!&amp;nbsp;
The results of this election lead to the historic meeting of the first independent Irish parliament - the Dáil.&amp;nbsp;
Then to conclude the episode we travel to rural Tipperary, and a place called Soloheadbeg. On January 21st 1919 members of the Irish Volunteers ambush by a convoy of explosives - an action widely considered to be the opening shots of the war.</description></item><item><title>The Road to War (The War of Independence III) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350119/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350119/</guid><description>Podcast Description An ambush at Soloheadbeg, Tipperary in January 1919 is often cited as the opening shots of the War of Independence. However as early as 1917 political tensions were leading to violence across Ireland. Several people were killed in 1917 and 1918. This podcast looks at this descent into war.&amp;nbsp;
The episode is based around the story of Edward Murray, a young Dubliner who played a key role in these events.</description></item><item><title>The 1916 Rising (The War of Independence Part II) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350120/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350120/</guid><description>Podcast Description The story of the War of Independence continues with the 1916 Rising. The&amp;nbsp;episode begins by looking at the how the revolt unfolded and explains why it was limited to Dublin. It then follows the rebels into captivity in the famous prison camp of Frongach in Wales. The second half of the show turns to the legacy of the Rising. The dramatic transformation of attitudes towards militant republicanism is revealed by focusing on the experiences of the most unlikely of rebels - Countess Markievicz.</description></item><item><title>The Irish War of Independence Part I - World War I | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350121/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350121/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the first episode in a 24 part series on the War of Independence. Today's show focuses on the First World War and how it destablised Irish society, following the lives of several people in one Irish town - Castlecomer, Co Kilkenny (where I grew up). It includes never before published letters from soldiers at the Front and accounts from life back in Ireland at the time. The episode also reveals how the legacy of the Famine, the Land War and growing labour unrest were adding to growing tensions in the country.</description></item><item><title>(Part III) The Triangle Shirtwaist Fire of 1911: An Emigrant's Experience | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350122/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350122/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Triangle Shirtwaist Fire of 1911 was pivotal moment in US history. The deadly workplace disaster in the heart of Manhattan detailed in the last two episodes, exposed the way many poor immigrants were exploited in the city. This podcast, the third and final installment in the series, looks at the profound legacy of the fire. Following the later lives of the two immigrants featured in the series, Annie Doherty&amp;nbsp;&amp;amp; Celia Walker, the podcast explores how the fire changed New York and the lives of the survivors.</description></item><item><title>(Part II) The Triangle Shirtwaist Fire of 1911: An Emigrant's Experience | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350123/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 05:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350123/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the second episode in the miniseries on the Triangle Shirtwaist Fire of 1911. Its worth checking out episode 1 before listening to this show. In the first installment of this series, we chronicled the lives of Annie Doherty&amp;nbsp;&amp;amp; Celia Walker and the often grueling experience of emigrants to the USA at the turn of the 20th Century.&amp;nbsp;This podcast follows these two women into one of the most deadly sweatshops in New York in 1911 - the Triangle Shirtwaist Factory.</description></item><item><title>The Triangle Shirtwaist Fire of 1911: An Emigrant's Experience | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350124/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350124/</guid><description>Podcast Description On March 25th 1911 a fire ripped through a sweatshop in Lower Manhattan where hundreds of immigrants worked long hours in dangerous conditions. The Triangle Shirtwaist Factory Fire would prove a pivotal moment not only in the history of New York but also the United States.&amp;nbsp;This podcast, the first of three episodes on the fire, looks at the early lives of two women Annie Doherty and Celia Walker who worked in the factory.</description></item><item><title>The War of Independence | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350125/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Through 2021 the podcast will be focusing on the story of the Irish War of Independence. It starts on February 1st but check out this short podcast to find out what you can expect...
www.twitter.com/irishhistory
www.instagram.com/irishhistory
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts
Patreon www.patreon.com/irishpodcast
Acast https://plus.acast.com/s/irishhistory
📢June 2023 Update - New Walking Tour 📢
I am thrilled to announce my brand new walking tour in Ireland's oldest city, Waterford.</description></item><item><title>John Charles McQuaid - A Ghost of Our Catholic Past | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350126/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 05:00:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Through the mid 20th century John Charles McQuaid, the archbishop of Dublin was one of the most influential people in Ireland. McQuaid has come to symbolise not only the power of the Catholic Church at the time but also for many the abuse of that power. He exerted huge influence over successive Irish governments and was also in a position to censor what films and literature Irish people had access to.</description></item><item><title>A History of the Police in Ireland | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350127/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350127/</guid><description>Podcast Description One of the first major challenges facing the Irish government after Independence in 1922 was how to police the country. The Royal Irish Constabulary which had existed under British rule was a highly discredited force so they established the Civic Guard which later developed into An Garda Síochána.&amp;nbsp;In this episode, I interview Dr Vicky Conway who reveals the complex history of An Garda Síochána from its early years when a mutiny rocked the force through to the Troubles.</description></item><item><title>The Forgotten Lives of the Women of Cahir | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350128/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 05:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350128/</guid><description>Podcast Description Women are all too often overlooked in history. The Daughters of Dun Iascaigh, written by the Cahir Womens History Group, addresses this imbalance by profiling the lives of over 20 women from this Tipperary town. The book highlights some fascinating but previously overlooked stories.&amp;nbsp;In this podcast I interview three contributors Josephine O'Neill, Maurice Casey and Annette Condon who reveal intriguing stories about rebels, nuns and revolutionaries from Cahir in the last century.</description></item><item><title>The Lepers’ Plot - A Medieval Conspiracy Theory | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350129/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 05:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350129/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conspiracy theories seem more popular than ever. Increasing numbers of people are turning to what are unorthodox understandings of the world. This is not a new phenomemum. In this episode I examine the Lepers Plot, one of the more bizarre chapters in medieval history. In 1321 the Kingdom of France was gripped by rumours lepers were plotting a coup. This had deadly consequences as you are about to hear.</description></item><item><title>The Irish History Summit 2021 – Calling LC History Teachers. | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350130/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350130/</guid><description>Podcast Description The first Irish History Summit takes place on January 19th 2021. The summit is an exclusive one day online event where leading Irish Historians will present talks on the Leaving Cert history curriculum. While the summit will be a great advantage for students sitting the taking Leavin Cert History Exams in 2021 the summit will appeal to anyone with a love of Irish History.
www.historysummit.eventbrite.com
Become a member at https://plus.</description></item><item><title>The Road to Oldcroghan #6 - An Afterlife | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350131/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350131/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's very human to wonder how we will be remembered. However few have a legacy like that of the victim from Oldcroghan. It was certainly one neither he nor his contemporaries could have envisaged.
Sound by Jason Looney
Artwork by Keith Hynes
Visit the National Museum - https://www.museum.ie/
Check out the shop - www.irishhistorypodcast.ie
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts
Patreon www.patreon.com/irishpodcast
Acast https://plus.acast.com/s/irishhistory
📢June 2023 Update - New Walking Tour 📢</description></item><item><title>The Road to Oldcroghan #5 Sacrifice | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350132/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350132/</guid><description>Podcast Description Several theories have been forwarded to explain the brutal murder that came to light in a bog at Oldcroghan in 2003.&amp;nbsp;Through meticulous research, the former Keeper of Antiquities in the National Museum of Ireland Eamon Kelly has developed the most convincing explanation. In this episode he reveals who exactly the victim was and why he died.
Sound by Jason Looney
Artwork by Keith Hynes
Check out the shop - www.</description></item><item><title>The Road to Oldcroghan #4 The Crime Scene | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350133/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350133/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode we return to the the scene of the crime Clonearl bog in Croghan where the body was found. This will help us understand who exactly may have carried out the murder…
Sound by Jason Looney
Artwork by Keith Hynes
Support the show - www.patreon.com/irishpodcast
Check out the shop - www.irishhistorypodcast.ie
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts
Patreon www.patreon.com/irishpodcast
Acast https://plus.acast.com/s/irishhistory
📢June 2023 Update - New Walking Tour 📢</description></item><item><title>The Road to Oldcroghan #3 Tír na nÓg - The Land of Youth | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350134/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bogs are strange places. Their unique properties slow down the process of decay. They not only preserve bodies, but also evidence of what may have happened to them...
Sound by Jason Looney
Artwork by Keith Hynes
Check out the shop - www.irishhistorypodcast.ie
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts
Patreon www.patreon.com/irishpodcast
Acast https://plus.acast.com/s/irishhistory
📢June 2023 Update - New Walking Tour 📢
I am thrilled to announce my brand new walking tour in Ireland's oldest city, Waterford.</description></item><item><title>The Road to Oldcroghan #2- Identification | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350135/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Marie Cassidy the state pathologist arrives in Croghan to examine the remains of the victim. When Kevin Barry leads her to the corpse she makes a startling discovery.
Sound by Jason Looney
Artwork by Keith Hynes
Support the show - www.patreon.com/irishpodcast
Check out the shop - www.irishhistorypodcast.ie
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts
Patreon www.patreon.com/irishpodcast
Acast https://plus.acast.com/s/irishhistory
📢June 2023 Update - New Walking Tour 📢</description></item><item><title>The Road to Oldcroghan #1 - Murder in a Land Time Forgot | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350136/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350136/</guid><description>Podcast Description Croghan, Co Offaly is a remarkable place. The scenery is stunning; the local community are friendly and welcoming. However their future is far from certain - the major employer in the region is closing down. In the midst of this crisis, local people are increasingly talking about a dark chapter in their past, a murder that came to light in 2003.
This is the start of the Road to Oldcroghan….</description></item><item><title>The Road to Oldcroghan Coming October 5th | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350137/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 1 of the Road to Oldcroghan drops on October 5th. Exclusive early access available at patreon.com/irishpodcast.
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts
Patreon www.patreon.com/irishpodcast
Acast https://plus.acast.com/s/irishhistory
📢June 2023 Update - New Walking Tour 📢
I am thrilled to announce my brand new walking tour in Ireland's oldest city, Waterford. Join me and explore 1,000 years of history from the Vikings to Cromwell &amp;amp; Strongbow to the Irish Revolution.</description></item><item><title>Ireland and the Anti Slavery Movement | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350138/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350138/</guid><description>Podcast Description From the 1790s onwards numerous Black anti-slavery activists visited Ireland to build support for the abolition of the slave trade and slavery itself. This would see some of the most famous African Americans in history including Frederick Douglas visit Ireland.&amp;nbsp;I was delighted to interview Christine Kinealy, one of the leading historians of 19th century Ireland, for this episode. She discusses three activists. Alongside Frederick Douglas she also talks about the lives of Equiano Olaudah and Sarah Parker Remond and their experiences in Ireland.</description></item><item><title>An Enduring Graveyard (Part 7) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350139/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Preban cemetery is not only where the communities in the surrounding region bury their dead, but it also has an important place in day to day life for many in the area. In this podcast, the final episode in 'Stories from a Living Graveyard’ Damian and myself look at how the graveyard has been used through the 20th century through to the present day.
The series will be released daily as part of Heritage Week 2020.</description></item><item><title>The Empty Grave - Stories From a Living Graveyard (Part 6) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350140/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350140/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Great Famine haunts every graveyard in Ireland. Alongside victims of the Great Hunger, many graveyards include the names of those who were forced to emigrate. In this podcast we look at how these events affected the communities around Preban.
This episode is the sixth of seven in 'Stories from a Living Graveyard’. The series will be released daily as part of Heritage Week 2020.
Sound by Jason Looney</description></item><item><title>The Big Snow Tragedy - Stories From a Living Graveyard (Part 5) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350141/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Graveyards chronicle the history of the communities where we. At Preban, Co Wicklow one of the most tragic stories is that of the Mulhall family. In this episode local resident Helen Byrne talks about the fate of the Mulhall family, who were killed in an avalanche in the hills above Wicklow a story that was covered across the world at the time.
This episode is the fourth of seven in 'Stories from a Living Graveyard’.</description></item><item><title>The 1798 Rebellion - Stories From a Living Graveyard (Part 4) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350142/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350142/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the summer of 1798 large parts of Ireland were ravaged by one of the largest rebellions in Irish history. Numerous people in communities around Preban marched off to fight alongside the rebels. Some paid a heavy price and their graves can be found in Preban Graveyard. In this episode you will hear the story of the 1798 rebellion and how people from Preban were involved.
This episode is the fourth of seven in 'Stories from a Living Graveyard’.</description></item><item><title>Pilgrimage - Stories From a Living Graveyard (Part 3) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350143/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350143/</guid><description>Podcast Description St Aidan's well is located in the environs Preban graveyard. Rituals have been performed at this holy well for centuries possibly even longer. Although these traditions are now dying out, in this episode we hear the words of the late Maura Carty who can remember pilgrims coming to the well. We also interview Dr Louise Nugent an expert on pilgrimmage and holy sites to hear more about this important archaeological site that links the present community around Preban to their distant ancestors</description></item><item><title>A History Through The Ages at Preban (Stories from a Living Graveyard Part 2) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350144/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350144/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part II of 'Stories from a Living Graveyard’ Damian and myself journey back into the earliest history of Preban. This takes us deep into the medieval period. We follow the story of the graveyard through the late Middle Ages and the religious turmoil that followed the Reformation. We also talk to archaeologist Chris Corlett to hear the fascinating story of the stonemasons who carved some of the outstanding gravestones that still stand in the cemetery today.</description></item><item><title>Preban Graveyard - Stories from a Living Graveyard (Part 1) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350145/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350145/</guid><description>Podcast Description The ancient graveyard of Preban is situated in the southern foothills of the Wicklow Mountains near the picteuresque town of Tinahely. While its history stretches back over 1,000 years, it fell into severe disrepair through the later 20th century. In 2010 local residents in the Preban Graveyard Committee set about cleaning up the cemetery. In the course of their work they discovered incredible stories stretching back thousands of years.</description></item><item><title>Preban: A Living Graveyard | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350146/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 09:08:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350146/</guid><description>Podcast Description This seven part series starting Monday August 17th, explores fascinating stories from a forgotten graveyard. Until 2010 Preban cemetery in Co Wicklow was completely overgrown and largely inaccessible. When the local community set about restoring their graveyard they discovered remarkable personal histories of their ancestors. These incude 1798 rebels, famine emigrants not to mention rock art that stretches back thousands of years. Tune in on Monday to find out more.</description></item><item><title>Divided Loyalties: Letters from World War II | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350147/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350147/</guid><description>Podcast Description During the&amp;nbsp;Second World War Irish Military Intelligence stepped up their activities monitoring potential threats to the Irish state. Their targets included the family of the far right Irish American activist Aileen O’Brien. Through the course of this investigation Irish Military Intelligence collected a unique set of letters that provided a fascinating and unusual insight into this families experience of the Second World War. By 1941 they found their allegiances tested.</description></item><item><title>Irish Farmers Don't Wear Cravats | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350148/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350148/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over the last few weeks I have been paralysed by writers block. In the hope of clearing&amp;nbsp;my mind, I headed off to explore an old stately home. While often crumbling ruins, buildings like this are absorbing places - they were once the houses of the wealthiest people in Ireland in the 18th &amp;amp; 19th century. The building I visited wasn't quite Downton Abbey but in its heyday this mansion was impressive.</description></item><item><title>Irish Spies in World War II | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350149/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 05:34:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350149/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ireland remained neutral in the Second World War. However by the summer of 1940 a German invasion seemed increasingly likely. Having conquered Western Europe the Nazis prepared Operation Sea Lion, an invasion of Britain which would inevitably have led to an invasion of Ireland.&amp;nbsp;
While preparations were made for a defence of the country, Ireland's intelligence community increased their surveillance on potential Nazi collaborators. Chief among these was Eoin O'Duffy who had fought for the fascists in the Spanish Civil War.</description></item><item><title>Could You Survive on a Pre-Famine Irish Diet? I Tried... | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350150/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350150/</guid><description>Podcast Description The diet of the rural poor in Ireland prior to the Famine is one of the most unusual in modern history. Adult males consumed as much as 14lb (6.35kg) of potatoes per day. Last week I tried this diet and in this podcast you find out what happened. The results make this the most unusual podcast I've made.&amp;nbsp;
Regina Sexton, a food historian in University College Cork also explains how people ate these potatoes and what they used to flavour them.</description></item><item><title>Fleeing The War: Basques Refugees in Ireland | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350151/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350151/</guid><description>Podcast Description This show look at a story related to the series Partisans. Its about the life of a Basque family briefly mentioned in that series - the Gallastegis - who moved to Ireland in the aftermath of the bombing of Guernica during the Spanish Civil War.&amp;nbsp;
This show was produced and researched by Ignacio Irigoien and Steward Reddin. I was delighted to be asked to narrate it and I am very grateful to be given permission to share it you now.</description></item><item><title>From Cork to Bermuda: An Irishwoman's Life in the British Army | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350152/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350152/</guid><description>Podcast Description Through the 18th and 19th century, large numbers of Irishmen served in the British Army. However there were also many Irishwomen whose lives were interwoven with the military. While not soldiers they became part of the army through marriage to members of the regiments stationed in Ireland. This lead to unusual and captivating lives.
In this episode I interview historian Dr Aoife Bhreatnach about a Cork woman called Bridget Kent who married a British Army soldier.</description></item><item><title>The Legacy of the Spanish Civil War (Partisans X) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350153/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350153/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the final episode in the series Partisans. While the Spanish Civil War came to an end in 1939 and the Irish returned home for many Spaniards, Basques and Catalans the conflict would not end for decades. To conclude the series I interview the expert Nick Lloyd for his insights into what happened after Franco took power. Nick explains what the Franco's regime was like, who were the winners and losers and how people resisted.</description></item><item><title>The Final Battle &amp; the Mysterious Death of Frank Ryan (Partisans IX) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350154/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 04:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350154/</guid><description>Podcast Description This podcast, the second last in Partisans, looks at the battle of the Ebro - the last major showdown in the Spanish Civil War. While the show looks at how the war ended for the Irish fighters, it also tackles one of the great mysteries of the Spanish Civil War - what happened to Frank Ryan. This intriguing story continues to perplex and divide historians today.
Research - Stewart Reddin</description></item><item><title>Paradise Lost (Partisans VIII) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350155/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350155/</guid><description>Podcast Description The enduring images of the Spanish Civil War depict armed fighters of one kind or another. This podcast, however, follows the story of a different Irish experience - that of Hannah Ormsby, an Irish nurse who arrived in Spain in the summer of 1937. The savagery of the war ensured she would be treated no different than other antifascists. Hannah had to work in appaling conditions often under fire from snipers.</description></item><item><title>The Bombing of Guernica &amp; the War in the North (Partisans VII) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350156/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 04:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350156/</guid><description>Podcast Description The most notorious incident of the Spanish Civil War was the bombing of Guernica by the Nazi Condor Legion. Immortalised by Pablo Picasso's painting it was the first time in world history carpet bombing was deployed against a civilian population. It was part of an overall campaign called 'The War in the North'. This saw General Franco turn his forces agains the antifascist zone along the north coast of Spain.</description></item><item><title>Bleeding for Spain (Partisans VI) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350157/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350157/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode continues Partisans - Irish Stories from the Spanish Civil War. In this podcast we follow the Irish in Spain into battle. The show begins with campaigns in Andalusia and takes you through one of the most famous battles of entire war - Jarama. We will see how the Blueshirts and the Antifascist International Brigaders fared when they faced the realities of war. This includes numerous first hand accounts of these battles.</description></item><item><title>The Blueshirts and the International Brigades (Partisans V) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350158/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 05:23:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350158/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode returns to the series Partisans - Irish stories from the Spanish Civil War. This show looks at the two groups of Irish fighters who traveled to Spain - the Irish Brigade better known as the Blueshirts and the antifascist International Brigades. Over the last eight decades they have been among the most controversial figures of 20th century Irish history. The podcast seperates the fact from fiction looking at who they were, why they traveled and how they got&amp;nbsp;there.</description></item><item><title>Making a Martyr - The Story of Oliver Plunkett | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350159/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350159/</guid><description>Podcast Description St Peter’s Church in Drogheda Co Louth contains what has to be one of the most unsettling religious relics on display anywhere in the world. This is the head of an Irish man - Oliver Plunkett - who was hanged drawn and quartered in London in 1681. For religious catholics, the head of Plunkett, who was later declared a saint, is believed to have supernatural powers and can cure illnesses.</description></item><item><title>Ireland's Deaf Community - A History | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350160/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350160/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Deaf community are rarely mentioned in general histories of Ireland. Prior to making this episode I knew almost nothing about their rich history. In this podcast I interview the historian Cormac Leonard from Trinity College Dublin. Cormac reveals the fascinating history of the Deaf Community in Ireland.
He provides vivid accounts of deaf people struggling against authorities in workhouses and prisons, to those who fought in IRA in the War of Independence.</description></item><item><title>Irish History Quiz: Test Your Knowledge | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350161/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 11:19:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350161/</guid><description>Podcast Description How well do you know your Irish history? Nows the time to find out!
In this podcast, I read out 63 history questions. As I read each question you select the correct answer from five options in the online answer sheet here www.irishhistorypodcast.ie/quiz. Once you submit your answers you will get your score and the correct answers automatically sent your email! The top score so far is 52/63. Can you beat it?</description></item><item><title>1000 Years from Home | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350162/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350162/</guid><description>Podcast Description This show is 40 minutes of escapism from Covid-19. In the podcast I explore some of the history and historic places within two kilometres of my home in Kilkenny. This journey starts in the 19th century and takes you back 1,000 years. You will hear stories from a 19th century mental asylum, visit a medieval hospital, walk down a medieval street, hear the strange story of a dog whose death symbolised an epoch of Irish history and finish with the story of a forgotten hero.</description></item><item><title>A History of Epidemics in Ireland | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350163/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 05:27:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350163/</guid><description>Podcast Description Recently I discovered that my great great grandmother Catherine Murphy lost her sister and her daughter within two days of each other in February 1919 during the Great Flu pandemic. This highlighted how disease has long been part of our history. For this episode I decided to catch up with the historian John Dorney who recently published an article on the history of epidemics in Ireland. You can find John's article on epidemics in Ireland and also his great podcast the Irish History Show at theIrishstory.</description></item><item><title>The History of Coffee Part II (1845-2020) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350164/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350164/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Great Famine, the Sitcom Friends and Prohibition campaigners in 19th century Belfast all have one thing in common –&amp;nbsp;in some way shape or form influenced the popularity of coffee in Ireland. This podcast which continues the story of coffee in Ireland revealing how modern Irish coffee culture is nothing new.&amp;nbsp;Indeed your great grandparents may well have enjoyed take away coffee as much as you do.
This show also includes a fascinating interview with Dr Órfhlaith Campbell on Ireland's first coffee chain in the later 19th century!</description></item><item><title>ONLINE IRISH HISTORY QUIZ NIGHT | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350165/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 08:10:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350165/</guid><description>Podcast Description Calling Irish History Fans!
Test your knowledge against listeners from across the world on April 11th. I will be hosting an online history table quiz on YouTube. Listeners from the US, Canada, the UK &amp;amp; Irleand have already signed up so global bragging rights are on offer!
Registration is free but essential at historyquiz.eventbrite.com
While the quiz is free but I am urging participants to donate to the Mater Foundation https://www.</description></item><item><title>The History of Coffee Part I (1000-1845) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350166/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350166/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Irish coffee industry generates hundreds of million of euros every year. This is a pretty recent development - when I was growing up in the 1980s and 1990s the only coffee available was instant coffee.&amp;nbsp;
However Ireland's relationship with coffee did not begin in the last 20 years. If anything this is the second or even third wave of coffee culture to hit this country. In this show I Iook at the early history of coffee tracing the origins of the drink in Ireland back to the 17th century</description></item><item><title>Preparing for a Pandemic in 1900 | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350167/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 08:52:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350167/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are all taking precautionary measures to avoid Covid-19, but this is not the first time humans have faced such threats. This short episode looks at the story of the humorous but frantic preparations that took place in 1900 when Ireland faced an potential outbreak of bubonic plague.
Its will sound strangely familiar!
The next episode of the podcast is part I of the Irish history of coffee. Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts</description></item><item><title>Voices from a Vanishing World - The Aran Islands 1901 | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350168/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350168/</guid><description>Podcast Description Between 1898 and 1902, the Irish playwright John Millington Synge spent several summers on the Aran Islands. Shaped by the harsh environment of the North Atlantic Ocean the islanders lived in a unique society. Old customs and traditions that had died in many parts of Ireland still survived on the islands.&amp;nbsp;
Synge left a mesmerising account of island life and this podcast transports you back to the summer of 1901.</description></item><item><title>Murder Will Out - A Land to Die For (Part II) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350169/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350169/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the last episode (A Land to Die For Part I) we followed the story of William Sheehan. Raised in a community obsessed with land he had become involved in a violent dispute over his family farm after his eviction in 1882. By late 1883 Sheehan, wanting a fresh start, had emigrated to New Zealand. However he could not escape his violent past. Within months of his arrival news reached New Zealand he was wanted for murder in Ireland</description></item><item><title>A Land to Die For (Part I) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350170/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 04:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350170/</guid><description>Podcast Description Land has been the cause of some of the most vicious feuds and brutal murders in modern irish history. Often portrayed as the poor tenant farmer against powerful landlords, the real stories were often more complex. In a society where people developed what was an unhealthy obsession with land there were all too many willing to kill friends family and neighbours over it.&amp;nbsp;
The sentiments which fuelled this were epitomised in John B Keane play and later an Oscar nominated movie The Field, where the central the Bull McCabe who commits murders over land says&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>Dublin 1916: The Calm Before the Storm | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350171/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350171/</guid><description>Podcast Description The year 1916 is known for one event in Irish history – the Easter Rising. However as that fateful weekend approached most Dubliners were oblivious to the fact that their city stood on the threshold of history. This podcast focuses on three of those&amp;nbsp;Dubliners, and takes look around their city on the eve of the rising, revealing what the city looked like, sounded like and even smelled like!</description></item><item><title>Nazi Loot &amp; Soviet Spies - Ireland in the Summer of '63 | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350172/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350172/</guid><description>Podcast Description This podcast transports you back to Ireland during the summer of 1963. This was a fascinating time; JFK visited Ireland, 1% of the population were priests or nuns and instead of downloading Tinder you found love in the classifieds of a newspaper! Rumours of hidden Nazi treausre from World War II was headline news while a Third World War with the Soviet Union seemed imminent.
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts</description></item><item><title>On the Lash! A History of Drinking in Ireland | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350173/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 06:10:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350173/</guid><description>Podcast Description First built in 1582, the Hole in the Wall pub in Kilkenny was the perfect location to record this episode. I was joined by DJ Walsh of the podcast Snugcast and we looked at the history of drinking in Ireland.&amp;nbsp;
Starting in the late Middle Ages, this podcast is a whistlestop tour through Irish drinking habits over 800 years. Myself and DJ talk about what Irish people drink and how this has changed.</description></item><item><title>Dunmore Cave &amp; Viking Massacres: A History From The Underworld | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350174/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350174/</guid><description>Podcast Description This history of Dunmore cave is mysterious and gripping. Around the year 930 the Vikings massacred large numbers of people in a battle fought around the cave. By the 18th century some of the earliest explorers found large numbers of human remains scattered across this extensive tunnel system. While this may be evidence of a brutal Viking massacre, recent archaeological excavations and analysis have suggested the full story may be more complex.</description></item><item><title>I Need Your Advice! | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350175/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350175/</guid><description>Podcast Description I have exciting plans for 2020. Amongst other things I will be starting a major series on the Irish War of Independence. However I need your advice on what shape this wil. Tune in to find out whats coming up in the next few months and how you can help me design this new series.
www.irishhistorypodcast.ie/survey
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts
Patreon www.patreon.com/irishpodcast
Acast https://plus.</description></item><item><title>The Rise and Fall of Carrickmines Castle | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350176/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350176/</guid><description>Podcast Description When creating episodes I normally try to tell wider events in Irish history by focusing on the lives of an individual person. This podcast takes a different approach. I interview Dr Mark Clinton about the history of one specific place - Carrickmines Castle. Mark lead the excavations that unearthed the ruins of the castle destroyed in the 17th century.
By focusing on this castle we were able to have a wide ranging conversation that covers centuries of history.</description></item><item><title>An Irish Rebel in Spain (The War Begins) Partisans #4 | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350177/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 06:59:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350177/</guid><description>Podcast Description In July 1936 Peadar O'Donnell, a veteran of the Irish war of Independence and civil war travelled to Spain on holiday. He was among those caught up in the opening stages of the Spanish Civil War. He witnessed the chaotic opening phase of the conflict providing gripping eye witness detail. As this podcast reveals O'Donnell was in Barcelona and was both inspired and horrified by what he saw. The city was convulsed by an attempted coup, a socialist revolution and extreme anticlerical violence all within one week!</description></item><item><title>The Irish Communist Partisan (Partisans #3) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350178/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 06:25:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350178/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode we continue the story of the Irish people who fought in the Spanish Civil War. Our focus turns to the life of Bob Doyle. A member of the IRA and later a communist his life explains why people went on to fight against fascism in Spain. Beginning with his early childhood set to the backdrop of grinding poverty in Dublin slums, the podcast is an evocative and fascinating journey through one family's experience of the struggle for Irish Independence and the decades that followed.</description></item><item><title>The Irish Fascist Partisan (Partisans #2) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350179/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 06:30:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350179/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the second episode in the series Partisans - Irish Stories from the Spanish Civil War. In this podcast we meet our first partisan Aileen O'Brien, a 22 year old Irish American who moved to Ireland in 1935. O'Brien was always a mysterious figure - her contemporaries were never quite sure what to make of her. Some considered her a fascist, others thought her a naive catholic while intelligence agenices suspected&amp;nbsp;she may have been a covert arms dealer.</description></item><item><title>Partisans#1 The Long Road to Stalingrad: The Origins of the Spanish Civil War | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350180/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 06:14:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350180/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the first episode of Partisans, a new weekly series created by myself and Stewart Reddin. While the series focuses on the experiences of Irish people in the Spanish Civil War, this episode sets the scene. It explains the backdrop of the Spanish Civil War, the crisis that consumed Spanish politics in the 1930s and the far reaching implications of that conflict not least for people in Ireland.</description></item><item><title>Rescuing History: The Four Courts Explosion | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350181/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 07:46:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350181/</guid><description>Podcast Description This bonus show looks at a famous event that haunts Irish history - the Four Courts Explosion. In June 1922 during the opening phase of the Irish Civil War, the Public Records Office was destroyed in a massive explosion that rocked Dublin City Centre. Several centuries of Irish historical records had been stored in the building, most of which were incinerated. In this episode I explain the background to the explosion and what was lost.</description></item><item><title>The Partisans Are Coming! | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350182/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 06:45:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350182/</guid><description>Podcast Description On November the 18th my new podcast series 'Partisans' begins. Created by mysef and Stewart Reddin it looks at the fascinating stories of Irish people who fought in Spanish Civil War. Tune in to find out more...
Thanks to Keith Hynes for the Artwork
Badges available at www.irishhistorypodcast.ie/shop
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts
Patreon www.patreon.com/irishpodcast
Acast https://plus.acast.com/s/irishhistory
📢June 2023 Update - New Walking Tour 📢</description></item><item><title>The Mater Hospital: Where History is Made | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350183/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 06:32:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350183/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Mater Hospital in Dublin first opened its doors in 1861. It has a fascinating although often forgotten history. From using cocaine as pain relief in the 19th century to treating the wounded of the 1916 Rising, the hospital has always been a fascinating place.
Strange as it sounds, it is also where I first came up with the idea to start podcasting. In 2010 having been diagnosed with Crohn's disease I was unable to work and to keep myself occupied I started making this show.</description></item><item><title>Muriel McSwiney: A Forgotten Revolutionary | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350184/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 15:35:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350184/</guid><description>Podcast Description Muriel McSwiney is a fascinating if tragic and forgotten figure in Irish history. Born in 1892 into one of Cork's wealthiest families, she rejected the privilege this life offered her. She first became a radical republican playing a key role in the War of Independence before becoming a communist in the 1920s. This podcast tells her story.
--------------------------------------------------------------
I have released a set of unique metal and enamel badges depicting some of the key figures in Irish history over the last 1000 years.</description></item><item><title>Winners &amp; Losers - How the Great Hunger Ended | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350185/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 06:03:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350185/</guid><description>Podcast Description 'Winners &amp;amp; Losers' looks at the how the Great Famine came to an end. It's set to the backdrop of a News Year's Eve Ball held in Kilkenny Castle on December 31st 1850. The castle was home to the Marquis &amp;amp; Marchioness of Ormonde, who had invited what was considered the elite of Kilkenny to the ball.&amp;nbsp;
However behind the finery and wealth on display we will see how the Great Famine continued to affect life in Ireland into the 1850s.</description></item><item><title>Jack the Ripper &amp; Irish Connections | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350186/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 06:33:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350186/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jack the Ripper brutally murdered five women in the Whitechapel area of London in the Autumn of 1888. While his identity remains a mystery, these murders have haunted our imaginations ever since. The case has spawned an entire industry with countless books, films and podcasts along with a disturbing and crass tourist industry in London.
In spite of all this coverage, most of us know very little history about the case.</description></item><item><title>Brehon Law: From Divorce to Irish Sex Magic | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350187/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 06:11:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350187/</guid><description>Podcast Description Divorce and sex magic are not things we associate with medieval Ireland. However for over one thousand years Irish society was governed by a unique and radically different legal system called Brehon Law. In this podcast I interview Dr Gillian Kenny (twitter.com/medievalgill) who explains what Brehon Law was and how it worked. She challenges widely held misconceptions and explains how divorce existed in medieval Ireland given it was banned in modern Ireland until 1995!</description></item><item><title>Was The Great Famine a Genocide? | The Great Famine XXXIII | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350188/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2019 07:20:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350188/</guid><description>Podcast Description This subject needs little by way of an introduction. It is one of the most controversial debates in Irish history. It continues to overshadow relations with our nearest neighbour - Great Britain.
In the 1840s one million Irish people died and another million famine refugees fled the island. The Irish population fell by 25% in less than a decade.
Over the past 25 years calls for the Great Famine to be defined as a genocide have gained in popularity.</description></item><item><title>Three Lives, Three Deaths &amp; One Life Unlived | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350189/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 06:39:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350189/</guid><description>Podcast Description (I am currently researching the final episodes in the Great Famine series. The next show on the Great Hunger is still two weeks away but in the meantime I have this pretty special bonus podcast.)
-----
One of the things that makes medieval history so interesting is that the very basics of life are astounding and fascinating in equal measure. We are endlessly intrigued by
What did people ate?</description></item><item><title>Landlords &amp; Mass Evictions - Exploiting the Great Hunger | The Great Famine XXXII | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350190/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 06:45:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350190/</guid><description>Podcast Description During the Great Hunger over 250,000 people were evicted by their landlords. Most of these people were left destitute with little hope in an Ireland decimated by the Great Famine. In this podcast I look at the struggle that took place between tenants and landlords in the final phase of the Great Hunger. The show tries to understand why landlords and their agents acted in such a ruthless manner and why the government in London actually encouraged this process.</description></item><item><title>The Beginning of the End &amp; Queen Victoria in Ireland (1849) | The Great Famine XXXI | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350191/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350191/</guid><description>Podcast Description In August 1849 Queen Victoria arrived in a famine ravaged Ireland. Contrary to what we might expect there were no protests and in many places the Queen received a rapturous welcome. However this only tells part of the story.&amp;nbsp;This podcast takes you on a journey deep into one of Dublin's most notorious slums - St Michan's. There we follow the lives of a poor couple George and Bridget Shea.</description></item><item><title>Tyranny, Cruelty &amp; Inhumanity - Surviving the Workhouse | The Famine in Clogheen II | The Great Famine XXX | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350192/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 08:27:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350192/</guid><description>Podcast Description This podcast (the second show on the town of Clogheen) introduces Richard Burke, a man who had a very unusual experience of the Great Famine. Between 1845 and 1848 he was the clerk of Clogheen Workhouse and Richard's life provide us with unique insights into this institution which was central to how the Great Hunger affected this community. The workhouse was where stories of kindness and cruelty played out side by side.</description></item><item><title>Corn, Gunpowder &amp; Class Conflict | The Famine in Clogheen I | The Great Famine XXIX | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350193/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350193/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is a return of the Great Famine Series. Focusing on the town of Clogheen in South Tipperary, this two part episode follows the lives of three individuals Robert Davis, David Keane and Richard Burke. Their stories delve into the fascinating yet often violent struggle for survival in Ireland during the Great Famine. While the show focuses on Clogheen the accounts are reflective of wider experiences.
The podcasts also examines controversial topics such as the export of food and the violent resistence to those exports.</description></item><item><title>The Hellfire Club - Debauchery in The Dublin Mountains | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350194/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 13:29:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350194/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Hellfire club is an 18th century ruin in the foothills of the Dublin Mountains. The building has a scandalous history and is considered by some to be one of Ireland's most haunted locations. A few years ago Neil Jackman of Abarta Heritage led an archaeological excavation on the site. This podcast is an interview with Neil. He reveals the history behind this building, where the folklore and mythology originates and what he uncovered in the course of his excavations.</description></item><item><title>Nebraska - Irish Emigrants Surviving on The Frontier | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350195/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 06:52:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350195/</guid><description>Podcast Description When we think of Irish Emigrants in the USA, images of New York or Boston spring to mind. However on a recent trip to the US I visited friends in Nebraska where I found a very different Irish American history.
Located in the midwest - the landcape and climate in Nebraska are pretty extreme - its very different from the large cities on the Eastern Coast.
In this podcast I look at how Irish emigrants survived on the Great Plains in the 1870s and 1880s.</description></item><item><title>The Last of Her Kind | Peig Sayers II | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350196/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 11:49:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350196/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1892 Peig Sayers married &amp;amp; moved from Dunquin in West Kerry to the Great Blasket Island. Her life provides us with fascinating insights into what marriage was like in the late 19th century (a combination of a first date and moving in with your in laws!).
Peig's later life also details how events like the 1916 Rising, the Great War and the War of Independence played out on this remote island.</description></item><item><title>The Last of Her Kind | Peig Sayers I | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350197/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 12:08:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350197/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Peig Sayers died in 1958, she as regarded as one of Ireland's greatest storytellers and folklorists.
Born in Dunquin in 1873 Co Kerry she grew up in the aftermath of the Great Famine in extreme poverty. However life in this remote corner of Ireland is both fascinating and at times unbelievable from a 21st century standpoint.
Later in her life Peig would recall the intriguing details of what is now a lost world.</description></item><item><title>A Very Irish Murder in Cincinnati | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350198/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 06:47:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350198/</guid><description>Podcast Description In April 1894 Cincinnati's Irish Amercian community was rocked by a shocking and brutal murder. It was so scandalous that many newspapers in Ireland refused to even mention it, even though both the victim and the perpetrator were both Irish.
In this podcast you will hear the extraordinary story of Mollie Gilmartin unearthed for the first time in over a century...
Thanks to Muireann Hogan for her narration.</description></item><item><title>A 21st Century Witch Hunt | Kilkenny Witch Trial of 1324 III | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350199/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 06:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350199/</guid><description>Podcast Description The city of Kilkenny was rocked by the notorious witchcraft trial of 1324 (covered in the last two episodes). These events took place seven centuries ago in the long distant past. To conclude the series on the trial embarked on my own witch hunt in the 21st century. I wanted to find if anything remained of the supposed witch Alice Kyteler who disappeared in 1324.
I took a recorder and soon found myself in buildings Alice herself used to frequent.</description></item><item><title>Plan 2019: New Series Announced &amp; New York Event. | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350200/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 12:30:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350200/</guid><description>Podcast Description The series on the Great Hunger of the 1840s will finish in the summer of 2019, but I have been busy planning something new. Find out what it is in this major announcement.&amp;nbsp;
I am visiting New York for the first time and speaking at the American Irish Historical Society on February 28th. You can get tickets at aihs.org
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts</description></item><item><title>Kilkenny Witchcraft Trial of 1324 (Part II) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350201/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350201/</guid><description>Podcast Description This podcast continues the fascinating tale of one of the first witchcraft trials in European history. It took place in Kilkenny in 1324.
This show picks up the story as the trial and surrounding scandal began in March 1324. This would see the Bishop Ossory clash with Alice Kyteler and her powerful but dangerous allies. The consequences would be devastating for those caught in the middle.
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts</description></item><item><title>Kilkenny Witchcraft Trial of 1324 (Part I) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350202/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 06:28:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350202/</guid><description>Podcast Description Growing up in Kilkenny I was surrounded by medieval history - its what drew me to study the past in the first place.
One of the most famous or perhaps notorious incidents in Kilkenny's medieval history took place in 1324 when the Bishop of Ossory accused Alice Kyteler, a powerful merchant in the city, of heresy and witchraft. This sparked a lethal struggle in the town that would end in shocking brutality.</description></item><item><title>The 1848 Famine Rebellion | The Great Famine XXVIII | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350203/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 10:43:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350203/</guid><description>Podcast Description 1848 was a year of revolt &amp;amp; rebellion across Europe and Ireland was no different. However unique to Ireland, the 1848 uprising took place to the back drop of one of the worst famine’s in modern history – the Great Hunger.
While it has been overshadowed by the much larger 1798 rebellion and the 1916 Rising, the story of the Famine rebellion is a fascinating if forgotten history.</description></item><item><title>Heroes of The Great Hunger - Famine Aid in the 1840s | The Great Famine XXVII | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350204/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350204/</guid><description>Podcast Description The history of the Great Hunger is rooted in stories of greed, racism and senseless suffering. This episode however sheds light on some of the amazing stories of compassion and solidarity that saved thousands of lives.
While it can be difficult not to focus on the disastrous actions of the British Government, it is also important to remember the forgotten heroes of the Great Famine – the Victorian equivalent of aid workers.</description></item><item><title>BONUS: Ireland's Most Famous Highwayman &amp; Cromwell's Siege of Wexford | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350205/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350205/</guid><description>Podcast Description This bonus episode contains the first two shows in my podcast series 'This Week in Irish history'. These shows look at the life of Ireland's most famous highwayman and Cromwell's Siege of Wexford in 1649.
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts
Patreon www.patreon.com/irishpodcast
Acast https://plus.acast.com/s/irishhistory
📢June 2023 Update - New Walking Tour 📢
I am thrilled to announce my brand new walking tour in Ireland's oldest city, Waterford.</description></item><item><title>Our Darkest Hour? The Forgotten Famine of 1847-48 | The Great Famine XXVI | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350206/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 11:41:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350206/</guid><description>Podcast Description Many histories of the Great Hunger refer to the famine ending in 1847. It is true that the famine did start to ease in some parts of the island in the following years.
However in the west the catastrophe was far from over - some of the darkest chapters lay ahead as 1847 drew to a close.
This episode focuses in on one area – Clifden in Co Galway where the famine in 1848 was arguably even worse than it had been during Black ’47.</description></item><item><title>How To Get My New Podcast Series: 'This Week in Irish History' | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350207/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 04:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350207/</guid><description>Podcast Description On October 1st my new free weekly podcast series 'This Week in Irish History' begins.
This short episode tells you want you can expect, what's in the first four shows and the simple step you need to take to make sure you dont miss out on Ireland's newest podcast.
&amp;nbsp;
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts
Patreon www.patreon.com/irishpodcast
Acast https://plus.acast.com/s/irishhistory
📢June 2023 Update - New Walking Tour 📢</description></item><item><title>Black '47 The Movie Reviewed | The Great Famine XXV | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350208/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 06:51:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350208/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week see the release of the first major movie set during the Great Famine. Starring James Frecheville, Stephen Rae, Jim Broadbent &amp;amp; Hugo Weaving Black '47 is one of the most eagerly awaited Irish films of 2018.
Last Wednesday I got a sneak preview of the movie and in this podcast I review Black '47.
Last Wednesday I got a sneak preview of the movie and in this podcast I review Black '47.</description></item><item><title>The Road to Black '47 - The History Behind The Movie | The Great Famine XXIV | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350209/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 04:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350209/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week sees the launch of the movie Black '47 &amp;amp; my return to the Great Famine series.
So whether you want to find out the history behind the movie or catch up on the series to date this is podcast for you. While it does summarise the series to date the show also includes lots of new information.&amp;nbsp;
The episode tells the fascinating but forgotten story of Margaret Murphy.</description></item><item><title>The Mulranny Police Conspiracy | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350210/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 06:17:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350210/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Mulranny Police Conspiracy is a little-known story that took place in the west of Ireland at the turn of the 20th century. The setting is Mulranny – a stunning village along the Wild Atlantic Way but in 1900 it was something of a forgotten backwater. However it was here, on the shores of Clew Bay that this story of deceit unfolded. In what is at times a bizarre and tragic plot, the Royal Irish Constabulary turned on this poor community in Co Mayo when they began to campaign for better rights.</description></item><item><title>The Iniskea Island Mysteries? | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350211/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 06:54:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350211/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Iniskea Islands are among the most remote places in Ireland. Although deserted today, throughout the 19th century the lives of the islanders were the source of bizarre rumours. Numerous outsiders accused the islanders of piracy &amp;amp; worshipping pagan gods into the 1870s.
In this podcast I look at whether these Islanders were truly the last pagans and pirates in Ireland. The answers are suprising to say the least.</description></item><item><title>The Massacre of Wildgoose Lodge | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350212/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 16:34:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350212/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the 1830s the British politican George Lewis described the fate of an informer in ireland as a man "doomed to certain death....he would be hunted through the country like a mad dog every hand would be raised against him".&amp;nbsp;
This was something of an understatement in some cases.&amp;nbsp;
In 1816 Edward Lynch became an informer. A few months later this resulted in one of the worst crimes in pre-famine Ireland - The Massacre of Wildgoose Lodge.</description></item><item><title>Did The Famine Drive Irish People Insane? | The Great Famine XXIII | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350213/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 12:11:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350213/</guid><description>Podcast Description Did the experiences of the Famine drive Irish people insane?
In this episode I look at the story of the famine survivor John Thompson who ended up in the Rainhill asylum in Lancashire in the 1860s. In this Victorian institution (which treated mental illnesses) he would find himself surrounded by other Irish people.
This podcast looks at why Irish peope found themsleves in British asylums in disproportionate numbers in the 1850s and 1860s.</description></item><item><title>The US Civil War and The Great Famine | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350214/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 07:09:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350214/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Great Hunger is not something we associate with war and certainly not wars in other countries. However the Famine is inextricably linked to the story of the American Civil War (1861-1865). Around 200,000 Irish people, most of them famine or post famine emigrants, fought in the conflict making it one of the largest wars in terms of Irish participation. This podcast is structured around an interview with Damian Shiels of www.</description></item><item><title>The Famine Irish in The USA - A Promised Land? | The Great Famine XXII | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350215/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 09:51:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350215/</guid><description>Podcast Description After Ireland, no country was more affected by the Great Famine than the USA. Millions of Irish people emigrated to the United States during and after the Great Famine. This is their story. Through this podcast you will follow them on voyages across the Atlantic before looking at several Irish communities from the Five Points Slum in New York to the Rocky Mountains. From persecuted Irish miners in the Pennsylvanian Coalfields to deeply racist Irish prospectors in the Californian Goldrush the Irish story in America is fascinating and complex.</description></item><item><title>American Wakes, Coffin Ships and Canada | The Great Famine XXI | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350216/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 07:01:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350216/</guid><description>Podcast Description Coffin Ships are one of the most enduring images from the Great Famine. This was the name given to the boats that carried Irish Famine emigrants to North America in 1847.&amp;nbsp;This sinister title comes from the appalling death rates onboard these ships. This show opens with the hopes and fears of famine emigrants in Black '47. Then I move on to the harrowing voyages and what awaited the emirgants when they landed in Canada, This fell far short of their expectations - this journey will take us onto the dreaded quarantine station of Gross Isle in the St Laurence river.</description></item><item><title>St Patricks Day in Black '47 | The Great Famine XX | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350217/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2018 21:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350217/</guid><description>Podcast Description As people across the world prepare to mark St Patrick's day this podcast looks what at happened on St Patricks Day during the worst year of the Great Famine. Celebrations were not cancelled but on a day supposed to celebrat all things Irish, events in Dublin revealed there were two very different Irelands in that year.&amp;nbsp;
While one half of the city starved the other half planned a party.</description></item><item><title>Dublin Famine Tour - A New Interactive Experience | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350218/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2018 11:47:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350218/</guid><description>Podcast Description This short podcast explains the Dublin Famine Tour, my new interactive historical experience which launches on St Patricks Weekend.
On this walking tour I guide you through Victorian Dublin, explaining the fascinating but forgotten story of how the Great Famine transformed Ireland’s capital city.
During the tour will also hear what Dublin sounded like in the 1840s along with recordings of accounts written by Dubliners at the time. Tune in for more exciting details.</description></item><item><title>Exiles - Irish Famine Emigrants | The Great Famine XIX) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350219/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 06:38:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350219/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emigration is arguably the greatest legacy of the Great Irish Famine. Between 1846 and 1851, 1.25 million Irish people passed through the port of Liverpool alone to escape the Great Hunger. This exodus of refugees transformed the Great Famine from an Irish catastrophe into a global phenomenon as these people established Irish communities across the world. It fitting then that the show opens with a story from the Canadian city of Montreal in the 1870s.</description></item><item><title>An Eye for an Eye: Evictions &amp; Assassinations | The Great Famine XVIII | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350220/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 06:44:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350220/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over the course of the Great Famine, hundreds of thousands of Irish people were evicted from their homes.
As ruthless landlords showed no pity, eviction was a death sentence for many starving tenants who were made homeless.
It was inevitable these evictions provoked resistance. On November 2nd 1847, the most famous assassination of the Great Famine took place in North Roscommon.
This podcast details the background of this assassination and how it relates to the wider story of other mass evictions in Ireland in the late 1840s.</description></item><item><title>The Great Famine 1845 - 47 | The Great Famine XVII | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350221/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350221/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode marks a return to the Great Famine Series. Coming podcasts will detail the later phase of the Famine including emigration and the bitter struggle that broke out between lanldords &amp;amp; tenants.&amp;nbsp;This show sets the stage by focusing on the life of the most famous Irish person of the 19th century - Daniel O’Connell.&amp;nbsp;Known as 'King Dan' the final years of his life provide a great opportunity to recap on what has happened so far and tie up loose ends before we continue our story.</description></item><item><title>Spies &amp; Jail Breaks: Female Rebels in Medieval Ireland | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350222/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 08:08:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350222/</guid><description>Podcast Description Isabella Cadel, Grace O Toole, Fynyna O Toohig. These are all women forgotten by history who lived intriguing and fascinating lives. The three had one thing in common - they were all rebels in medieval Ireland.
In this podcast I look at their forgotten stories which took place in an Ireland ravaged by deadly conflict. These medieval female warriors played an overlooked role in the brutal and deadly war that broke out between Norman settlers and Gaelic Rebels in the late Middle Ages.</description></item><item><title>Ireland's Nazi Commando II (Otto Skorzeny) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350223/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2017 08:44:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350223/</guid><description>Podcast Description The last podcast looked at the arrival of the one time Nazi Commando Otto Skorzeny in Ireland in 1957 and the welcome he received from some of the most influential people in Dublin.&amp;nbsp;This podcast continues this bizarre story using recently released files from Ireland's intelligence agency G2. These files contain serious allegations about Skorzeny in Ireland.&amp;nbsp;
Was he using Cork Harbour to smuggle arms to North Africa?Was he guilty of testing a gas gun on concentration camp inmates?</description></item><item><title>Ireland's Nazi Commando: Otto Skorzeny (Part I) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350224/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350224/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the first of two podcasts which looks at the story of Otto Skorzeny, a notorious Nazi with a long but forgotten connection to Ireland.
It is set in the aftermath of World War II to the intriguing backdrop of the hunt for Nazi war criminals after the war. Once labelled the most dangerous man in Europe the focus of the podcast, Otto Skorzeny, was a man plagued with rumours of war crimes, gun running and Neo-Nazi activities all his life.</description></item><item><title>The First Irishman in China (Outsiders Part II) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350225/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 09:47:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350225/</guid><description>Podcast Description Believe it or not the first Irish person to visit China left Europe in 1318 arriving. His fascinating journey would take several years. Known only as 'James of Ireland' this a story embroiled in the rise of the Mongols, medieval papal diplomacy and the tediously slow world of medieval travel.&amp;nbsp;
Hear his story in this podcast...
This podcast is brought to you by Irish Newspaper Archives
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts</description></item><item><title>Ireland's Last Executioners (Outsiders Part I) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350226/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 09:39:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350226/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over the coming weeks I am taking a break from the Great Famine Series to make a mini series entitled 'Outsiders'. These podcasts will focus on people who for one reason or another lived at the peripherary of Irish society.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;First up is Ireland's last executioners. These were members of a family who included one of the most prolific hangmen of all time. This is the story of the Pierrepoints who between them probably executed over 1,000 people in the mid 20th century.</description></item><item><title>The Workhouse and The Unwanted | The Great Famine XVI | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350227/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 07:09:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350227/</guid><description>Podcast Description The crumbling ruins of workhouses are one of the last visible reminders of the horrors of the Great Hunger in the Irish landscape. During the Great Famine they became home to the unwanted in Irish society. Ultimately over 300,000 people Irish people died in these institutions during the Great Hunger.&amp;nbsp;
While they may have been unwanted by the late 1840s very few of the so called 'inmates' of workhouses were born unwanted.</description></item><item><title>A Doomed Land? Piracy, Elections and The 1847 Harvest | The Great Famine XV | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350228/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 04:58:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350228/</guid><description>Podcast Description This show opens with the fascinating story of communities in Mayo who resorted to piracy to survive in 1847. This is only a prelude however before we look at two pivotal events later in the year.&amp;nbsp;
After two years of starvation, the only election held during the Great Famine took place in August 1847. In some constituencies this poll was more like a blood sport than modern elections.&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>At a Crossroads - Salvation or Starvation (1847) | The Great Famine XIV | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350229/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 07:18:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350229/</guid><description>Podcast Description This podcast continues our journey through the summer of 1847 as we reach one of the pivotal moments in the history of the Great Famine. The British government finally realise a new policy is needed in Ireland but will it help or hinder?
Decisions taken in this podcast overshadow life Ireland for years to come.&amp;nbsp;
Tune in to find out more.&amp;nbsp;
This episode is brought to you by Irish Newspaper Archives</description></item><item><title>A Tale of Transportation | The Great Famine XIII | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350230/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350230/</guid><description>Podcast Description Transportation was a particularity cruel punishment. For centuries those condemned to this fate were shipped to penal colonies on the far side of the globe to serve out their sentences. It has become synonymous with injustice during the famine when many caught stealing food suffered this fate. For this podcast I dug deep into the archives and found the story of the Nangle family whose lives were ripped apart after they were caught stealing sheep.</description></item><item><title>The Great Hunger in Dublin | The Great Famine XII | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350231/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2017 05:23:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350231/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dublin is often forgotten in the story of the Great Famine. While death rates in the capital were not as severe as the west of Ireland, the city suffered nevertheless. The show follows the story of the Mulherins, a family who fled famine in their home in Co Leitrim and settled in the Smithfield - Stoneybatter area of Dublin. They quickly found life in the capital city was very different but not necessarily easier.</description></item><item><title>Voices from Black '47 - Irish Emigrants in Their Own Words | The Great Famine XI | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350232/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 06:38:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350232/</guid><description>Podcast Description From January 1847 Irish people desperately trying to flee the famine began to leave the island in huge numbers.&amp;nbsp;
220,000 left in that year alone and by 1853 more than one in six people who had lived in Ireland in 1845 had emigrated. While we know a lot about where they went and the horrendous conditions they faced, we know less about the lives they left behind. This show tells that story through the words of these Irish emigrants.</description></item><item><title>Black '47 - A World Turned Upside Down (1847) | The Great Famine X | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350233/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 11:20:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350233/</guid><description>Podcast Description This series continues the story of the Great Famine into the notorious year of Black '47 by returning to the town of Skibbereen. Looking at how life in the town changed it details the horrifying lives many had to endure. However starvation was not the only way the famine changed Ireland and the show begins by looking at the unusual story of James Dillon, a coroner in Co Offaly who was tasked with investigating two suspicious deaths in December 1846.</description></item><item><title>Insurrection and Starvation - A Tale of Two Towns (1846) | The Great Famine IX | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350234/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 06:46:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350234/</guid><description>Podcast Description As the situation deteriorated in Ireland in late 1846, the two Cork towns of Youghal and Skibbereen experienced the unfolding horrors in very different ways. The people of Youghal, due to local dynamics, were in a position to rise up against some of the causes of famine. Through the Autumn of 1846 they launched an insurrection in a desperate bid to stop food being exported. However at Skibbereen&amp;nbsp;in west Cork the people found themselves in a far worse situation.</description></item><item><title>History vs Reality. What Was Life Really Like in 1840s Ireland? | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350235/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 09:13:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350235/</guid><description>Podcast Description Many travellers who visited the west of Ireland in the 19th century considered it as a frontier of sorts. They were more often than not deeply racist, yet we still rely heavily on their accounts to reconstruct a picture of life at the time. In this show I question&amp;nbsp;how reliable their accounts are. In an effort to create a more vivid picture of life in the 1840s I have interviewed with two archaeologists - Franc Myles and Eve Campbell for this show.</description></item><item><title>An Abandoned Village and Ireland's Newest Beach: Achill Island Day 1 | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350236/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 17:20:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350236/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join Fin as he treks around Achill island visiting Ireland's newest beach and the ruins of a famine era village.
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts
Patreon www.patreon.com/irishpodcast
Acast https://plus.acast.com/s/irishhistory
📢June 2023 Update - New Walking Tour 📢
I am thrilled to announce my brand new walking tour in Ireland's oldest city, Waterford. Join me and explore 1,000 years of history from the Vikings to Cromwell &amp;amp; Strongbow to the Irish Revolution.</description></item><item><title>Crisis Turns into Catastrophe (1846) | The Great Famine VIII | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350237/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2017 10:30:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350237/</guid><description>Podcast Description Through the summer of 1846 Ireland had endured terrible hunger and suffering. However against the odds the numbers who had starved to death were few. As many waited in great anticipation for the coming harvest, disaster struck when the potato blight returned on a much wider scale than in 1845. As the Irish MP Daniel O'Connell stated a 'death dealing famine' was on the cards. This show begins with a story of emigration and passengers on an early coffin ship.</description></item><item><title>All Aboard - Virtual Road Trip to the 1840s | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350238/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2017 12:04:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350238/</guid><description>Podcast Description Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts
Patreon www.patreon.com/irishpodcast
Acast https://plus.acast.com/s/irishhistory
📢June 2023 Update - New Walking Tour 📢
I am thrilled to announce my brand new walking tour in Ireland's oldest city, Waterford. Join me and explore 1,000 years of history from the Vikings to Cromwell &amp;amp; Strongbow to the Irish Revolution.&amp;nbsp; Enhanced by wireless headsets 🎧 you will hear the sounds of the city through the ages and the words of the people who made history in Waterford.</description></item><item><title>The 1846 Summer of Starvation | The Great Famine VII | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350239/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 10:52:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350239/</guid><description>Podcast Description The summer of 1846 was a tense time in Ireland. As food grew scarce lawlessness, riots and violence became frequent. Everyone eagerly awaited May 15th when the British Government would open it's emergency food depots. Perhaps then the tensions and anxiety at the heart of Irish society would ease? However would the food in these emergency depots be enough to stave off famine until the harvest was ready in Autumn?</description></item><item><title>Free Trade or Famine 1845-46 | The Great Famine VI | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350240/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 10:38:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350240/</guid><description>Podcast Description This show takes you through the winter of 1845 through to April 1846 as the situation in Ireland deteriorates. Food riots and protests become common, while the Famine crisis facing Ireland is consumed in bitter political disputes around free trade in London.&amp;nbsp;
While the show follows the fate of millions through increasingly uncertain times it begins (as is often the case now) in a quite secluded spot in the west of Ireland in Co Leitrim.</description></item><item><title>The Great Hunger Begins | The Great Famine V | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350241/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 09:31:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350241/</guid><description>Podcast Description As the harvest of 1845 approached in Ireland, rumours circulated that&amp;nbsp;a mysterious disease was attacking the potato crop. While well informed botanists in London grew increasingly anxious about what lay ahead, many Irish peasants dependent on potatoes had little idea what was happening. When the harvest did fail, the Great Famine had begun. Terror gripped the population and I look at what the British authorities did to respond.</description></item><item><title>On The Verge of Disaster: Ireland 1845 | The Great Famine IV | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350242/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 09:26:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350242/</guid><description>Podcast Description 1845 is famous for one thing in Irish history – the beginning of the Great Famine. However contrary to what you might expect, if you lived in Ireland through most of 1845 there was little evidence to suggest Irish society stood on the brink of one of the greatest famines in history. This episode looks at the highs and lows of life in Ireland as the Famine approached.</description></item><item><title>The Scandalous Life of Lola Montez | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350243/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 09:42:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350243/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lola Montez, born Elizabeth Rosanna Gilbert, was one of the most scandalous women of the 19th century. She took Europe by storm with 'dances' that left little to the imagination - she was known to wear nothing beneath her tutu.
Married three times she also had a string of famous lovers including a king, the composer Franz Liszt and the author Alexander Dumas. Were she alive today her friends would include the most powerful people alive, she would be plagued by the paparazzi, have millions of twitter followers and if she had a website it would be most definitely x rated.</description></item><item><title>Was Ireland Overpopulated in 1845? | The Great Famine III | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350244/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 12:20:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350244/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1845 the population of Ireland was heading towards 9 million with many people surviving on a diet of potatoes. This has lead many to claim that the island was overpopulated. In this podcast I head to a remote village of Inver in Erris to see how the population has changed over the past 150 years. I also investigate exactly how many people lived in Ireland, what was the standard of living and whether the people were healthy.</description></item><item><title>Rents, Riots and Volcanoes | The Great Famine II | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350245/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 15:10:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350245/</guid><description>Podcast Description The series on the Great Famine got off to a bloody start with the story of Anne Devlin and the rebellions of 1798 and 1803. By the end of the first episode, Ireland had been incorporated into the United Kingdom under the Act of Union.&amp;nbsp;
In this show we will see what life in Ireland was like after the Act of Union. Within a few decades inequality was soaring.</description></item><item><title>Rebel Isle (1750-1803) | The Great Famine I | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350246/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 14:53:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350246/</guid><description>Podcast Description This podcast, the first in my new series on the Great Famine, gives a background to Ireland in the 19th century. Entitled 'Rebel Island' it focuses on the life of one extraordinary Irish rebel -&amp;nbsp;Anne Devlin. She lived a remarkable life and was involved in the 1798 and 1803 rebellions. These reshaped Ireland and had profound consequences impacting life right up to and during the Great Famine.
Anne Devlin's life also explains why sectarian tensions between Catholics and Protestants dominated life in Ireland, what the Act of Union was and why it was so important.</description></item><item><title>The Great Irish Famine Series - An Introduction | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350247/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 14:25:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350247/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over the past few months I have been preparing a major podcast series on the Great Famine of the 1840s and its finally here! This short episode is an introduction to the series, what you can expect from it and why I am making it. Basically its like an introduction to a book.
If this isn't your thing and you want to crack on with the series the first episode - Rebel Island is available for patrons now at patreon.</description></item><item><title>Hitchhiker's Guide to 1820s Ireland | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350248/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 18:31:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350248/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the opening line of his novel The Go Between the writer L.P. Hartley famously quipped ‘The past is a foreign country; they do things differently there’. For me history is about attempting to visit this foreign country L.P. Hartley talked about and seeing what life was like. In this podcast I have&amp;nbsp;trawled through eye witness accounts of travelers to early 19th century Ireland to give you a sense of what life was like in a past where they did things very differently.</description></item><item><title>Letters from Dakota | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350249/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2016 07:19:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350249/</guid><description>Podcast Description 'Letters from Dakota' is the story of my grandaunt Mollie Dwyer who emigrated to the USA when she was 15 years of age in 1906. Her emigrant experience was very different to most. Within two months she found herself in a convent in South Dakota training to be a nun. She would never return to the town she grew up in, save for the very occasional visit.&amp;nbsp;
However for over 40 years she wrote to her brother Jack Dwyer (my grandfather) in Castlecomer revealing intriguing insights into her unusual life as a nun in rural Dakota.</description></item><item><title>The Land War (1879-1882) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350250/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 10:57:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350250/</guid><description>Podcast Description I launched my first exclusive patron’s podcast on the Land War yesterday.The Land War is a fascinating struggle between Irish landlords and tenants between 1879 and 1882.
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts
Patreon www.patreon.com/irishpodcast
Acast https://plus.acast.com/s/irishhistory
📢June 2023 Update - New Walking Tour 📢
I am thrilled to announce my brand new walking tour in Ireland's oldest city, Waterford. Join me and explore 1,000 years of history from the Vikings to Cromwell &amp;amp; Strongbow to the Irish Revolution.</description></item><item><title>The Phoenix Park Murders II - The Manhunt | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350251/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 09:12:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350251/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Phoenix Park Murders are one of the most famous assassinations in Irish History. On May 6th 1882 Lord Frederick Cavendish and Thomas Henry Burke were killed in brutal circumstances in the Phoenix Park. The full story is covered in Part I.
This episode follows the manhunt for the assassins. While the police quickly identified the likely suspects, they had almost no evidence to make arrests.
This lead to a fascinating and relentless pursuit for evidence through victorian Dublin, while the assassins prepared to carry out more attacks.</description></item><item><title>The 1882 Phoenix Park Murders Part I - A Fatal Day in Dublin | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350252/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2016 15:08:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350252/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Phoenix Park Murders are among the most famous political assassinations in Irish History. On May 6th 1882, Lord Frederick Cavendish the new chief secretary for Ireland was assassinated in the Phoenix Park in brutal circumstances. Taking place at the height of the Land War, the fascinating story of the murders is set to the backdrop of riots, protests and other assassinations. In part I, I look at this context by following Frederick Cavendish on his last day alive before finishing up with the assassination itself.</description></item><item><title>Tales From The Great Famine in Dublin | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350253/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2016 17:46:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350253/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode I took my recorder and headed around my neighbourhood looking for the history of the Great Famine. Unsurprisingly I didn't have to travel far. With the Women's prison, the North Dublin Workhouse and the residence of the Lord&amp;nbsp;Lieutenant all within a kilometre, this show is full of fascinating accounts recorded at the sites they took place. From the mansions of the powerful to the prison cells of the powerless, this is a fascinating account of life in Dublin in the late 1840s.</description></item><item><title>The Maamtrasna Murders Part III - The Guilty and the Innocent | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350254/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 18:21:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350254/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this final episode on the Maamtrasna murders, we begin by picking up the story of this fascinating murder case in December 1882. Eight men have been sentenced to die in Galway Jail on December the 15th for their role in the brutal killings of the Joyce family.
While five get their sentences commuted to the life imprisonment three are set to die. However at the last minute new evidence emerges.</description></item><item><title>The Maamtrasna Murders Part II - The Trials | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350255/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 12:57:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350255/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Part I of this series on the Maamtrasna murders I looked at one of the most brutal killings in 19th century Ireland when the Joyce family were attacked in their remote home in Maamtrasna on the Mayo-Galway border.
This podcast follows looks at the trials. While the police made a major break through within days of the murder a botched attempt at swift justice would see the story of the trials become nearly as famous the murders themselves.</description></item><item><title>The Maamtrasna Murders Part I - The Killings | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350256/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 07:38:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350256/</guid><description>Podcast Description Prior to 1882, Maamtrasna a remote townland in the west of Ireland, was known to few outside Co. Galway. That all changed on the night of August 17th 1882 when one of the most brutal murders in 19th century Ireland took place there.
Five members of the Joyce family were killed in a horrific and disturbing attack. In a deeply unnerving aspect of a case still shrouded in mystery, the perpetrators were almost certainly known to the victims.</description></item><item><title>The Tale of Jack of Ireland: A Medieval Outlaw | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350257/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 06:07:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350257/</guid><description>Podcast Description Medieval outlaws have captured the human imagination for centuries. The story of Robin Hood who famously robbed from the rich to give to the poor has proved the most enduring. However most were ruthless individuals, many were willing to rob from the rich but few ever gave their bounty to the poor.
This podcast is about a Irish man who was an outlaw in all but name. While Jack would avoid being declared an outlaw his life gives a much better sense of what a medieval outlaw was like rather than the oft recounted tales of Robin Hood.</description></item><item><title>Haunted By Our History: Ireland and Child Sexual Abuse | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350258/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 08:22:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350258/</guid><description>Podcast Description This podcast was funded by the Mary Raftery Journalism Fund.
We don’t remember 1980s fondly in Ireland. Emigration and recession were features of life. The political atmosphere was defined by divisive and bitter debates around abortion in 1983 and divorce in 1986.
There was also a third deeply discomforting debate that rocked Irish society. Almost completely forgotten, this debate around child sexual abuse lifted the lid on a topic previously shrouded by shame, taboo and a code of silence.</description></item><item><title>The Manchester Martyrs | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350259/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 08:29:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350259/</guid><description>Podcast Description In November 1867 tension and fear gripped the city of Manchester. A regiment of the British Army was drafted in to support a police force already bolstered by an extra 2,000 recruits.
With the most contentious execution in a century due to take place at the New Bailey Prison, it was feared racial tensions in Manchester would erupt into violence.
The three condemned men Michael O'Brien, Michael Larkin and William Allen were all Irish.</description></item><item><title>Fatal Feuds V - Medieval Downfall | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350260/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 08:29:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350260/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Fatal Feuds series has tracked the dramatic rise of the de Burgh Lords of the West and Earls of Ulster - the most powerful family in Medieval Irish history.
In 1326 the family Patriarch, the Red Earl, died leaving the family facing an uncertain future. The heir, known as the Brown Earl, was only 15 years of age. He now had to unify his vassals and powerful relations many of whom had ambitions of their own in an Ireland beset by war and hardships.</description></item><item><title>Bonus: An Irish Childhood in a Stately Mansion | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350261/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2016 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350261/</guid><description>Podcast Description TV series like Downton Abbey offer a sensationalised view of life in Stately Homes but what was it really like? This podcast uses the never before published words of Florence Doreen Wandesforde who wrote a short account of her childhood in Castlecomer House before she died in 1999 at the age 95.
This is a fascinating insight to the world of upstairs-downstairs. Doreen and her family had their own butler, cook, servants and even gym instructor.</description></item><item><title>Fatal Feuds IV - The Fall of the Red Earl | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350262/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2016 14:55:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350262/</guid><description>Podcast Description The show picks up the story of the de Burgh family in August 1316 as the biggest battle in medieval Irish history approaches. The De Burghs have paid an huge ransom to free their best battle commander William 'Liath' de Burgh. He will lead the Norman forces against the might of the O'Connors and their king Felim. This battle fought beneath the walls of Athenry will decide the fate of a generation.</description></item><item><title>Bonus: Stealing the Stone of Destiny | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350263/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2016 06:43:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350263/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1296 King Edward I of England invaded Scotland. During this campaign he removed the Stone of Destiny (a.k.a. The Stone of Scone) bringing it back to England. The removal of the stone which had been used to inaugurate medieval Scottish Kings, symbolised Scotland's domination by her southern neighbour. That was until Christmas 1950 when three students and a teacher attempted to take the stone back north of the border.</description></item><item><title>Fatal Feuds III - The Bruce Invasion | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350264/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2016 13:25:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350264/</guid><description>Podcast Description The third part of the mini-series Fatal Feuds focuses on the Bruce Invasion of Ireland in 1315. This sees the famous Scottish King Robert the Bruce wage war on his father-in-law the Red Earl of Ulster Richard de Burgh. This podcast on the greatest war in Medieval Irish history is packed full of fascinating characters and stories not to mention the longest siege in Irish history.
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts</description></item><item><title>Bonus - Medieval Ireland's Red Wedding | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350265/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2016 06:28:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350265/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Red Wedding is an infamous chapter in the Game of Thrones series. It saw one family wipe out their rivals in a treacherous and brutal massacre. In this podcast I look at a comparable event from Ireland in the 14th century.
In 1305 the Lord of Tethmoy Peter de Bermingham invited several leading members of the O'Connor-Faly family to Carrick castle for a feast. The guests included his godchild.</description></item><item><title>Fatal Feuds II - The Making of a Medieval Superpower | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350266/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2016 10:14:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350266/</guid><description>Podcast Description This show picks up the story of Richard de Burgh, the Red Earl of Ulster at Christmas 1294. At the end of Fatal Feuds Part I he had been kidnapped &amp;amp; imprisoned in Lea castle by his rival John Fitzthomas. This&amp;nbsp;plunged Ireland into chaos.
In this show with the the Earl in captivity Fitzthomas goes on the offensive attacking his rivals in Connacht. Mayhem sweeps across Ireland in an event known as The Time of Disturbance.</description></item><item><title>2019 Update on the Future of The Podcast | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350267/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2016 16:18:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350267/</guid><description>Podcast Description This short epsiode updates you on changes coming in the show.
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts
Patreon www.patreon.com/irishpodcast
Acast https://plus.acast.com/s/irishhistory
📢June 2023 Update - New Walking Tour 📢
I am thrilled to announce my brand new walking tour in Ireland's oldest city, Waterford. Join me and explore 1,000 years of history from the Vikings to Cromwell &amp;amp; Strongbow to the Irish Revolution.&amp;nbsp; Enhanced by wireless headsets 🎧 you will hear the sounds of the city through the ages and the words of the people who made history in Waterford.</description></item><item><title>Fatal Feuds Part I – The Rise of the Red Earl (1281 – 1295) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350268/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2016 12:45:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350268/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is the first of four that looks at a series of related feuds that ripped Ireland apart in the late Middle Ages. 'Fatal Feuds' begins in the late 13th century when the de Burgh and FitzGerald families fought out a private war of epic proportions. This episode begins by introducing the most important character in the series&amp;nbsp;- Richard Og de Burgh, The Red Earl of Ulster and Lord of Connacht.</description></item><item><title>Bridget Cleary - The Last Woman Burned Alive in Ireland | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350269/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 14:13:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350269/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1895 Bridget Cleary made international news after she was burned to death in South Tipperary. Rumours circulated she had been accused of being a witch. Could this be true? On the eve of the 20th century a woman was burned as a witch in Ireland. This podcast tells the full story and looks at the horrific murder of Bridget Cleary - the last person who was burned to death in Ireland.</description></item><item><title>The 'Witch' Mary Doheny and a 19th Century Supernatural Scam | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350270/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2016 12:34:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350270/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mary Doheny was born in Ireland in the 1820s.&amp;nbsp;A ruthless, mysterious and controversial woman she gained notoriety in the 1860s. In 1864 she stood trial for organising one of the most bizarre scams of the 19th century which involved among other things raising people from the dead. Unsurprisingly rumours of witchcraft were never far from what was an incredible story. Hear her fascinating but forgotten history in the latest show.</description></item><item><title>Ireland’s Forgotten World War II Bombings | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350271/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2016 13:16:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350271/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Irish Free State remained neutral in World War II. Nevertheless the country and its people still faced attack. In 1941 the Nazis bombed the North Strand in Dublin. However the most lethal explosion took place in a remote corner of Donegal killing 19 people. An eyewitness recalled a "tremendous explosion shook the heavens and a brilliant blinding flash of light illuminated the countryside lighting up mountains many miles to the rear"</description></item><item><title>Hubert Butler - Ireland’s Forgotten World War II Hero | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350272/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 13:30:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350272/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hubert Butler (1900-1991) is a forgotten Irish hero. In 1938-39 he traveled to the Nazi Third Reich to help Jews escape persecution. While he ultimately helped save 150 people from the holocaust, he was not celebrated in Ireland. Instead after he revealed how the church was involved in supporting the Nazi allies in Yugoslavia he suffered what was in effect internal exile. Listen to Hubert's fascinating story in this podcast.</description></item><item><title>Black Death Book (Preview &amp; Listeners Discount) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350273/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2016 15:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350273/</guid><description>Podcast Description '1348: A Medieval Apocalypse' will immerse you in a fascinating and forgotten world. Late medieval Ireland was a land ravaged by invasion, famine and disease where history proves stranger than fiction.
The book begins in 1315 when a Scots army invaded Ulster triggering three years of devastating war and famine. Ireland had scarcely recovered before the greatest killer in recorded human history – The Black Death – struck in 1348.</description></item><item><title>Free State or Fair State: Ireland After Independence | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350274/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2016 17:50:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350274/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1921 the War of Independence came to an end. Many had high hopes for what the future held in store for them in an Independent Ireland. However while people lived in what was officially called the Irish Free State, Fin asks was it a free or fair state?
This episode is not suitable for younger listeners as it contains references to sex.
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts</description></item><item><title>The Revolution Underground (Secret Societies, Communism and Coal (Part V) (1919-1922) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350275/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2016 09:13:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350275/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1919 the War of Independence broke out in Ireland. In Castlecomer, Ireland’s largest mining community, this had a profound effect. While the I.R.A. fought the British Army in the surrounding countryside, below ground the miners waged their own revolution. This brought not only ambushes and assassination to Castlecomer but strikes, industrial Sabotage &amp;amp; kidnapping. Listen to the full show to hear this enthralling story!
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts</description></item><item><title>The Road to War (1894 -1918) – Secret Societies, Communism and Coal (Part IV) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350276/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2016 09:17:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350276/</guid><description>Podcast Description 'The Road to War' returns to my series on the Castlecomer Coalfields. It takes you on a gripping journey through life in one small Irish town and the surrounding coalfields between 1894 &amp;amp; 1918. From the relative peace of the 1890s to the dark years of World War I and the tumultuous days of the Easter Rising, life in Castlecomer and its mines was never dull.
This show also reveals for the first time the attitude&amp;nbsp;of R.</description></item><item><title>A Christmas Feast in Medieval Ireland | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350277/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2015 08:47:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350277/</guid><description>Podcast Description The turkey only arrived in Northern Europe in 16th century so what did people eat for Christmas Dinner? In this episode I look at the foods available in medieval Ireland. This includes everything from larks cooked in cinnamon and cloves, geese cooked in garlic to soggy pies and lethal takeaways!
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts
Patreon www.patreon.com/irishpodcast
Acast https://plus.acast.com/s/irishhistory
📢June 2023 Update - New Walking Tour 📢</description></item><item><title>The Superstitions and Strange Customs of Medieval Ireland | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350278/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2015 08:05:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350278/</guid><description>Podcast Description Strange as it may sound, if you lived in the Northwest of Ireland 1000 years ago you may well have witnessed your king attempting to mate with a horse! Medieval Ireland was a very strange place and this show looks at the stranger aspects of magic, superstition and the custom from the world of our medieval ancestors...
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts
Patreon www.patreon.com/irishpodcast</description></item><item><title>Ireland's Hidden Hand in History | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350279/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 09:21:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350279/</guid><description>Podcast Description Its Christmas and to celebrate I am releasing three podcasts this week. This episode looks at the Ireland's hidden hand in history - Irish people who you have never heard of but nevertheless played key roles in history. For example the first is a 50 year old Irish woman who tried to assassinate the Italian dictator Benito Mussolini in 1920s. Others include Eliza Lynch a cork woman who became the first lady of Paraguay in the 19th century and Joseph Kavanagh a leading figure in the French Revolution.</description></item><item><title>The Land War &amp; the Great 1881 Strike – Secret Societies, Communism and Coal (Part III) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350280/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2015 13:54:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350280/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the aftermath of the famine the people of Castlecomer were shell-shocked, reeling from years of death, disease and emigration. However by the 1880s this had changed. When yet another famine threatened in 1879, and landlords threatened eviction, tenants across Ireland rose up in rebellion. The miners of Castlecomer, not to be left behind, launched the Great Coal Strike of 1881. Hear this fascinating story here in this latest episode of Secret Societies, Communism and Coal – Life in the Castlecomer Colliery.</description></item><item><title>The Great Famine in Castlecomer - Secret Societies, Communism and Coal Part II | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350281/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2015 14:21:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350281/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1845 life in the Castlecomer Coalfields was racked by economic recession and grinding poverty. When the potato crop, the staple diet of millions across Ireland, failed disaster struck. In the following years around one million Irish people died and over one million emigrated.
In Castlecomer the fate of thousands lay in the hands on one man - Charles Wandesforde - the mine owner and local landlord. His decisions were controversial but it not easy to decide whether they were good bad.</description></item><item><title>Secret Societies, Communism &amp; Coal; Life in the Castlecomer Colliery (Part I) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350282/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 14:12:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350282/</guid><description>Podcast Description For three centuries the town of Castlecomer in North Co. Kilkenny staged one of the most fascinating but forgotten struggles in Irish history. Miners who worked in some of the most harsh working conditions constantly struggled against the mine owner. Given it was often a matter of life and death this struggle was often bitter and conflict was never far from the surface. This saw the miners form secret societies, trade unions, republican and indeed even communist organisations.</description></item><item><title>The Black Death, Black Lung &amp; The Great Famine | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350283/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2015 07:41:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350283/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fin hasn't joined a Black Metal band. However this episode is a break from the usual format and explores three very different topics. The Black Death section takes you through the medieval equivalent of the Battle of Stalingrad - The Siege of Calais 1346-47, while updating you on when my upcoming book on the plague is out. Then the show delves into the harsh world of mining in the 19th century before turning to some thoughts on the Great Famine.</description></item><item><title>The Conquered Lands - The Norman Invasion Part XXIII | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350284/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2015 14:42:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350284/</guid><description>Podcast Description By 1190 the Normans were utterly dominant throughout much of Ireland. As undisputed masters they set about tranforming their lands into societies modelled on their homelands in Wales and England. Gaelic Society was destroyed. This podcast looks at what exactly this change was like, what happened and what it was like to live in the Norman Colony. In order to gain a clear insight the show focuses on the Gaelic Kingdom of Ossory and how it became the Norman County of Kilkenny.</description></item><item><title>The North - The Norman Invasion XXII (1190 - 1205) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350285/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2015 13:18:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350285/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode the Normans push far into the North and North west. There they come up against one of the greatest powers in medieval Ireland&amp;nbsp;- the kingdom of Tyrone and its ruling families - the O’Neills and their cousins the McLochlainns. The last of the great Gaelic Irish kingdoms faces an onslaught but will it survive? Hear the full story in this podcast.&amp;nbsp;
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts</description></item><item><title>The Battle for Connacht - The Norman Invasion XXI (1190 - 1205) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350286/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2015 07:24:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350286/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Kingdom of Connacht in the west of Ireland represented one of the greatest obstacles to Norman domination of Ireland. The ruling family, the O'Connors had resisted Norman intrusion into their kingdom on several occasions. However in the 1190s their power began to fade.&amp;nbsp;As three members of the family&amp;nbsp;- Cathal 'of the Red Hand' O'Connor, his brother and grandnephew battled for the crown, the Normans were quick to intervene.</description></item><item><title>My Enemy's Enemy is Still My Enemy: The Norman Invasion XX (1190s) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350287/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2015 06:28:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350287/</guid><description>Podcast Description Part XX sees us enter the 1190s and the Norman Invasion enters what might be called end game. In this decade they begin to advance in to the far west of the island. The Gaelic Irish response is at times baffling. Old internal feuds only intensify as the ruling families cannot let go of past transgressions and unify against the Normans. This leads to a disasterous otcome. This episode looks at events in Munster while coming shows will look at Connacht and Ulster.</description></item><item><title>Living and Dying by The Sword - The Norman Invasion XIX (1186-89) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350288/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2015 06:24:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350288/</guid><description>Podcast Description This show covers the chaotic years between 1186 and 1189. Assassinations, warfare and violence break out across Ireland as many of&amp;nbsp;the key figures in the story so far struggle to survive in what is an increasingly unpredictable world.&amp;nbsp;
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts
Patreon www.patreon.com/irishpodcast
Acast https://plus.acast.com/s/irishhistory
📢June 2023 Update - New Walking Tour 📢
I am thrilled to announce my brand new walking tour in Ireland's oldest city, Waterford.</description></item><item><title>Prince John in Ireland - Norman Invasion XVIII (1185) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350289/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2015 15:11:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350289/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bad, possibly mad and very dangerous, Prince John was one of the most notorious men of the Middle Ages. While his cruel reputation is preserved in the Robin Hood myths his real life notoriety began in Ireland in 1185. If the Island did not have enough problems in the aftermath of the Norman Invasion, the arrival of this prince threatened not only the Gaelic Irish kings but the existing Norman Colonists aswell.</description></item><item><title>Road Trip Through Medieval Ireland | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350290/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2015 06:35:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350290/</guid><description>Podcast Description A few weeks ago I hit the road with a recorder taking in some of the best medieval sites in Ireland. The show takes in 1000 years of Irish history in one day-trip. Starting in around the year 600 in the monastery Glendalough at sunrise before driving through the Wicklow mountains to Kilkenny, I visited many places mentioned in the podcast. The trip finished off in the 16th century in a spot off the beaten track, but a real forgotten gem.</description></item><item><title>Liberty and Riots: Magna Carta in Ireland | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350291/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2015 19:22:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350291/</guid><description>Podcast Description Magna Carta is the most famous medieval document ever written and the story behind it a fascinating. Forged amidst a civil war in England some people even claim it is the cornerstone of modern democracy. This podcast looks at the brutal reign of King John which led to Magna Carta being written, before looking at its impact in Ireland. The show concludes with why I think its over rated and perhaps why medieval riots are as important.</description></item><item><title>Irish-American Radicals - The Forgotten Emigrants | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350292/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2015 17:52:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350292/</guid><description>Podcast Description This podcast tells the story of Irish-Americans who have been forgotten by history. These were the revolutionaries, feminists, socialists, and trade union organisers in the early 20th century . Often dubbed as unamerican they strenuously rejected this notion. They saw themselves as much Americans or Irish American as much as anyone else, they just held a very different view of what America should be. Hear their fascinating story in the show.</description></item><item><title>The Conquest of Ulster - The Norman Invasion of Ireland XVII (1177-85) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350293/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2015 08:15:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350293/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode covers a frenetic period of activity. The show starts in 1181 when Hugh de Lacy is suspected of treason by Kking Henry II. The Normans in Ireland wait with bated breath to see what future holds for their most powerful Lord. From there we travel to Munster in 1182 where a revolt breaks out leading to the death of one of the most well known of the invaders.</description></item><item><title>The Arrival of Hugh de Lacy - The Norman Invasion XVI (1177-81) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350294/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2015 14:52:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350294/</guid><description>Podcast Description This show sees the arrival of the man who is probably the most important figure in our story after Strongbow. Hugh de Lacy, the Lord of Meath ruled over 800,000 acres of land north of Dublin. When he arrived however it was ruined by years of war. During his first four years as the kings representative in Ireland he transformed these territories, but it came at a cost. Nevertheless by the time he was finished many would struggle to recognise what had once been the Southern O'Neill kingdom of Meath.</description></item><item><title>(1177) The Norman Invasion XV - The Invasion of Munster | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350295/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2015 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350295/</guid><description>Podcast Description So far in the story of the invasion the kingdoms of Munster - Desmond and Thomond have escaped relatively unscathed. That is until this episode. In this show we see a fresh Norman army land in Waterford bent on conquering Munster. They are however stepping into a minefield of bloody feuds that stretch back centuries. In this episode I take a different approach, focusing on experience of the Gaelic Irish rather than the Normans.</description></item><item><title>(1176-77) The Norman Invasion XIV – New Blood | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350296/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2015 10:41:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350296/</guid><description>Podcast Description The last show on the Norman Invasion ended in somewhat dramatic circumstances with the death of Strongbow, the leader of the Norman Invasion. As you can imagine the fall out from this was immense.
The episode begins with a group of Normans lead by Raymond le Gros who hear the news when they are deep in Gaelic territory. No one knows how the kings of Gaelic Ireland will react when they hear the news.</description></item><item><title>Grubs Up - Food in Medieval Ireland | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350297/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2014 13:55:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350297/</guid><description>Podcast Description Many of the foods you will eat on Christmas day were unknown to medieval Europeans. Turkey, cranberries and even potatoes only arrived in Europe after the conquest of the Americas began. This podcast looks at the world of medieval food to see at what was available . You will be surprised at the variety of food in medieval Ireland (if you had the money). This show also looks at the strange, lethal and somewhat scary world of takeaway food in medieval Ireland.</description></item><item><title>(1175-76) The Norman Invasion XIII – The End of the Beginning | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350298/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2014 17:47:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350298/</guid><description>Podcast Description This podcast takes the story to a pivotal year in the Norman Invasion of Ireland - 1176. The episode begins where part XII left off - the aftermath of Raymond le Gros' successful siege of Limerick. Raymond makes his way back to Dublin where he receives the shock of lifetime. He is not welcomed by his fellow Normans but instead faces accusations of treachery.&amp;nbsp;This show sees the Normans turn on each other and then ends in the most dramatic of circumstances!</description></item><item><title>(1173-75) The Norman Invasion XII - Revolt and Reprisal | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350299/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2014 18:18:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350299/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1173 Strongbow returned to Ireland after fighting in Normandy for his king Henry II. Within months he faced one of the biggest crises since the invasion had begun as Gaelic resistance to the Invasion surged. Not only was his castle at Kilkenny destroyed but west of the Shannon Ireland's most powerful king Rory O'Connor was planning a major assault on the colony. The Norman presence in Ireland teetered on the brink of potential annihilation.</description></item><item><title>Did the Irish Government Cover Up Mass Starvation in 1920s? | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350300/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 13:45:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350300/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the Spring of 1925 newspapers around the world carried stories that a famine had broken out in Ireland. The Manchester Guardian reported 750,000 people were at risk, a figure repeated by the Soviet Union's daily Pravda. However there is no mention of this "famine" in Irish history books so in I went to the National Archives in search of evidence. What I found was tragic details of yet another cover up.</description></item><item><title>Update on the Norman Invasion | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350301/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 21:22:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350301/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a brief update on whats coming next in the Norman invasion series. Become a member at https://plus.acast.com/s/irishhistory.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>(1174) The Norman Invasion XI: A Tour of Ireland in 1174 | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350302/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2014 11:37:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350302/</guid><description>Podcast Description The year is 1174, much of Ireland is reeling from 5 years of warfare since the Norman Invasion began in earnest in 1169. The island is gripped by sweeping change and chaos. This podcast is an enthralling journey through this land ravaged by conflict.&amp;nbsp;
Before I continue the story of the invasion this episodes stops and takes stock of how the invasion so far was changing life in Ireland.</description></item><item><title>Halloween Special: Ireland's First Witch-Burning (Kilkenny 1324) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350303/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2014 15:15:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350303/</guid><description>Podcast Description On November 2nd 1324, Petronilla of Meath, one of 12 people charged with witchcraft in Kilkenny was burned at the stake in the town. She was the first person to suffer this horrendous fate in Irish history. In this festively themed podcast I trace the story behind this fascinating case and those accused and convicted of witchcraft. What actually happened in Kilkenny in 1324? Was Petronilla of Meath a witch?</description></item><item><title>Riots, Murder and The Mob; Protest in Medieval Ireland | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350304/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2014 10:31:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350304/</guid><description>Podcast Description The story of protest in medieval Ireland is a forgotten but fascinating chapter in our history. While forthright and often violent these protests voiced the concerns of ordinary people so often excluded from written records. In this podcast I look at five protests from late medieval Ireland including a water tax in 1244 and Ireland's first recorded strike in 1299. The intriguing stories behind these protests are brought to light for the first time in centuries in this podcast.</description></item><item><title>(1172-1174) The Norman Invasion X. The Return to War | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350305/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2014 09:53:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350305/</guid><description>Podcast Description At Easter 1172, Henry II left Ireland, having spent six months on the island. Before departing he conferred the Kingdom of Meath onto the Norman baron Hugh de Lacy. However Meath already a king, in fact it had several. Through most of the 12th century numerous Irish kings had been laying claim to what was one of the oldest territories in Ireland. Naturally when de Lacy tried to claim what Henry II had no right to give him he faced opposition.</description></item><item><title>(1171-72) The Norman Invasion IX - King Henry II in Ireland | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350306/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2014 09:49:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350306/</guid><description>Podcast Description On October 17th, 1172, Henry II became the first King of England to set foot in Ireland. Henry had come in the hope to proclaiming himself lord over the entire island. Awaiting him were not just his own Norman subjects who had been fighting in Ireland since 1169 but also dozens of Gaelic kings. How these kings in particular would react to Henry's claims would be crucial. The King however had prepared for all eventualities bringing an army of over 4,000 warriors and even prefabricated siege towers.</description></item><item><title>(1171) The Norman Invasion VIII – The Arrival of Henry II | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350307/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2014 10:05:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350307/</guid><description>Podcast Description Despite their victory at the siege of Dublin (covered in Part VII), Strongbow and his Normans followers in Ireland are by no means in a secure position. In Wexford their comrade-in-arms Robert FitzStephen is being held prisoner. Meanwhile across Leinster they face widespread opposition. The man who invited them to Ireland Diarmait McMurrough is dead and his brother is hostile to the Normans. Meanwhile the neighbouring king of Ossory, Gillapatrick, is a constant threat.</description></item><item><title>(1171) The Norman Invasion VII - The Second Siege of Dublin | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350308/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2014 12:19:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350308/</guid><description>Podcast Description This podcast sees the Normans suffer a ferocious backlash after their conquests in the year of 1170. A Norse army including beserkers - feared viking warriors - attack Dublin before a vast host lead by the king of Connacht - Rory O'Connor besieges the town. The Norman presence in Ireland hangs by a thread as they lose the few friends they had. This episode also sees tensions ramp between Strongbow and his king back home Henry II who is increasingly fearful Strongbow is about to establish a rival kingdom in Ireland.</description></item><item><title>(1170-71) The Norman Invasion VI - The First Siege of Dublin | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350309/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350309/</guid><description>Podcast Description After their brutal conquest of Waterford, Diarmait McMurrough and his Norman allies marshaled their forces and marched on Dublin. If the most important town in medieval Ireland fell into their hands it could be a game changer. The claims of Rory O'Connor of Connacht to be Ireland's most powerful king would be in tatters. This scenario set up a major conflict over Dublin as Rory marched west, reaching the town before the Normans and digging in.</description></item><item><title>(1170) The Norman Invasion V. The Arrival of Strongbow and the Siege of Waterford | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350310/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2014 15:06:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350310/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the summer of 1170, Ireland stood on a precipice. After the arrival of several hundred Norman mercenaries in 1169 the fortunes of Diarmait McMurrough had changed. He had reconquered his lost power in the kingdom of Leinster and re-established himself as a major player in Irish politics.
However this was only the beginning, a violent prelude to Diarmait’s main ambition. He was still waiting for the main force of his mercenaries lead by the Norman Lord Strongbow to arrive and when they did they in the summer of 1170 they did not fail to make their mark.</description></item><item><title>(1169-70) The Norman Invasion IV. The Siege of Wexford and the Conquest of Leinster | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350311/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2014 05:59:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350311/</guid><description>Podcast Description On May 1st 1169, Robert FitzStephen a Norman Knight from Wales, finds himself on Bannow Strand, Ireland leading 300 Norman mercenaries. Their mission - to restore Diarmait McMurrough, the one time gaelic king of Leinster to power. However both they and Diarmait have much greater ambitions.
With a few days of arriving in Ireland the Normans are outside the walls of Wexford besieging what is one of Ireland's most important medieval towns.</description></item><item><title>(1167-1169) The Norman Invasion III: The Conquest Begins | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350312/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2014 17:48:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350312/</guid><description>Podcast Description This podcast looks at the first Normans to arrive in Ireland, in a chapter often forgotten by the history books. These mercenaries accompany Diarmait McMurrough who returned to Ireland in 1167&amp;nbsp;to pave the way for the larger forces of Strongbow. However if these warriors&amp;nbsp;led by Robert FitzGodibert, thought the Gaelic Irish were going to be a pushover they are in for a rude awakening.
They quickly run into the might of Rory O'Connor, perhaps the most powerful Gaelic King in Irish history and things don't go according to plan.</description></item><item><title>Dark Truths and Open Secrets – Who Knew What About Ireland's Child Abuse Scandal? | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350313/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2014 12:26:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350313/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over the last few weeks Ireland has been rocked by yet another child abuse scandal. Newspaper headlines around the world have reported in disbelief details of how society in Ireland treated unmarried mothers and their children in so called “Mother and Child homes". Child mortality rates reached over 50% in some of these institutions.
While many around the world are understandably astounded as to how a society could be so cruel to children, in Ireland this is only the latest chapter in a long horrific story of institutional abuse that has been emerging over the last two decades.</description></item><item><title>(1166-67) The Norman Invasion II - In Search of Kings, Lords &amp; Allies. | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350314/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2014 07:28:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350314/</guid><description>Podcast Description This show looks at some of the most pivotal events in Ireland's history. As Part I of the Norman invasion drew to a close Diarmait McMurrough, the King of Leinster was routed after his powerful ally Muirchertach McLochlainn was killed in 1166. His rivals Rory O'Connor and Tiernan O'Rourke then forced him into exile.
This episode follows Diarmait as he journeys across into the medieval crossroads that was the Irish sea in the Middle Ages.</description></item><item><title>(1156 -1166) The Norman Invasion (Part I) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350315/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2014 14:09:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350315/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the first in a multipart series on the Norman invasion of Ireland. The Invasion was one of the most important and fascinating events in Irish history beginning Ireland's turbulent relationship with England. This episode sets the same in the brutal struggle for dominance between Irish kings in the 12th century.
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts
Patreon www.patreon.com/irishpodcast
Acast https://plus.acast.com/s/irishhistory
📢June 2023 Update - New Walking Tour 📢</description></item><item><title>The IRA, The Boston College Tapes and Who Tells The Past? | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350316/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2014 17:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350316/</guid><description>Podcast Description 1972 was one of the darkest yet defining years in modern Irish history. Nearly five hundred people were killed in the conflict known as “The Troubles” in Northern Ireland. Events of that year like Bloody Sunday, Bloody Friday and Operation Motorman would shape Ireland for decades to come. In many ways one death has been remembered more than any other – this was abduction and murder of Jean McConville in December 1972.</description></item><item><title>Ireland 1014 - What a Difference a Millennium Makes | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350317/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 16:56:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350317/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this day 1000 years today, one of the most famous battle in Irish history, the Battle of Clontarf&amp;nbsp;took place. In this show I look at day to day life in Ireland in 1014. Its a strange world that would stun, shock and surprise in equal measure.
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts
Patreon www.patreon.com/irishpodcast
Acast https://plus.acast.com/s/irishhistory
📢June 2023 Update - New Walking Tour 📢</description></item><item><title>Five of the Greatest Killers in Irish History | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350318/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2014 13:24:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350318/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a show with a title such as this you might expect names such as Oliver Cromwell or Strongbow to feature heavily. While these men are responsible for the deaths of thousands of people in Ireland, the greatest killers in Irish history are not humans but disease. In this show I take a look at the worst diseases to hit Ireland and how they changed the course of our history.</description></item><item><title>Friend or Foe: The Impact of the Potato on Irish History | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350319/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2014 10:43:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350319/</guid><description>Podcast Description The potato is synonymous with the biggest disaster in Irish history – the Great Famine of the 1840s. However this is only part of the story of the potato in Irish history. The arrival of the potato in Ireland transformed the island and resulted in changes in how people lived their lives. In the podcast I examine the good, the bad and the ugly of the potato's fascinating and chequered relationship with Ireland.</description></item><item><title>Ireland's Other Great Famine - The Year of Slaughter of 1740-41 | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350320/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2014 14:19:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350320/</guid><description>Podcast Description Everyone has heard of the Great Irish Famine of the 1840's when around 10% of the Irish population died from starvation and disease. This however was not the worst famine in Irish history. A century earlier in the 1740s the island was ravaged by an event known as the year of slaughter when as much as 20% of the population perished.
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts</description></item><item><title>The Battle of Ath-an-Chip and The Life of the Rebel King Aodh O'Connor. | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350321/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2014 11:02:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350321/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1270 the battle of Ath-an-Chip saw a major Gaelic Army take on the forces of the powerful Norman Lord of Connacht Walter de Burgh on the upper reaches of the river Shannon. This decisive battle would shape the history of medieval Ireland in Connacht for decades if not centuries to come...
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts
Patreon www.patreon.com/irishpodcast
Acast https://plus.acast.com/s/irishhistory
📢June 2023 Update - New Walking Tour 📢</description></item><item><title>Medieval Ireland - Was There Ever Any Good Old Days? | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350322/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2014 09:31:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350322/</guid><description>Podcast Description Most of the podcasts I make focus on the darker aspects of medieval life. War is a common theme and famine is never far away. However in this podcast I am asking the question was life in medieval Ireland ever anything other than an endless struggle for survival. The show starts in the Vale of Dublin in 1326 when the region was an apocalyptic wasteland before looking back to 1234 when the region enjoyed better days.</description></item><item><title>Climate Change in Medieval Ireland; A Warning From The Past | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350323/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 16:28:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350323/</guid><description>Podcast Description Climate change is constantly in the news. In the late 13th &amp;amp; early 14th centuries Ireland was also battered by storms and maligned by poor weather. This podcast takes a look at some of the ways it impacted the medieval world. While society didn't collapse if the experience of our ancestors is anything to go by our future could be something of a rocky and hungry road!
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts</description></item><item><title>A Real Medieval Mile - A Walk Through Dublin in 1320 | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350324/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 11:33:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350324/</guid><description>Podcast Description What did Dublin sound like in 1320? What was the news of the day? Who were the people who lived there? In this episode you will experience the world of late medieval Dublin. The podcast takes the form of a walk through the city as it was in 1320 where we encounter everything from pigs roaming the streets to the city hangman Philip of Colchester.
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts</description></item><item><title>From Carpenter's Son to King - The Lambert Simnel Conspiracy of 1487. | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350325/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 09:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350325/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lambert Simnel's life must be one of the most unusual stories from medieval history. Born the son of a carpenter he became embroiled in a conspiracy to overthrow Henry VII and before he knew what was happening he became the only english King crowned in Ireland and was on his way to invading England...
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts
Patreon www.patreon.com/irishpodcast
Acast https://plus.acast.com/s/irishhistory
📢June 2023 Update - New Walking Tour 📢</description></item><item><title>Prostitution in Medieval Ireland - The Story of Cristiana la Sadelhackere | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350326/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2014 17:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350326/</guid><description>Podcast Description This podcast is based on this article I wrote on my blog (irishhistorypodcast.ie) about Cristiana la Sadelhackere, a woman who worked as a prostitute in medieval Ireland. Her story is an intriguing account of a precarious life on the fringes of medieval society struggling against the authorities of the day. The podcast also takes a fascinating look at why women became prostitutes in medieval Ireland and how wider society viewed them.</description></item><item><title>Drogheda 1310 - Murder and Solidarity in a Medieval Crisis | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350327/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2013 08:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350327/</guid><description>Podcast Description The year is 1310. Ireland was gripped by a severe economic, military and political crisis - pretty much everything that could go wrong had gone wrong for the Norman colonists. In October, a man called Jordan the Chaplain made his way to Drogheda, a major port in medieval Ireland. However not long after arriving he got involved in a dispute with one of the townspeople - Robert the Tailor.</description></item><item><title>(1101 - 1103) The Great War of Ulster and Munster (Part II) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350328/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2013 11:44:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350328/</guid><description>Podcast Description This show returns to the story of Gaelic Ireland in the final decades prior to the Norman Invasion. Ireland is being torn apart by long running tensions between the kings of Munster and Ulster. The show begins in 1101 with Donal McLochlainn the king of the O'Neills on his knees. His great rival Muirchertach O'Briain, the king of Munster had just invaded and ravaged his kingdom. However Donal is by no means finished; further war and bloodshed loom ahead.</description></item><item><title>The Top 5 Turning Points in Medieval Ireland: (Part II ) The Battle of Athenry | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350329/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 13:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350329/</guid><description>Podcast Description This podcast concludes our journey through the Top 5 turning points of Medieval Ireland. This show focuses on one of the most intriguing events of our medieval past, the Battle of Athenry in 1316. This conflict occurred during one of the most fascinating wars in Irish history - the Bruce Invasion of 1315-18. In May 1315, a Scots army led by Edward Bruce, brother to the King of Scotland, invaded Ireland, so this podcast starts in Scotland, with none other than William Wallace a.</description></item><item><title>The Top 5 Turning Points in Medieval Ireland (Part I) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350330/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2013 18:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350330/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is a whistlestop tour through medieval Ireland stopping off at battlefields along the way, taking a look at the top five&amp;nbsp;turning points as I see them. This podcast will introduce some of the key characters from Irish history, some of whom are well known such as Strongbow and Brian Boru, others less well-known but equally fascinating such as Flann Sinna and William 'Liath de Burgh'. Part I starts in 908 at the long forgotten battle of Ballymoon and finishes at the siege of Dublin in 1171.</description></item><item><title>Ireland 1300 A.D. A Tale of Honour, Violence and Justice | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350331/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2013 14:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350331/</guid><description>Podcast Description Honour was all important in Ireland in 1300 A.D. Unsurprisingly when a miller, Walter de Capella, insulted the mistress of John Thebaud it sparked a row between the two men. This row escalated and within a few short weeks a vicious and ultimately violent feud broke out. This podcast tells the story of the previously untold, hair-raising story of medieval&amp;nbsp;honour, violence and justice...
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts</description></item><item><title>Castlekevin: Life and Death on a Medieval Frontier | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350332/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2013 13:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350332/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, the long forgotten ruins of the medieval fortress and town of Castlekevin, are situated in a remote valley in the Wicklow mountains. In the early 14th century this was the epicentre of a ferocious struggle between Gaelic Irish and Norman Colonists in the Wicklow Mountains. This podcast charts the long and bloody battle for survival at Castlekevin when the surrounding region became a warzone.
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts</description></item><item><title>The Norman Conquest of Connacht | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350333/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 16:11:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350333/</guid><description>Podcast Description During the high summer of 1235 the west of Ireland witnessed one of the most violent chapters in its history when the Normans launched their conquest of the west. This campaign culminated in the storming of an Island fortress using siege engines on floating platforms and fire-ships. Need I say more?
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts
Patreon www.patreon.com/irishpodcast
Acast https://plus.acast.com/s/irishhistory
📢June 2023 Update - New Walking Tour 📢</description></item><item><title>The 1317 Siege of Dublin | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350334/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 16:01:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350334/</guid><description>Podcast Description In February 1317 Dublin faced its greatest crisis. A huge army lead by Robert the Bruce, king of Scotlan d was making its way to lay siege to the city. With no army to defend the city, Dubliners were effectively on their own. However everyone in the city could not be trusted, a few days earlier the Earl of Ulster who also happened to be Bruce’s father in law arrived.</description></item><item><title>Special: Dennis Doherty – A Life of Survival Against the Odds | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350335/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2013 15:49:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350335/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode looks at the fascinating story of Dennis Doherty. Born in Derry in 1814, Doherty would spend most of his life in Australian prisons. His story is remarkable – he was flogged 3,000 times and spent years in solitary confinement but yet he continually struggled for freedom.
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts
Patreon www.patreon.com/irishpodcast
Acast https://plus.acast.com/s/irishhistory
📢June 2023 Update - New Walking Tour 📢</description></item><item><title>The Great Gaelic Revolt of the 1270s | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350336/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 16:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350336/</guid><description>Podcast Description After the Norman conquest of Ireland, the Wicklow region was surprisingly peaceful. Despite the fact the Gaelic Irish had been dispossessed, many appeared to be getting on with life. This was deceptive and in 1270 a massive rebellion broke out deep in the Mountains that would see settlement after settlement raided and burned. This is the story of that rebellion...
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts</description></item><item><title>Dublin 1303: The Business of War | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350337/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 16:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350337/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1303 the Earl of Ulster, Richard de Burgh, amassed a large army in Dublin which was destined for Scotland. In the podcast we look at a forgotten story of medieval Dubliners who had to undertake what now seem as strange, unusual and often chaotic preparations to get a medieval army to the battlefield and the chaos this caused for people in early 14th century Dublin.
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts</description></item><item><title>(1090-1101) The Great War of Ulster and Munster (Part I) | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350338/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 16:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350338/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1090 Muirchertach O Briain, grandson of Brian Boru, faced the darkest moment of his rule as King of Munster. Defeated and vanquished by his rival the king of Ulster, Domnal McLochlainn, he faced two options; either accept his fate or try to claw his way back to power. As grandson of Brian Boru giving up wasn't in his DNA.
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts</description></item><item><title>(1072 -1090) The Return of the O Briains | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350339/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 16:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350339/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1072 the aging King of Leinster Diarmait Mc Mael na mBó died. His death saw the descendents of Brian Boru try to follow in the footsteps of their famous ancestor and dominate Ireland but there was a queue of people waiting to stop them.&amp;nbsp;Although initially Ireland witnessed a certain amount of stability, the rise of the O Briains sparked a ferocious struggle as several kings sought to dominate the island.</description></item><item><title>Life in Ireland in the 11th Century | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350340/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 16:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350340/</guid><description>Podcast Description The year is 1067. Godwin Godwinson the son and heir to the dead Saxon king Harold Godwinson fled to Ireland after the Norman Invasion of England. This podcast looks at the world he found in Ireland. How did he travel to Ireland? What did Dublin look like, sound like and smell like? What did people eat? What did they look like? What weapons did people use? What was the Brehon law?</description></item><item><title>Special: The Assassination of the Land Agent John Ellis | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350341/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 16:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350341/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 15 is a story of murder and injustice, set in 19th century Ireland. In a country struggling to recover from the famine tenants despised landlords and their agents who had treated them brutally during the famine. When an agent John Ellis was assassinated in north Tipperary in 1857 almost everyone in the area became a suspect. Find out what happened next...
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts</description></item><item><title>(1022-1072) The Man Who Would be King | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350342/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 16:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350342/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 14 sees Gaelic Ireland struggle to deal with the crisis and chaos that followed the death of the high king Maelseachnaill Mac Domnaill. In a highly uncertain world where war was frequent and life had little value as several kings battled to control the island. We will see many try and fail to emulate the great high kings of the past
This show also includes a close look at the strange place that was Viking Dublin and the unknown history of the Gaelic Irish reaction to the Norman invasion of England in 1066.</description></item><item><title>Special: The Nine Years War and the Great Dublin Explosion of 1597 | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350343/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 16:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350343/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1597 Dublin was ripped apart by a massive explosion which killed over 1% of the city’s population. This podcast looks at the background to the incredible events of March 1597. The 9 Years War was raging and tensions ran high in Dublin as an English Army used the city as a logistical base. In March a huge shipment of gunpowder arrives in Dublin and the rest is history!</description></item><item><title>(1000 -1022) Brian Boru, The Battle of Clontarf and Its Aftermath | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350344/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 16:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350344/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brian Boru is without doubt Ireland’s most well known medieval king, while a battle he fought in 1014, the Battle of Contarf, is Irelands most famous medieval conflict. In this podcast we look at the real story behind Brian and the Battle of Clontarf. How did he become high-king? Was he really the first man to unify Ireland? What happened after Brian Boru died?
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts</description></item><item><title>(980 -1000) The Pursuit of Power: (Part III) A New Millennium and A New King | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350345/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350345/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 10 sees a titantic struggle between the two most powerful Iirsh Kings of the early medieval Ireland - the O Neill High King, Maelseachnaill II and Brian Boru, the King of Munster.
In a story full of intriguing naval attacks, sieges and deceit the superpowers of 10th century Ireland, unleash their devastating military power on each other with fascinating consequences....
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts</description></item><item><title>(944 – 980) The Pursuit of Power: (Part II) The Rise of Brian Boru and the Dál Cais | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350346/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350346/</guid><description>Podcast Description Medieval Ireland stands on the edge of a precipice. A rootless struggle for control of the O'Neill kingdom breaks out in the North, while in Munster a new comer to the podcast – the Dal Cais challenge the King of Munster for power in the South. With Ireland on the verge of chaos we look at how war impacted the lives of ordinary people as they had to battle famine, hard winters and an out break of leprosy and dysentery.</description></item><item><title>(919-944) The Pursuit of Power: (Part 1) The Decline of the O’Neills | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350347/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2013 15:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350347/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode charts a fascinating story that wil finish with the rise of Brian Boru. Gripping, ruthless and at times blood curdling this history is full of twists and turns. Over the next three shows we will see the O Neill kingdom challenged by the Dal Cais (the family of Brian Boru). This will see many challengers rise and fall as these two families battle it out for supremacy in medieval Ireland.</description></item><item><title>St. Patrick and the Conversion of Ireland | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350348/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 16:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350348/</guid><description>Podcast Description Each year on March 17th, millions of people attend St Patrick’s day parades in memory of the man who reputedly converted the Irish to Christianity. He is a figure shrouded in myth but in this podcast we examine the truth behind the one time slave and famous bishop Patrick…
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts
Patreon www.patreon.com/irishpodcast
Acast https://plus.acast.com/s/irishhistory
📢June 2023 Update - New Walking Tour 📢</description></item><item><title>(902-930) Changing Times in Medieval Ireland | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350349/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 16:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350349/</guid><description>Podcast Description This show begins an exciting journey through one of the most turbulent years in Medieval Ireland. From 902 - 930 Ireland’s most powerful family – The O Neills go to war with their traditional enemies – The Eoganacht. However the Vikings are waiting in the wings to take advantage of the chaos that follows starting an even larger conflict.
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts</description></item><item><title>(820 - 902) Raiding and Trading With The Vikings | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350350/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 16:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350350/</guid><description>Podcast Description The early 9th century saw the Vikings step up their raids and attacks on Ireland. Terror gripped coastal communities as vast fleets appeared on the horizon unleashing brutal raids. This podcast looks at how the Gaelic fought back. Will also Vikings found a rough trading post known as 'An Dubh Linn', The Dark Pool or as we know it today Dublin.
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts</description></item><item><title>Ireland and the Viking World | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350351/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 16:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350351/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 3 is a whistle stop tour through the Viking World visiting places from Baghdad to Newfoundland explaining how the Vikings connected these far flung places to Ireland. In this episode we also see the first Africans arrive in Ireland in the 9th century and explain how a coin from Armenia ended up amongst the remains of people massacred by the vikings in rural Ireland in the 10th century!</description></item><item><title>The Vikings Arrive | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350352/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 16:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350352/</guid><description>Podcast Description This shows looks at the arrival of one of the most fearsome and notorious warriors in Irish history – the Vikings. These Scandinavians have been caricatured throughout the centuries as marauding maniacs a somewhat undeserved reputation. However in this episode they don’t exactly cover themselves in glory.
The show will reveal what drove people in Scandinavia to launch what were terrifying raids, how these raiders reached Ireland and then before the episode ends we will join them for their onslaught on Irish monasteries.</description></item><item><title>Barbarians | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350353/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2013 16:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350353/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode begins what will be a fascinating journey through the last 1500 years of Irish History looking at some of the most fascinating chapters in the island’s past. While the coming episodes will chart everything from great battles to Viking raids all the way to rebellions we will also stop in the houses, towns and villages to see what daily life was like for our distant and not so distant ancestors.</description></item><item><title>What You Can Expect From The Irish History Podcast | Irish History Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1894350354/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2010 07:16:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1894350354/</guid><description>Podcast Description From Viking raids to mysterious murders in remote comunities, Irish history has inspired some of the greatest stories ever told. This introductory episode gives you a flavour of what you can expect from the Irish History Podcast.
Twitter - @irishhistory
Email - info(at)irishhistorypodcast.ie
www.irishhistorypodcast.ie
Become a supporter &amp;amp; access dozens of exclusive podcasts
Patreon www.patreon.com/irishpodcast
Acast https://plus.acast.com/s/irishhistory
📢June 2023 Update - New Walking Tour 📢
I am thrilled to announce my brand new walking tour in Ireland's oldest city, Waterford.</description></item></channel></rss>