<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/hamish-andys-remembering-project/</link><description>Recent content in Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 13:05:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/hamish-andys-remembering-project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>We Force Ronan Keating To Issue A Public Apology | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andy remembers the one and only time he swore live on-air, and the boys thoroughly enjoy listening back to the fashion faux pax Ronan Keating made on their show in 2009!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>New Episodes out now - here is the Trailer! | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390002/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 04:09:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season 5 of Hamish and Andy's Remembering Project starts Thursday December 7 wherever you get your podcasts.
New episodes then drop every Thursday across Summer... or you can hear them 1 week earlier on the Free Listnr App (or at LiSTNR.com for International listeners).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>'We Have The Cassettes From Our First Ever Community Radio Shows!' | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390003/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this special episode, Hamish &amp;amp; Andy listen back to audio they’ve never heard before; their first community radio breaks from over 20 years ago that have been digitised from cassette!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Andy’s Mum Can’t Tell Us Apart | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390005/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boys remember their failed attempts at learning ‘Uptown Funk’ when rehearsing for Cool Boys &amp;amp; The Frontman, and pivoting to an easier song. Plus they remember the time they pranked Andy’s mum in the Switch Up Game.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What Happened In Dream Week Again? | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390004/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the season finale the boys remember the time they lost a lot of money making DVDs for True Story which would never sell, Hamish fondly remembers Layla’s Loot Shoot, and the guys reminisce about Dream Week, where Hamish had a psychic dream about Adam Levine.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Winds Of Glory Update After 8 Years | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390006/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boys remember the time Matt Damon named a listener’s baby as part of, “Baby Namin’ with Matt Damon,” going totally nuts with listeners in Beijing, and look back at one of their favourite segments, ‘Winds of Glory,’ where listeners would fart in famous places.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How The Logies Ruined Our Friendship | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390007/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boys remember an iconic quote from Catherine Zeta-Jones, as well as Hamish’s dad’s aversion to Emojis. Plus, they recall when they were both nominated for the Gold Logie - which nearly tore their friendship apart.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>All About Dogs | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390008/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boys remember Paris Hilton’s brief prison stint, and reminisce about dog movies that they saw over the years. Plus, they deep dive into a shortlived segment called “Loophole Hunters” where the guys try to find a loophole in the rules of soccer that also happened to involve dogs.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>I Shouldn’t Have Cupped For Streaking Duk | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390009/</guid><description>Podcast Description A good memory test about an old Holly Valance film, plus the hard task of trying to get an emoji approved. Then the boys remember the time they streaked with Peking Duk, purely because they thought “Streaking Duk” was a funny pun, and they recall the woes of one of their producers who had to drive the four naked men home from a soccer pitch for the stunt.</description></item><item><title>The Full Backstory Of The U2 Surprise | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390011/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390011/</guid><description>Podcast Description A special look back at the boy's 'Thank You Tour' in 2010, where in front of a packed crowd at Melbourne's Sidney Myer Music Bowl the guys from U2 walked on stage and performed some of their hits. Go behind the scenes and hear the whole story of how that surprise came to happen.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Tax Office... Please Don't Listen! | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390010/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish remembers Andy’s huge crush on DJ Havana Brown (that Andy disputes), and the date with her that Andy was supposedly too nervous to go on. Then's there's a little joking around that the Tax Office definitely shouldn't take too seriously and the guys recall ringing a Car Wash to find out if they did kids parties.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Laughing About The Thing That Just Happened | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390013/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390013/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boys remember the time they bought an island (or islet) off the coast of Australia, and debate its size. Plus, they dig up audio of the time Hugh Jackman may have given out his address, and recall one of their favourite radio moments, a segment called “The Thing That Just Happened.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Time We Pranked The Oscars As Hugh Jackman | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390012/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boys recall the day they lost power to the studio, they try to remember the premise of their 'Minus 1 Letter Movie Trailers' and they play back the audio from the time they pretended to be Hugh Jackman while he was hosting the 2009 Oscars at the Kodak Theatre, and caught a member of the Oscars props department unaware…
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Horgs' 'I Hate Mondays' Song Comes To Life | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 14:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390014/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boys remember an old game they would play called Force Connect, where they would connect two strangers together and see who would hang up first. Plus, Horgs’ song about hating Mondays is brought to life by Newton Faulkner.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Horne Identity | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 14:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390015/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boys remember appearing on Jay Leno when they invented ghosting, which was banned from several schools around Australia. Hamish recalls an ill-fated bike ride with a celebrity chef, and the guys remember a gossip segment they never wanted to do, 'The Horne Identity'.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Season 4 Out Now | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish and Andy are looking at the run sheets from over 2,500 shows across two decades of radio shows and picking one singular talk break to try and remember.
In Season 4... they recall Layla's Loot Chute, pranking the Oscars, settling the People's Island, how the Logies nearly ended their friendship, Winds of Glory, Streaking Duk and they give you the full backstory to the epic U2 surprise in 2010.</description></item><item><title>Early Days With Rove | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390017/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the Season 3 Finale...The boys look back on a classic segment they did in 2014, &amp;lsquo;Ripley&amp;rsquo;s Eat It Or Not,&amp;rsquo; in which listeners would send in crazy things they found in packaged foods, such as a double Mentos in a single Mentos packet - which Hamish believes could have been fake. Plus, Rove drops into the studio on the boys&amp;rsquo; Saturday morning show way back in 2005.</description></item><item><title>The Shoe Horn Blitz Apology | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390018/</guid><description>Podcast Description The guys give an insight to the perils of putting live callers to air on the radio without much time for the producers to prep them. They revisit one of their early terrible pun-based ideas for a celebrity guest. Plus, Hamish recalls his infamous &amp;lsquo;Shoehorn Blitz&amp;rsquo; phase, in which he would give out shoehorns to listeners who wanted them. But on this particular date, Hamish was apologising about the shoehorns, as he over-promised and under-delivered&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Our Band's First Ever Performance | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390019/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boys remember some of the huge celebrities they had on the show, including Borat, and the fact that Sacha Baron Cohen would never break character while promoting the film, and Sam Worthington, who was promoting Avatar. They then tell the story of the genesis of their band &amp;lsquo;Cool Boys and the Frontman&amp;rsquo; and we relive their first ever performance with Rob Thomas as they attempt to cover Santana&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Smooth&amp;rsquo;.</description></item><item><title>We Egged Our Bosses' House | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390020/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boys remember the time they egged their boss Grumpy Dave&amp;rsquo;s house with a listener, and Andy drove away in the getaway car without him. They try to dissect why their early prank calls were so bad. Plus, the boys look back at when they created an acapella version of Bohemian Rhapsody, followed by Britney Spears&amp;rsquo; classic song, Piece of Me.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jack's First Song For The Show | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390021/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390021/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boys remember one of Hame&amp;rsquo;s best ideas to mark the passing of a celebrity. They discuss one of their many overseas trips and they play the audio from Jack&amp;rsquo;s first ever song on the show.&amp;nbsp; Spoiler alert&amp;hellip;it wasn&amp;rsquo;t very good.&amp;nbsp;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Stealing From Richard Wilkins | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390022/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boys remember their old audio producer, Deano, who would constantly sleep in, use company resources to download music from Limewire, and have extended smoke breaks. They look back at some alternative flavour options for The People&amp;rsquo;s Chip, and talk about the time they dressed as Robin Hood to steal from entertainment reporter Richard Wilkins.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Ant Fart | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390024/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boys had a lot of guests on the show over the years - some more often than others and they recall a rule about guests that had an unintended consequence.&amp;nbsp; They play the audio from one of the greatest moments to ever happen in the history of radio: the broadcast of an ant farting. Plus Andy remembers the time they tried to position Baileys as a sports drink.</description></item><item><title>Wippa Tries To Buy A Lamborghini | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390023/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boys reminisce about celebrities they completely forgot were on the show, like &amp;lsquo;Weird Al&amp;rsquo; Yankovic. This causes an argument about his back catalog of Parody Songs. Plus, they look back at the time they set their friend Wippa up to try and test drive a Lamborghini, in a prank that wasn&amp;rsquo;t thought out well at all.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Spinning The Gympie KFC Bucket | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390025/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390025/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boys reminisce about when Andy thought he was tougher than Mick Gatto, and was later confronted by Mick about his comments. They remember their challenge to find out who could be the ultimate Daryl Braith-mate, and finish by listening to the time they got Gympie&amp;rsquo;s KFC bucket to spin again.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The First Ever Rattle Your Rival | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390026/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390026/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boys reminisce about when cricketer David Boon blessed their Tall Ship before setting out on their adventure to cross Bass Straight. They recall their attempts to rig a raffle to win a Bull. Then go back to the origins of a now regular segment, when they try to prank several of Andy&amp;rsquo;s brother&amp;rsquo;s mates in the first ever &amp;ldquo;Rattle Your Rival&amp;rdquo; on the show.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Australia's Best Bloke | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390028/</guid><description>Podcast Description What did K-Rudd do in the studio that may have lost him the 2013 election? Plus how hard is it to score a Private Jet for free? Finally the boys revisit one of the best pranks they ever did&amp;hellip; trying to find a complete stranger to be an instant job referee.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rihanna Stole Our Song | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390027/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390027/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boys look back at the time they hypnotised their Web Geezer Jez to try and recover the password for their lost Bitcoin. They also discuss a shock move from the Federal Government in 2009 that still hasn&amp;rsquo;t happened. They educate Mike about Stable Tables and remember the time they tried to sue Rihanna in 2012, for stealing one of Hamish&amp;rsquo;s musical ideas.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Season 3 Available Now | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390029/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish and Andy are looking at the run sheets from over 2,500 shows across two decades and picking one singular talk break to discuss.
In Season 3... they talk about trying to sue a famous celebrity for theft, attempting to rig a raffle for a Bull, the efforts to score a private jet for free and egging their bosses house.
So download the LiSTNR App now and listen for free.</description></item><item><title>Tackle Talk | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390030/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390030/</guid><description>Podcast Description 14 years later and Andy&amp;rsquo;s tackle is still being talked about! &amp;nbsp;The boys replay a call to Andy&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Dick Doc&amp;rsquo; from the sperm bank!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The boys also&amp;nbsp;remember the one night they spent on The People&amp;rsquo;s Island, and their very own Lord of the Flies moment.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Hamish recalls the summer he spent playing Band Hero with his housemates, and the pain of not winning the title of Summer Drummer.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Do You Have Any Ugly Models On Your Books? | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390031/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390031/</guid><description>Podcast Description The &amp;lsquo;Andy by Hamish&amp;rsquo; fragrance photoshoot was one of the most bizarre moments in the history of the Hamish &amp;amp; Andy Show.&amp;nbsp; The boys listen back to the negotiation and list of demands Andy had before the shoot.&amp;nbsp; They also fondly remember their London Lair from Gap Year in 2012, and Hamish regrets a chance encounter with actor Jon Hamm. The boys recall making t-shirts for the Peoples Cruise, and the black-market cash-only stall they ran to sell them.</description></item><item><title>Fred's First Race | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390032/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish &amp;amp; Andy remember their early days on the Saturday morning show, and listen back to one of their first song-parodies and understand why the radio bosses told them to stop singing! Brian McFadden makes yet another appearance, as well as Chris Hemsworth and Mark Ruffalo. On this day in 2017 they had their first band rehearsal and they discuss the external influences that were responsible for it sounding average!</description></item><item><title>What “Do Not Put On The Website” Used To Mean | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390033/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish &amp;amp; Andy remember all the different ways they have celebrated Andy&amp;rsquo;s birthdays on the show, including when Hamish pole danced for him dressed as Khaleesi, and the logistical disaster that was Andy Fest! The boys remember playing Celebrity Crush-hunt and how much harder it was to contact celebrities 14 years ago. They revisit the time they spent an hour with Will Ferrell, and replay audio of the big-name golfers Hamish organised to wish Andy a happy birthday!</description></item><item><title>Pranking The Nicest Guy We Know | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390034/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish &amp;amp; Andy remember one of their favourite Rick Davies stories, &amp;lsquo;The Christmas Turd&amp;rsquo;, and listen back to the time they pranked Rick and he cemented himself as the nicest human ever.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; The also look back on the &amp;lsquo;Kids Meals for Everybody&amp;rsquo; initiative, and the subsequent backlash from the hospitality industry! They discuss a favourite segment, International Phrasebook, and&amp;nbsp;the time their dads were&amp;nbsp;thrilled&amp;nbsp;about receiving&amp;nbsp;free power tools!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;And to round things out we hear about when&amp;nbsp;Shane Jacobson offered&amp;nbsp;them the use of his tour bus.</description></item><item><title>Chopping Up A Studio With A Machete | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390035/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish &amp;amp; Andy recall the technical difficulties they faced surrounding The People's Island, and Hamish&amp;rsquo;s ratbag behaviour at a regional radio station which he apologies for 7 years later! The boys then reminisce about taking competition winners to the 2008 Beijing Olympics and taking them to Hooters! They then replay one of the all-time greatest &amp;lsquo;Blast from the Past&amp;rsquo; segments when Hamish calls a random number pretending to be an Olympic athlete and asks for a &amp;ldquo;cheeky wee sample&amp;rdquo;!</description></item><item><title>The Great Ten Tenors Mystery | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390036/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2021 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish &amp;amp; Andy remember how they had to interview the whole cast of High School Musical when all they wanted to chat to was Zac Efron! They also had the 10 Tenors on the show but cannot remember why! They get completely derailed trying to remember which old radio acquaintance married one of the Tenors. The boys listen back to the high stakes Peoples Bet that they placed in a Vegas Casino trying to win enough money for a Hoverboard!</description></item><item><title>Origins: Timomatic’s Autograph | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390037/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish &amp;amp; Andy fondly remember the waitress at the Penis-eating restaurant in Beijing, and how ripped off they felt about the Phelps vs a shark race. The boys listen back to when they called actor Brett Tucker to see if he was hitting on their friend Tanya, and to the original prank call that Hamish made which spiraled into a yearlong side-hustle selling Timomatic's forged autographs! &amp;nbsp;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Becoming Celebrity Friends with Will Arnett | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390038/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish &amp;amp; Andy discuss one of Hamish&amp;rsquo;s greatest regrets from The People's Cruise. The boys remember their UK and Ireland Caravan of Courage trip, including a suspect and slippery massage, as well as fearing for their lives at Appleby Fair. The boys recall the first time Will Arnett came on the show and how they set up the room to make the interview as awkward as possible!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>You’re Full Of Lies Not Dumplings | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390039/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish &amp;amp; Andy remember the year Andy won Cleo Bachelor of the Year, and how 10 years later to the day, Shane Warne was on the show pitching a new bachelor style TV show starring him &amp;amp; Andy! They peak behind the curtain when it comes to radio station rivalries, and some of the lengths they had to go to, to win clients over. The boys remember back to when Horg&amp;rsquo;s mate claimed he could eat 100 dumplings which sparked one of our favourite lines of all time; &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;re full of lies, not dumplings&amp;rdquo;!</description></item><item><title>We Loved Pranking The Office Staff | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390040/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish &amp;amp; Andy remember how much fun they used to have tormenting the staff who worked at the radio station! They listen back to a time they got access to the elevator security footage to see which staff members were the most vain. They also reminisced about a super awkward Christmas stitch-up that forced staff members to choose a hamper over donating to charity.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How The Private Jet Tour Nearly Didn’t Happen | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390041/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish &amp;amp; Andy reveal for the first time how their private jet tour very nearly fell apart at the last minute. They also reminisce about one of the more bizarre shows they ever did, involving Johanna Griggs, Hamish&amp;rsquo;s Grandma Moosey, and a couch!&amp;nbsp;
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ultimate Wingman Works His Magic With Lily Allen | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390042/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish &amp;amp; Andy remember some of their earliest feedback from radio bosses &amp;ndash; &amp;ldquo;Stop singing...you&amp;rsquo;re not the Scared Weird Little Guys!&amp;rdquo; They recall when the Frank Stallone concert sold out in 6 minutes, as well as interviews with Seth Rogen, Olly Murs and Lily Allen. They listen back to a Lily Allen interview where she barely gets a word in, and Andy hesitantly reminds Hamish of one of his only Ultimate Wingman success stories &amp;ndash; Andy&amp;rsquo;s pash with Lily!</description></item><item><title>The Time We Did The Whole Show On The Phone | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390043/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish &amp;amp; Andy remember one of the times they had to do an on-air retraction for something they got wrong on the show, which naturally they blame Jack for. They recall chatting to Buzz Aldrin and how much it bugged Buzz that nobody remembers his famous line from the moon. On this day in 2016 Hamish was thrilled to discover there are golf club &amp;lsquo;captains&amp;rsquo; and the process that new golfers need to go through to be accepted.</description></item><item><title>Confirming a Crazy Rod Stewart Rumour | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390044/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish &amp;amp; Andy reminisce about the tactics they used to wriggle out of doing extra work, and reopen the debate about whether fish are ornamental or a pet. The boys remember taste-testing samples for the Gravy Chip and how they decided between chicken or beef gravy. They also confirmed a bizarre rumour Hamish had heard about Rod Stewart, and we hear when Andy was surprised with his childhood celebrity crush and it didn't quite go to plan.</description></item><item><title>Robbing with Rob Thomas…And Paul | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390045/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish &amp;amp; Andy remember their first EVER guest back in 2004, and a special memory from the Business Brunch days. The boys relive the week in 2007 that they spent as conjoined twins and the length Hamish went to, to conceal Andy while at his then-girlfriend&amp;rsquo;s family dinner! The boys then listen back to an interview with Rob Thomas and his less famous band member, Paul.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Free Kick For Farting | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390046/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish &amp;amp; Andy recall a vow that Hamish took back in 2014 and he's just as fired up about it 7 years on. The boys remember preparing to visit the troops in Afghanistan and some of the safety precautions put in place in the lead up to their departure. They also revisit one of the great sports stories &amp;ndash; a soccer player who got a yellow card for farting!</description></item><item><title>Staking Out Bob Panic’s House | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390047/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish &amp;amp; Andy remember the extremely fast &amp;amp; loose way that Hame started the year off in 2008, and the inappropriate request they put forward to the Australian Government regarding Kevin Rudd&amp;rsquo;s son. The boys reminisce about the &amp;lsquo;Ideas Bonanza&amp;rsquo; and listener Bob Panic who was put in charge of answering all incoming calls to the Bonanza hotline. There was also a competition the show ran involving V8 supercars and Sambuca and how, unsurprisingly, they ran into legal troubles.</description></item><item><title>Kyle and Jackie O Banned Us From The Station | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390048/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish &amp;amp; Andy recall one of their first forays into client integration with Mitsubishion Impossible! How you could become a Million-Yen-Aire and why they ended up in Adelaide at Mitsubishi&amp;rsquo;s head office. They discuss why it was smart of Kyle &amp;amp; Jackie O to ban them from broadcasting on the same station, and they question why Brian McFadden was on the show so often in the early days! The boys also listen back to the first ever Trading Post Game, and listener Nath finally gets the credit he deserves!</description></item><item><title>Andy Living Next Door To Kylie and Dannii Minogue | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390049/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish &amp;amp; Andy relive the time they attempted to &amp;lsquo;Eat the Board&amp;rsquo; at Maccas and how controversial the Chicken and Cheese burger became in their quest. Hamish remembers when Andy first began dating Bec and a major hurdle they had to overcome. They also reminisce about the time that Karl Stefanovic dabbled in documentary making, and when Andy had some very famous Neighbours. The boys then replay the moment Dannii Minogue brought in audio of Andy performing in his primary school musical!</description></item><item><title>It’s Amazing That Tom Cruise Bothers | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390050/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish &amp;amp; Andy remember how they got on actor Colin Firth&amp;rsquo;s good side, and the incredible interview preparation that Tom Cruise must have done before they spoke to him.&amp;nbsp; The boys also talk about a time they had to make a formal apology to a client after explaining on air how easy it is to steal from them.&amp;nbsp; They also listen back to a time way back in 2007 when a listener agreed to let them look after their kids for a weekend.</description></item><item><title>Frank Stallone’s Parade Through Melbourne | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390051/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish &amp;amp; Andy remember broadcasting from the Beijing Olympic Games, especially the Channel Seven team worrying about getting food poisoning.&amp;nbsp; The boys also recall when Daryl Braithwaite sung a charity song to help them raise funds to buy a hoverboard.&amp;nbsp; We also listen back to when they took Frank Stallone on a parade thought the streets of Melbourne just hours before the concert of the year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hamish the Futurist | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390052/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish &amp;amp; Andy recall the time their mate Horgs was challenged to swim across a pond to win a bet.&amp;nbsp; The boys remember two celebrities that made them wait for an interview, Johnny Knoxville and Edward Norton.&amp;nbsp; They also recall their decision to try and sail across Bass Strait in treacherous conditions.&amp;nbsp; And they listen back to audio of Hamish predicting the future in 2010.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Talking Gravox with Margot Robbie | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390053/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish &amp;amp; Andy relive two stitch ups they are not proud of.&amp;nbsp; A time they forced Dean Geyer to perform with his shirt off to a bunch of adoring fans, and a questionable way to test Anthony Callea&amp;rsquo;s height.&amp;nbsp; The boys then replay a moment when they invited Margot Robbie to the Logies Spit Roast Party, but spend the entire conversation talking about Gravox.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Timomatic’s Autograph | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390054/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish and Andy remember that when Todd Sampson was a guest on the show he really didn&amp;rsquo;t understand how the censorship &amp;lsquo;beep&amp;rsquo; worked, and consequently dropped an F Bomb live on air.&amp;nbsp; They try to recall why they made life hard for themselves during the Caravan of Courage, including Hamish sleeping in a gorilla suit.&amp;nbsp; They then listen back to 2014 when Hamish started a side-hustle selling Timomatic&amp;rsquo;s autograph.</description></item><item><title>The Bacon 100 | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390055/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish &amp;amp; Andy remember back to when Hamish&amp;rsquo;s dad Noel challenged Justin Bieber to a table tennis match.&amp;nbsp; They discuss a theory that Wippa told them about the rules of disclosing blackbelt karate skills.&amp;nbsp; And listen back to what is possibly the longest tribute song of all time&amp;hellip;the Bacon 100.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hamish’s Drum Audition | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390056/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish &amp;amp; Andy remember some of Horgs&amp;rsquo;s best/worst inventions, and the time that Jerry Seinfeld told them off.&amp;nbsp; Their attention then turns to their band Cool Boys &amp;amp; The Frontman and their constant infighting as well as a prank where Hamish auditioned for a band down the phone line.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Most Violent Fred Basset Of All Time | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390057/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish &amp;amp; Andy remember definitely not flirting with Jessica Alba and Shannon Elizabeth. They then reflect on the most violent Fred Basset reading that drew blood from Hamish&amp;rsquo;s bum, and resulted in an F Bomb dropped live to air from Japan.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ricky Gervais Critiques A Horgs' Invention | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390058/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish &amp;amp; Andy reveal the trick to wrangling holidays from their radio boss, Grumpy Dave. Andy shares too much about the time he pooed his pants at school camp, and Hamish reminisces about the marathon he ran with zero preparation. The boys then listen back to an interview from 2009 with one of the show's favourite guests, legendary comedian Ricky Gervais.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Mysterious Note Left On Hamish’s Girlfriend’s Car | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390059/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish &amp;amp; Andy try to remember why they had Chopper Reid on the show so often, given he was a convicted murderer. The boys recall a surprise visit to a stripper car wash in Darwin, and listen back to the moment Jack gave up on his panelling career. Plus, the boys look back on an uncomfortable investigation into a note left on Hamish's girlfriend's car.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Pat Your Head | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390060/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish &amp;amp; Andy have attempted some very ambitious phone topics over the years, none more so than this one in 2009 with a game that literally stopped traffic.&amp;nbsp; The boys also recall a pretty unfair prank they played on Glenn Robbins and feel that Glenn had every right to be a little pissed off about it.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Post ARIAS Potty Mouth | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390061/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Nov 2020 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish &amp;amp; Andy explain how Mike Munro from &amp;lsquo;This is Your Life&amp;rsquo; ended up in Hamish&amp;rsquo;s living room waiting for a couch delivery. They then take us back to the day after the 2007 ARIAS where they spoke to Missy Higgins and John Butler, who used language that made Hamish and Andy fear for their jobs. The boys also discuss how recording segments for the Caravan of Courage would sometimes mean making something out of nothing, including a segment about &amp;lsquo;a big tree&amp;rsquo;.</description></item><item><title>Will Jack Cry? | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390062/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish &amp;amp; Andy remember how 'Layla&amp;rsquo;s Loot Shoot' came about and tell a story about how their old boss used some insider knowledge to leave the company and become the sponsor of the show.&amp;nbsp; The boys then revisit two of their more awkward moments: a challenge to see if Andy could make Cackling Jack cry, and a fake surprise birthday party for a fairly new employee.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hamish’s New Girlfriend In 2010 Is Now His Wife | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390063/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish &amp;amp; Andy discuss a secret they had to keep from Tom Hanks&amp;nbsp;and Ron Howard after something went wrong at the preview screening of Angels &amp;amp; Demons. The boys then go back to 2010 where Hamish is talking about his new girlfriend who, as it turns out, is now his wife. They also discuss the technique they used to talk about their girlfriends without fear of them hearing.</description></item><item><title>The First 'Ahoy' | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390064/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish &amp;amp; Andy recall having a porn star on the show during the early days and whether that was a good idea at all. &amp;nbsp;It leads them to discuss why they made their friend Wippa, now a breakfast radio host himself, get his nuts bronzed and we hear a pivotal moment for the show - the very first time it was suggested that all callers should greet the show with the word &amp;lsquo;Ahoy&amp;rsquo;.</description></item><item><title>The Secret Song | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390065/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390065/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boys learn that Andy&amp;rsquo;s Dad may have kissed Pete Hellier&amp;rsquo;s Mum and reflect on the time they attempted a very ambitious interactive phone topic with the help of a two thousand strong crowd at a live show. Hamish and Andy then discuss their &amp;lsquo;secret song&amp;rsquo; performed live at their final show of the year in 2016, both wondering whether it should have remained a secret from the public rather than broadcast at all.</description></item><item><title>Nice And Easy Adam Labrizzi And The Not So Easy Eugene Levy | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390066/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390066/</guid><description>Podcast Description The two times Hamish &amp;amp; Andy's rhyming game names backfired, plus they remember back to Dicko hosting My Restaurant Rules, the deal they had with our boss for 3 Hungover shows a year and one of Jack&amp;rsquo;s worst button pushing efforts ever.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Celebs We Were Worried About In 2009 | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390067/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish and Andy float the idea of performing their original footy song &amp;ldquo;Duggins Duggins&amp;rdquo; at this years Grand Final. They also revisit the time just before the Marriage Equality Plebiscite with the PM and Hamish shares his deep concern for 2009 Lindsay Lohan living beyond her means.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Tin Whistle | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390068/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390068/</guid><description>Podcast Description The four Caravan of Courage trips became one of Hamish &amp;amp; Andy's most loved expeditions as they travelled for up to two weeks in a van meeting locals and having adventures. In 2010, the boys were making their way through Great Britain and Ireland, where they stayed at a haunted castle, went on dates with local girls despite both having girlfriends at home and Hamish conducted an impromptu performance at an Irish Pub.</description></item><item><title>The First We’d Heard Of Taylor Swift | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390069/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 13:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390069/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2009, a 19 year old Taylor Swift made her first appearance on the Hamish &amp;amp; Andy show, performing live and agreeing to try a prank call as Swifty Taylor! In this episode the boys also remember Michael Clarke and Lara Bingle's failed energy drink, and Hamish reveals why he was hoping to bump into Chris Martin backstage at a Coldplay concert.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project - Trailer | Hamish &amp; Andy’s Remembering Project</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2233390070/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2020 02:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2233390070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamish and Andy are looking at the run sheets from over 2,500 shows across two decades and picking one singular talk break to discuss.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>