<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/armchair-expert-with-dax-shepard/</link><description>Recent content in Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 08:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/armchair-expert-with-dax-shepard/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Best of Mondays 2023 | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170198/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170198/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this special episode, we revisit some of our favorite moments from Monday episodes in 2023. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Armchair Anonymous: Holiday Vacation | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170196/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170196/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dax and Monica talk to Armcherries! In today&amp;rsquo;s episode, Armcherries tell us about a wild holiday vacation. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Yearbook - Chapter 5: Teenage Love &amp; Danger | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170197/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 08:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170197/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nothing compares to the butterflies of teenage love in high school. But teenage romance can lead to grave outcomes. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Adam Frank (physicist and astronomer) | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170194/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170194/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adam Frank (The Little Book of Aliens) is a physicist, astronomer, and writer. Adam joins the Armchair Expert to discuss how he dealt with being an outsider in school, why he was drawn to science fiction, and how he discovered a secret language in mathematics. Adam and Dax talk about what the search for intelligent life outside Earth looks like, how common it is for other planets to have water, and what the concept of a liquid brain is.</description></item><item><title>Synced: It's Rustic | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170195/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170195/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Synced, Monica and Liz discuss the social politics of pooping around others, the difficulties of sharing a bed, and in true sleepover fashion they call all the boys they know. They answer listener questions on how to deal with a narcissistic friend, when it&amp;rsquo;s appropriate to look through a partner&amp;rsquo;s phone, and they break down types of therapists. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Quilts | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170001/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170001/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David Farrier takes Monica’s advice from an earlier episode and investigates America’s obsession with quilts. He begins his journey by interviewing quilting podcaster Ashelyn Downs of “The Grateful Thread”. Farrier discovers that quilting is not just oldies sitting by the fire, but that there’s a new movement of younger, more diverse quilters taking over America. He sets off to meet Latifah Saafir, an engineer who now makes some of the most amazing quilts you’ll see, incorporating bits of her culture and life into the quilts she makes.</description></item><item><title>Willem Dafoe | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Willem Dafoe (Poor Things, Platoon, The Lighthouse) is an actor. Willem joins the Armchair Expert to discuss how he doesn’t have the desire to buy things, how being raised by his siblings affected his perspective, and how his parents encouraged him to be ambitious in life. Willem and Dax talk about how one’s identity can be defined by social conditioning, how he loves collaborating with others on a project, and how he feels about playing big characters.</description></item><item><title>Armchair Anonymous: Meet Cute | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170003/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dax and Monica talk to Armcherries! In today&amp;rsquo;s episode, Armcherries tell us about a meet cute. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Yearbook - Chapter 4: Local Celebrity | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170004/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 08:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170004/</guid><description>Podcast Description As the Blake basketball team roars through its thrilling season, Chad and his teammates experience local stardom. With his newfound status, Chad gets access to all of the hottest house parties…and ends up in white student’s houses for the first time with their parents out of town. Behold, the high school rager. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Maria Sharapova | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Maria Sharapova is a 5x Grand Slam-winning former professional tennis player, investor, and entrepreneur. Maria joins the Armchair Expert to discuss how her priorities changed after retiring from tennis, her experience as a child moving to the US from Russia, and where her strong work ethic came from. Maria and Dax talk about how isolating success can be, what it takes to be critical of yourself, and how they both approach conflict in their relationships.</description></item><item><title>Synced: Vorsh! | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170006/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Synced, Monica and Liz debate high school hotness, they role play an important negotiation, and a special guest joins the squad to talk about eating while masturbating &amp;amp; fluid sexuality. They answer listener questions on how to set a boundary with a family member who drinks too much and if one needs to tell their new love interest that they slept with a hometown ex.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: American Accents | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170007/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170007/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David Farrier seeks to be better understood by his co-hosts by diving headfirst into the American accent. He meets with dialect coach Joel Goldes, who’s helped coach actors like Viola Davis through her various accent roles. As “The Dialect Coach” (www.thedialectcoach.com), Joel teaches David how to place his tongue to sound more American, and takes Farrier through what he’s been doing wrong. Monica, Rob, and David also take an accent quiz to see how good they are at picking American accents (which you can try at home too: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Jon Batiste | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jon Batiste (American Symphony) is a musician and composer. Jon joins the Armchair Expert to discuss why some people feel unworthy of others, why it’s important to feel rejection, and how music can connect all types of people together. Jon and Dax talk about why they want to evolve as artists, how priorities can change when a loved one is sick, and what it’s like to have a relationship in the public eye.</description></item><item><title>Armchair Anonymous: Wild Card III | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170009/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dax and Monica talk to Armcherries! In today&amp;rsquo;s episode, Armcherries tell us their craziest stories. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Yearbook - Chapter 3: Insecurity | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170010/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Like every high schooler, Chad wanted to be cool and wanted to be liked. He twisted himself in knots trying to be popular, trying to be an athlete, and trying to be a lady’s man. But some kids never get the luxury of normal teenage angst… Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Daniel Markovits (on meritocracy) | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Daniel Markovits (The Meritocracy Trap) is a law professor and author. Daniel joins the Armchair Expert to discuss what it was like growing up in different countries, why freedom of speech can sometimes be controversial, and why great art can impact society as much as scientific breakthroughs. Daniel and Dax talk about what it means to study meritocracy, how the landscape of going to college has changed, and how having educated parents affects a child’s development.</description></item><item><title>Synced: Maxing Out | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170012/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Synced, Liz and Monica discuss an important vacation hack, Monica shares her infamous fetish with Liz, and they debate the validity of a &amp;rsquo;twin flame&amp;rsquo;. The two answer listener questions on giving unsolicited career advice and what to do when you break the trust of a friend. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Cereal | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170013/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170013/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David Farrier investigates America’s extreme love of cereal. He sets out to answer why America needs over 5000 different types of cereal, and why some of the most popular cereals have been discontinued. He meets with YouTube cereal reviewer Thomas Hicks, AKA The Cereal Snob (https://www.youtube.com/c/CerealSnob), to get the lowdown on how much milk should be used in cereal, and what types of cereal are the best.</description></item><item><title>Eva Longoria | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eva Longoria (Desperate Housewives, Flamin’ Hot) is an actor, producer, and director. Eva joins the Armchair Expert to discuss why she loved having kids later in life, how she views religion versus spirituality, and what growing up on a Texas ranch was like. Eva and Dax talk about what types of people they are attracted to, why acting in soap operas is so much work, and what biohacking techniques they use to improve their health.</description></item><item><title>Armchair Anonymous: Piercing &amp; Tattoos | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dax and Monica talk to Armcherries! In today&amp;rsquo;s episode, Armcherries tell us about a crazy piercing or tattooing incident. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Yearbook - Chapter 2: The Driver | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 08:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who was driving the car when Chad’s best friend died? What really happened the night when a student was killed in front of Blake High? Chad goes looking for answers to the questions he’s buried for 20 years. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jedidiah Jenkins (author and memoirist) | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jedidiah Jenkins (Mother, Nature) is an author and memoirist. Jedidiah joins the Armchair Expert to discuss how being Christian affected his identity, what sexuality could be like without social rules, and practicing not getting a boner. Jedidiah and Dax talk about what it means to be a centrist now, how it’s difficult for him to know when someone is flirting with him, and his relationship with his mother and her faith.</description></item><item><title>Synced: Morning After Slumber Party | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170018/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Synced, the ladies chat about Liz&amp;rsquo;s documentary, Monica gives an update on dating multiple people at once, and they rave about &amp;lsquo;Couples Therapy&amp;rsquo;. They answer listener questions about gossip in the workplace, how to address changes in one&amp;rsquo;s sex life when in a committed relationship, and how to respond when not given a plus one for a wedding. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Cars | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170019/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David Farrier begins to notice how much America loves cars. Why do 92% of American households have at least one vehicle? That&amp;rsquo;s so many cars! The country&amp;rsquo;s love of cars has transformed it, with not only roads - but with millions and millions of parking spaces. David becomes obsessed with all of America’s parked cars, sitting down with Henry Grabar - a staff writer at Slate who writes about cars and transportation, urban policy, and housing.</description></item><item><title>Wiz Khalifa | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wiz Khalifa (Khali Sober, Khalifa Kush) is a multi-platinum selling rapper and singer. Wiz joins the Armchair Expert to discuss his life growing up as a military kid, why it was tough to grow up scrawny, and what drove him to start writing at a young age. Wiz explains to Dax the difference between a mixtape and an album, how he and Snoop Dogg became friends, and the importance of putting in the work.</description></item><item><title>Yearbook - Chapter 1: The Perfect School | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170021/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chad’s junior year at Blake High School started off like pure magic. Blake was one of those perfect suburban high schools you see on TV and Chad was finally coming into his own. Then a tragedy struck that rocked the school and changed Chad&amp;rsquo;s life forever. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Welcome to Yearbook | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 08:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170022/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the inaugural episode of Yearbook, Dax and Monica sit down with Chad Sanders and they discuss season 1 of Armchair Umbrella&amp;rsquo;s new anthology series. They talk about the working process, the reason they wanted to make the show, and the discomfort that accompanies quaking what you believe to be a solid foundation of identity. They prep the audience for what is to come in the following 7 episodes including self-exploration, death, sex, love, and redemption.</description></item><item><title>Dr. Becky Kennedy (psychologist on parenting) | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Becky Kennedy (Good Inside) is a clinical psychologist and author. Becky joins the Armchair Expert to discuss why she wants to help people understand themselves through their kids, why some traditional parenting techniques aren’t effective, and how to set boundaries with your children. Dr. Becky and Dax talk about how much a person’s past shapes who they are now, why she was compelled to share her ideas on social media, and how expectations of parents can sometimes be unfair.</description></item><item><title>Synced: T.B.C. | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170024/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Synced, Monica encourages Liz to rethink her relationship to social media to protect her mental health &amp;amp; they discuss Monica&amp;rsquo;s blossoming love life. They answer listener questions on how to disclose an STI to a new partner, asking family to stop using certain language around children, and how to proceed when the love of your life picks out a terrible engagement ring. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Pinball | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170025/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170025/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David Farrier sets out to understand America’s obsession with pinball. He heads to Long Beach California for a meeting of the Long Beach Pinball League, headed by passionate pinball man Tom Walker. His league is part of the International Flipper Pinball Association which is made up of 96,000 players from 45 countries. David then meets Tom Radar, a man who has been obsessively collecting pinball machines for years.</description></item><item><title>Trevor Noah | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170026/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trevor Noah (What Now, The Daily Show) is a comedian, writer, and podcaster. Trevor joins the Armchair Expert to discuss why silence scares him, people’s aversion to being blamed, and how language helps you get to the granularity of meaning. Trevor and Dax discuss the false idea that you have to consume the news all the time, the history of the apartheid system in South Africa, and having patience for people only if they’re engaged in the fight.</description></item><item><title>Armchair Anonymous: Bartending | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170027/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dax and Monica talk to Armcherries! In today&amp;rsquo;s episode, Armcherries tell us about a crazy bartending story. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Barbara Kingsolver (author of Demon Copperhead) | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170028/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Barbara Kingsolver (Demon Copperhead) is a Pulitzer Prize-winning author. Barbara joins the Armchair Expert to discuss why she loved to read as a kid, how there can be truth in writing fiction, and how she went from being a biologist to a novelist. Barbara and Dax talk about the struggle in being creative, the effects of structural classism, and why being an author is the best profession to have.</description></item><item><title>Synced: Trips &amp; Falls &amp; Pies &amp; Creams | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170029/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170029/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Synced, Monica shares her holiday traditions, Liz confesses she went to church for a year, and they talk about loss via addiction. They answer listener questions on how to give oneself grace and how to set boundaries when finding naked photos on a partner&amp;rsquo;s phone. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Fantasy Football | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170030/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170030/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David Farrier sets out to understand the mysterious world of fantasy football. He joins a group of manly men as they do a fantasy football draft in a Buffalo Wild Wings restaurant, trying to understand the appeal of a game played by 50 million Americans. David then meets sports reporter and ESPN correspondent Mina Kimes who drills down into the finer details of fantasy football, even offering some expert tips.</description></item><item><title>Tom Hansen | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170031/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tom Hansen is an entertainment lawyer and Dax’s best friend. Tom joins the Armchair Expert to discuss what knowing people from the Dust Bowl era is like, how much he loved working on his grandparent’s farm as a kid, and why he thinks he isn’t a good listener. Tom and Dax talk about why some people just aren’t ambitious in life, why he got into a lot of trouble in school, and their experiences with illicit drugs.</description></item><item><title>eff won: Christian Horner Debrief | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170032/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dax sits down in the attic with Red Bull Team Principal, Christian Horner. Christian is a former racer who has won six constructors championships with Red Bull Racing. He also loves Disneyland. Follow eff won with DRS over at https://spotify.link/effwon or search &amp;ldquo;eff won&amp;rdquo; wherever you listen to podcasts for new episodes every week. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Armchair Anonymous: Babysitting | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170033/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dax and Monica talk to Armcherries! In today&amp;rsquo;s episode, Armcherries tell us about a bad babysitting experience. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dan Ariely (on behavioral economics) | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170034/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan Ariely is a social scientist, professor, and author. Dan joins the Armchair Expert to discuss why people often want to regulate other’s behavior, what factors can affect workplace employees’ motivations, and how people live in different realities from each other. Dan and Dax talk about the funnel of misbelief, what happens when people are excluded from a group, and how to engage people with differing opinions from your own.</description></item><item><title>Synced: The OT's are OK | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170035/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170035/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Synced, Monica and Liz report from a storage closet and a bed. They discuss repeating old family dynamics in relationships, codependency in therapy, and Liz&amp;rsquo;s theory of &amp;lsquo;5 crushes&amp;rsquo;. They answer listener questions on navigating jealousy in a friendship and if the first date spark is real. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Haunted Houses | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170036/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170036/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David Farrier takes Monica to a haunted house to celebrate Halloween. And not just any haunted house! Each year Universal Studios puts on its Halloween Horror Nights, using its Hollywood tricks to create some of the scariest haunted houses in America. David and Monica meet with John Murdy, the creative director behind the haunted houses. Monica then comes face to face with her ultimate fear: Chucky.</description></item><item><title>Craig Ferguson | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170037/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Craig Ferguson is a talk show host, comedian, and podcaster. Craig joins the Armchair Expert to discuss why he carries extra underwear with him, how diverse Scotland is, and his journey into late-night television. Craig and Dax talk about what they have learned in getting older, who the desert fathers were, and their experiences with meditation. Craig explains what made him want to get sober, how he defines attractiveness, and why he wants to talk to people who aren’t comedians.</description></item><item><title>Armchair Anonymous: Halloween | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170038/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dax and Monica talk to Armcherries! In today&amp;rsquo;s episode, Armcherries tell us about a time something crazy happened on Halloween. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Adam Grant Returns Again | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170039/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adam Grant (Hidden Potential) is an organizational psychologist, professor, and author. Adam joins the Armchair Expert again to discuss how much he misses his family when on a book tour, how most people achieve their goals by being motivated, and the most effective way to teach someone a new language. Adam and Dax talk about how being a perfectionist can stifle someone’s learning, how to overcome the fear of public speaking, and what the difference is between receiving advice and feedback.</description></item><item><title>Synced: Future Surf | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170040/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170040/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Synced, Monica introduces Liz to the term &amp;lsquo;future surfing&amp;rsquo;, they talk about how friendships have evolved post-pandemic, and they evaluate their relationships to social media. They answer questions from the Synced Squad on how to explore one&amp;rsquo;s sexuality while in a relationship, addressing a suspected domestic abuse situation with a co-worker, and the pros and cons of obsessing over celebrity relationships. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>The Chainsmokers | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170041/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170041/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Chainsmokers are musicians, DJs, and producers. Alex and Drew join the Armchair Expert to discuss their anonymity as DJs, how they have maintained a successful partnership, and where they get creative inspiration from. Alex &amp;amp; Drew talk about why they became interested in venture capitalism, their love for performing live, and how they balance who they are on stage versus real life. They explain what their experience has been collaborating with other musicians, how they handle reading misinformation about themselves, and what social media has done for young creators.</description></item><item><title>Armchair Anonymous: Generous Hospitality | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170042/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dax and Monica talk to Armcherries! In today&amp;rsquo;s episode, Armcherries tell us about the most generous act of hospitality they’ve received. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Robert Sapolsky (on human behavior and free will) | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170043/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Robert Sapolsky (Behave, Determined) is a behavioral scientist and author. Robert joins the Armchair Expert to discuss why he was drawn to studying the social habits of baboons, how their behavior relates to human psychology, and what we learned from Phineas Gage. Robert and Dax talk about how conditioning helps people get through stressful situations, how culture affects the development of the human brain, and how child raising is different in a collective society.</description></item><item><title>Synced: The Smell | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170044/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Synced, Monica goes Pamela Anderson style while discussing her egg retrieval, they explore complicated relationships with food and bodies, and debate THE smell. They answer listener questions about getting PQ&amp;rsquo;s from a friend&amp;rsquo;s husband and if one needs to tell family about a polyamorous relationship. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Bail Bonds | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170045/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170045/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird David Farrier investigates bail bonds in America, and more specifically - the bail bondsman. With 15,000 bail bond agents in America, it seems to be a thriving private enterprise. In Oklahoma, he meets with Ron Eden, a bail bondsman who inherited the business from his mother. What’s it like to deal with people accused of crimes and the families desperate to get their loved ones out while they await trial?</description></item><item><title>Jada Pinkett Smith | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170046/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jada Pinkett Smith is an actor, producer, and talk show host. Jada joins the Armchair Expert to discuss where she got her sense of punctuality from, how difficult it can be to share your life with the public, and her experience with abandonment. Jada and Dax talk about what she learned about loyalty from Tupac, what it was like being robbed at gunpoint, and how she feels about asking for help.</description></item><item><title>Armchair Anonymous: Teacher/Principal | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170047/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dax and Monica talk to Armcherries! In today&amp;rsquo;s episode, Armcherries tell us about their craziest story as a teacher or principal. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Morgan Neville (documentary filmmaker) | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170048/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Morgan Neville (The Saint of Second Chances, Roadrunner, Won’t You Be My Neighbor) is a filmmaker, producer, and writer. Morgan joins the Armchair Expert to discuss why people love documentaries, why he had so many books in his childhood home, and how Los Angeles&amp;rsquo;s history differs from other American cities. Morgan and Dax talk about what it means to be a good singer, what Mr. Rogers did for the perception of masculinity, and why some people are addicted to work.</description></item><item><title>Synced: AMA | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170049/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170049/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Synced, Monica shares realizations she&amp;rsquo;s been having on her second egg-freezing journey, Liz raves about &amp;lsquo;The Golden Bachelor,&amp;rsquo; and they have a heart-to-heart while discussing last week&amp;rsquo;s cliffhanger. They answer a listener&amp;rsquo;s question on whether one can cry at work and still be taken seriously, which leads to a very special guest appearance from Rihanna. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Fred Armisen | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170050/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fred Armisen (SNL, Portlandia, Documentary Now!) is a comedian, actor, and musician. Fred joins the Armchair Expert to discuss why he doesn’t speak up when he’s uncomfortable, why he will eat something he didn’t order, and why he doesn’t like to return purchases. Fred and Dax talk about how fun it is to rediscover music that you love, what interviewing your friends is like, and Fred’s unique family heritage.</description></item><item><title>Armchair Anonymous: Service Industry | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170051/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dax and Monica talk to Armcherries! In today&amp;rsquo;s episode, Armcherries tell us a crazy service industry story. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Vivek Murthy Returns (US Surgeon General) | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170052/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Vivek Murthy (House Calls) is the Surgeon General of the United States and an author. Vivek joins the Armchair Expert to discuss how he defines loneliness, strategies for strengthening connections, and what hustle culture has done to creativity. Vivek and Dax talk about what it takes for people to confide in each other, how taking time away from work can improve mental health, and the power of service.</description></item><item><title>Synced: Stay in Your Hula Hoop | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170053/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170053/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Synced, Monica &amp;amp; Liz deep dive into the difference between anxiety &amp;amp; intuition, they chat about codependency, and another strange man talks to Monica. They answer listener questions about having different expectations around sex in a relationship and give advice to a 30 year old virgin. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Laundromats | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170054/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170054/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird David Farrier investigates whether we have America to thank for the modern laundromat. After all, there are over 30,000 laundromats in the US - employing 39,000 people, making $5 billion in revenue each year. To help him in his investigation David meets with Brain Wallace of the Coin Laundry Association to discuss how on April 18th,1934 a Texan named CA Tannahill opened the world&amp;rsquo;s first coin-operated laundromat.</description></item><item><title>Kerry Washington | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170055/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kerry Washington (Thicker Than Water) is an award-winning actor, producer, director, and writer. Kerry joins the Armchair Expert to discuss her anthropology degree, not feeling like the protagonist of her own story, and finding out the truth about her family. Kerry and Dax talk about what it takes to keep secrets, their experiences with abuse in the household, and James McAvoy in The Last King of Scotland. Kerry explains how her relationship with food has changed over the years, what she learned from moving to India, and how she strove to carve her own path in life.</description></item><item><title>Armchair Anonymous: Failed Romantic Pursuit | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170056/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dax and Monica talk to Armcherries! In today&amp;rsquo;s episode, Armcherries tell us about a failed romantic pursuit. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Gabor Maté (on trauma &amp; addiction) | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170057/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Gabor Maté (The Myth of Normal) is a physician and author. Gabor joins the Armchair Expert to discuss how most people exhibit addictive behaviors, how the mind is connected to physical health, and how human societies are like lab cultures. Gabor and Dax talk about why airports can be sources of anxiety, what happens to the body when someone goes through trauma, and why children have the expectation to be loved unconditionally.</description></item><item><title>Synced: Long End of the Stick | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170058/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170058/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Synced, Monica talks about temporarily giving up drinking, they contemplate Liz&amp;rsquo;s trusting nature, and debate the deliciousness of club soda. A special guest joins for listener questions about tardiness and if a sixteen year age gap is too much between romantic partners. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jonathan Van Ness | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170059/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jonathan Van Ness (Queer Eye, Getting Curious) is a hairstylist, television personality, and podcaster. Jonathan joins the Armchair Expert to discuss the idea of older women having younger sexual partners, dealing with skin issues, and how news organizations choose political sides. Jonathan and Dax talk about transgender participation in sports, what it means to challenge progressive ideas, and how state laws around gender-affirming care can differ. Jonathan explains why judging in cheerleading is not objective, what the motivation was to start a science-based podcast, and how relationships can truly grow.</description></item><item><title>Armchair Anonymous: Waxing Debacle | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170060/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dax and Monica talk to Armcherries! In today&amp;rsquo;s episode, Armcherries tell us about a waxing debacle. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Prachi Gupta (on the model minority myth) | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170061/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Prachi Gupta (They Called Us Exceptional) is a journalist and author. Prachi joins the Armchair Expert to discuss why she was grounded for reading fiction, how she views the institution of arranged marriages, and what the American Dream meant to her parents. Prachi and Dax talk about why she wanted to tell her brother’s story, how she feels about happiness being correlated to success, and why being emasculated can affect how men treat one another.</description></item><item><title>Synced: My Best Friend's Boobs | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170062/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170062/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Synced, Monica and Liz chat about naked bodies, Liz teaches Monica about underwater hockey, and they debate how one never knows what is going on behind closed doors or social media captions. They discuss listener questions about whether there is such a thing as too much therapy, would they want to know if their parents cheated, and how much should parents contribute financially to a wedding?</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Healthcare II | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170063/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170063/</guid><description>Podcast Description After two American surgeons told David he needed back surgery, he fled back to his home of New Zealand where healthcare was less scary! What he discovered in New Zealand surprised him. David calls up journalist Luke O’Neil (writer of the Welcome to Hellworld newsletter and new book A Creature Wanting Form) to chat through what he discovered: two very different medical systems with vastly different approaches. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Jimmy Kimmel Returns | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170064/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jimmy Kimmel (Strike Force Five) is a talk show host and podcaster. Jimmy returns to the Armchair Expert to discuss how much the attic hasn’t changed in five years, what it’s like working with his competition on a podcast, and how much of a temper he doesn’t have. Jimmy and Dax talk about the state of trout fly fishing, what they think being retired from show business means, and how much they appreciate a good standup.</description></item><item><title>Armchair Anonymous: School Dance | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170065/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dax and Monica talk to Armcherries! In today&amp;rsquo;s episode, Armcherries tell us about a school dance disaster. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mustafa Suleyman (on artificial intelligence) | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170066/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mustafa Suleyman (The Coming Wave) is an artificial intelligence researcher, co-founder of DeepMind, and author. Mustafa joins the Armchair Expert to discuss how he became interested in the concept of universal human rights, what deep learning is, and how machines can actually become creative. Mustafa and Dax talk about how close artificial intelligence is getting to matching the human brain, how people might feel about computers creating all content, and how AI might revolutionize the energy industry.</description></item><item><title>Synced: September 13th | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170067/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170067/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Synced, Liz and Monica explore the change in the air regarding women&amp;rsquo;s culture and Monica gives an update on her egg freezing journey, all while her dad&amp;rsquo;s sim works overtime. They discuss listener questions on should one speak up when they don&amp;rsquo;t like their close friend&amp;rsquo;s significant other, when given the chance should one choose the gender of their child, and how to trust oneself when trying to move on while grieving a spouse.</description></item><item><title>Idina Menzel | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170068/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Idina Menzel is a singer and actor. Idina joins the Armchair Expert to discuss her scary theater accident, how her dad was a pajama salesman, and her feelings about the Happy Birthday song. Idina and Dax talk about how much pride goes into parenting, what being in relationships with other successful people is like, and her strategy for performing day after day. Idina explains how she views being a voice for people that she didn’t intend to be, why she has always wanted to do a stage dive, and how she is always messing up well-known sayings.</description></item><item><title>Armchair Anonymous: Worst USA Trip | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170069/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dax and Monica talk to Armcherries! In today&amp;rsquo;s episode, international Armcherries tell us about their worst trip to the USA. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Amy Edmondson (organizational behavioral scientist) | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170070/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amy Edmondson (Right Kind of Wrong: The Science of Failing Well) is a professor and author. Amy joins the Armchair Expert to discuss why she was drawn to studying organizational learning, what psychological safety is, and how systems exist to make societies better. Amy and Dax talk about why working groups can have different interpersonal climates, the definition of learning behaviors, and what the three types of failure are.</description></item><item><title>Synced: i drizzle | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170071/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170071/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Synced, Liz explains “girl dinner”, they debate whether singles should set up other singles, they hear a very special voice memo and Monica peels back the layers of her “fear of the streets”. They discuss a listener’s question on how to cook the perfect roast chicken. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Pizza | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170072/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170072/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David Farrier investigates pizza, one of America’s favorite foods. He discovers that around 76,000 pizza joints bring in $44 billion dollars each year in the US - where every day 13% of the population will eat a slice of pizza. David begins his journey in Los Angeles, as Rob takes him and Monica to a fancy pop-up called “Chain”. Here, chefs riff on chain food but with their own upgraded twists - and tonight it’s Pizza Hut!</description></item><item><title>Jake Johnson Returns | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170073/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jake Johnson is an actor, director, and podcaster. Jake returns to the Armchair Expert to discuss what he remembers about being on the show in the early days, why he stopped going to casinos, and how much he respects AA. Jake and Dax talk about why they wanted their daughters to learn self-defense, how they feel about doing manual labor, and how hard it can be to see the red flags in some situations.</description></item><item><title>Jim Farley (CEO of Ford) | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170074/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jim Farley is the CEO of Ford. Jim joins the Armchair Expert to discuss what growing up in Argentina was like, how much he loved watching car races as a kid, and the time his dad sold the car he gifted him. Jim and Dax talk about their shared car nightmare, the stereotypes of being a car guy, and how to achieve positive car karma. Jim explains the hurdles of reengineering cars for electric, how Ford joining the Red Bull Formula 1 team came to be, and the generational differences in car culture.</description></item><item><title>Synced: Third Location | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170075/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170075/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Synced, Monica and Liz chat about circumcision, power dynamics in relationships, and Liz shares details of her week-long second date. They discuss listener questions on inviting a toxic friend back into one&amp;rsquo;s life, and how to handle one partner doing a 180 on the idea of having children. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tig Notaro | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170076/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tig Notaro is a comedian, actor, and podcaster. Tig joins the Armchair Expert to discuss what she thinks about cold plunges, how much she hates texting, and how having unconventional parents influenced her outlook on life. Tig and Dax talk about how much they value a sense of humor, how they pictured having kids, and their shared love of Edie Brickell. Tig explains why she started sharing her personal medical history on stage, her views on being a people-pleaser, and what she thinks being handsome means.</description></item><item><title>Armchair Anonymous: Bad Landlord | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170077/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dax and Monica talk to Armcherries! In today&amp;rsquo;s episode, Armcherries tell us about a bad landlord experience. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Brian Chesky (co-founder of airbnb) | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170078/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brian Chesky (Co-founder and CEO of Airbnb) is a businessman and industrial designer. Brian joins the Armchair Expert to discuss if gaining success lived up to the expectations, how he struggled to fit in at school, and what his first startup was. Brian and Dax talk about what being an industrial designer means, where the idea for Airbnb came from, and how detrimental loneliness can be to human health.</description></item><item><title>Synced: Bubbles | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170079/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170079/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Synced, Monica and Liz become armchair gynecologists, they ponder if a man should ever ask a woman where she lives, and Liz shares a scary experience she had in front of a Los Angeles drug store. They discuss listener questions on how to cope with changing friendships when children are added to the mix and challenge the age-old question - does money really buy happiness?</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Storm Chasers | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170080/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170080/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird David Farrier investigates the incredibly American pastime of storm chasing. There are about 1200 tornados in America each year - for some, they are a source of fear and worry, but for others, they are a challenge to be bested. David travels to tornado alley, visiting Oklahoma in search of answers. There he meets storm chasers Stephanie &amp;amp; Justin Cox (@oklahoma_weather_couple) who talk about falling in love while chasing storms and their shared obsession with finding the next big Twister.</description></item><item><title>Jason Derulo | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170081/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jason Derulo (Sing Your Name Out Loud) is a singer, songwriter, and author. Jason joins the Armchair Expert to discuss how intermittent fasting has affected his overall health, his experience going to a performance arts school, and paying his dues in the music industry. Jason and Dax talk about betrayal, how inspiring Taylor Swift is, and how the joy is in the journey. Jason explains how he broke his neck, his songwriting process, and his approach to get people to stop scrolling on social media.</description></item><item><title>Armchair Anonymous: Grateful for a Lie | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170082/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dax and Monica talk to Armcherries! In today&amp;rsquo;s episode, Armcherries tell us about a time they were grateful they lied. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Wendy Mogel | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170083/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Wendy Mogel (Nurture vs Nurture, Voice Lessons for Parents) is a clinical psychologist, author, and podcaster. Wendy joins the Armchair Expert to discuss how interesting linguistics are, how she developed her confidence to talk to strangers, and why she is worried about the future of young men. Wendy and Dax talk about how to notice the signs of puberty, why they feel kids have fewer experiences growing up than they used to, and big daddy love.</description></item><item><title>Synced: The O.W. | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170084/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170084/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Synced, Monica and Liz question if modern women are replacing their intimate relationships with female friendships, they delve into the romance of Barnes &amp;amp; Noble, and they explore some Liz-isms. The two discuss listener questions on whether to expedite a marriage proposal and how to handle financial inequity in a marriage. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nurture vs Nurture: Family #12: Denise &amp; Ryan | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170085/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Mogel speaks with family #12: Denise and Ryan and answers the question: Will our children hate us if we disagree about how to raise them? She also teaches us a new concept: Jimi Halloween. Make sure to subscribe to weekly episodes, dropping every Tuesday only on the Nurture vs Nurture feed. Just search “Nurture vs Nurture” on Apple Podcast, Spotify, or wherever you listen to podcasts. Or visit bit.</description></item><item><title>Kristen Bell, by the grace of God, returns | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170086/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kristen Bell is an actor, singer, philanthropist, and producer. Kristen joins the Armchair Expert to discuss her career in the tabloids, how you need thick skin to be a parent, and going to channel two. Kristen and Dax talk about what they Google, her Bart Simpson laugh, and give an update on how much they each cry. Kristen explains what happened to them at the Boston airport, what being kind to people means, and how she responds to negative feedback.</description></item><item><title>Michael Waldman [Rerelease from 5/25/23] | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170087/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michael Waldman (The Supermajority, The Fight to Vote, The Second Amendment) is an attorney, presidential speechwriter, and author. Michael joins the Armchair Expert to discuss how the U.S. Supreme Court is involved in modern policymaking, what the concept of originalism is, and how extremism is influencing judges rulings on cases. Michael and Dax talk about the changes Congress can make to how justices are appointed, how public hearings have become spectacles for entertainment, and what role the media has in shaping the court of public opinion.</description></item><item><title>Synced: The Pins Have Pins | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170088/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170088/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Synced, Monica and Liz reminisce on how many times they’ve each held a hammer, Liz talks about settling into LA, and they debate the lengths one should go to turn a parasocial relationship into a real one. They discuss listener questions about being a people pleaser and how to find one&amp;rsquo;s personal style. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Ice | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170089/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170089/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David Farrier investigates America’s obsession with ice. From excessive ice in drinks to the joy of frozen food, Farrier finds that ice is deeply American. Meeting with Reid Mitenbuler, the author of Bourbon Empire, David discovers the story of Frederic “the Ice King” Tudor, who dug up ice from the lakes of New England and got America, and the world, hooked on ice in the 1800s.</description></item><item><title>Robert Downey Jr. [Rerelease from 6/19/23] | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170090/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Robert Downey Jr. (Downey’s Dream Cars, Sr., Iron Man) is an actor and producer. Robert joins the Armchair Expert to discuss their journey to becoming soulmates, how important it is to have deep meaningful relationships, and what acting process works best for him. Robert and Dax talk about what it’s like to have an addictive personality, finding closure with their fathers, and whether life is a joke or tragedy.</description></item><item><title>Phil Stutz [Rerelease from 1/5/23] | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170091/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Phil Stutz (Stutz, The Tools) is a psychologist, therapist, and author. Phil joins the Armchair Expert to discuss what his experience was being the subject of a documentary, what it was like being a psychiatrist at Rikers Island prison, and how he can tell if someone is a narcissist. Phil and Dax talk about how abstract psychology can be, why people pursue perfection, and why it can be hard to ask for help from others.</description></item><item><title>Synced: M+R or L+D | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170092/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170092/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Synced, Monica and Liz evaluate their wedding-to-funeral ratio, Monica talks about humiliating her dad and Dax joins the two, which instigates potty humor and a significant battle. They discuss listener questions on how to date as a single parent and how to fall out of “love” with a celebrity. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Anna Kendrick [Rerelease from 1/9/23] | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170093/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Anna Kendrick (Alice, Darling, Pitch Perfect, Trolls) is an actor. Anna joins the Armchair Expert to discuss her experience being in a toxic relationship, how she feels about the term “gaslighting,” and her strategies in dealing with a traumatic event. Anna and Dax talk about apologizing after having fights with friends, why people sometimes need to vent about their problems, and the dynamic of women being the breadwinners in relationships.</description></item><item><title>David Sedaris [Rerelease from 10/7/21] | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170094/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170094/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Sedaris is an author and comedian. David joins the Armchair Expert to discuss his new book A Carnival of Snackery, why he can get away with saying things other people can’t say, and how he takes five mile walks at midnight. David and Dax talk about the things they would get into before sobriety, knowing where every bathroom in New York City is, and how he is just never offended by anything.</description></item><item><title>Synced: We’re Back | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170095/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170095/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s been almost a year since Monica and Liz took over the attic for Race to 35, a podcast produced by the Armchair Umbrella on egg freezing. They are back for a weekly podcast, Synced. In this inaugural episode, Liz kicks it off with a bang by limping into the attic and Monica is forced to re-visit her fertility journey. The two answer listener questions about complicated family dynamics, how to split a group check, and more.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: School Cafeterias | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170096/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170096/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David Farrier goes behind the scenes of the food that’s dished up to 30 million American kids at the school cafeteria. Back in New Zealand, they don&amp;rsquo;t have school cafeterias, so all he knows is what he&amp;rsquo;s learned from Euphoria and Saved By The Bell. In Hemet, Farrier meets Kate Kloet, assistant director of nutrition services for Hemet Unified School District. Donning a hairnet, she takes Farrier into the industrial kitchen where food is made for 23,000 kids in the area before the pair drive to a local high school to experience the cafeteria.</description></item><item><title>Matt Damon [Rerelease from 8/2/21] | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170097/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matt Damon (Good Will Hunting, Ocean’s Eleven, Stillwater) is an Oscar Award-Winning and Golden Globe Award-Winning actor, producer, and screenwriter. Matt joins the Armchair Expert to talk about his experience writing Good Will Hunting with Ben Affleck, what it was like attending the Monaco Grand Prix with Brad Pitt, and how your subjective experience changes when you become famous. Matt explains how easy it is to be generous when things are going your way, how he picked his movies based on the directors rather than the roles, and what he learned after surrounding himself with oil roughnecks for his new movie.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: PSA / Farrier Takes Flight | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170098/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170098/</guid><description>Podcast Description An update on Flightless Bird! David explains to Monica and Rob why he’s had to take flight to New Zealand. Defeated by the US healthcare system and his bad health insurance plan, David has temporarily returned to Aotearoa, New Zealand for some minor back surgery! This has disrupted the usual smooth flow of making the show, so for July and August, Flightless Bird will arrive fortnightly instead of weekly.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Independence Day | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170099/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170099/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David Farrier sets out to investigate what the heck is going on with Independence Day, one of America’s 11 officially mandated holidays. What makes this day so American and how is he meant to spend it? To learn about Independence Day the day, Farrier turns to Independence Day the movie. Farrier talks to film critic David Chen of DecodingEverything.com to find out what made this film so patriotic it was literally named after the 4th of July.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Attics &amp; Basements | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170100/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170100/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David Farrier realizes that New Zealand doesn’t have attics or basements, so sets out to discover why so many of America’s 333 million homes do. David talks to Stephen Fox, an architectural historian and a lecturer at the Rice School of Architecture in Houston, who explains the practical reasons for these spaces, as well as why they’ve turned into habitable spaces. David then talks to filmmaker and architect Giorgio Angelini about what these spaces mean culturally to Americans, as paradoxically a place of safety and warmth but also of mystery and horror.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Electric Kettles | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170101/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170101/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David Farrier sets out to discover why America is yet to fully embrace the electric kettle. Why does America insist on the stovetop kettle when it could be boiling its water so much faster? To find out, David talks to Bruce Richardson, a tea master who founded Elmwood Inn Fine Teas in Kentucky, and wrote a book called “The New Tea Companion.” Bruce is a man obsessed with the correct boiling point of water, whose worst enemy is the microwave.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: DMV Pt II | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170102/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170102/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David Farrier attempts to get over the trauma of his last trip to the DMV, where Monica Padman’s dirty Prius ruined everything. Will David finally get his license or are he and Monica doomed to fail for all eternity? To help him on his quest, Farrier talks to the head of the California DMV, Steve Gordon. Gordon was brought in four years ago by the governor of LA, Gavin Newsom, to sort out a DMV plagued by issues - and Farrier figures he might have some tips.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Beavers | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170103/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170103/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David becomes fixated on the beaver, the rodent that’s become synonymous with Buc-ees, the giant American gas station. But David quickly learns there is so much to the beaver, the biggest rodent in the United States. With over 15 million of them spread over North America, they were once hunted almost to extinction for their pelts. David talks to Leila Philip, author of Beaverland, an incredible book about how the beaver transformed America.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Drug Rehab | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170104/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170104/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David sets out to look at drug rehab in the state of Florida. According to the CDC, since 1999 over 932,000 people have died from a drug overdose. Since 1999, overdoses involving opioids have increased eight times. With those stats came an exploration of drug rehab facilities - many of which gamed the system and became corrupt. Why did Florida end up leading America in having the most drug centers per capita?</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Exotic Pets | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170105/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170105/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week&amp;rsquo;s Flightless Bird, David Farrier sets out to understand Florida’s obsession with exotic pets. Why does the sunshine state have more exotic animal species than any other state and, quite possibly, than any other country? David discovers that there are about 50 different reptile species now thriving in Florida - most of them imports. With that in mind, he explores the Burmese python, an escaped imported creature that is now eating alligators out in the Everglades, taking the position of top dog in the ecosystem.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: The Villages | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170106/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170106/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David sets off for The Villages, America’s biggest retirement community, home to over 100 thousand people over the age of 55. What lies in this mysterious land spread out over about 32 square miles, an area bigger than Manhattan? David discovers the Villages are so big, they get their own designation on the census. Taking a tour with a resident, Farrier discovers golf courses, pickleball courts, grocery stores, banks, and a roading system just for golf carts.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: EPCOT vs Universal | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170107/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170107/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David continues his Florida series by going to EPCOT, Disney’s “Experimental Prototype Community of Tomorrow.” Joined by two Disney Adults, Elizabeth and Patrick, David eats his way around the world, and discovers why many also choose to drink their way around the world. Along the way, Farrier discovers Figment, a Disney character that only exists in EPCOT. After finding out why no one is allowed to die in Disney World, Farrier heads back to LA to compare Disney World with Universal Studios.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Alligators | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170108/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170108/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week&amp;rsquo;s Flightless Bird, David Farrier sets out to discover Florida’s relationship with its 2,000 crocodiles and whopping 1.25 million alligators. Traveling to America’s oldest city, St Augustine, Farrier visits the Alligator Farm to discover why crocs are more feisty than gators, and what food they like eating. He then dives headfirst into the phenomenon of Florida Man, after discovering a man high on bath salts once climbed into the very croc enclosure he’s now looking at!</description></item><item><title>Danny Ric + Daxy Shep “eff won” Teaser | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170109/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subscribe to eff won with DRS by searching &amp;ldquo;eff won with DRS&amp;rdquo; wherever you listen to podcasts and get new episodes every week. Enjoy a preview of the conversation between Dax and Danny, scantily dressed, with a bit of F1, a dash of Pulp From The Paddock, and a bazillion giggles. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Spiritualists | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170110/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170110/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week&amp;rsquo;s Flightless Bird, David Farrier sets out to the “psychic capital of America,” Cassadaga. On the way, he comes across his first Big Tent Revival, so he stops to find out what’s going on. Eventually winding his way to Cassadaga, Farrier encounters a group of Americans who not only believe in life on the other side of death, but the fact that you can communicate with those who have crossed over.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Gladesmen | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170111/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170111/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s Flightless Bird, David Farrier sets out to Florida’s south, deep into the Everglades, in search of the men who live in the glades: Gladesmen. Descending by airboat into the wet marshlands, David discovers he’s on a giant river 100 miles long and 60 miles wide. Surrounded by alligators, bugs, birds and fish, his guide Steve - a third-generation gladesman - takes David to a “camp” - the place where gladesmen live.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Eggs | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170112/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170112/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week&amp;rsquo;s Flightless Bird, David Farrier sets out to understand why Americans put their eggs in the fridge. Why the fridge, when the rest of the planet puts them in the pantry? David learns that each year, each American eats an average of 277 eggs and that America has enough chickens to provide each American with at least an egg a day. David then discovers a plethora of organizations exist around the humble egg, from the International Egg Commission to the American Egg Board.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Movies | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170113/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170113/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s Flightless Bird, David Farrier sets out to understand how Americans interact with movies. Motivated by watching Nicole Kidman’s heartfelt introduction before every movie at the AMC theater chain, Farrier sets out to understand the other big chains like Regal. How are these chains enticing people in the door? He finds that AMC has the Stubs A-List, and Regal has Regal Unlimited. Then Farrier talks to Stacy Spikes, the founder and brains behind MoviePass - a subscription service he started, then was kicked out of, then bought back again.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Pickleball | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170114/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170114/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s Flightless Bird, David Farrier sets out to understand America’s fastest growing sport, pickleball. Why did five million Americans turn to pickleball during the pandemic, and why did Tom Brady and LeBron James buy franchises in various Pickleball leagues? David goes to meet and play Pickleball with one of America’s best players, Jessie Irvine, to discover some tips and tricks. Along the way he discovers why Americans are suing each other over pickleball, before talking to Chuck Menke, Chief Marketing Officer for Pickleball America.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Rabies | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170115/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170115/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s Flightless Bird, David Farrier gets bitten by a squirrel, forcing him to come face-to-face with his greatest nightmare: rabies. Why does this virus have a near 100% mortality rate and how are you meant to be treated for it? David joins the 60,000 Americans who find themselves having to reckon with the risk of rabies every year, whether they are bitten by dogs, raccoons, bats… or in David’s case, a squirrel.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: BBQ | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170116/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170116/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s Flightless Bird, David Farrier travels to Austin, Texas to investigate America’s love of BBQ. Why do 7 out of 10 adults in America own some kind of BBQ device, and why is there so much BBQ in Texas? David meets up with the BBQ editor of Texas Monthly, Daniel Vaughn. David discovers that Daniel has eaten at over 2,000 barbecue spots all over the planet… 2,119 to be precise - many of them in Texas.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Waco | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170117/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170117/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s Flightless Bird, David Farrier sets out to Waco, Texas - taking a drive to visit the Branch Davidians compound, the old home of David Koresh. David is surprised to find that the strange offshoot of the Seventh Day Adventist church still exists and sits down to interview their new leader. Why are they still on the same grounds where so many terrible things happened? What do they believe?</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Waffle House | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170118/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170118/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s Flightless Bird, David Farrier sets out to understand Waffle House, the much loved diner found scattered throughout the American south. What makes this chain so special, and what the heck is the Waffle House Index? David interviews Waffle House’s Njeri Boss about the magic of waffles and why it’s actually more about the hash browns. He also talks to photographer Micah Cash about his book Waffle House Vistas (https://bittersoutherner.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: DMV | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170119/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170119/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s Flightless Bird, David Farrier sets out for the DMV in an attempt to get his American driver’s license. By his side (and scared in the passenger seat) is Monica Padman, there to assist the New Zealander in his quest. Things take a turn when they discover Monica’s car is far too dirty. A diversion to a carwash, a quick quiche, and a lot of debate over the road rules take the pair to the DMV.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Valentine's Day | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170120/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170120/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s Flightless Bird, David Farrier sets out to understand America’s obsession with Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day. Why do Americans fork out $20 billion each year in an attempt to woo a mate or prove their love to an existing one? David discovers he doesn’t have a valentine, so interviews online dating coach Perri Schneider. What are the do’s and don’ts of American dating? Farrier then discovers that sales of vibrators go up on and around Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day, so talks to engineer Anna Lee of Lioness who invented a smart vibrator.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Sandwiches | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170121/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170121/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s Flightless Bird, David Farrier looks at America’s obsession with sandwiches. Why is Subway the United State’s biggest fast food chain, leaving Starbucks and McDonalds in its wake? To get answers, David heads to Philly to investigate one of America’s greatest inventions: The Philly Cheesesteak Sandwich. There he discovers two sandwich stores locked in a decades-long rivalry. What’s the beef between Geno’s and Pat’s? And what of the man who supplies both stores with their tasty sodas?</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: New Zealand Summer Vacation | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170122/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170122/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s Flightless Bird, David Farrier returns to Aotearoa, New Zealand, to investigate why so many of New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s native birds are flightless. Literally. David sets out to find three such creatures: the little penguin, the kakapo, and - of course - the useless kiwi bird. What happened to their wings, and why does the world’s heaviest parrot choose to live on the forest floor instead of the majestic trees?</description></item><item><title>Race to 35: Esther Perel | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170123/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170123/</guid><description>Podcast Description BONUS episode of Race to 35 with Esther Perel. Months after their retrievals, Monica and Liz return to the attic to discuss their feelings surrounding the egg retrieval process with some distance from the experience. Esther Perel joins the women in the attic to talk about ambiguous loss, jealousy/discomfort, and plans for the future. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Christmas | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170124/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170124/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s Flightless Bird, David Farrier looks at why Christmas is the OG holiday in America. He brings back Mike McHargue from the very first episode of Flightless Bird to talk about how religion and commerce mix. In 2021 Americans spent $800 billion on Christmas-related purchases and this year it looks to soar to new heights! Mike and David delve into the origins of Santa Claus, before David takes a trip to “Holiday Road,&amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo; a giant Christmas display in Calabasas.</description></item><item><title>Race to 35: Post Retrieval | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170125/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Monica and Liz get retrieved in episode 10 (out of 10) of Race to 35. In the final episode, L &amp;amp; M chat mere hours after their retrieval. They discuss their feelings, talk about the trigger shot experience, and discuss how their teams performed. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Soft Drinks | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170126/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170126/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s Flightless Bird, David Farrier sets out to understand the vast array of soft drinks on offer in the United States of America. He ends up stumbling into Waco, Texas - home of Dr. Pepper - where he attempts to solve the riddle of what the heck Dr. Pepper tastes like. Along the way, he discovers Big Red and the chaotic history of bottled soda water. He visits the Dr.</description></item><item><title>Race to 35: Day 9 + Andrew Solomon | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170127/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Monica and Liz are all synced up in episode 9 (out of 10) of Race to 35. The two are feeling unexpectedly sad as this process comes to an end. They have resigned to the idea that their follicles are players and that they, the coaches, can only do so much. Liz re-visits trauma from her synchronized swimming days and talks about the time she interviewed for Anna Wintour.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Leaf Blowers | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170128/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170128/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s Flightless Bird, David Farrier sets out to understand why Americans love leaf blowers so much. Plagued by leaf blowers around his tiny one-bedroom apartment, David attempts to reach President Joe Biden to discuss leaf blower use at the White House. Failing miserably, he has to settle for another politician - also powerful - Pleasantville Village Trustee, Nicole Asquith. Why are various cities and states attempting to phase out gas-guzzling leaf blowers and why are they so dangerous?</description></item><item><title>Race to 35: Day 8 + Chelsea Handler | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170129/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170129/</guid><description>Podcast Description Liz and Monica declare their sisterhood in episode 8 (of 10) of Race to 35. The two discuss how pain is passed down, Monica cries over Delta, and they talk about how this experience is affecting the way they view their parents. In the second half of the episode, they discuss the choice to not have kids with Chelsea Handler. They talk about the value of being able to give globally instead of insularly, Chelsea shares the story of when she realized she didn&amp;rsquo;t want kids, and she reinforces the idea that one can have a full life without children.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Bears | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170130/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170130/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s Flightless Bird, David Farrier sets out to understand one of America’s grandest animals, the Grizzly Bear. Emblazoned on the California flag and seal, what does this giant predator have to say about the American people? David discovers that animals kill about 400 Americans every year… how many of those deaths involve bears? To get some perspective on this often misunderstood creature, David sits down with journalist and newspaper editor Rob Chaney, who wrote an incredible book about Grizzlies called “The Grizzly in the Driveway”.</description></item><item><title>Race to 35: Day 7 + Dana | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170131/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Liz and Monica are “feeling superior to men today&amp;quot; in episode 7 (of 10) of Race to 35. The two talk about their fears of being needy and question what it would look like to build a non-traditional family. They chat with a choice mom, Dana, who has a two year old son via IUI and donor. She talks the women through the process of picking a donor and the highs and lows of having a child without a partner.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Thanksgiving | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170132/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170132/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s Flightless Bird, David Farrier sets out to find the perfect turkey and in doing so discovers what Thanksgiving is all about. Somehow, Farrier gets acclaimed celebrity chef Michael Voltaggio to cook him, Dax, Monica, and Rob a full Thanksgiving meal - which involves a lot of turkey, sides, stuffing and pies. Voltaggio and Farrier discuss turkey jacuzzis and where Michael can be found most Thanksgivings. Puzzled by the origins of Thanksgiving, David talks to Crystal EchoHawk, founder &amp;amp; Executive Director of illuminative.</description></item><item><title>Race to 35: Day 6 + Christina Perri | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170133/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Monica and Liz&amp;rsquo;s trays finally arrive in Episode 6 (out of 10) of Race to 35. In this episode, the two women start a new shot and Monica lies to Liz about how much it hurts. Additionally, Liz is put on a blood thinner because she tested positive for a genetic blood mutation. The two talk to singer/songwriter Christina Perri about her struggle with fertility and her experience enduring multiple miscarriages.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Airports | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170134/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170134/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s Flightless Bird, David Farrier sets out to understand the American airport and what makes it tick. Why are the top seven busiest airports in the world all based in America, and what does that mean for the traveler? David sets off for the world’s third business airport, Denver, to dig into the various conspiracy theories surrounding the airport. Why does it greet passengers with a giant terrifying mustang with glowing red eyes and did it really kill the artist who made it?</description></item><item><title>Race to 35: Day 5 + Andrew Huberman | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170135/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Liz and Monica decide they can&amp;rsquo;t get canceled in ep 5 (of 10) of Race to 35. They revisit a final destination moment from last night&amp;rsquo;s shots and Liz declares she finally feels like a person after hearing words of encouragement from an Uber mom. Monica receives some encouraging news about her follicles and they lament about the stingy medication implementation. Then they get science-y with professor at Stanford, podcaster and friend of the pod - Andrew Huberman.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: News | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170136/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170136/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s Flightless Bird, David sets out to understand American Network News, and the country’s obsession with rolling 24/7 news coverage. Why does the Fox News Channel averaged more total viewers than CNN and MSNBC combined and how is American TV news faring in the wake of Twitter and TikTok? David talks to Stacy Scholder, a professor at the University of Southern California who teaches TV journalism. What is she teaching the next generation of TV journalists and what was it like covering OJ Simpson’s escape on the LA freeway?</description></item><item><title>Race to 35: Day 4 + Eve Wiley + Bee | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170137/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Liz and Monica don&amp;rsquo;t know what&amp;rsquo;s real in episode 4 (of 10) of Race to 35. Monica receives unfortunate news from her doctor, we learn about Liz&amp;rsquo;s synchronized swimming history and they remind each other they can do hard things. The remainder of the episode focuses on fertility fraud. They speak with Eve Wiley, advocate for regulation and legislation in the fertility industry, who tells a harrowing personal experience in uncovering her genetic truth.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Maths | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170138/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170138/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s Flightless Bird, David Farrier sets out to understand why Americans say “math”, while New Zealand - and most of the rest of the world - says “maths”. He speaks to Dean Koorey about the mysteries of language, before stumbling into the depths of math/maths and the perils of the metric system. How many ounces in a pound? How many pounds are in a stone? And why is America stuck using the imperial system when the rest of the planet loves the sensible metric system?</description></item><item><title>Race to 35: Day 3 + Emily Oster + January Jones | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170139/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Monica and Liz are owning their dumbness in episode 3 (of 10) of Race to 35. They discuss last night&amp;rsquo;s shots which were an utter disaster involving Monica giving Liz a proper stabbing. They talk to Emily Oster, American author and professor of economics at Brown, who talks about how to apply the principles of economics to fertility and pregnancy. She applies cost/benefit, optimizing the margin and opportunity cost to their egg freezing journey.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Halloween | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170140/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170140/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s Flightless Bird, David Farrier sets to understand where the heck Halloween came from, a holiday that generates over $10 billion in retail sales in the US each year. Why does an average American spend $60 on the scary day, and is it more tied in with paganism, Christianity, or scary monsters? David meets with Regina Hansen - a writer and scholar who teaches at Boston University - to talk about why we used to carve turnips instead of pumpkins, before calling up professor of philosophy and religion Justin Sledge to talk horror movies.</description></item><item><title>Race to 35: Day 2 + Douglas NeJamie + Dre &amp; Rachel | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170141/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Monica and Liz are feeling &amp;ldquo;floopy&amp;rdquo; in episode 2 (of 10) of Race to 35. They discuss the previous nights&amp;rsquo; shots, the potentially deathly air bubble, substitute trays, and how they shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be allowed to make purchases or decisions of any kind. They talk to Douglas NeJaime who is a professor of Law at Yale. Douglas specializes in parentage law and provides insight on what we deem legal parents in this country.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Shower Curtains | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170142/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170142/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s Flightless Bird, David Farrier sets out to understand why America - despite all its advancements in innovation and technology - has decided to stick with the puzzling shower curtain. Why, while countries like New Zealand embrace the shower door, is America stuck in a long-term love affair with the fabric (or sometimes plastic) mistress? David calls his old friend Harvey from the Toilets episode to discuss American showering habits, before spending the day with the self-proclaimed “Glass Queen” who spends her days removing shower curtains and replacing them with glistening shower doors.</description></item><item><title>Race to 35: Day 1 | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170143/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170143/</guid><description>Podcast Description Day 1 - Liz and Monica embark on their fertility journey. They sit down with Monica’s BFF - who has gone through the egg retrieval process herself - to ask questions and discuss their fears about the upcoming 10 days. They talk needles, they learn what follicles are, and they equate the vaginal ultrasound wand to an uncomfortable dildo. At the end of the episode, Liz and Monica administer their first shot on air and it is quite a rollercoaster.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Amish | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170144/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170144/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s Flightless Bird, David Farrier sets out to understand the Amish, a group of Swiss Germans slash Alsatians that chose America as their home away from home. Why does a country that embraces fast cars, fast money, and fast food also embrace the very slow-moving Amish? David discovers why back in 2000 there were only 178,000 Amish in the US, and why that number has climbed to well over 367,000 - an increase of 106%.</description></item><item><title>Introducing... Race to 35 | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170145/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170145/</guid><description>Podcast Description The producers of Armchair Expert present their newest podcast venture, Race to 35. Race to 35 is co-hosted by Monica Padman and Liz Plank and focuses on Fertility. Throughout this 10 episode podcast, Monica and Liz will be going through the egg freezing process as they hit the critical age of 35. The top of each episode will check in on the two women- see how they are feeling, how their hormone shots are progressing and share their ever evolving thoughts, emotions, fears, joys, etc.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Game Shows | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170146/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170146/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s Flightless Bird, David Farrier embraces the American institution of game shows. He sets out to understand how in this time of high-caliber TV, Celebrity Wheel of Fortune still manages to pull in four million ahead of shows like Dateline, Undercover Boss, and Masterchef. David joins fellow kiwi Rhys Darby as he’s invited on Celebrity Family Feud - thrilled at the idea of meeting comic, actor, author, and Emmy Award-winning talk-show host Steve Harvey.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Pornography | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170147/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170147/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David Farrier sets out to explore America’s adult film industry, which has its heart in California’s San Fernando Valley. In this episode Farrier heads for a mansion in the hills of Calabasas to attend an adult film shoot, hoping to understand why Americans spend an average of 9 minutes and 44 seconds on porn sites at a time. David meets a porn director also called “David” to ask why they still have all that dialogue and plot in amongst all the sex, before chatting with porn stars Hadley and Lucas about the joys, trials, and tribulations of their unique job.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: RVs | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170148/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170148/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David sets out to understand America&amp;rsquo;s obsession with recreational vehicles, also known as RVs. Joined by Monica and Dax, David discovers why 11.2 million American homes have an RV of some kind and why 10 million more are considering buying one within the next five years. David sits down with Monica Geraci, the official spokesperson for the American RV Industry Association, to find out some tips and tricks before descending into Griffith Park to meet an actor who lives in an RV full time.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Bunkers | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170149/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170149/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David descends underground into the world of preppers and bunkers, learning that 40% of Americans believe that stocking up on supplies or building an underground shelter is a better investment than saving for retirement. Joined by Monica Mouse, David discovers that humans have wanted to live underground for the last 2000 years. David interviews ethnographic researcher Bradley Garrett about the mindset of the American bunker enthusiast since Covid and finds out why Brad was arrested on the tarmac back in 2012, spending two years marooned in the UK.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Baseball | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170150/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170150/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David heads to San Francisco to meet the San Francisco Giants. Joined by Wobby Wob, David attempts to learn how to catch a baseball, before becoming distracted by some loud screams coming from the field. It&amp;rsquo;s there he meets the Chicago White Sox&amp;rsquo;s Liam Hendriks, an outspoken Australian with a good arm and lots of opinions. David learns why 16 million Americans play baseball in some kind of organized fashion and talks to bench coach Kai Correa about how to win a game.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Tipping | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170151/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170151/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David gets out his wallet and dives into the culture and politics of tipping. Joined by Monica Padman, he sets out to discover why 52% of Americans tip their hairdresser while only 14% always tip their barista. David interviews Mike Lynn, a professor at the Cornell Hotel School, about the social pressures of tipping and why we tip what we tip. David also talks to Saru Jayaraman of “One Fair Wage”, who explains that tipping is a deeply warped version of what Americans brought back from Europe - and that in America tipping has some fairly racist origins - which has led to power imbalances for the 5.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Juggalos | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170152/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170152/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David dives into the insane world of Insane Clown Posse fans, who called themselves “Juggalos.” David is shocked to discover that due to the criminal enterprises of certain members of the fandom, the FBI decided to classify them as a gang. David talks to one of the first people to document Juggalo culture, Derek Erdman - before meeting another documentary maker who spent years with ICP’s “Violent J” and “Shaggy 2 Dope”, unlocking the magic that makes this band a $10 million-dollars-a-year business.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Amazon | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170153/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170153/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David prepares to hit “Buy Now” as he embarks into the world of Amazon, the company that notched up $116 billion in sales during the first three months of this year. Joined by Monica, he looks at how this company has slowly inserted itself into the American lifestyle, from TV and film, to products, to Alexa living in everyone’s house, tending to their every need.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Healthcare | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170154/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170154/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David sets out to make sense of the very confusing American healthcare system. Joined by Monica, he tries to figure out why some Americans end up paying their own ambulance bill and why over half of the American population is riddled with medical debt. David talks to Luke O’Neil - the journalist and writer behind the popular newsletter &amp;ldquo;Welcome to Hellworld&amp;rdquo; - about why it falls on children to raise money for their parent&amp;rsquo;s medical bills and discovers why in the US healthcare system teeth are considered “luxury bones”.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Diners | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170155/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170155/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David sets out to understand what makes the American diner experience so special, by traveling to Reno, Nevada. There he meets the staff of Peg&amp;rsquo;s Glorified Ham N Eggs and meets the regulars who&amp;rsquo;ve made the diner their home away from home - including Rainbow Man, a man obsessed with painting human bodies at Burning Man. What makes a diner a diner? How have they changed over the years?</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Circumcision | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170156/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170156/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David sets out to discover why America loves circumcision so much, to the point where 115 million American men now find themselves without a foreskin. Joined by Monica, he tries to figure out why this medical procedure became so popular here, leading to some medical diagrams not bothering to include a foreskin anymore. David talks to a man in his 30s who’s furious he got circumcised when he was a baby, and another who’s annoyed he wasn’t circumcised, as he considers getting an adult circumcision.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Football | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170157/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170157/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David sets out to understand a game that simply doesn’t exist in New Zealand: American Football. He tries to figure out America’s most popular sport and asks why over 100 million Americans watched the Super Bowl. After watching the Super Bowl for the first time, David travels to Seattle to get schooled by NFL Hall-of-Famer Walter Jones, who was drafted by the Seahawks in 1997.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Bottled Water | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170158/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170158/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David sets out to understand America’s obsession with bottled water. Joined by Monica, he tries to figure out why tap water just won’t cut it in many US States, leading Americans to spend billions on bottled water every year. David talks to author and scientist Peter Gleick about tap water myths, and how some bottled water companies have accidentally added things like arsenic and cricket parts to their bottled creations.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Disney II | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170159/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170159/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David embarks on his first-ever trip to Disneyland with Dax, Monica, and Wobby Wob to see if the magic of the place rubs off on him. In amongst discovering the joys of Star Wars: Galaxies Edge and the Cars ride, David investigates Disney Social Clubs, also known as &amp;ldquo;Disney Gangs.&amp;rdquo; He learns about the alleged beef between two groups, the Main Street Fire Station 55 Social Club and the White Rabbits, and talks to a member of the Sons of Anakin.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Flags | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170160/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170160/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David sets out to understand why Americans love their flag so much, buying nearly 150 million of them every year. Joined by Dax and Monica, David quizzes them about what it’s like to go to school and pledge allegiance to the flag, before Dax recalls his colorful interactions with an American flag and a flag pole. David talks to flag expert, TedTalker and podcaster Roman Mars about what makes a good flag design, before chatting with vexillologist Tory Laitila - curator of Textiles and Historic Arts of Hawai&amp;rsquo;i at the Honolulu Museum of Art - about the dos and don’ts of flag etiquette.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Burgers | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170161/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170161/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David sets out to discover why Americans love burgers so much, eating 50 million of them a year. Joined by Monica, he tries to figure out why in America it’s always beef for dinner and how that fact has drastically altered the biology of the humble cow. David talks to Ben Wurgaft, author of “Meat Planet: Artificial Flesh and the Future of Food” about the triumphs and problems of creating artificial meat.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Dog Shows | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170162/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170162/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David sets out to understand his favorite American mockumentary &amp;ldquo;Best in Show&amp;rdquo; by attempting to immerse himself in the world of competitive dog shows. Joined by Monica, David shares his unusual history in the animal-showing world, before meeting happy animal owners who love nothing more than selectively breeding an animal that is superior to all others. We discover the story of a dog assassination attempt and look at how ethics and boundless enthusiasm collide in the world of competitive animal showing.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Suing | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170163/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170163/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David sets out to discover why Americans love suing each other so much - filing over 40 million lawsuits a year. Joined by Dax and Monica, David attempts to figure out how to avoid being sued and talks about the time a New York man sued him&amp;hellip; twice. Dax weighs in with his own legal battles and David talks to New York media lawyer Cameron Stracher about what it was like defending the National Enquirer during the Michael Cohen Trump Fiasco.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Disney Adults | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170164/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170164/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David sets out to discover how Disney’s parks and experiences division made 17 billion dollars last year - seeing 77 million people through its rollercoasters, rides, and massive queues. Joined by Monica, David tries to figure out what Disney Adults are all about, and why they love those Mickey Mouse ears so much. David talks to a hardcore Disneyland fan to learn about Disney’s biggest secrets, including SEA - the hidden backstory worked into every Disney Park on the planet.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Toilets | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170165/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170165/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David sets out to discover why the water level on American toilets is terrifyingly high, almost filling up the entire toilet bowl. Joined by Monica, he tries to figure out why it’s so hard to find a public restroom and why the gaps in the doors are so big. David talks to urban sociologist and toilet expert Harvey Molotch, who explains why public restrooms unchanging - segregated into male and female sections - seem to be locked in time.</description></item><item><title>Flightless Bird: Religion | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170166/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170166/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Flightless Bird, David sets out to understand religion in America. Joined by Dax and Monica, he tries to figure out why over 200 million Americans are Christians, and how uniquely Americanized this religion has become - with franchises, brands, and celebrity endorsements. David talks to Mike McHargue - a Baptist who became an atheist who then became a Christian again. We discover how someone can love both Christianity and science - and you may be very surprised to learn your brain may well believe in God… even if you’re a stone-cold atheist!</description></item><item><title>Introducing... Flightless Bird with David Farrier | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170167/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170167/</guid><description>Podcast Description Armchair Umbrella and David Farrier introduce you to Flightless Bird, a show that follows kiwi journalist David Farrier as he embarks on a quest to understand American culture, after getting accidentally marooned here. From football to flags, religion to burgers, David wants to learn about the things that make America tick. “Why do adults love Disneyland so much?” and “why are American toilets filled to the brim with water?</description></item><item><title>We are supported by... the Future is Female | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170168/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170168/</guid><description>Podcast Description We Are Supported By, hosted by Kristen Bell and Monica Padman is a 10 episode limited series podcast. Each episode deep dives with a woman who has put a crack in the glass ceiling. Bonus Episode: The Future is Female Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We are supported by... Sheryl Sandberg | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170169/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170169/</guid><description>Podcast Description We Are Supported By, hosted by Kristen Bell and Monica Padman is a 10 episode limited series podcast. Each episode deep dives with a woman who has put a crack in the glass ceiling. Episode 10: Sheryl Sandberg Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We are supported by... Reese Witherspoon | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170170/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170170/</guid><description>Podcast Description We Are Supported By, hosted by Kristen Bell and Monica Padman is a 10 episode limited series podcast. Each episode deep dives with a woman who has put a crack in the glass ceiling. Episode 9: Reese Witherspoon Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We are supported by... Kim Kardashian West | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170171/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170171/</guid><description>Podcast Description We Are Supported By, hosted by Kristen Bell and Monica Padman is a 10 episode limited series podcast. Each episode deep dives with a woman who has put a crack in the glass ceiling. Episode 8: Kim Kardashian West Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We are supported by... Abby Wambach | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170172/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170172/</guid><description>Podcast Description We Are Supported By, hosted by Kristen Bell and Monica Padman is a 10 episode limited series podcast. Each episode deep dives with a woman who has put a crack in the glass ceiling. Episode 7: Abby Wambach Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We are supported by... Esther Duflo | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170173/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170173/</guid><description>Podcast Description We Are Supported By, hosted by Kristen Bell and Monica Padman is a 10 episode limited series podcast. Each episode deep dives with a woman who has put a crack in the glass ceiling. Episode 6: Esther Duflo Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We are supported by... Diane von Furstenberg | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170174/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170174/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are supported by, hosted by Kristen Bell and Monica Padman is a 10 episode limited series podcast. Each episode deep dives with a woman who has put a crack in the glass ceiling. Episode 5: Diane von Furstenberg Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We are supported by... Samantha Power | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170175/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170175/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are supported by, hosted by Kristen Bell and Monica Padman is a 10 episode limited series podcast. Each episode deep dives with a woman who has put a crack in the glass ceiling. Episode 4: Samantha Power Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We are supported by... Oprah Winfrey | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170176/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170176/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are supported by, hosted by Kristen Bell and Monica Padman is a 10 episode limited series podcast. Each episode deep dives with a woman who has put a crack in the glass ceiling. Episode 3: Oprah Winfrey Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We are supported by... Malala Yousafzai | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170177/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170177/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are supported by, hosted by Kristen Bell and Monica Padman is a 10 episode limited series podcast. Each episode deep dives with a woman who has put a crack in the glass ceiling. Episode 2: Malala Yousafzai Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We are supported by... Gloria Steinem | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170178/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170178/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are supported by, hosted by Kristen Bell and Monica Padman is a 10 episode limited series podcast. Each episode deep dives with a woman who has put a crack in the glass ceiling. Episode 1: Gloria Steinem Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Introducing... We Are Supported By | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170179/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170179/</guid><description>Podcast Description The producers of Armchair Expert present a new 10 episode podcast, We Are Supported By&amp;hellip; with hosts Kristen Bell and Monica Padman. In this podcast, Kristen and Monica will talk to a woman each episode who has made a significant crack in the ceiling. They will talk to women in many fields - entrepreneurship, entertainment, sports, politics and activism - and during these conversations, they will talk through their guests&amp;rsquo; accomplishments, struggles, points of resilience, inspiration and fears.</description></item><item><title>Nurture vs Nurture: Family #3: Joan &amp; Todd | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170180/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Mogel answers the question: Will our children hate us for a bucolic childhood on the farm? She also teaches us new words: poronkusema &amp;amp; mbuki-mvuki
Make sure to subscribe to weekly episodes, dropping every Tuesday only on the Nurture vs Nurture feed. Just search “Nurture vs Nurture” on Apple Podcast, Spotify, or wherever you listen to podcasts. Or visit bit.ly/wendymogel. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>Nurture vs Nurture: Family #2: Brooke | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170181/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170181/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Mogel answers the question: Will my children hate me for becoming a cool secret agent? She also teaches us a new word: allomother
Make sure to subscribe to weekly episodes, dropping every Tuesday only on the Nurture vs Nurture feed. Just search “Nurture vs Nurture” on Apple Podcast, Spotify, or wherever you listen to podcasts. Or visit bit.ly/wendymogel. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nurture vs Nurture: Family #1: Erick and Elsie | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170182/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170182/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Mogel speaks with family #1: Erick and Elsie and answers the question: Will our children hate us if we stop loving them so much? She also teaches us a new word: Familect
Listen to a BONUS EPISODE right now on the Nurture vs Nurture feed. And make sure to subscribe to weekly episodes, dropping every Tuesday only on the Nurture vs Nurture feed. Just search “Nurture vs Nurture” on Apple Podcast, Spotify, or wherever you listen to podcasts.</description></item><item><title>Part 10: Monica &amp; Jess Love Each Other with Dax &amp; Kristen | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170183/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 07:30:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170183/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Part 10: Monica and Jess love each other, M and J chat with Kristen and Dax for their final episode. The four discuss what Monica and Jess learned from the experience, how they&amp;rsquo;ve grown and the things they can&amp;rsquo;t un-learn after this journey. Monica talks about a newfound relationship to her narrative and Jess has a growing acceptance of addiction. Dax wonders what the big take-aways have been, Kristen praises M and J&amp;rsquo;s vulnerability and the four verbally &amp;ldquo;write&amp;rdquo; their relationship manuals.</description></item><item><title>Part 9: Monica &amp; Jess love Love Addiction with Dr. Alex Katehakis | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170184/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 07:30:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170184/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Part 9: Monica &amp;amp; Jess love Love Addiction, M and J chat with author and the Clinical Director of Center for Healthy Sex in Los Angeles, Dr. Alex Katehakis. Dr. Alex talks about the tenants of unmanageability and addiction. Monica wonders if you can be a love addict who’s never fallen in love and Jess asks questions about post relationship nostalgia. Dr. Alex declares both Monica and Jess have some dissociative tendencies in relationships and adhere to fantasy as an outlet.</description></item><item><title>Part 8: Monica &amp; Jess Love Cock Buffets with Dan Savage | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170185/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 07:30:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170185/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Part 8: Monica &amp;amp; Jess Love Cock Buffets, M and J welcome Dan Savage (author, media pundit, journalist, and LGBT community activist) to the attic via video chat. Dan delineates many differences between dating in the gay community vs. the straight one. He talks to Monica about why women are engrained to &amp;ldquo;vet a guy before they bed a guy&amp;rdquo; and talks to Jess about transgressive behaviors in the gay community.</description></item><item><title>Part 7: Monica &amp; Jess Love Goblins with Esther Perel | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170186/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 07:30:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170186/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Part 7: Monica &amp;amp; Jess Love Goblins with Esther Perel, M and J are thrilled to welcome psychotherapist, Esther Perel to the attic. Esther makes the distinction between love and desire and she reminds them that having a lot of sex with many partners is equivalent to avoiding sex- both are methods to avoid rejection. Esther encourages Monica to let go of the goblin on her shoulder and she removes the phrase &amp;ldquo;losing feelings for&amp;rdquo; from the relationship vocabulary.</description></item><item><title>Part 6: Monica &amp; Jess Love Tough Love with Patti Stanger (the Millionaire Matchmaker) | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170187/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 07:30:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170187/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Part 6: Monica &amp;amp; Jess Love Tough Love with Patti Stanger, M and J welcome the Millionaire Matchmaker to the attic. Patti is direct and no-nonsense when giving her opinion on Monica and Jess’s love lives. She asks about their dream men, she prods for details about Monica’s fantasies and believes Jess wants to be chased. She talks about the differences between “beta” and “alpha” partners, differences between matchmaking in gay vs.</description></item><item><title>Part 5: Monica &amp; Jess Love Getting Called Out on Their Bullshit with Dr. Drew | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170188/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 07:30:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170188/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Part 5: Monica and Jess Love Getting Called Out on Their Bullshit with Dr. Drew, M and J invite the esteemed addiction medicine specialist and personality Dr. Drew Pinsky to the attic. Dr. Drew cuts right to the chase asking Jess about his relationship to mania, asking Monica about family trauma and he calls both of them out on negating themselves. He talks about removing expectations and how our country puts pathological love on a pedestal.</description></item><item><title>Part 4: Monica &amp; Jess Love Therapy with Harry the Therapist | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170189/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 08:30:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170189/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Part 4: Monica and Jess Love Therapy with Harry the Therapist, M and J invite Harry - Kristen and Dax&amp;rsquo;s couples therapist, to the attic. Harry specializes in both personal and couples therapy and Kristen and Dax have credited Harry for giving them the tools for relationship longevity. But today he brings his expertise to Monica and Jess&amp;rsquo;s love lives. Harry wonders if Monica has any unresolved parental issues and he encourages Jess to listen to his small inner voice.</description></item><item><title>Part 3: Monica &amp; Jess Love Motherly Advice with Kristen Bell | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170190/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 08:30:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170190/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Part 3: Monica and Jess Love Motherly Advice with Kristen Bell, M and J invite their mom to the attic. Using her mother&amp;rsquo;s intuition, Kristen warns Jess on the falsity of butterflies, they discuss the prevalence of blocking people on apps and Kristen asks Jess about the rigidity of tops and bottoms in the gay dating community. She encourages Monica to externalize her sexuality, she tells a story of a friend who leaves her underwear at bars and Monica reveals a recent fantasy slip.</description></item><item><title>Part 2: Monica &amp; Jess Love Boys who like Christmas | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170191/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 08:30:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170191/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Part 2: Monica and Jess Love Boys who like Christmas, M and J have one solo episode (before they bring in experts) where they dive deeper into their histories. They discuss their experiences completing last week’s challenge. Jess lived in fear all week that he ruined his challenge and Monica adds “needs to like Christmas” to her list. Jess talks about having secret moments in his youth with other boys while openly having a girlfriend and Monica goes through some of her boy-crazy artifacts.</description></item><item><title>Part 1: Monica and Jess Love Boys with Dax Shepard | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170192/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 08:30:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170192/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Part 1: Monica and Jess Love Boys with Dax Shepard, M and J sit down with the Armchair Expert. Dax knows Monica and Jess better than anyone and he uses his previous knowledge to help diagnose individual and collective dating patterns. He asks Jess about addiction, his propensity for sex, “dating” rituals and he asks why Jess isn’t leading with his superpower: personality. He talks to Monica about her tendency to overanalyze, her pattern of wanting people she can’t have and not being attracted to people who find her attractive.</description></item><item><title>Introducing: Monica &amp; Jess Love Boys | Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5136170193/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 08:30:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5136170193/</guid><description>Podcast Description Monica and Jess Love Boys is a 10 episode series brought to you by the Armchair Expert that follows the relationship struggles of two opposites. Jess, who dates too much and Monica who dates too little. They approach relationships from opposing ends but quickly realize how the underlying issues are universal. Jess dates in the gay community while Monica dates in the straight one. They get to deep dive not only into individual patterns but societal ones as well in the different dating scenes.</description></item></channel></rss>