<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Wild Things Siegfried &amp; Roy on SWIEST - Transcripts 路 Screenplays 路 Lyrics</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/categories/wild-things-siegfried-roy/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Wild Things Siegfried &amp; Roy on SWIEST - Transcripts 路 Screenplays 路 Lyrics</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 15:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/categories/wild-things-siegfried-roy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Wild Things Siegfried &amp; Roy - Hell on Earth</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1310000008/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1310000008/</guid>
        <description>This episode contains graphic descriptions of violence and language that may not be suitable for all listeners.
Please be advised.
As far as birthday parties, Roy Horn 59th birthday party with you know most extravagant ones I&amp;rsquo;ve ever been to.
Curtis Rowe is attending Roy&amp;rsquo;s birthday party at The Mirage on October 2nd, 2003.
No expense has been spared.
There&amp;rsquo;s a balloon drop, a conga line with hundreds of people and ice sculptures of tigers.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Wild Things Siegfried &amp; Roy - Bit by a Tiger</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1310000007/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1310000007/</guid>
        <description>This episode contains graphic descriptions of violence, sexual content, and language that may not be suitable for all listeners.
Please be advised.
I was at my parents house before I went to work.
My mom was a stay at home mom and so she was always there.
Scotty Briscoe is a seamstress working on Siegfried and Roy show at the Stardust Hotel and Casino.
It&amp;rsquo;s just there&amp;rsquo;s something magical about it.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Wild Things Siegfried &amp; Roy - White Tiger Conundrum</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1310000006/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1310000006/</guid>
        <description>Thank you.
Pleasure for us to be here tonight.
It&amp;rsquo;s April 29th, 2003, and Siegfried and Roy are performing their usual Tuesday night show.
Just five months from now, Monocor will attack Roy on this very stage.
Tonight&amp;rsquo;s show, however, will go off without a hitch.
Boy and I gonna do all the work, all right?
Boy, when I found out that I was going to go to Las Vegas, I immediately knew I was going to buy a ticket to Siegfried and Roy.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Wild Things Siegfried &amp; Roy - The Jesus Man</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1310000005/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1310000005/</guid>
        <description>This episode contains descriptions of violence and language that may not be suitable for all listeners.
Please be advised.
On September 21st, 1997, the Oakland Raiders are facing the New York Jets.
In the first quarter, Raider kicker Cole forward is called out to attempt a 44 yard field goal.
So far this season, the 24 year old USC alum has become the most accurate kicker in Raiders history.
But that statistic will be short lived.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Wild Things Siegfried &amp; Roy - An Inside Job?</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1310000004/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1310000004/</guid>
        <description>Siegfried and Roy.
They&amp;rsquo;ve been doing this for you know, 30 years and never had an incident and now all of a sudden they had an incident.
They&amp;rsquo;re like, whoa, this is not typical.
Michael Game is the police detective with the Las Vegas counterterrorism unit.
He is investigating whether the tiger attack wasn&amp;rsquo;t an accident.
So everybody I think was just kind of like something had to happen.
So what we were looking at was did somebody in the audience do something to cause the animal to react differently than it was normally known to react?</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Wild Things Siegfried &amp; Roy - Rumors and Ridicule</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1310000003/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1310000003/</guid>
        <description>This episode contains language that may not be suitable for all listeners.
Please be advised.
When you see it outside of your window, it&amp;rsquo;s the best feeling.
People just cheer and clap when they arrive.
In Puerto Rico, Gina Goodwin was born in Puerto Rico, where her mother, Kathy, is a dancer at the Americana Hotel there.
Kathy first meets a new opening act called Siegfried and Roy.
Back in the day when she was performing, she was in Puerto Rico and Siegfried and Roy happened to be opening up for her show.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Wild Things Siegfried &amp; Roy - The Pet Detective</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1310000002/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1310000002/</guid>
        <description>It&amp;rsquo;s April 3rd, 2002 and families are lining up outside a big carnival like attraction at the Cielo Vista Mall in El Paso, TX.
From what I remember, it was out in the parking lot.
They&amp;rsquo;ve all bought tickets to do something special.
You had to go inside of the cage.
I was sitting in a chair, I believe from my recollection that the cat was in a cage right to the side of where you sit down and got your picture taken.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Wild Things Siegfried &amp; Roy - What Went Wrong</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1310000001/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1310000001/</guid>
        <description>It was just another night.
That&amp;rsquo;s all it was.
I think we had to be there at 7 and this should start at 7:30.
I&amp;rsquo;m in the mail dressing room which is a mix of dancers and acrobats, and then, but we&amp;rsquo;re wearing these body suits that make us look like we&amp;rsquo;re super muscular and took like 10 minutes to squeeze into them every day.
I was still getting used to the fact that I was dancing alongside giant wild animals.</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
