<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Simon Bridges: Generally Famous on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/simon-bridges-generally-famous/</link><description>Recent content in Simon Bridges: Generally Famous on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/simon-bridges-generally-famous/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Episode 51: Shane Cameron | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710001/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710001/</guid><description>Podcast Description The &amp;lsquo;Mountain Warrior&amp;rsquo; proves the heavyweight champion of Mike Tyson impressions in a knockout chat about life before, during and after his hugely successful boxing career. No punches are pulled as he recalls his country upbringing, his rivalry with David Tua (and how he patched it up) and sparring with Tyson. He also addresses his ADD diagnosis, adjusting to life as a businessman - and whether he’s ready for a return to the ring.</description></item><item><title>Episode 50: Matthew Ridge | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sporting legend and former larrikin Matthew Ridge interrupts a family holiday in LA to record a very special 50th episode of Generally Famous. The ex All Black, Kiwi and Warrior weighs up the problems facing New Zealand, recalls life as a primetime TV staple with Marc Ellis, bemoans the treatment of public figures, and explains why family is much more important than wealth. You can watch Matthew Ridge&amp;rsquo;s Designing Dreams on SkyGo.</description></item><item><title>Episode 49: Greg Murphy | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710003/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Motorsport great Greg Murphy parks up in the Generally Famous studio for a straight-up chat about racing, road safety and why he&amp;rsquo;s happy to keep speaking his mind. The co-host of Sky Speed also explains the legendary Holden vs Ford rivalry and the enduring influence of the Dukes of Hazzard. You can read stories supporting this episode on stuff.co.nz. Need more great podcasts? Check out Stuff&amp;rsquo;s full catalogue here.</description></item><item><title>Episode 48: Theresa Gattung | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710004/</guid><description>Podcast Description With an “elder sister” management style, Theresa Gattung became the youngest woman to run a large public company when she took over Telecom aged 37. Since stepping back from fulltime corporate work, she’s focused on philanthropy and entrepreneurship - while continuing to spearhead change for women in business. The trailblazer explains how her father’s groundbreaking attitudes shaped her success, says women still face “the motherhood penalty” and reveals the industry she believes is still one big boys’ club.</description></item><item><title>Episode 47: Pax Assadi | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710005/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pax Assadi started working life as a vacuum cleaner salesman. Now he’s hoovering up plaudits as a stand-up comic, TV presenter and creator and star of Sky sitcom Raised by Refugees. Born in Auckland to a Pakistani mum and Iranian dad, he discusses representation in mainstream media, the one country where he’s experienced outright racism, and why the backlash against The Simpsons character Apu was unfair. You can watch Raised by Refugees on Sky Go and Neon.</description></item><item><title>Episode 46: Geoff &amp; Justine Ross | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710006/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trailblazing business brains and childhood sweethearts Geoff and Justine Ross sold their premium vodka brand 42 Below to Bacardi for $138 million. Now they&amp;rsquo;ve swapped &amp;ldquo;wine and cheesing&amp;rdquo; in Auckland for running a 6500-hectare sheep and beef farm in Otago. The self-confessed environmental activists and passionate New Zealanders discuss why they took &amp;ldquo;the harder road&amp;rdquo;, reaction to their Country Calendar appearance and why regenerative farming is much more than a &amp;ldquo;hippie crock of shit&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Episode 45: Michael Galvin | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710007/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710007/</guid><description>Podcast Description From Dr Love to Dr Loving Life, Shortland Street&amp;rsquo;s sole surviving original reflects on playing Chris Warner for almost three decades. He opens up on the panic attack that marred his return to the show, ageing on set, and &amp;ldquo;calming the f down&amp;rdquo; and finding happiness. He also talks his new play, Mannbannd, his love of theatre - and the celebrity he&amp;rsquo;s mistaken for. Mannbannd runs from November 18 to December 16 at the Centrepoint Theatre in Palmerston North.</description></item><item><title>Episode 44: Dr Alia Bojilova | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710008/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr Alia Bojilova is a registered psychologist who worked in the NZ Defence Force, including with members of the SAS, and recently starred alongside Hollywood hardman Vinnie Jones in international reality TV show Tracked. She shares her story of working as a United Nations military observer in Syria, where she and two colleagues were kidnapped, held at gunpoint and told they were going to be decapitated. Alia specialises in resilience and has recently written a book called The Resilience Toolkit.</description></item><item><title>Episode 43: Blair Strang | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710009/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710009/</guid><description>Podcast Description After early appearances in The Billy T. James Show and Once Were Warriors, Blair Strang became a household name as ambulance driver Rangi Heremaia on Shortland Street. Six years later he quit to complete his legal degree and now juggles family law with acting and running his own theatre company. Beaming in from his Northland home, he discusses how he handled fame in the heyday of Kiwi TV, getting recognised in court and why he finally agreed to reality TV when Celebrity Treasure Island came calling.</description></item><item><title>Episode 42: Ben Bayly | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710010/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Top chef and TV favourite Ben Bayley has returned to his Kiwi roots after almost a decade of culinary discovery in top kitchens across the globe. With a string of highly regarded venues in Auckland and Otago, he&amp;rsquo;s also a regular on our screens. Ben has fronted two series of A New Zealand Food Story, with a third on the way, and The Restaurant That Makes Mistakes, an experiment that saw volunteers with dementia run a restaurant under his supervision.</description></item><item><title>Episode 41: Carl Hayman | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710011/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710011/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 1000th All Black talks frankly about the brutal toll of rugby, life with early-onset dementia and his battles with alcohol. He outlines how the sport should change and recalls the circumstances in which he left to play - and stay - overseas. Oh, and he explains why he doesn&amp;rsquo;t want to ditch his 1992 Nissan Patrol! (Carl also offered his thoughts on New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s Rugby World Cup prospects, but it&amp;rsquo;s only fair to point out the interview was recorded before the All Blacks&amp;rsquo; record defeat, to South Africa.</description></item><item><title>Episode 40: Antonia Prebble | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710012/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Best known - in Aotearoa at least - for her roles in Outrageous Fortune and its prequel Westside, Antonia chats about her distinguished career and why she&amp;rsquo;s big in Germany. She also offers insight into her royal links and swaps stories with Simon about on-set snack tables. Watch her latest show Double Parked. Listen to her podcast What Matters Most. You can read stories supporting this episode on stuff.</description></item><item><title>Episode 39: Dai Henwood | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710013/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kiwi comedy icon Dai Henwood drops in to talk about his incredible career and surprising family back-story. Born into a proud Welsh lineage with illustrious forebears, he knew he wanted to make people laugh from a very young age. He talks comedy in Aotearoa, Eastern religion and mindfulness - and how his latest gig on the phenomenon that is Taskmaster NZ gave him a positive focus after he went public with his stage 4 cancer diagnosis.</description></item><item><title>Episode 38: Andy Cooks | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710014/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Finding himself out of work as Covid decimated the hospitality industry, he decided to create cooking videos packed with tips and tricks to educate and inspire home foodies. Twenty months since posting the first, he has 13 million followers and more than a billion views across multiple platforms. Beaming in from his current home on Australia’s Sunshine Coast, he discusses his “surreal” success, the pressures of working in top restaurant kitchens and the state of New Zealand’s food scene.</description></item><item><title>Episode 37: Jay-Jay Feeney | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Radio legend Jay-Jay Feeney first graced our airwaves as a teenager and remains an unstoppable force more than three decades on. She shares some highly impressive celebrity encounters and opens up about a life of complex relationships, including with her former partner - on and off air - Dom Harvey. You can read stories supporting this episode on stuff.co.nz. Need more great podcasts? Check out Stuff&amp;rsquo;s full catalogue here.</description></item><item><title>Episode 36: Kylie Bax | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kylie Bax went from winning a beauty contest in Thames to the catwalks of Milan in a matter of months. Soon she was gracing the cover of every top fashion magazine in the world. She gives Simon a rare insight into life as an elite model - from the hard work involved in getting a break, to hanging out with the A-list. She also talks her second career - breeding and syndicating race horses - and teases an exciting new business venture.</description></item><item><title>Episode 35: Paddy Gower | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kicking off an all-new season of Generally Famous, current affairs kingpin Paddy Gower drops in to discuss his storied career, his new show and how he&amp;rsquo;s changed. He recalls his &amp;ldquo;absolutely brutal&amp;rdquo; introduction to TV reporting, reveals his regrets about his time covering Parliament and considers his shifting stance on addiction. Paddy&amp;rsquo;s new show, Paddy Gower Has Issues, is available to stream on ThreeNow. New episodes also debut live on Three at 7.</description></item><item><title>Generally Famous Season 5 Trailer | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 02:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Generally Famous is back soon for another noteworthy season. To make sure you don&amp;rsquo;t miss it, follow Generally Famous wherever you get your podcasts.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 34: Suzy Cato | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Legendary children&amp;rsquo;s TV host Suzy Cato (Suzy Cato!) joins Simon Bridges to discuss education in New Zealand, talk career highlights and even sing a song or two. She tears up as she talks about her passion for making children feel safe through her content. Suzy continues to produce a wealth of content for young minds - check it out here. You can read stories supporting this episode on stuff.</description></item><item><title>Episode 33: Brianne West | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710020/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710020/</guid><description>Podcast Description The creator of wildy successful eco-conscious cosmetics company Ethique drops in to talk animals, leadership styles and what on earth a Nudibranch is. The episode was recorded before Brianne&amp;rsquo;s recent announcement that she was stepping down as chief executive of Ethique. She&amp;rsquo;s now focused on business mentoring with another company she founded, Business but Better. You can read stories supporting this episode on stuff.co.nz. Need more great podcasts? Check out Stuff&amp;rsquo;s full catalogue here.</description></item><item><title>Episode 32: Hayden Paddon | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710021/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Already New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s most successful rally driver, Hayden Paddon is showing no signs of slowing down. He tells Simon about his mission to win at the highest level, the dangers of high-speed racing on rough roads and why non-petrol cars are the future. You can read stories supporting this episode on stuff.co.nz. Need more great podcasts? Check out Stuff&amp;rsquo;s full catalogue here. GET IN TOUCH Feedback? Got a guest you’d like Simon to talk to?</description></item><item><title>Episode 31: The Casketeers | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710022/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Francis and Kaiora Tipene are global stars thanks to five seasons of The Casketeers, the reality TV show about their funeral business. They catch up with Simon to talk pies, the pressures of fame, leafblowers - and their own funeral plans. You can read stories supporting this episode on stuff.co.nz. Need more great podcasts? Check out Stuff&amp;rsquo;s full catalogue here. GET IN TOUCH Feedback? Got a guest you’d like Simon to talk to?</description></item><item><title>Episode 30: Shaun Wallace | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710023/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Chaser is on! Specifically Shaun Wallace, the very first Chaser from global TV mega-hit The Chase. Ahead of his visit to Aotearoa-New Zealand, Simon&amp;rsquo;s first international celebrity guest beams in from his London home to discuss juggling criminal law work and a television career, growing up Black in 1960s Britain, and how he keeps his mind and body healthy. Shaun even agrees to take on Simon in a general knowledge quiz.</description></item><item><title>Episode 29: Irene van Dyk | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710024/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Still one of the world&amp;rsquo;s best-known netballers almost a decade after retiring from the international arena, Irene van Dyk grew up in apartheid-era South Africa before moving to Aotearoa in 2000 and becoming one of our most popular athletes. She beams in from her Napier home to tell Simon about her incredible life and career - meeting Nelson Mandela, carrying a gun and overcoming criticism when she first moved to New Zealand.</description></item><item><title>Episode 28: Tom Sainsbury | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710025/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tom Sainsbury is a walking definition of polymath. An acclaimed actor, comedian, director and writer - not to mention Snapchat Dude - he tells Simon about swapping his parents&amp;rsquo; Matamata farm for the bright lights of Auckland. They talk Buddhism, veganism and why he wants a statue. Tom also explains why he decided to impersonate Simon - complete with acrostic poems! - in a series of viral videos. Tom is part of the New Zealand International Comedy Festival.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode: General Knowledge S3 | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710026/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join Simon Bridges and various guests from season 3 as they respond to his quickfire General Knowledge questions. Generally Famous will return shortly for its fourth season.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 27: Hayley Holt | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710027/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710027/</guid><description>Podcast Description After excelling as a dancer and snowboarder, Hayley Holt became a regular and popular face on our TV screens. Professional success was offset by alcoholism and losing a child in late pregnancy before she battled back. She chats to Simon about facing her demons, her ADHD diagnosis, her brush with politics - and the joys of family life with her partner and baby son, Raven. Hayley&amp;rsquo;s autobiography, Second Chances, is out now.</description></item><item><title>Episode 26: Ryan Fox | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710028/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ryan Fox interrupts preparations for arguably the most prestigious golf tournament in the world to tell Simon what life&amp;rsquo;s really like as a top pro. He reveals why he turned down the huge payday offered by LIV Golf, recalls the pivotal moment his father, Grant Fox, stopped him quitting and explains why he thinks he can win the 2023 Masters - with a bit of help from Simon&amp;rsquo;s old boss!</description></item><item><title>Episode 25: Dame Miranda Harcourt | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710029/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Acting Royalty Dame Miranda Harcourt has worked with some of the biggest names in Hollywood but says the her most useful acting experience was working in the New Zealand prison system, using theater for social change. She tells Simon about Alison Holst&amp;rsquo;s pantry, using the Samoan concept of le va in her job, and how it&amp;rsquo;s important to be a human first. Check out her substack at https://mirandaharcourt.substack.com/ You can read stories supporting this episode on stuff.</description></item><item><title>Episode 24: Mike King | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710030/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710030/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a frank and thought-provoking conversation, Mike King opens up on his transformation from celebrated TV stand-up comedian to mental health champion via drug and alcohol addiction. He discusses what some parents get wrong and the state of mental health treatment in Aotearoa. He and Simon also chat about cancel culture, Billy T James and what it means to feel Māori. Mike is the founding ambassador of I Am Hope, a charitable organisation that seeks to normalise mental health and create positive societal attitudinal changes.</description></item><item><title>Episode 23: Simran Kaur | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710031/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Optometrist turned investor: Girls That Invest co-founder Simran Kaur shares the secrets of buying a house at 23 and becoming a millionaire by 26. Simon and Simran talk Warren Buffet, making financial education equitable for all and how she works out where to put her money. Keep up to date with Girls That Invest here. You can read stories supporting this episode on stuff.co.nz. Need more great podcasts? Check out Stuff&amp;rsquo;s full catalogue here.</description></item><item><title>Episode 22: Dion Nash | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710032/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Black Cap great Dion Nash explains how being caught putting on moisturiser sparked the idea for life after elite sport. He tells us how he met his wife Bernice Mene over tequila, the importance of ambition and compares T20 cricket to UberEats. You can read stories supporting this episode on stuff.co.nz and if you need more great podcasts, check out Stuff&amp;rsquo;s full catalogue here. GET IN TOUCH Feedback? Got a guest you’d like Simon to talk to?</description></item><item><title>Episode 21: Teuila Blakely | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710033/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710033/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Sione&amp;rsquo;s Wedding star reflects on the power of Pasifika story-telling and how to make it mainstream. She recalls growing up at her parents&amp;rsquo; takeaway shops in Tauranga, trades tales with Simon about teenage years in Te Atatu, and explains how she found positives from the sex tape scandal that saw her take years out of the public eye. You can read stories supporting this episode on stuff.co.nz and if you need more great podcasts, check out Stuff&amp;rsquo;s full catalogue here.</description></item><item><title>Episode 20: Kimbra | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710034/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710034/</guid><description>Podcast Description The New York-based double Grammy winner discusses new album A Reckoning, her career plans and how she comes up with her rhythm-centric songs. The Hamilton-born star is showing no signs of slowing down, revealing she has four more albums in the works. Kimbra&amp;rsquo;s podcast: https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/playing-with-fire/id1651012571
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 19: Liam Lawson | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710035/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kiwi motorsport sensation Liam Lawson is on the cusp on landing a dream spot in Formula One. He tells Simon about the physical toll of driving the fastest racing cars in the world, how Drive to Survive has changed the sport and why coming from Aotearoa New Zealand can be a big plus for young drivers.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Generally Famous Season 3 Trailer | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710036/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 22:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Generally Famous is back on Feb 8 for another star-studded season. To make sure you don&amp;rsquo;t miss the first episode with Liam Lawson, follow Generally Famous wherever you get your podcasts.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Summer bonus 5: Generally starstruck | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710037/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Generally Famous is having a short summer holiday. But we didn&amp;rsquo;t want to abandon you during the break, so we&amp;rsquo;ve pulled together some of the best bits from seasons one and two. Today: some of our favourite guests talk about times they were starstruck. Simon will be back in early 2023 with more generally famous - but always interesting - guests chatting about life, love and what makes them tick.</description></item><item><title>Summer bonus 4: Generally money | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710038/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Generally Famous is having a short summer holiday. But we didn&amp;rsquo;t want to abandon you during the break, so we&amp;rsquo;ve pulled together some of the best bits from season one and two. Today: some of our favourite guests talk money. Simon will be back in early 2023 with more generally famous - but always interesting - guests chatting about life, love and what makes them tick. Until then, thanks for listening.</description></item><item><title>Summer bonus 3: Generally origins | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710039/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Generally Famous is having a short summer holiday. But we didn&amp;rsquo;t want to abandon you during the break, so we&amp;rsquo;ve pulled together some of the best bits from seasons one and two. Today: some of our favourite guests tell us about their origins. Simon will be back in early 2023 with more generally famous - but always interesting - guests chatting about life, live and what makes them tick.</description></item><item><title>Summer bonus 2: Generally wellbeing | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710040/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Generally Famous is having a short summer holiday. But we didn&amp;rsquo;t want to abandon you during the break, so we’ve pulled together some of the best bits from seasons one and two. Today: some of our favourite guests talk wellbeing and health. Simon will be back in early 2023 with more generally famous - but always interesting - guests chatting about life, love and what makes them tick. Until then, thanks for listening.</description></item><item><title>Summer bonus 1: Generally food | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710041/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Generally Famous is having a short summer holiday. But we didn&amp;rsquo;t want to abandon you during the break, so we’ve pulled together some of the best bits from seasons one and two. Today: some of our favourite guests talk food and drink. Simon will be back in early 2023 with more generally famous - but always interesting - guests chatting about life, love and what makes them tick. Until then, thanks for listening.</description></item><item><title>Generally Famous Season 3 Teaser | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710042/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Simon will bring you more brilliant guests very soon. In the meantime, keep following Generally Famous for special bonus episodes over the holiday period. And for more great summer listening from Stuff, visit: www.stuff.co.nz/podcasts
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 18: Liam Malone | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710043/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Liam Malone was one of the fastest people on the planet when he won double gold at the 2016 Paralympics. The double below-knee amputee tells Simon about seeing his disability as an opportunity not a disadvantage, describes the pain of running on blades and offers his insights on Oscar Pistorius. Liam also recalls the modelling assignment for Vogue in New York that prompted a &amp;lsquo;date&amp;rsquo; with a pop superstar.</description></item><item><title>Episode 17: Jehan Casinader | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710044/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Award-winning journalist Jehan Casinader walked away from a full-time role with TVNZ and now spends much of his time as a keynote speaker, offering insights on mental health, leadership and diversity. His book, This Is Not How It Ends: How rewriting your story can save your life, covers his four-year struggle with depression and how the power of storytelling helped him to survive. He talks to Simon about masculinity, the state of modern media and the family background that inspired his journey.</description></item><item><title>Episode 16: Ross Taylor | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710045/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Arguably New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s greatest male batter joins Simon for a chat about his childhood, cricket career and the reaction to his autobiography, Black &amp;amp; White. Ross explains how Australians have treated him since his retirement, tells the Taj Mahal story he teases his wife about and reveals a taste for fine - and pricey - wine. And he discusses the fallout from losing the Black Caps captaincy to Brendon McCullum and the role race plays within the game.</description></item><item><title>Episode 15: Nadine Higgins | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710046/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710046/</guid><description>Podcast Description The award-winning broadcaster explains why she has no regrets about leaving her fulltime role with TVNZ, why she&amp;rsquo;s loving her new profession, and the &amp;ldquo;emotional roller coaster&amp;rdquo; of four years trying to have a baby with her husband. She and Simon also discuss their first Top Gear-inspired meeting - and the secrets of controlling audiences during corporate MC gigs.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 14: Nick Mowbray | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710047/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Zuru co-founder Nick Mowbray quit law school because he didn&amp;rsquo;t want to do the reading. Now he&amp;rsquo;s one of New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s richest men, with a share in a family fortune estimated at $3 billion. In a rare interview, he opens up about the sacrifices he made on his journey to global success, what the future holds - and what it&amp;rsquo;s really like hanging out with the Kardashians.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 13: Mitch James | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710048/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710048/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Kiwi pop icon went from being a homeless busker in London to the top of the charts. He tells Simon about falling out - and making up - with his parents, fitting manicures into his rock &amp;rsquo;n&amp;rsquo; roll lifestyle, touring with Ed Sheeran and being ready to meet Ms Right and settle down. Mitch&amp;rsquo;s new album, Patience, is out now.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 12: Sid &amp; Chand Sahrawat | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710049/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710049/</guid><description>Podcast Description The power couple behind some of Auckland&amp;rsquo;s most memorable restaurants reveal where they eat out, consider the value of Michelin stars and explain why some young people are impatient about careers in hospitality. They also discuss the changing behaviour of head chefs and share a story about their hero dog!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 11: Morgan Penn | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710050/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Morgan Penn never felt like she was fulfilling her soul purpose until she found Somatic Sexology. From vulva cushions and full body orgasms to sex education and consent, nothing is off limits in this chat with Simon.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode: General Knowledge | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710051/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join Simon Bridges and his guests as they respond to his quickfire General Knowledge questions. Generally Famous returns for a second season on October 26.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Generally Famous Season 2 Trailer | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710052/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 00:12:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Expect the unexpected in Stuff&amp;rsquo;s new podcast as Simon finds out what makes his generally famous - but always interesting - guests tick. Season 2 returns on October 26!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 10: Brodie Kane | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710053/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Media personality Brodie Kane chats with Simon Bridges about why she&amp;rsquo;d never go into politics, running her own media company, and the negative stigma of being single. She also candidly shares the story about the time she met then-Prime Minister Sir John Key while hungover.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 9: Andrea Vance | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710054/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710054/</guid><description>Podcast Description The tables are turned when Simon puts the questions to Andrea Vance, journalist and author of Blue Blood, the best-selling book about National&amp;rsquo;s struggles in the post-Key years. Andrea talks about growing up in Northern Ireland during the violence of The Troubles, working at the News of the World and why she loves Derry Girls.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 8: Nathan Wallis | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710055/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710055/</guid><description>Podcast Description The parenting guru discusses the importance of the first 1000 days of human life, the problems with daycare and devices, and why 7-year-olds should get the vote. The &amp;ldquo;walking contradiction&amp;rdquo; also tells how he overcame his &amp;ldquo;Once Were Warriors&amp;rdquo; childhood and why he&amp;rsquo;s got a replica of part of Doctor Who&amp;rsquo;s spaceship in his home.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 7: Sonya Williams | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710056/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Frustrated at being rebuffed by brokers, Sonya Williams helped found fin-tech phenomenon Sharesies. Six years on she&amp;rsquo;s a &amp;ldquo;3EO&amp;rdquo; and it&amp;rsquo;s one of Aotearoa New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s biggest financial platforms. She tells Simon about the role of smashed avo on toast - and withstands rigorous questioning about the company&amp;rsquo;s pineapple logo!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 6: Dame Denise L'Estrange Corbet | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710057/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710057/</guid><description>Podcast Description World co-founder Dame Denise L&amp;rsquo;Estrange Corbet talks longevity in fashion, getting started and her challenging childhood. Other topics include the amount of black worn in New Zealand, why she&amp;rsquo;s still okay with skinny models and her work as Patron of IHC NZ. Warning: Dame Denise also talks about living with depression and a historic suicide attempt. If you, or anyone you know, needs help with their mental health, a range of organisations can help.</description></item><item><title>Episode 5: Ganesh Raj | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710058/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710058/</guid><description>Podcast Description TV foodie Ganesh Raj tells Simon about his &amp;ldquo;gangster&amp;rdquo; mum and the grit he needed growing up in Singapore. The Eat Well For Less star reveals how he got healthy through meditation, fasting and ditching alcohol - and explains the role of hypnosis. Plus, he recalls his time on MTV, before trading Prince stories with Simon.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 4: Kim Crossman | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710059/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710059/</guid><description>Podcast Description From Shortland Street to Hollywood Boulevard: Direct from her home in sunny Santa Monica, Kim Crossman talks acting, fame and life in LA. She discusses the &amp;ldquo;Taika Effect&amp;rdquo; and being a &amp;ldquo;mule&amp;rdquo; for the Kiwi contingent in Hollywood, explains the benefits of owning a tarantula and shares a sickly story about her best night out. And, to Simon&amp;rsquo;s delight, she reveals her extraordinary efforts to have a cup of tea with the Queen.</description></item><item><title>Episode 3: Petra Bagust | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710060/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Petra has been a household name since bursting onto our screens aged 22 as part of the Ice TV hosting team. The broadcaster, podcaster and media chaplain chats to Simon about turning 50, perceptions, menopause and why she&amp;rsquo;s more than okay about going grey. She also talks candidly about her time on Breakfast and explains why she wouldn&amp;rsquo;t change a thing.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 2: Lucy Blakiston | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710061/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Generations collide when Simon meets wildly successful digital entrepreneur Lucy Blakiston. The 24-year-old is the co-founder of the SYSCA (Shit You Should Care About) empire which delivers news - and more - via emailed newsletters, social media and podcasts, and counts Joe Rogan and Ariana Grande among its 3.6 million social media followers. Lucy, who is probably New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s biggest Harry Styles stan, explains why she wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have her picture taken with Simon, considers whether she&amp;rsquo;ll meet Harry next year and offers tips on talking like a member of Generation Z.</description></item><item><title>Episode 1: Eric Murray | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710062/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710062/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s the premiere episode, and Simon chats to Kiwi rowing icon Eric Murray about the toll of elite-level sport, adjusting to life after competition and his son Zac, who has autism. Eric also offers tips about appearing on reality TV - and recalls a memorable night with a swan. Eric is a patron of Autism NZ - you can find out more about the organisation at: https://autismnz.org.nz/ Warning: This episode contains discussion of issues related to mental health and a suspected suicide.</description></item><item><title>Generally Famous - Trailer | Simon Bridges: Generally Famous</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5698710063/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 03:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5698710063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Expect the unexpected in Stuff&amp;rsquo;s new podcast as Simon finds out what makes his generally famous - but always interesting - guests tick. Launching August 3!
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>