<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Just Trish on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/just-trish/</link><description>Recent content in Just Trish on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/just-trish/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Brooke Schofield EXPOSES Matt Rife, The Weeknd &amp; Rachel Zegler DM Trisha... | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150001/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150001/</guid><description>Podcast Description On episode 38 of &amp;lsquo;JUST TRISH&amp;rsquo;, Trisha shares her most EXCITING news ever&amp;hellip; The Weeknd reached out to her. Will &amp;lsquo;The Idol&amp;rsquo; star be a guest on the podcast? Plus, Rachel Zegler calls Trish out after her controversial Zach Sang interview. Plus, we have the EXCLUSIVE tea from Brooke Schofield after she EXPOSED ex-boyfriend Matt Rife on &amp;lsquo;CANCELLED&amp;rsquo;! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Gigi Gorgeous on Becoming a Mom &amp; EXPOSING Trisha's Crush on Shane Dawson | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150002/</guid><description>Podcast Description The nostalgia is real as Gigi Gorgeous joins Trish to reminisce on their most iconic moments over the years! Plus, Gigi drops a SHOCKING career bombshell, and details her tumultuous IVF journey as she prepares to enter her mommy era. And the blonde bombshell also exposes the awkward moment when Trisha confessed her crush on Shane Dawson! Subscribe to the Podcast:
Apple Podcasts: https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/just-trish/id1698564262?at=1010lSCj
Spotify: https://open.spotify.com/show/6bZ5tfeCt6naGMw24pRMLe
YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/@justtrishpodcast</description></item><item><title>James Charles CONFRONTS Trisha!? + Tana &amp; Brooke’s MESSY Meghan Trainor Interview | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150003/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150003/</guid><description>Podcast Description On episode 36 of &amp;lsquo;JUST TRISH&amp;rsquo;, Trisha gets an OMINOUS message from James Charles. Plus, what went wrong when Meghan Trainor joined Tana Mongeau and Brooke Schofield on &amp;lsquo;Cancelled&amp;rsquo;? Are the rumors about Brooke and Matt Rife true? And Trish finally learns about &amp;lsquo;The Hunger Games&amp;rsquo;&amp;hellip; nearly 12 years after the first movie came out. Subscribe to the Podcast:
Apple Podcasts: https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/just-trish/id1698564262?at=1010lSCj
Spotify: https://open.spotify.com/show/6bZ5tfeCt6naGMw24pRMLe
YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/@justtrishpodcast
All Podcast Platforms: https://link.</description></item><item><title>Daus Mendoza Teaches Trish Spanish, Gay Slang &amp; the TRUTH About Working At McDonald's | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150004/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150004/</guid><description>Podcast Description On episode 35 of &amp;lsquo;JUST TRISH&amp;rsquo;, skinny legend and TikTok superstar Daus Mendoza gives Trisha a lesson on Spanish and gay slang. Plus, Daus spills secrets about what it was like working at McDonald&amp;rsquo;s before making it big on social media. And he dishes about the friendships and frenemies he&amp;rsquo;s made in the beauty influencer community. Subscribe to the Podcast:
Apple Podcasts: https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/just-trish/id1698564262?at=1010lSCj
Spotify: https://open.spotify.com/show/6bZ5tfeCt6naGMw24pRMLe
YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/@justtrishpodcast
All Podcast Platforms: https://link.</description></item><item><title>Forgiving Shane &amp; Ryland, Matt Rife Is a MENACE &amp; Exposing the David Dobrik Documentary | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150005/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trisha&amp;rsquo;s got a bun in the oven, and tea on the stove&amp;ndash;she&amp;rsquo;s back with her hottest topics EVER. With Shane Dawson and Ryland Adams moving back in town ahead of the birth of their twins, would Trish consider making up with her former besties? And Casey Neistat teases his EXPLOSIVE Vlog Squad documentary that has David Dobrik shook. Plus, Trisha reacts to alleged &amp;ldquo;comedian&amp;rdquo; Matt Rife&amp;rsquo;s cringey Netflix standup special.</description></item><item><title>Trisha is PREGNANT With Baby Elvis! | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150006/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Surprise! Trisha and Moses are expecting baby number 2! That&amp;rsquo;s right, Malibu Barbie is officially a big sister as the Paytas-Hacmon family gets ready to welcome baby Elvis. How long has Trish been keeping her pregnancy a secret? Plus, the &amp;lsquo;JUST TRISH&amp;rsquo; crew reacts to Colleen Ballinger&amp;rsquo;s MESSY return to YouTube for one FINAL segment on the disgraced creator&amp;ndash;as well as new details emerging from James Charles&amp;rsquo; creepy past.</description></item><item><title>Shawty Bae Talks Getting a BBL, Her Friend With Benefits &amp; Being BANNED From Malls | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150007/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s a meme queen crossover event as Trisha sits down with the illustrious @shawtybaeofficial on episode 31 of &amp;lsquo;JUST TRISH&amp;rsquo;! Shawty Bae spills ALL the tea&amp;ndash;from her aspirations on getting a BBL to her current &amp;ldquo;friends with benefits&amp;rdquo; relationship status with her roommate. Plus, Shawty Bae reveals her WILDEST meet &amp;amp; greet moments where she nearly got trampled and got a drink thrown in her face! Subscribe to the Podcast:</description></item><item><title>Rosanna Pansino CALLS OUT Colleen Ballinger, the TRUTH About MatPat &amp; EXPOSING Bears | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150008/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150008/</guid><description>Podcast Description The vibes are IMMACULATE and the tea is HOT on episode 31 of &amp;lsquo;JUST TRISH&amp;rsquo;! Trisha reacts to Rosanna Pansino&amp;rsquo;s statement on her past friendship with Colleen Ballinger. Why did it take so long for Ro to take a stand? Plus, the TRUTH about YouTube&amp;rsquo;s golden boys, MatPat and Markiplier. And Trisha drops a conspiracy theory about BEARS that will leave the Internet reeling. Oh yeah, and Trisha is going to next year&amp;rsquo;s Met Gala!</description></item><item><title>Riley Reid On RETIRING From Adult Films, Being A Modern Mom &amp; Befriending Logan Paul | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150009/</guid><description>Podcast Description On episode 30 of &amp;lsquo;JUST TRISH&amp;rsquo;, Trisha sits down with iconic adult entertainer Riley Reid to discuss the ups and downs of being a porn star&amp;ndash;from WILD fan encounters to collaborating with David Dobrik and Logan Paul. Plus, Riley reveals what it&amp;rsquo;s like raising a daughter in the spotlight, and why she made the decision to NEVER show her child&amp;rsquo;s face on social media again. And the two bombshells talk through their past OF collaboration&amp;hellip; and how much money they made from it!</description></item><item><title>Charli CALLS OUT Trish, James Charles Is DUBIOUS and A Shane &amp; Friends REUNION? | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150010/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trish is back and causing a RUCKUS with more hot topics! Charli D&amp;rsquo;amelio seemingly calls out Trisha over their past feud. Is there still bad blood between the two TikTok legends? Plus, James Charles is caught being DUBIOUS after admitting to lying about a past makeup collab. And is there any hope for a &amp;ldquo;Shane &amp;amp; Friends&amp;rdquo; reunion? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Brooke Schofield On Her Toxic Ex, Feuding With Tana &amp; the Future of CANCELLED | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trisha sits down with &amp;lsquo;CANCELLED&amp;rsquo; host Brooke Schofield to discuss her meteoric rise to social media fame. Brooke tells all: From new details about her toxic ex, to feud rumors between her and Tana Mongeau. What is the future like for the &amp;lsquo;CANCELLED&amp;quot; podcast and tour? Plus, Brooke and Trish bond over the hardships of living with BPD, and how they continue to live with their mental illness. Subscribe to the Podcast:</description></item><item><title>Cops Are Called On Eugenia Cooney &amp; the MrBeast Drama Gets Even Worse... | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150012/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trick or Trish! It’s a spooky Halloween edition of ‘JUST TRISH’—and Trisha is back to spill the tea on all the kooky and creepy drama. A new report reveals the cops have been called on Eugenia Cooley after fans continue to grow concerned for the YouTube star. Plus, Trish reveals what REALLY went down as Rosanna Pansino exposed MrBeast in our exclusive interview. Plus, a horrifying run-in with the Vlog Squad!</description></item><item><title>Rosanna Pansino Reveals She Was BETRAYED by MrBeast &amp; Reality TV Producers | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150013/</guid><description>Podcast Description On episode 26 of &amp;lsquo;JUST TRISH&amp;rsquo;, RosannaPansino speaks out for the first time about unfairly being EDITED OUT of Beast&amp;rsquo;s $1,000,000 Influencer Tournament–and why it&amp;rsquo;s been so hard to watch his content ever since. Plus, Ro reveals the scary truth about her experience competing on the reality TV show &amp;lsquo;Scream Queens&amp;rsquo; on VH1. And the Nerdy Nummies mogul opens up about expanding her empire even further. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Trisha Addresses the Drama with Sofia Franklyn, SSSniperWolf &amp; British People... | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150014/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150014/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week&amp;rsquo;s Hot Topics, Trish responds to Sofia Franklyn after the &amp;lsquo;Sofia with an F&amp;rsquo; host called her out on TikTok. Plus, Trisha unpacks her beef with British people in the wake of Millie Bobby Brown and Emily Blunt&amp;rsquo;s CRINGEY viral food interviews. And Trisha reacts to the latest updates in SSSniperWolf&amp;rsquo;s feud with JackFilms. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tana Mongeau Exposes DMs From Her STALKER | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150015/</guid><description>Podcast Description On episode 24 of &amp;lsquo;JUST TRISH&amp;rsquo;, Tana Mongeau is BACK for a spooky Halloween special where she exposes DMs from her infamous stalker. Plus, Tana addresses the theory that someone from her team is being PAID to leak her personal information. Then, Trish gets all the tea on Tana&amp;rsquo;s dating life and that heated argument with her &amp;lsquo;CANCELLED&amp;quot; cohost, Brooke. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices</description></item><item><title>The SSSniperWolf VS Jacksfilms Drama is OUT OF CONTROL! | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trisha is ready to spill some positiviTEA–even with the MESSY feud between SSSniperWolf and Jacksfilms. Should Lia face repercussions from allegedly doxxing her longtime enemy? Plus, is there still bad blood between Trish and Jack from the Vlog Squad days? And Trisha is ready to make peace after a one-sided feud with the ladies of &amp;lsquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve Had It&amp;rsquo;! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Zach Sang on INTRODUCING Trish to Ariana Grande &amp; Cringey Interview Moments | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trisha turns the tables on prolific interviewer Zach Sang to get the tea on his famous friendships with stars like Ariana Grande and Demi Lovato. Can Zach pull some strings to get Ari on &amp;lsquo;Just Trish&amp;rsquo;? Plus, Zach reveals his messiest interview moments and how he found love for the first time with a HOT Australian model. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trisha Paytas EXPOSES Drake, Dolphins &amp; Emma Chamberlain? | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150018/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trish is back with her SPOOKIEST episode yet–reacting to Emma Chamberlain&amp;rsquo;s breakup with Role Model, and spilling some tea about her time with the Vlog Squad when she was just 17 years old. Plus, she goes OFF on Drake for his cringey recent behavior. And listen as Trisha shockingly EXPOSES the most adored marine mammal&amp;hellip; the dolphin. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Karmalita Fox on FAT-PHOBIC Videos &amp; Pretty Privilege | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150019/</guid><description>Podcast Description On episode 20 of &amp;lsquo;JUST TRISH&amp;rsquo;, Trisha sits down with both the enigmatic Karmalita Fox to discuss her controversial fat-phobic TikToks where she YELLS at viewers to lose weight. How does the self-help guru feel about the hardships that come with pretty privilege? Plus she reveals how &amp;lsquo;RuPaul&amp;rsquo;s Drag Race&amp;rsquo; stars Sugar and Spice helped manifest her social media career. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices</description></item><item><title>Does Ariana Grande SUPPORT Colleen Ballinger &amp; Did MrBeast Go TOO FAR?! | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150020/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trish is back with another Hot Topics Tuesday–this time investigating the theory that Ariana Grande is SUPPORTING Colleen Ballinger through her cancellation. Why hasn&amp;rsquo;t Ari unfollowed the &amp;ldquo;Toxic Gossip Train&amp;rdquo; singer? Plus, Trisha reacts to MrBeast&amp;rsquo;s CONTROVERSIAL video ideas after he got called out on X. And meet the first-ever JUST TRISH GOLDEN BACHELORETTE&amp;hellip; Lenna Paytas! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jeff Wittek Talks Vlog Squad Trauma &amp; MOVING IN with Tana Mongeau | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150021/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tana Mongeau is BACK on &amp;lsquo;JUST TRISH&amp;rsquo;&amp;hellip; and she brought her &amp;ldquo;friend with benefits&amp;rdquo; Jeff Wittek! Jeff and Trisha rehash their complicated history–from their traumatic Vlog Squad days to the infamous Starbucks incident. Plus, Trisha questions Jeff and Tana on their flirtatious relationship. Is there any hope for Teff? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Reacting to JoJo Siwa's MESSY Interview With Tana Mongeau on CANCELLED | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150022/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trisha is back to dish on the juiciest hot topics–including the fallout from JoJo Siwa&amp;rsquo;s interview with Tana Mongeau on &amp;lsquo;CANCELLED&amp;rsquo; and why she chose to unfollow the &amp;lsquo;Dance Moms&amp;rsquo; star after her controversial stance on the allegations against Colleen Ballinger. Plus, Trish discovers what global warming REALLY is, and why she&amp;rsquo;s considering running for president in the 2024 election. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices</description></item><item><title>Carrot Top Reveals the Most CHAOTIC Moments From His Career | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trisha sits down with legendary comedian Carrot Top to discuss the most chaotic and iconic moments from his extraordinary career. Plus, he reveals what REALLY happened to the woman in that viral &amp;ldquo;not real&amp;rdquo; plane video that broke the internet. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Exposing Colleen Ballinger's Manipulation &amp; Trisha's Recent Drama | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150024/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trish is back with her hot takes after a wild week of drama–from an unexpected apology tour to the never-ending twists and turns of Colleen Ballinger&amp;rsquo;s toxic gossip train. Listen as Trisha explains why she believes JoJo Siwa was allegedly manipulated to stand up for Colleen. Plus, Trish reacts to SWOOP&amp;rsquo;s shocking exclusive interview with Colleen&amp;rsquo;s ex-husband, Joshua David Evans. Go to morelabs.com and use code TRISH for 25% off your first order of Morning Recovery Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Donny Osmond Makes Trisha's WILDEST Dreams Come True | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150025/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trisha sits down with her DREAM guest–legendary entertainer Donny Osmond! Together, the two reminisce on their long friendship, sing some of Donny&amp;rsquo;s biggest hits and reflect on the peaks and valleys of his iconic career. Plus, Donny surprises Trisha with a FaceTime call from his son, Chris, to spill ALL the tea about competing on the hit ABC reality show &amp;lsquo;Claim to Fame&amp;rsquo;! Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Abby Lee Miller &amp; NYFW Influencers NEED To Be Stopped | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150026/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trisha reacts to the icky viral video of Abby Lee Miller revealing she’s “still into” high school football players—and weighs in on the controversy surrounding the young ‘Dance Moms’ stars. Plus, Trish reveals the messiest moments from influencers at 2023 New York Fashion Week. And the gripping Givenchy boots saga comes to an end when TikToker Matthew Stevens joins Trisha after fundraising $6,500 for charity in her honor. Go to morelabs.</description></item><item><title>Psyiconic on the END of Terri Joe &amp; STEALING "I Love You Jesus" From Trisha | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150027/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trisha sits down with both the iconic Psyiconic and self-proclaimed &amp;ldquo;God Warrior&amp;rdquo; Terri Joe to discuss their viral success on TikTok Live. Is the end near for the beloved character? Plus, Trish confronts Terri Joe about stealing her hit song &amp;ldquo;I Love You Jesus&amp;rdquo; during that infamous duet with Madonna. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The RETURN of Gabbie Hanna &amp; David Dobrik's NEW Reality Show? | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150028/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trish is back with her hot takes on the WILDEST hot topics–from David Dobrik&amp;rsquo;s rumored new reality TV show to Gabbie Hanna&amp;rsquo;s quiet return to social media after nearly a year of being offline. Plus, Trisha claps back at Miley Cyrus&amp;rsquo; older brother for shaming OF models&amp;hellip; and her hubby, Moses, for critiquing her buttered noodles! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tana Mongeau Addresses ALL Her Current Scandals &amp; Messiest Moments | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150029/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trisha sits down with the un-cancellable Tana Mongeau to spill ALL the tea. From her international wine tour scandal that made headlines, to becoming frenemies with Bryce Hall, and even the possibility of finding love with Jeff Wittek–Tana doesn&amp;rsquo;t hold back as Trisha hilariously tries to keep up with all her drama. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The 2023 Streamy Awards Were a Mess... | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150030/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trisha reacts to the messiest, most chaotic moments from the 2023 Streamy Awards–from the Colleen Ballinger ukulele spoof to Tana Mongeau&amp;rsquo;s on-stage mishap. She may just be banned from the award show for good after this! Plus, Trish gives her hot take on Bad Bunny&amp;rsquo;s caliente nude selfie that left the Internet thirsty for more. THANK YOU TO TODAY&amp;rsquo;S SPONSOR http://www.manscaped.com use code &amp;ldquo;TRISH&amp;rdquo; for 20% OFF + FREE SHIPPING Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Trisha Confesses to Christine Quinn That She COPIED Her Wedding | Just Trish #8 | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150031/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trisha confesses to reality TV queen Christine Quinn that she copied her entire “gothic Barbie”-themed wedding as the two blonde bombshells confront those feud rumors. Plus, Christine reveals that the future of Netflix’s ‘Selling Sunset’ may be in jeopardy after she quit the show. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Colleen Ballinger Drama Keeps Getting Worse... | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150032/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trisha reacts to Swoop&amp;rsquo;s jaw-dropping revelations about Johnny Silvestri as the Colleen Ballinger saga takes another dark turn&amp;ndash;and claps back at other influencers who are calling it a &amp;ldquo;misstep.&amp;rdquo; Plus, find out why Trish thinks she was BLOCKED by Britney Spears on Instagram. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dr. Drew addresses Trisha's Past Scandals &amp; Controversies | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150033/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150033/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this emotional episode of ‘JUST TRISH’, Trisha is joined by media personality, internist and addiction specialist—Dr. Drew Pinsky—to address her most infamous past scandals and controversies. Dr. Drew doesn’t hold back as he gives Trish real advice on how to apologize and move forward. **TRIGGER WARNING: This episode contains mentions of addiction, sexual abuse and eating disorders.
Subscribe for free to Just Trish wherever you listen to podcasts and get episodes before anyone else: https://link.</description></item><item><title>Trisha Investigates Lil Tay Conspiracies &amp; Jaclyn Hill's Business Closures | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150034/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150034/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on ‘JUST TRISH’, Trisha investigates the MIND BLOWING conspiracy theories surrounding the recent Lil Tay hoax. Plus, she reacts to Jaclyn Hill&amp;rsquo;s controversial new announcement. Plus, why does everyone hate Kendall Jenner? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Holly Madison Reveals the TRUTH About Dating &amp; Breaking Up With Hugh Hefner | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150035/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 18:09:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150035/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the milestone fourth episode of ‘JUST TRISH’, Trisha is joined by ‘Girls Next Level’ host Holly Madison to spill even more tea on what REALLY happened in the Playboy Mansion on ‘The Girls Next Door’—and what her relationship with Hugh Hefner was like behind closed doors. Plus, the two blonde bombshells reveal how much money it takes to be a bougie Disney adult. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Breaking Down Lizzo’s INSANE Allegations &amp; Trisha Goes On Her OWN Eras Tour | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150036/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trisha breaks down the INSANE allegations against Lizzo. Did Lana Del Rey predict her downfall? Plus, Trish converts into a Taylor Swift stan and embarks on her OWN Eras Tour—reliving her most iconic memes. Subscribe to the Podcast:
Apple Podcasts: https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/just-trish/id1698564262?at=1010lSCj
Spotify: https://open.spotify.com/show/6bZ5tfeCt6naGMw24pRMLe
YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/@justtrishpodcast
All Podcast Platforms: https://link.chtbl.com/JustTrish?at=1010lSCj
Follow Just Trish on Social Media: https://www.instagram.com/justtrishpod/
Follow Oscar: https://www.instagram.com/oscargracey
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Reacting to Colleen Ballinger’s SHOCKING Vanity Fair Article | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150037/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 16:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trisha reacts to the mind-boggling Vanity Fair article defending Colleen Ballinger—and spills some shocking tea about her former cohost. Plus, Trish gives her take on the viral video pointing out Ariana Grande’s history of seemingly breaking up relationships, as well as Doja Cat’s sudden cancellation. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trisha's Viral NPC TikTok &amp; Ariana Grande Drama | Just Trish</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4448150038/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 17:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4448150038/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s the beginning of a new era! On the premiere episode of &amp;lsquo;JUST TRISH&amp;rsquo;, Trisha reacts to going viral and being interviewed after taking part in the TikTok NPC trend. Plus, Trish reveals why Kourtney Kardashian gave her a panic attack, and shares her hot take on Ariana Grande&amp;rsquo;s divorce drama. Have you ever wondered how a podcast is named, or why your favorite celebrities break up? This episode of Just Trish will ease your curiosity.</description></item></channel></rss>