<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/the-new-yorker-the-writers-voice-new-fiction-from-the-new-yorker/</link><description>Recent content in The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/the-new-yorker-the-writers-voice-new-fiction-from-the-new-yorker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Caleb Crain Reads “Keats at Twenty-Four” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400152/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400152/</guid><description>Podcast Description The author reads his story from the December 11, 2023, issue of the magazine.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Teju Cole Reads “Incoming” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400151/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400151/</guid><description>Podcast Description The author reads his story from the December 4, 2023, issue of the magazine.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Madeleine Thien Reads Yoko Ogawa | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400001/</guid><description>Podcast Description The author joins Deborah Treisman to read and discuss the story “The Cafeteria in the Evening and a Pool in the Rain,” which was published in a 2004 issue of the magazine.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sheila Heti Reads “According to Alice” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400002/</guid><description>Podcast Description The author reads her story from the November 20, 2023, issue of the magazine.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Clare Sestanovich Reads “Our Time Is Up” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400003/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400003/</guid><description>Podcast Description The author reads her story from the November 13, 2023, issue of the magazine.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Junot Díaz Reads “The Ghosts of Gloria Lara” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400004/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400004/</guid><description>Podcast Description The author reads his story from the November 6, 2023, issue of the magazine.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Han Ong Reads “I Am Pizza Rat” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400005/</guid><description>Podcast Description The author reads his story from the October 23, 2023, issue of the magazine.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mary Costello Reads “The Choc-Ice Woman” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400006/</guid><description>Podcast Description The author reads her story from the October 16, 2023, issue of the magazine.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lore Segal Reads “On the Agenda” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400007/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lore Segal reads her story “On the Agenda,” which appears in the September 18, 2023, issue of the magazine. Segal’s most recent books are “The Journal I Did Not Keep: New and Selected Writing” and “Ladies’ Lunch: and Other Stories,” which comes out later this month.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lara Vapnyar Reads “Siberian Wood” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lara Vapnyar reads her story “Siberian Wood,” which appears in the September 11, 2023, issue of the magazine. Vapnyar has published two short story collections and four novels, including “Still Here” and “Divide Me By Zero,” which came out in 2019.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tessa Hadley on Her Years of Learning to Write | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400009/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400009/</guid><description>Podcast Description In July, The New Yorker published its thirtieth story by Tessa Hadley—a higher count that of any other fiction writer in the past two decades. On a recent episode of the New Yorker Radio Hour, the fiction editor Deborah Treisman spoke with Hadley about her genesis as a fiction writer. Hadley’s latest story collection is “After the Funeral.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>T. Coraghessan Boyle Reads “The End Is Only a Beginning” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400010/</guid><description>Podcast Description T. Coraghessan Boyle reads his story “The End Is Only a Beginning,” which appears in the August 21, 2023, issue of the magazine. Boyle has published more than two dozen books of fiction, including the story collection, “I Walk Between the Raindrops,” and the novel “Blue Skies,” which came out earlier this year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Karan Mahajan Reads “The True Margaret” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400011/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Karan Mahajan reads his story “The True Margaret,” which appears in the August 14, 2023, issue of the magazine. Mahajan is the author of two novels, “Family Planning” and “The Association of Small Bombs,” which won the New York Public Library Young Lions Fiction Award in 2017.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jamie Quatro Reads “Yogurt Days” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jamie Quatro reads her story “Yogurt Days,” which appears in the August 7, 2023, issue of the magazine. Quatro is the author of the story collection “I Want to Show You More” and the novel “Fire Sermon.” A new novel, “Two-Step Devil,” will be published next year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tessa Hadley Reads “The Maths Tutor” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400013/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tessa Hadley reads her story “The Maths Tutor,” which appeared in the July 24, 2023, issue of the magazine. Hadley has published twelve books of fiction, including the novels “Free Love’ and “The Past,” and the story collections “Bad Dreams” and “After the Funeral.” She is a winner of the 2016 Windham Campbell Literature Prize.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Camille Bordas Reads “Colorín Colorado” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Camille Bordas reads her story “Colorín Colorado,” which appeared in the July 10 &amp;amp; 17, 2023, issue of the magazine. Bordas published two novels in France. Her first novel in English, “How to Behave in a Crowd,” came out in 2017.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Paul Yoon Reads “Valley of the Moon” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Paul Yoon reads his story “Valley of the Moon,” which appeared in the July 3, 2023, issue of the magazine. Yoon is the author of four books of fiction, including the story collection “The Mountain” and the novel “Run Me to Earth,” which came out in 2020. A new collection, “The Hive and the Honey,” will be published later this year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Weike Wang Reads “Status in Flux” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Weike Wang reads her story “Status in Flux,” which appeared in the June 26, 2023, issue of the magazine. Wang is the author of two novels: “Chemistry,” which won the PEN/Hemingway Award in 2018, and “Joan Is Okay,” which was published in 2022.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Saïd Sayrafiezadeh Reads “Civil Disturbance” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Saïd Sayrafiezadeh reads his story “Civil Disturbance,” which appeared in the June 19, 2023, issue of the magazine. Sayrafiezadeh is the author of the story collections “Brief Encounters with the Enemy,” which was a finalist for the pen/Robert W. Bingham Prize for début fiction in 2014, and “American Estrangement,” which was published in 2021.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>George Saunders Reads “Thursday” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400018/</guid><description>Podcast Description George Saunders reads his story “Thursday,” which appeared in the June 12, 2023, issue of the magazine. Saunders won the Booker Prize in 2017 for his novel “Lincoln in the Bardo.” He is the author of five story collections, including “Tenth of December” and “Liberation Day,” which came out last year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nicole Krauss Reads “Long Island” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nicole Krauss reads her story “Long Island,” which appeared in the May 22, 2023, issue of the magazine. Krauss is the author of four novels, including “The History of Love” and “Forest Dark.” Her story collection, “To Be a Man,” was published in 2020 and won the Wingate Literary Prize.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rebecca Makkai Reads “The Plaza” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rebecca Makkai reads her story “The Plaza,” which appeared in the May 8, 2023, issue of the magazine. Makkai is the author of a story collection and four novels, including “The Great Believers,” which won the Andrew Carnegie Medal for Excellence in Fiction and was a finalist for the National Book Award, and “I Have Some Questions for You,” which came out in February.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rachel Cusk Reads “The Stuntman” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rachel Cusk reads her story “The Stuntman,” which appeared in the April 24 &amp;amp; May 1, 2023, issue of the magazine. Cusk, a Guggenheim fellow, is the author of four nonfiction works and eleven novels, including the “Outline” trilogy and, most recently, “Second Place.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ben Lerner Reads “The Ferry” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ben Lerner reads his story “The Ferry,” which appeared in the April 10, 2023, issue of the magazine. Lerner is the author of the novels “Leaving the Atocha Station,” “10:04,” and “The Topeka School,” which was a finalist for the Pulitzer Prize in 2020. He was awarded a MacArthur Fellowship in 2015.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sterling HolyWhiteMountain Reads “False Star” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sterling HolyWhiteMountain reads his story “False Star,” which appeared in the March 20, 2023, issue of the magazine. HolyWhiteMountain is a former Stegner fellow and current Jones Lecturer at Stanford University, and an unrecognized citizen of the Blackfeet Nation. He is at work on a novel.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rivka Galchen Reads “How I Became a Vet” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rivka Galchen reads her story “How I Became a Vet,” which appeared in the March 13, 2023, issue of the magazine. Galchen is the author of three books of fiction, including the story collection “American Innovations” and the novel “Everyone Knows Your Mother Is a Witch,” which was published in 2021.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Allegra Goodman Reads “The Last Grownup” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Allegra Goodman reads her story “The Last Grownup,” which appeared in the February 27, 2023, issue of the magazine. Goodman has published two story collections and seven novels, including “Kaaterskill Falls,” which was a National Book Award finalist, “The Chalk Artist,” and, most recently, “Sam,” which came out earlier this year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Clare Sestanovich Reads “Different People” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400026/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Clare Sestanovich reads her story “Different People,” which appeared in the January 30, 2023, issue of the magazine. Sestanovich’s début story collection, “Objects of Desire,” which came out in 2021, was a finalist PEN/Robert W. Bingham Prize. She was named a “5 Under 35” honoree by the National Book Foundation in 2022.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Yiyun Li Reads “Wednesday’s Child” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400027/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yiyun Li reads her story “Wednesday’s Child,” which appeared in the January 23, 2023, issue of the magazine. Li is the author of two story collections and five novels, including “Must I Go” and “The Book of Goose,” which was published last year. She won the Windham Campbell Literature Prize in 2020.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Han Ong Reads “Hammer Attack” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400028/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Han Ong reads his story “Hammer Attack,” which appeared in the January 16, 2023, issue of the magazine. Ong, the recipient of a MacArthur Fellowship and a Berlin Prize, is the author of more than a dozen plays and two novels, “Fixer Chao” and “The Disinherited.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ayşegül Savaş Reads “Notions of the Sacred” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400029/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ayşegül Savaş reads her story “Notions of the Sacred,” which appeared in the January 2 &amp;amp; 9, 2022, issue of the magazine. Savaş is the author of two novels, “Walking on the Ceiling,” which was published in 2019, and “White on White,” which came out in 2021.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Matthew Klam Reads “The Other Party” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400030/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matthew Klam reads his story “The Other Party,” which appeared in the December 19, 2022, issue of the magazine. Klam is the author of the collection “Sam the Cat: And Other Stories” and the novel “Who Is Rich?,” which was published in 2017.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Danielle Dutton Reads “My Wonderful Description of Flowers” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400031/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Danielle Dutton reads her story “My Wonderful Description of Flowers,” which appeared in the December 5, 2022, issue of the magazine. Dutton is the co-founder of Dorothy, a publishing project, and the author of three books of fiction, including the novel “Margaret the First.” A new book, “Prairie, Dresses, Art, Other,” will be published in 2024.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Louise Erdrich Reads “The Hollow Children” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400032/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Louise Erdrich reads her story “The Hollow Children,” which appeared in the November 28, 2022, issue of the magazine. Erdrich is the author of more than a dozen works of fiction, nonfiction, and poetry, most recently “The Sentence” and “The Night Watchman,” which won the Pulitzer Prize in 2021.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>T. Coraghessan Boyle Reads “Princess” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400033/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400033/</guid><description>Podcast Description T. Coraghessan Boyle reads his story “Princess,” which appeared in the November 7, 2022, issue of the magazine. Boyle has published more than two dozen books of fiction, including the novels “Outside Looking In” and “Talk to Me.” his most recent story collection, “I Walk Between the Raindrops,” came out earlier this year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jonathan Lethem Reads “Narrowing Valley” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400034/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jonathan Lethem reads his story “Narrowing Valley,” which appeared in the October 31, 2022, issue of the magazine. Lethem’s books of fiction include the story collection “Lucky Alan and Other Stories” and the novels “Motherless Brooklyn,” “The Feral Detective,” and, most recently, “The Arrest,” which was published in 2020.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Marisa Silver Reads “Tiny Meaningless Things” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400035/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Marisa Silver reads her story “Tiny Meaningless Things,” which appeared in the October 24, 2022, issue of the magazine. Silver is the author of seven books of fiction, including the story collection “Alone with You,” and the novels “Little Nothing” and “The Mysteries,” which was published last year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>David Gilbert Reads “Come Softly to Me” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400036/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400036/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Gilbert reads his story “Come Softly to Me,” which appeared in the October 17, 2022, issue of the magazine. Gilbert is the author of the story collection “Remote Feed,” and two novels, “&amp;amp; Sons” and “The Normals.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Thomas McGuane Reads “Take Half, Leave Half” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400037/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Thomas McGuane reads his story “Take Half, Leave Half,” which appeared in the October 10, 2022, issue of the magazine. McGuane has published more than a dozen books of fiction, including the story collections “Gallatin Canyon,” “Crow Fair,” and “Cloudbursts: Collected and New Stories,” which came out in 2018.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nicole Krauss Reads “Shelter” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400038/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nicole Krauss reads her story “Shelter,” which appeared in the October 3, 2022, issue of the magazine. Kruass is the author of four novels, including “The History of Love,” and “Forest Dark.” Her story collection, “To Be a Man,” was published in 2020 and won the Wingate Literary Prize.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Caleb Crain Reads “Easter” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400039/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Caleb Crain reads his story “Easter,” from the September 26, 2022, issue of the magazine. Crain is the author of one book of nonfiction and two novels, “Necessary Errors” and “Overthrow,” which was published in 2019 and was a finalist for the Lambda Literary Award.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ben Okri Reads “The Secret Source” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400040/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ben Okri reads his story “The Secret Source,” from the September 19, 2022, issue of the magazine. Okri is the author of eleven novels, including “The Famished Road,” which won the Booker Prize in 1991, and “The Freedom Artist,” which came out in 2019. His poetry collection “A Fire in My Head: Poems for the Dawn” was published last year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Joan Silber Reads “Evolution” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400041/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joan Silber reads her story “Evolution,” from the September 12, 2022, issue of the magazine. Silber is the author of nine books of fiction, including, most recently, “Secrets of Happiness” and “Improvement,” for which she won the pen/Faulkner Award in 2018.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ben Lerner Reads “Café Loup” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400042/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ben Lerner reads his story “Café Loup,” from the September 5, 2022, issue of the magazine. Lerner is the author of the novels “Leaving the Atocha Station,” “10:04,” and “The Topeka School,” which was a finalist for the Pulitzer Prize in 2020. He was awarded a MacArthur Fellowship in 2015.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>David Sedaris Reads “Roy Spivey,” by Miranda July | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400043/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400043/</guid><description>Podcast Description The August 29, 2022, issue of The New Yorker is an archival issue, bringing together pieces from past issues of the magazine on the theme of Celebrity. It features the story “Roy Spivey,” by Miranda July, which was published in The New Yorker in 2007. Instead of a Writer’s Voice episode, this week we are rereleasing an episode of the New Yorker Fiction Podcast, taped in 2012, in which David Sedaris joins Deborah Treisman to read and discuss “Roy Spivey.</description></item><item><title>Alejandro Zambra Reads “Skyscrapers” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400044/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alejandro Zambra reads his story “Skyscrapers,” which was translated from the Spanish by Megan McDowell, from the August 22, 2022, issue of the magazine. Zambra is a Chilean poet and fiction writer whose books translated into English include “Multiple Choice,” “Chilean Poet,” and “Bonsai,” his first novel, which was published in a new translation this month.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sana Krasikov Reads “The Muddle” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400045/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sana Krasikov reads her story “The Muddle,” from the August 15, 2022, issue of the magazine. Krasikov is the author of the story collection “One More Year,” for which she won the National Book Foundation’s “5 Under 35” Award, and the novel “The Patriots,” which was published in 2017.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Clare Sestanovich Reads “You Tell Me” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400046/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Clare Sestanovich reads her story “You Tell Me” from the August 1, 2022, issue of the magazine. Sestanovich was named a “5 Under 35” honoree by the National Book Foundation in 2022. Her début story collection, “Objects of Desire,” which came out last year, was a finalist for the PEN Robert W. Bingham Prize.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Han Ong Reads “Elmhurst” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400047/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Han Ong reads his story “Elmhurst” from the July 25, 2022, issue of the magazine. Ong, the recipient of a MacArthur Fellowship and the Berlin Prize, is the author of more than a dozen plays and two novels, “Fixer Chao” and “The Disinherited.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bryan Washington Reads “Arrivals” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400048/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bryan Washington reads his story “Arrivals,” from the July 11 &amp;amp; 18, 2022, issue of the magazine. Washington is a winner of the Ernest J. Gaines Award for Literary Excellence, the International Dylan Thomas Prize, and the Lambda Literary Award. His story collection, “Lot,” was published in 2019, and his novel, “Memorial,” came out in 2020.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rachel Kushner Reads “A King Alone” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400049/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rachel Kushner reads her story “A King Alone” from the July 11 &amp;amp; 18, 2022, issue of the magazine. Kushner has published three novels, “Telex from Cuba,” “The Flamethrowers,” and “The Mars Room,” which was shortlisted for the Man Booker Prize in 2018. Her most recent book, “The Hard Crowd: Essays 2000-2020,” came out last year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lauren Groff Reads “To Sunland” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400050/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lauren Groff reads her story “To Sunland,” from the July 4, 2022, issue of the magazine. Groff has published four novels, including “Fates and Furies” and “Matrix,” which came out last year. Her second story collection, “Florida,” which was published in 2018, won the Story Prize and was a finalist for the National Book Award.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Etgar Keret Reads “Mitzvah” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400051/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Etgar Keret reads his story “Mitzvah,” translated from the Hebrew by Jessica Cohen, from the June 27, 2022, issue of the magazine. Keret’s books include the memoir “The Seven Good Years” and the story collections “Suddenly a Knock on the Door” and “Fly Already,” which was published in 2020.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>André Alexis Reads “Houyhnhnm” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400052/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400052/</guid><description>Podcast Description André Alexis reads his story “Houyhnhnm,” from the June 20, 2022, issue of the magazine. Alexis received the Windham-Campbell prize for fiction in 2017. His novels include “Childhood,” “Fifteen Dogs,” and “Days by Moonlight,” and his story collection, “The Night Piece,” was published in 2020.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Souvankham Thammavongsa Reads “Trash” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400053/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Souvankham Thammavongsa reads her story “Trash,” from the June 13, 2022, issue of the magazine. Thammavongsa has published four volumes of poetry and the short-story collection “How to Pronounce Knife,” which won the 2020 Scotiabank Giller Prize.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Joshua Ferris Reads “The Boy Upstairs” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400054/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joshua Ferris reads his story “The Boy Upstairs,” from the June 6, 2022, issue of the magazine. Ferris is the author of one story collection and four novels, including “To Rise Again at a Decent Hour,” which won the Dylan Thomas Prize in 2014, and “A Calling for Charlie Barnes,” which was published last year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Claire-Louise Bennett Reads “Invisible Bird” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400055/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Claire-Louise Bennett reads her story “Invisible Bird,” from the May 30, 2022, issue of the magazine. Bennett is the author of the short-story collection “Pond” and the novel “Checkout 19,” which was shortlisted for the Goldsmiths Prize.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jamil Jan Kochai Reads “Occupational Hazards” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400056/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jamil Jan Kochai reads his story “Occupational Hazards,” from the May 23, 2022, issue of the magazine. Kochai’s first novel, “99 Nights in Logar,” was published in 2019 and was a finalist for the pen/Hemingway Award. His story collection, “The Haunting of Hajji Hotak and Other Stories,” will come out in July.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mohsin Hamid Reads “The Face in the Mirror” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400057/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mohsin Hamid reads his story “The Face in the Mirror,” from the May 16th, 2022, issue of the magazine. Hamid is the author of four novels, including “How to Get Filthy Rich in Rising Asia” and “Exit West,” a winner of the L.A. Times Book Prize. A new novel, “The Last White Man,” from which this story was adapted, will be published in August
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Saïd Sayrafiezadeh Reads “Nondisclosure Agreement” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400058/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Saïd Sayrafiezadeh reads his story “Nondisclosure Agreement,” from the May 9th, 2022, issue of the magazine. Sayrafiezadeh is the author of the story collections “Brief Encounters with the Enemy,” which was a finalist for the PEN/Robert W. Bingham Prize for début fiction in 2014, and “American Estrangement,” which was published last year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Elif Batuman Reads “The Repugnant Conclusion” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400059/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Elif Batuman reads her story “The Repugnant Conclusion,” from the April 25 &amp;amp; May 2, 2022, issue of the magazine. Batuman is the author of “The Possessed: Adventures with Russian Books and the People Who Read Them” and the novel “The Idiot,” which was a finalist for the Pulitzer Prize. “The Repugnant Conclusion” was adapted from her second novel, “Either/Or,” which will be published in May.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sheila Heti Reads “Just a Little Fever” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400060/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sheila Heti reads her story “Just a Little Fever,” from the April 18, 2022, issue of the magazine. Heti is a Canadian writer, whose books of fiction and nonfiction include the novels “How Should a Person Be,” “Motherhood,” which was a finalist for the Scotiabank Giller Prize, and “Pure Colour,” which was published earlier this year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kevin Barry Reads “The Pub with No Beer” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400061/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kevin Barry reads his story “The Pub with No Beer,” from the April 11, 2022, issue of the magazine. Barry is the author of six books of fiction, including the novel “City of Bohane,” for which he won the International Dublin Literary Award, and, most recently, the story collection “That Old Country Music,” which was published in 2020.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tessa Hadley Reads “After the Funeral” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400062/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tessa Hadley reads her story “After the Funeral,” from the March 28, 2022, issue of the magazine. Hadley has published eleven books of fiction, including the story collection “Bad Dreams and Other Stories, ” and the novel “Free Love,” which came out this year. She is a winner of the 2016 Windham-Campbell Literature Prize.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Zach Williams Reads “Wood Sorrel House” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400063/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Zach Williams reads his story “Wood Sorrel House,” from the March 21, 2022, issue of the magazine. Williams is a Stegner Fellow at Stanford University. He is working on a collection of short stories.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Camille Bordas Reads “One Sun Only” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400064/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Camille Bordas reads her story “One Sun Only,” from the March 7, 2022, issue of the magazine. Bordas published two novels in France. Her first novel in English, “How to Behave in a Crowd,” came out in 2017.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Claire Keegan Reads “So Late in the Day” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400065/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Claire Keegan reads her story “So Late in the Day,” from the February 28, 2022, issue of the magazine. Keegan is the author of four books, including the novella “Foster,” which appeared in abridged form in The New Yorker, and, most recently, the novel “Small Things Like These,” which was published last year. She is a winner of the William Trevor Prize and the Rooney Prize for Irish Literature, among others.</description></item><item><title>Kate Folk Reads “Out There” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400066/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400066/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a special episode of the Writer’s Voice podcast, Kate Folk reads her story “Out There,” which ran in the magazine two years ago, in the March 23, 2020, issue. Folk’s recording session at the time was cancelled due to the pandemic lockdown. Folk was a Wallace Stegner fellow at Stanford University. Her first book, the story collection “Out There,” will be published next month.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lauren Groff Reads “Annunciation” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400067/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lauren Groff reads her story “Annunciation,” from the February 14 &amp;amp; 21, 2022, issue of the magazine. Groff has published four novels, including “Arcadia,” “Fates and Furies,” and most recently “Matrix,” which came out last year. Her second story collection “Florida,” which was published in 2018, won the Story Prize and was a finalist for the National Book Award.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Alexander MacLeod Reads “Once Removed” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400068/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alexander MacLeod reads his story “Once Removed,” from the February 7, 2022, issue of the magazine. MacLeod is the author of the story collection “Light Lifting,” which was published in 2010 and shortlisted for the Frank O’Connor International Short Story Award. His second story collection, “Animal Person,” will be published in April.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ayşegül Savaş Reads “Long Distance” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400069/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ayşegül Savaş reads her story “Long Distance,” from the January 31, 2022, issue of the magazine. Savaş’s first novel, “Walking on the Ceiling,” was published in 2019, and her second novel, “White on White,” came out last year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jennifer Egan Reads “What the Forest Remembers” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400070/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jennifer Egan reads her story “What the Forest Remembers,” from the January 3 &amp;amp; 10, 2022, issue of the magazine. Egan is the author of six books of fiction, including “A Visit from the Goon Squad,” which won the Pulitzer Prize in 2011, and “Manhattan Beach,” which won the Andrew Carnegie Medal in 2018. A new book, “The Candy House,” will be published in April.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Adam Levin Reads “A Lot of Things Have Happened” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400071/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adam Levin reads his story “A Lot of Things Have Happened,” from the December 27, 2021, issue of the magazine. Levin is the author of the story collection “Hot Pink,” and two novels, “The Instructions” and “Bubblegum,” which was published last year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Madeleine Thien Reads “Lu, Reshaping” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400072/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Madeleine Thien reads her story “Lu, Reshaping,” from the December 20, 2021, issue of the magazine. Thien is the author of four books of fiction, including the novels “Dogs at the Perimeter” and “Do Not Say We Have Nothing,” which won Canada’s Governor General’s Literary Award and the Scotiabank Giller Prize in 2016.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Colin Barrett Reads “A Shooting in Rathreedane” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400073/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Colin Barrett reads his story “A Shooting in Rathreedane,” from the December 13, 2021, issue of the magazine. Barrett is the author of the story collection “Young Skins,” which won the Frank O’Connor International Short Story Award and the Guardian First Book Award in 2014. A new collection, “Homesickness,” will be published in May.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kate Walbert Reads “Marriage/Quarantine” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400074/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kate Walbert reads her story “Marriage/Quarantine,” from the December 6, 2021, issue of the magazine. Walbert’s novels include “A Short History of Women,” “His Favorites,” and “Our Kind,” which was a finalist for the National Book Award in 2004. Her story collection, “She Was Like That,” was published in 2019.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Greg Jackson Reads “The Hollow” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400075/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Greg Jackson reads his story “The Hollow,” from the November 29, 2021, issue of the magazine. Jackson, a winner of the National Book Foundation’s 5 Under 35 award, is the author of the story collection “Prodigals,” which came out in 2016. His first novel, “The Dimensions of a Cave,” will be published in 2023.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Gish Jen Reads “Detective Dog” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400076/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gish Jen reads her story “Detective Dog,” from the November 22, 2021, issue of the magazine. Jen has published five novels, including “World and Town” and “The Resisters,” which came out last year, as well as the story collection “Who&amp;rsquo;s Irish?” A new story collection, “Thank You, Mr. Nixon,” will come out in January.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Yiyun Li Reads “Hello, Goodbye” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400077/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yiyun Li reads her story “Hello, Goodbye,” from the November 15, 2021, issue of the magazine. Li is the author of two story collections and four novels, including “Where Reasons End” and “Must I Go,” which was published last year. She won the Windham-Campbell Literature Prize in 2020.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jamil Jan Kochai Reads “The Haunting of Hajji Hotak” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400078/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jamil Jan Kochai reads his story “The Haunting of Hajji Hotak,” from the November 8, 2021, issue of the magazine. Kochai was a Truman Capote fellow at the Iowa Writers Workshop. His first novel, ”99 Nights in Logar,” was published in 2019, and a story collection, “The Haunting of Hajji Hotak and Other Stories,” will come out next year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>David Means Reads “The Depletion Prompts” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400079/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400079/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Means reads his story “The Depletion Prompts,” from the November 1, 2021, issue of the magazine. Means is the author of the novel “Hystopia” and five story collections, including “The Spot” and “Instructions for a Funeral,” which was published in 2019.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Thomas McGuane Reads “Not Here You Don’t” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400080/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Thomas McGuane reads his story “Not Here You Don’t,” from the October 18, 2021, issue of the magazine. McGuane has published more than a dozen books of fiction, including “Gallatin Canyon,” “Crow Fair,” and “Cloudbursts: Collected and New Stories,” which came out in 2018.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Karen Russell Reads “The Ghost Birds” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400081/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Karen Russell reads her story “The Ghost Birds,” from the October 11, 2021, issue of the magazine. Russell is the author of five books of fiction, including the story collection “Orange World,” which was published in 2019, and the novel “Swamplandia,” which was a finalist for the Pulitzer Prize in 2012. She was made a MacArthur fellow in 2013.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Esther Freud Reads “Desire” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400082/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Esther Freud reads her story “Desire,” from the September 27, 2021, issue of the magazine. Freud is the author of nine novels, including “Hideous Kinky,” “Mr. Mac and Me,” and “I Couldn’t Love You More.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Han Ong Reads “The Monkey Who Speaks” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400083/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Han Ong reads his story “The Monkey Who Speaks,” from the September 13, 2021, issue of the magazine. Ong, the recipient of a MacArthur Fellowship and the Berlin Prize, is the author of more than a dozen plays and two novels, “Fixer Chao” and “The Disinherited.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>George Saunders Reads “The Mom of Bold Action” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400084/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400084/</guid><description>Podcast Description George Saunders reads his story “The Mom of Bold Action,” from the August 30, 2021, issue of the magazine. Saunders won the Man Booker Prize in 2017 for his novel, “Lincoln in the Bardo.” He is the author of four story collections, including “CivilWarLand in Bad Decline” and “Tenth of December.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Emma Cline Reads “The Iceman” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400085/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emma Cline reads her story “The Iceman,” from the August 23, 2021, issue of the magazine. Cline’s first novel, “The Girls,” a winner of the Shirley Jackson Award, came out in 2016, and her story collection, “Daddy,” was published last year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>hurmat kazmi Reads “Selection Week” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400086/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400086/</guid><description>Podcast Description hurmat kazmi reads their story “Selection Week,” from the August 16, 2021, issue of the magazine. kazmi, a graduate of the Iowa Writers Workshop, is a writer from Karachi, Pakistan, who lives and teaches in Iowa City.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sarah Braunstein Reads “Superstition” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400087/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sarah Braunstein reads her story “Superstition,” from the August 9, 2021, issue of the magazine. Braunstein is the author of the novel “The Sweet Relief of Missing Children,” which won the 2012 Maine Literary Award for Fiction and a recipient of the National Book Foundation’s 5 Under 35 Award.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tessa Hadley Reads “Coda” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400088/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tessa Hadley reads her story “Coda,” from the August 2, 2021, issue of the magazine. Hadley has published ten books of fiction, including the story collection “Bad Dreams and Other Stories” and the novel “Late In the Day,” which was published in 2019. She is a winner of the 2016 Wyndham-Campbell literature prize.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rebecca Curtis Reads “Satellites” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400089/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rebecca Curtis reads her story “Satellites,” from the July 12 &amp;amp; 19, 2021, issue of the magazine. Curtis is the author of the story collection “Twenty Grand: And Other Tales of Love and Money” and a winner of the Rona Jaffe Foundation Writers’ Award for Fiction.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sam Lipsyte Reads “My Apology” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400090/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Lipsyte reads his story “My Apology,” from the July 5, 2021, issue of the magazine. Lipsyte is the author of six books of fiction, including the story collection “The Fun Parts,” and the novels “The Ask” and “Hark,” which was published in 2019.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Camille Bordas Reads “Offside Constantly” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400091/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Camille Bordas reads her story from the June 28, 2021, issue of the magazine. Bordas has published two novels in France, “Les Treize Desserts” and “Partie Commune.” Her first novel in English, “How to Behave in a Crowd,” was published in 2017.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bryan Washington Reads “Foster” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400092/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bryan Washington reads his story from the June 14, 2021, issue of the magazine. Washington is a winner of the Ernest J. Gaines award, the International Dylan Thomas Prize, and the Lambda Literary award. His story collection, “Lot,” was published in 2019, and his novel, “Memorial,” came out in 2020.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rachel Heng Reads “Before the Valley” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400093/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rachel Heng reads her story from the June 7, 2021, issue of the magazine. Heng is the author of the novel “Suicide Club,” which was a national bestseller in Singapore and has been translated into ten languages. A new novel, “The Great Reclamation,” will be published next year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Saïd Sayrafiezadeh Reads “A, S, D, F” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400094/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Saïd Sayrafiezadeh reads his story from the May 31, 2021, issue of the magazine. Sayrafiezadeh is the author of the story collection “Brief Encounters with the Enemy,” which was a finalist for the PEN/Robert W. Bingham Prize for début fiction, in 2014. A new collection, “American Estrangement,” will be published in August.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Margaret Atwood Reads “Old Babes in the Wood” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400095/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Margaret Atwood reads her story from the April 26 &amp;amp; May 3, 2021, issue of the magazine. Atwood has published more than two dozen books of fiction, including the story collection “Stone Mattress,” and the novels “The Handmaid’s Tale” and “The Testaments,” which won the Booker Prize in 2019.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jonas Eika Reads “Alvin” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400096/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jonas Eika reads his story from the April 19, 2021, issue of the magazine, which was translated from the Danish by Sherilyn Nicolette Hellberg. Eika, a Danish writer, won the Nordic Council Literature Prize in 2019 for his short-story collection “After the Sun,” which will be published in English in August.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Clare Sestanovich Reads “Separation” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400097/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Clare Sestanovich reads her story from the April 12, 2021, issue of the magazine. Sestanovich will publish her début story collection, “Objects of Desire,” in June.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sterling HolyWhiteMountain Reads “Featherweight” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400098/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sterling HolyWhiteMountain reads his story from the April 5, 2021, issue of the magazine. HolyWhiteMountain is a former Stegner Fellow and current Jones Lecturer at Stanford University. He is an unrecognized citizen of the Blackfeet Nation. He is at work on a novel.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ayşegül Savaş Reads “Future Selves” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400099/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ayşegül Savaş reads her story from the March 29, 2021, issue of the magazine. Savaş’s first novel, “Walking on the Ceiling,” was published in 2019. Her second novel, “White on White,” will be published this year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Imbolo Mbue Reads “The Case for and Against Love Potions” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400100/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Imbolo Mbue reads her story from the March 22, 2021, issue of the magazine. Mbue is the author of two novels, “Behold the Dreamers,” which won the PEN/Faulkner Award for Fiction, and “How Beautiful We Were,” which was published this month.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>T. Coraghessan Boyle Reads “The Shape of a Teardrop” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400101/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400101/</guid><description>Podcast Description T.Coraghessan Boyle reads his story from the March 15, 2021, issue of the magazine. Boyle is the author of more than two dozen books of fiction, including “The Terranauts” and “Outside Looking In.” A new book, “Talk to Me,” will be published in September.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jonathan Lethem Reads “The Crooked House” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400102/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jonathan Lethem reads his story from the March 8, 2021, issue of the magazine. Lethem is the author of seventeen books of fiction, including the novels “Motherless Brooklyn,” “The Feral Detective,” and, most recently, “The Arrest,” which was published last year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Souvankham Thammavongsa Reads “Good-Looking” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400103/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Souvankham Thammavongsa reads her story from the March 1, 2021, issue of the magazine. Thammavongsa has published four volumes of poetry and the short-story collection “How to Pronounce Knife,” which won the 2020 Scotiabank Giller Prize.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jhumpa Lahiri Reads “Casting Shadows” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400104/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jhumpa Lahiri reads her story from the February 15 &amp;amp; 22, 2021, issue of the magazine. Lahiri is the author of two novels and two short-story collections. Her first book, “Interpreter of Maladies,” won the Pulitzer Prize in 2000 and she was a recipient of the National Humanities Medal in 2014. Her new novel, “Whereabouts,” from which this story is adapted, was published in Italian in 2018 and will come out in Lahiri’s translation in April.</description></item><item><title>Ben Okri Reads “A Wrinkle in the Realm” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400105/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ben Okri reads his story from the February 8, 2021, issue of the magazine. Okri is the author of eleven novels, including “The Famished Road,” which won the Booker Prize in 1991, and “The Freedom Artist,” which came out in 2019. His story collection, “Prayer for the Living,” was published in the U.S. this month.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lauren Groff Reads “The Wind” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400106/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lauren Groff reads her story from the February 1, 2021, issue of the magazine. Groff has published three novels, including “Arcadia,” in 2012, and “Fates and Furies,” in 2015. Her second story collection, “Florida,” won the Story Prize in 2018.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Allegra Goodman Reads “A Challenge You Have Overcome” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400107/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Allegra Goodman reads her story from the January 25, 2021, issue of the magazine. Goodman’s books include “The Family Markowitz” and “The Chalk Artist.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Andrea Lee Reads “The Rivals” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400108/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andrea Lee reads her story from the January 4 &amp;amp; 11, 2021, issue of the magazine. Lee is the author of four books, including the novel “Lost Hearts in Italy” and the story collection “Interesting Women.” A new book, “Red Island House,” will be published in March.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rebecca Curtis Reads “The Christmas Miracle” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400109/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400109/</guid><description>Podcast Description For a special holiday episode of the Writer’s Voice podcast, Rebecca Curtis reads “The Christmas Miracle,” her story from the December 23 &amp;amp; 30, 2013, issue of the magazine. Curtis is the author of the story collection “Twenty Grand: And Other Tales of Love and Money” and a winner of the Rona Jaffe Foundation Writers’ Award for Fiction.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Patricia Lockwood Reads “The Winged Thing” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400110/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Patricia Lockwood reads her story from the November 30, 2020, issue of the magazine. Lockwood has published two collections of poetry and the memoir “Priestdaddy,” which came out in 2017. Her first novel, “No One Is Talking About This,” from which this story is adapted, will come out next year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Salman Rushdie Reads “The Old Man in the Piazza” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400111/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Salman Rushdie reads his story from the November 23, 2020, issue of the magazine. Rushdie has published twelve novels, including the Booker Prize-winning “Midnight’s Children,” “The Satanic Verses,” “The Golden House,” and, most recently, “Quichotte,” which came out last year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rebecca Curtis Reads “Hansa and Gretyl and Piece of Shit” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400112/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rebecca Curtis reads her story from the November 16, 2020, issue of the magazine. Curtis is the author of the story collection “Twenty Grand: And Other Tales of Love and Money” and a winner of the Rona Jaffe Foundation Writers’ Award for Fiction.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>George Saunders Reads “Ghoul” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400113/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400113/</guid><description>Podcast Description George Saunders reads his story from the November 9, 2020, issue of the magazine. Saunders won the Man Booker Prize in 2017, for his novel “Lincoln in the Bardo.” He is the author of four story collections, including “CivilWarLand in Bad Decline” and “Tenth of December.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Curtis Sittenfeld Reads “A for Alone” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400114/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Curtis Sittenfeld reads her story from the November 2, 2020, issue of the magazine. Sittenfeld is the author of one short-story collection, “You Think It, I’ll Say It,” and six novels, including “Prep,” “Eligible,” and “Rodham,” which came out earlier this year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Roddy Doyle Reads “Life Without Children” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400115/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Roddy Doyle reads his story from the October 19, 2020, issue of the magazine. Doyle is the author of thirteen novels, including the Booker Prize-winning “Paddy Clarke Ha Ha Ha” and “The Dead Republic.” His most recent novel, “Love,” came out earlier this year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>David Rabe Reads “Suffocation Theory” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400116/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400116/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Rabe reads his story from the October 12, 2020, issue of the magazine. Rabe is the author of more than a dozen plays, including the Tony-award-winning “Sticks and Bones,” “In the Boom Boom Room,” and “Hurlyburly.” His novels include “Recital of the Dog” and “Girl by the Road at Night.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Joseph O’Neill Reads “Rainbows” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400117/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joseph O’Neill reads his story from the October 5, 2020, issue of the magazine. O’Neill is the author of four novels, including “Netherland,” which won the PEN/Faulkner award in 2009, and “The Dog.” His first story collection, “Good Trouble,” came out in 2018.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Douglas Stuart Reads “The Englishman” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400118/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400118/</guid><description>Podcast Description Douglas Stuart reads his story from the September 14, 2020, issue of the magazine. Stuart published his first novel, “Shuggie Bain,” earlier this year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Susan Choi Reads “Flashlight” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400119/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Susan Choi reads her story from the September 7, 2020, issue of the magazine. Choi is the author of five novels, including “My Education” and “Trust Exercise,” which won the National Book Award for Fiction in 2019.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>David Wright Faladé Reads “The Sand Banks, 1861” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400120/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400120/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Wright Faladé reads his story from the August 31, 2020, issue of the magazine. Wright Faladé is the author of the nonfiction book “Fire on the Beach: Recovering the Lost Story of Richard Etheridge and the Pea Island Lifesavers” and the young-adult novel “Away Running.” This story was adapted from his novel-in-progress “Nigh-On a Brother,” which will be published in 2022.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>David Gilbert Reads “Cicadia” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400121/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400121/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Gilbert reads his story from the August 24, 2020, issue of the magazine. Gilbert is the author of the story collection “Remote Feed” and two novels, “&amp;amp; Sons” and “The Normals.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Madhuri Vijay Reads “You Are My Dear Friend” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400122/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400122/</guid><description>Podcast Description Madhuri Vijay reads his story from the August 17, 2020, issue of the magazine. Vijay is the author of the novel “The Far Field,” which won the J.C.B prize for literature in 2019.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bryan Washington Reads “Heirlooms” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400123/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400123/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bryan Washington reads his story from the August 3 &amp;amp; 10, 2020, issue of the magazine. Washington’s first story collection, “Lot,” was published in 2019 and his first novel, “Memorial,” from which this story was adapted, will come out in October.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A. M. Homes Reads Shirley Jackson’s “The Lottery” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400124/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400124/</guid><description>Podcast Description A.M. Homes joins Deborah Treisman to read and discuss Shirley Jackson’s short story “The Lottery,” in this 2008 episode of the New Yorker Fiction Podcast. The story was originally published in 1948 and is included in the July 27, 2020, issue of The New Yorker—a bonus issue made up of pieces from the magazine’s archive on the subject of American dissent.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hari Kunzru Reads “A Transparent Woman” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400125/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hari Kunzru reads his story from the July 6 &amp;amp; 13, 2020, issue of the magazine. Kunzru is the author of five novels, including “Gods Without Men” and “White Tears.” A new novel, “Red Pill,” from which this story was adapted, will be published this September.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Emma Cline Reads “White Noise” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400126/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emma Cline reads her short story from the June 8 &amp;amp; 15, 2020, issue of the magazine. Cline’s first novel, “The Girls,” winner of the Shirley Jackson award, came out in 2016. Her story collection, “Daddy,” will be published later this year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>David Means Reads “Two Nurses, Smoking” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400127/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400127/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Means reads his short story from the June 1, 2020, issue of the magazine. Means is the author of the novel “Hystopia” and five story collections, including “The Spot” and “Instructions for a Funeral,” which was published last year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Fiona McFarlane Reads “Demolition” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400128/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400128/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fiona McFarlane reads her story from the May 25, 2020, issue of the magazine. McFarlane is the author of the novel “The Night Guest” and the story collection “The High Places,” which was awarded the international Dylan Thomas Prize in 2017.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jonathan Lethem Reads “The Afterlife” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400129/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400129/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jonathan Lethem reads his story from the May 18, 2020, issue of the magazine. Lethem is the author of more than fifteen books of fiction, including “Motherless Brooklyn,” “The Gambler’s Anatomy,” and “The Feral Detective.” A new novel, “The Arrest,” will be published later this year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sarah Shun-lien Bynum Reads “Bedtime Story” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400130/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400130/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sarah Shun-Lien Bynum reads her story from the April 27, 2020, issue of the magazine. Bynum is the author of two novels, “Madeleine Is Sleeping” and “Ms. Hempel Chronicles.” Her story collection, “Likes,” will be published in September.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ben Lerner Reads “The Media” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400131/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ben Lerner reads his story from the April 20, 2020, issue of the magazine. Lerner is the author of the novels “Leaving the Atocha Station,” “10:04,” and “The Topeka School,” which was published last year. He was awarded a MacArthur fellowship in 2015.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>George Saunders Reads “Love Letter” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400132/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400132/</guid><description>Podcast Description George Saunders reads his story from the April 6, 2020, issue of the magazine. Saunders won the Man Booker prize in 2017 for his novel, “Lincoln in the Bardo.” He is the author of four story collections, including “In Persuasion Nation” and “Tenth of December.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Han Ong Reads “Futures” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400133/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Han Ong reads his story from the March 30, 2020, issue of the magazine. Ong, the recipient of a MacArthur Fellowship and the Berlin Prize, is the author of more than a dozen plays and two novels, “Fixer Chao” and “The Disinherited.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Matthew Klam Reads “The Liver” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400134/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matthew Klam reads his story from the March 16, 2020, issue of the magazine. Klam is the author of the collection “Sam the Cat and Other Stories” and the novel “Who Is Rich?,” which was published in 2017.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Anne Enright Reads “Night Swim” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400135/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Anne Enright reads her story from the March 9, 2020, issue of the magazine. Enright is the author of three short-story collections and seven novels, including “The Gathering,” which won the Man Booker Prize in 2007, and “Actress,” which was published this month.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Adam Levin Reads “Kid Positive” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400136/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400136/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adam Levin reads his story from the March 2, 2020, issue of the magazine. Levin is the author of the novel “The Instructions” and the story collection “Hot Pink.” A new novel, “Bubblegum,” will be published in April.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Anthony Veasna So Reads “Three Women of Chuck’s Donuts” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400137/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Anthony Veasna So reads his story from the February 10, 2020, issue of the magazine. So is an MFA Candidate in Fiction at Syracuse University. His writing has appeared in n+1, Granta, and ZYZZYVA. This is his first piece of fiction in the magazine.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>David Rabe Reads “Things We Worried About When I Was Ten” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400138/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400138/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Rabe reads his story from the February 3, 2020, issue of the magazine. Rabe, a fiction writer, playwright, and screenwriter, is the author of more than a dozen plays, including the Tony Award-winning “Sticks and Bones,” “In the Boom Boom Room,” and “Hurlyburly.” His novels include “Recital of the Dog” and “Girl by the Road at Night.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mary South Reads “You Will Never Be Forgotten” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400139/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mary South reads her story from the January 27, 2020, issue of the magazine. South will publish her first book, the story collection “You Will Never Be Forgotten,” in March.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bryan Washington Reads “Visitor” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400140/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400140/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bryan Washington reads his story from the January 20, 2020, issue of the magazine. Washington is a National Book Award 5 Under 35 honoree. His first story collection, “Lot,” was published last year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Douglas Stuart Reads “Found Wanting” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400141/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Douglas Stuart reads his story from the January 13, 2020, issue of the magazine. Stuart, who was born in Glasgow, Scotland, will publish his first novel, “Shuggie Bain,” in February. This is his first published piece of fiction.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jamil Jan Kochai Reads “Playing Metal Gear Solid V: The Phantom Pain” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400142/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400142/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jamil Jan Kochai reads his story from the January 6, 2020, issue of the magazine. He was a Truman Capote Fellow at the Iowa Writers’ Workshop. His first novel, “99 Nights in Logar,” was published in 2019.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Camille Bordas Reads “Only Orange” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400143/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400143/</guid><description>Podcast Description Camille Bordas reads “Only Orange,” her story from the December 23, 2019, issue of the magazine. She has published two novels in France, “Les Treize Desserts” and “Partie Commune.” Her first novel in English, “How to Behave in a Crowd,” was published in 2017.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Clare Sestanovich Reads “Old Hope” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400144/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400144/</guid><description>Podcast Description Clare Sestanovich reads her story from the December 9, 2019, issue of the magazine. Sestanovich is working on her first collection of stories. She is a member of The New Yorker’s editorial staff. This is her first story in the magazine.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Roddy Doyle Reads “The Curfew” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400145/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400145/</guid><description>Podcast Description Roddy Doyle reads his story from the December 2, 2019, issue of the magazine. Doyle is the author of twelve novels, including the Man Booker Prize-winning “Paddy Clarke Ha Ha Ha” and “The Dead Republic.” His most recent novel, “Charlie Savage,” came out earlier this year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Weike Wang Reads “The Trip” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400146/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400146/</guid><description>Podcast Description Weike Wang reads her story from the November 18, 2019, issue of the magazine. Wang’s first novel, “Chemistry,” which won the PEN/Hemingway Award, was published in 2017, and she was named one of the National Book Foundation’s 5 Under 35 the same year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Joseph O’Neill Reads “The Flier” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400147/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400147/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joseph O’Neill reads his story from the November 11, 2019, issue of the magazine. O’Neil is the author of four novels, including “Netherland,” which won the PEN/Faulkner Award for Fiction in 2009, and “The Dog.” His first story collection, “Good Trouble,” was published last year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tiphanie Yanique Reads “God’s Caravan” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400148/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400148/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tiphanie Yanique reads her story from the November 4, 2019, issue of the magazine. Yanique is the author of “How to Escape from a Leper Colony: a Novella and Stories” and the novel “Land of Love and Drowning,” which won the Center for Fiction’s First Novel Prize in 2014.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tessa Hadley Reads “The Bunty Club” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400149/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400149/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tessa Hadley reads “The Bunty Club,” her story from the October 28, 2019, issue of the magazine. Hadley has published ten books of fiction, including the story collections “Married Love” and “Bad Dreams and Other Stories,” and the novel “Late in the Day,” which was published earlier this year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>David Means Reads “Are You Experienced?” | The New Yorker: The Writer's Voice - New Fiction from The New Yorker</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3950400150/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3950400150/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Means reads his story “Are You Experienced?” from the October 21, 2019, issue of the magazine. Means is the author of the novel “Hystopia” and five story collections, including “The Spot” and “Instructions for a Funeral,” which was published earlier this year.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>