<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Today in Focus on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/today-in-focus/</link><description>Recent content in Today in Focus on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 03:00:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/today-in-focus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Barclays and the battle for the Telegraph | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110300/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 03:00:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110300/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Barclay family may still legally own the newspaper titles, but politicians alongside some of the world’s richest men are contesting who will control them in the future. Jane Martinson, author of You May Never See Us Again: The Barclay Dynasty, reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How Madonna changed pop culture for ever | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110001/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 03:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110001/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s 40 years since Madonna began scandalising and delighting fans and critics around the world. But is she still misunderstood? With Mary Gabriel. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is Israel deliberately trying to make Gaza uninhabitable? – Podcast | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 03:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110002/</guid><description>Podcast Description With 40% of homes destroyed in the strip, legal experts are raising the question of ‘domicide’ – but what it is it, and is it taking place in Gaza?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rishi Sunak, Rwanda and the rebels | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 03:00:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110003/</guid><description>Podcast Description The prime minister faced down rebels within his party to win a vote on his controversial bill to send asylum seekers to Rwanda. But more trouble awaits him in the new year. Kiran Stacey reports from Westminster. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why Argentinians are gambling everything on ‘anarcho-capitalist’ Javier Milei | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 03:00:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110004/</guid><description>Podcast Description The libertarian economist won the election with his radical ideas. Can he deliver? Tom Phillips reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The stories behind Europe’s unmarked migrant graves – podcast | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 03:00:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110005/</guid><description>Podcast Description What happens to the people who risk everything to get to Europe – and don’t survive the journey? Ashifa Kassam reports from Lanzarote. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sellafield: Europe’s most toxic nuclear site | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110006/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 03:00:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110006/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Guardian’s investigation into safety concerns at Europe’s most hazardous nuclear plant. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Revisited: a conversation with Benjamin Zephaniah | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 17:00:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110007/</guid><description>Podcast Description The British poet Benjamin Zephaniah died this week after a short illness. Here we revisit a conversation between Zephaniah and George the Poet from 2020. They discussed why, having been born a generation apart, their work was exposing racial injustice. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The lives and lies of George Santos | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 03:00:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110008/</guid><description>Podcast Description The US politician was accused of telling extraordinary lies about everything from his previous jobs to his religion. Why did it take so long to boot him out of Congress? Adam Gabbatt explains. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Boris Johnson v the Covid inquiry | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 03:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110009/</guid><description>Podcast Description After accusations of erratic decision-making during the pandemic, the former prime minister will finally face the inquiry. Aletha Adu reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why are so many councils going ‘bankrupt’? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110010/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 03:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nottingham council is the latest to in effect declare itself bankrupt, and one in 10 county councils in England are at risk of following suit. What does it mean for the services that so many people rely on? Jessica Murray reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why is the Israel-Hamas conflict so deadly for journalists? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110011/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 03:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110011/</guid><description>Podcast Description More reporters are said to have been killed in this conflict than any in decades. Jonathan Dagher, from Reporters Without Borders, discusses what it means for public understanding of the region. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Israel-Gaza: a week of tearful reunions and an uneasy truce | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110012/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 03:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110012/</guid><description>Podcast Description As Israeli hostages were exchanged for Palestinian prisoners, the intense fighting was paused this week. Jason Burke reports on an emotional few days and what happens next. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The secret plan to ‘hook’ the developing world on oil | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 03:00:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110013/</guid><description>Podcast Description As the Cop28 climate summit begins in Dubai today, a secret Saudi Arabian plan to get poorer countries ‘hooked on its harmful products’ has emerged. Damian Carrington reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Geert Wilders and Europe’s lurch to the far right | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 03:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110014/</guid><description>Podcast Description How did far-right politician Geert Wilders win so many seats in the Dutch election? Jon Henley and Senay Boztas report. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How King Charles profits from the assets of dead citizens | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 03:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110015/</guid><description>Podcast Description An archaic custom allows the king’s estate to absorb the assets of people in the north of England who die without a will or a known next of kin. Maeve McClenaghan investigates King’s estate to transfer £100m into ethical funds after bona vacantia revelations. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The spy tech firm managing NHS data | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 03:00:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Palantir, the US spy-tech firm co-founded by the billionaire Peter Thiel, has won a contract to handle NHS data. It’s a deal that has left privacy advocates such as Cori Crider with serious questions. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>He’s back: Sam Altman and the chaos at the heart of the AI industry | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110017/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 03:00:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110017/</guid><description>Podcast Description The CEO of OpenAI was sacked and then rehired days later, after staff threatened to follow him. But what does this corporate drama tell us about the future of AI? Blake Montgomery explains. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Can tax cuts save the Tories? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110018/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 03:00:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeremy Hunt has offered up sweeping tax cuts in an attempt to jolt the UK economy back to life and salvage his party’s hopes of staying in power beyond the next election. Heather Stewart reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A truce agreement in Gaza | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 03:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110019/</guid><description>Podcast Description On late Tuesday night, Israel’s cabinet met to vote on a temporary ceasefire in Gaza and a hostage and prisoner exchange. Julian Borger reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How much legal trouble is Donald Trump in? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110020/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 03:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Various polls have the ex-president as favourite to retake the White House in the US election next year, but he faces growing legal jeopardy. Hugo Lowell reports on the many charges Trump is facing. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The families stuck living in Britain’s unlicensed bedsits | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 03:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why do so many people end up in unlicensed houses of multiple occupation? And what are the conditions like? Robert Booth reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Israel’s raid on al-Shifa hospital | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 03:00:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gaza’s biggest hospital was filled with doctors, patients and people seeking safety when Israel laid siege to it. Ruth Michaelson reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How the UK government’s Rwanda asylum plan came unstuck | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 03:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110023/</guid><description>Podcast Description The supreme court has ruled that the government’s plan to deport asylum seekers to Rwanda is unlawful. Peter Walker explains what happens next. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Has Putin got the upper hand in Ukraine? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 03:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110024/</guid><description>Podcast Description With the world’s attention on the Middle East, Ukraine seems to be at a stalemate – which may sound like good news for Russia, but is not so straightforward, Luke Harding reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The return of David Cameron | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110025/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 03:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former prime minister David Cameron has been installed as foreign secretary in Rishi Sunak’s reshuffle, in which Suella Braverman was also sacked from the cabinet. Pippa Crerar reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rebuilding Paradise: five years on from California’s deadliest fire | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110026/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 03:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Five years after a wildfire killed 85 people in the Californian town of Paradise, the area has been rebuilt from the ashes. Dani Anguiano and Alastair Gee report. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Suella Braverman, the police and the protests | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110027/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 03:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Senior members of the government have spent the week calling for Saturday’s pro-Palestinian march to be banned but the Metropolitan police have resisted the pressure. Daniel Boffey reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What will it take to free the hostages taken by Hamas? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110028/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 03:00:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110028/</guid><description>Podcast Description On 7 October, 240 people in Israel were kidnapped and taken into Gaza. A month on, only a handful have been released. Bethan McKernan reports The mothers whose children are held hostage by Hamas: ‘All we want is them home’ Israel-Hamas war – live updates. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Fear and fury in the West Bank | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110029/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 03:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Palestinians in the West Bank say that while all the attention is on Gaza, Israeli settlers overseen by the military are killing people and forcing them from the land. Julian Borger reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Crypto on trial: the downfall of Sam Bankman-Fried | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110030/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 03:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Bankman-Fried, founder of cryptocurrency exchange FTX, is facing up to 110 years in jail after being found guilty of fraud on a massive scale, exposed when his company collapsed last year. Blake Montgomery reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why are Britain’s new homes so rubbish? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110031/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 03:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Oliver Wainwright reports on the increasingly poor standards of newly built homes in the UK and what consumers can do to protect themselves. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How oligarchs use English courts to silence their critics | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110032/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 03:00:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Use of Slapps by the super-rich against journalists is increasingly common, and campaigners say new legislation to deter such actions does not go far enough. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How the Israel-Gaza conflict is dividing Labour | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110033/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 03:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Since a show of unity at Labour conference, anger and upset have been growing over the leader’s stance. Can Keir Starmer heal the rift? Aletha Adu reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is the AI safety summit already too late? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110034/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 03:00:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rishi Sunak has convened a global summit of world leaders and tech executives to discuss how the power of artificial intelligence can be safely harnessed. Dan Milmo reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>‘We’re totally isolated’: inside Gaza as Israel’s war intensifies | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110035/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 03:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110035/</guid><description>Podcast Description As Israel steps up its military campaign in Gaza, residents trapped in the territory are facing a humanitarian crisis. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What we’ve learned so far from the Covid inquiry | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110036/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 03:00:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hearings for the government Covid inquiry resume today in Westminster with former Downing Street adviser Dominic Cummings slated to appear this week. Peter Walker reports on the story so far. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The last whale hunter in Iceland | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110037/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 02:00:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kristján Loftsson has stubbornly refused to bow to public opinion or an overwhelming international consensus against whaling. But with a full ban coming in Iceland, has he killed his last whale?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The rise of antisemitism in the UK | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110038/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 02:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110038/</guid><description>Podcast Description There has been a 1,350% increase in hate crimes against Jewish people in London, according to the Metropolitan police. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>In the wake of Storm Babet | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 02:00:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Thousands of homes across Scotland and the Midlands have been flooded in recent days. Jessica Murray reports from Chesterfield. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Could the conflict in Israel tip into regional war? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110040/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 02:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Presidents, prime ministers and diplomats are trying to stop the conflict from spinning further out of control. Is it working?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How a contested history feeds the Israel-Palestine conflict | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110041/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 02:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Certain dates are seared into the minds of those who have tried to untangle the decades-long Israel-Palestine conflict, be it 1917, 1947, 1967, 1973 – and now 2023. Chris McGreal reports on an escalating war that is only understandable by looking to the past. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How Taylor Swift built her music empire | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110042/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 02:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110042/</guid><description>Podcast Description After its opening last weekend, Taylor Swift: the Eras Tour is on track to be the biggest concert film of all time. How did Swift create this level of success? Laura Snapes reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kicking out the populists: how young voters helped swing Poland’s election | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110043/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 02:00:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Poland’s far-right Law and Justice party was a disaster for many of the country’s democratic institutions and the LGBT community. Now it appears voters have got rid of it. Shaun Walker reports from Warsaw. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The deadly stakes of a ground invasion of Gaza | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 02:00:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110044/</guid><description>Podcast Description With more than 2 million people trapped in Gaza, what are the consequences of an Israeli invasion?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is the SNP’s independence dream fading? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110045/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 02:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110045/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Scottish National party has agreed a new strategy for pursuing independence at its annual conference. But is declining support for the party placing the issue out of reach? Libby Brooks reports from Aberdeen. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The hidden cost of cancer | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110046/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 02:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Getting ill shouldn’t be expensive. But for many patients, being diagnosed with cancer can be a financial catastrophe. Hilary Osborne looks at why. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The fight to give Indigenous Australians a voice | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110047/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 02:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110047/</guid><description>Podcast Description As Australians prepare to vote in a referendum to give Indigenous people a voice in parliament, Prof Marcia Langton explores the long struggle for equal rights. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Human catastrophe unfolds in Israel and Gaza | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110048/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 02:00:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Deadly assault by Hamas militants across southern Israel has been followed by devastating airstrikes on Gaza and threats of full-scale invasion by Israeli military. Bethan McKernan reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Keir Starmer’s plan to rebuild Britain | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110049/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 02:00:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Keir Starmer promises to bring in a new era of ‘rebuilding’, ‘renewal’ and even ‘healing’ after 13 years of Conservative rule. Kiran Stacey reports on the Labour leader’s keynote conference speech. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>From Blair to Starmer: Labour’s path to power – part 2 | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110050/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 02:00:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Labour went into the 1997 general election full of confidence. Now, 26 years on from that famous victory, Kiran Stacey hears as those who helped craft it look ahead and ask if it is time to be more radical. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How the Israel-Gaza conflict erupted | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110051/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 18:52:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110051/</guid><description>Podcast Description A bloody attack by Hamas has shocked the world – and left Israel reeling. As the country responds with devastating airstrikes, Peter Beaumont explains how the surprise attack unfolded and what could happen next. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>From Blair to Starmer: Labour’s path to power, part 1 | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110052/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 02:00:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110052/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1996 Labour was a year out from an election after more than a decade out of power. Its leader, Tony Blair, was surrounded by advisers and strategists plotting their way to victory. Kiran Stacey hears how they did it and what lessons there are for Keir Starmer’s party as it gathers for its annual conference. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why Britain is mourning the Sycamore Gap tree | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110053/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 02:00:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110053/</guid><description>Podcast Description The felling of a Northumberland tree has made headlines around the world – and led to a criminal investigation. Why did it mean so much to people?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Do Rishi Sunak's new policies add up? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110054/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rishi Sunak has declared himself an enemy of the ‘30-year status quo’. In doing so, he scrapped much of the HS2 rail link and said A-levels would be replaced. Kiran Stacey reports on whether it all adds up. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>HS2: how the costly rail project ran out of track | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110055/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 02:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110055/</guid><description>Podcast Description It started out with high hopes and a higher budget. Helen Pidd explains why the government has lost faith in the ambitious – and controversial – rail project. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Out in the cold: the spy scandal gripping Denmark | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110056/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 02:00:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Claus Hjort Frederiksen, Denmark’s former defence minister and Lars Findsen former head of Denmark’s foreign intelligence agency, have been charged with divulging state secrets and face lengthy prison sentences. Harry Davies investigates why the scandal will reverberate well beyond Scandinavia. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Gangs of Stockholm: the rise of gun crime in Sweden | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110057/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110057/</guid><description>Podcast Description September has become the worst month for shooting deaths in Sweden since records began in 2016. Miranda Bryant and Sebastian Stakset, a former gang member, talk about what’s behind the shocking rise in violence. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Culture 2023: the films, music and TV shows not to miss this autumn | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110058/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 02:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Guardian music critic Alexis Petridis, film editor Catherine Shoard and TV critic Leila Latif guide you through what’s on offer. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nagorno Karabakh: Why a frozen conflict suddenly exploded | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110059/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 02:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tens of thousands of refugees have already fled their homes in the disputed region, and more are set to follow. Andrew Roth explains why. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Overcrowded and understaffed: life in England’s crumbling prisons | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110060/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 02:00:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rats, broken windows and overfilled cells are a daily reality for prisoners in England’s crumbling jails. Helen Pidd reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why are London firearms officers laying down their guns? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110061/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 02:00:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Metropolitan police firearms officers have downed their weapons in protest at the charging of a colleague with murder. Vikram Dodd reports on what happens now. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Blind Side and Hollywood’s blind spot | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110062/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 02:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why is the retired NFL player Michael Oher bringing a lawsuit against the family who took him in as a teenager? Andrew Lawrence reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Looking for alternatives: a tale of two German towns | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110063/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 02:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110063/</guid><description>Podcast Description As Germany heads into a recession, tensions over its migration policy and its national identity are throwing up unusual results in local elections. Michael Safi reports View the front page of the Guardian’s newly launched Europe edition. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rishi Sunak’s net zero U-turn | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110064/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 02:00:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110064/</guid><description>Podcast Description The PM has torn up his ambitious plans for Britain to achieve its commitments on net zero emissions, saying they were ‘unrealistic and punitive’. Kiran Stacey reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The destruction of Derna | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110065/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 02:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110065/</guid><description>Podcast Description What left the city of Derna vulnerable to such a devastating flood? The Libyan freelance journalist Johr Ali reports on the city in which he grew up. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The horrifying allegations against Russell Brand | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110066/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 02:00:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110066/</guid><description>Podcast Description The comedian, presenter and actor has been accused of sexual assault, emotional abuse and rape between 2006 and 2013 – allegations Brand denies. Alexandra Topping explains why such stories can be particularly difficult to investigate. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Naomi Klein’s doppelganger | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110067/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 02:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110067/</guid><description>Podcast Description When the author Naomi Klein began being mistaken for Naomi Wolf it set her off on a quest to examine the slippery nature of truth in the post-pandemic world. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What have a year of protests really changed in Iran? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110068/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 02:00:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Twelve months after 22-year-old Mahsa Amini died in the custody of the regime’s ‘morality police’, we look at her legacy. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ukraine’s counteroffensive: breaking the Russian lines | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110069/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 02:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ukraine’s much-anticipated summer offensive has been slow to the point of stalling. But a recent breakthrough of the Russian lines has provided new hope for the country’s leaders – and its partners. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A day in the ruins of Morocco’s earthquake | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110070/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 02:00:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Peter Beaumont reports from the High Atlas mountains in Morocco, where residents deal with the huge loss of life and destruction of their villages. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The concrete crisis: is Britain falling apart? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110071/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 02:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last-minute safety worries about the structural soundness of school buildings threw the new term into chaos for many children and their parents. Could the episode spell disaster for Rishi Sunak’s government?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Has the plant-based food revolution lost its sizzle? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110072/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 02:00:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110072/</guid><description>Podcast Description There has been a boom in the market for plant-based foods and products that mimic meat in recent years. But that boom has hit a blip amid a cost of living crisis and increasing consumer worries about ultra-processed food, says Bee Wilson. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The mystery of Bangladesh’s missing children – part three | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110073/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 02:00:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110073/</guid><description>Podcast Description What would you do if everything you believed about your childhood was wrong? Rosie Swash and Thaslima Begum investigate an international adoption scandal that is still shattering lives today. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The scandal of Bangladesh’s missing children – part two | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110074/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 04:32:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110074/</guid><description>Podcast Description What would you do if everything you believed about your childhood was wrong? Rosie Swash and Thaslima Begum investigate an international adoption scandal that is still shattering lives today. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The mystery of Bangladesh’s missing children – part one | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110075/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 02:00:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110075/</guid><description>Podcast Description What would you do if everything you believed about your childhood was wrong? Rosie Swash and Thaslima Begum investigate an international adoption scandal that is still shattering lives today. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How safe are the priceless treasures in our museums? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110076/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 02:00:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110076/</guid><description>Podcast Description As many as 2,000 historic items are thought to have gone missing from the British Museum’s collections in the past decade. How could it have happened, and how easily can museums get stolen artefacts back?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The chilling rise of AI scams | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110077/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 02:00:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Criminals are cloning voices and making calls to trick victims into sending them money. How can they be stopped?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The curious world of the Guardian’s Experience column | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110078/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 02:00:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rebecca Liu discusses her role as a commissioning editor at the Guardian’s Experience column and we hear three stories from those who have been featured in the column. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why wasn’t Lucy Letby stopped sooner? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110079/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 02:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110079/</guid><description>Podcast Description The nurse is the most prolific child serial killer in modern British history. Could the NHS have prevented her committing so many crimes?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rats, fires and floods: why Parliament is falling down | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110080/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 02:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110080/</guid><description>Podcast Description It is the symbol of Britain’s democracy and it is falling into decay. The Palace of Westminster needs extensive – and expensive – repairs. But are MPs ready to do what it takes to save it?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The final weeks of Yevgeny Prigozhin | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110081/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 02:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110081/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Wagner leader seemed to have achieved the unthinkable: humiliating Putin and getting away with it. But had he really been forgiven – or was the Kremlin playing for time?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Revisited: Trafficked: Marta – part four – podcast | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110082/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 02:00:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110082/</guid><description>Podcast Description The story of a Ukrainian woman who escaped modern slavery in the UK. Annie Kelly reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Revisited: Trafficked: the operation – part three – podcast | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110083/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 02:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110083/</guid><description>Podcast Description The story of a Ukrainian woman who escaped modern slavery in the UK. Annie Kelly reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Revisited: Trafficked: the closed door – part two | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110084/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 02:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Julia, a Ukrainian woman who escaped modern slavery in the UK, tells the journalist Annie Kelly about the years she was shipped between brothels. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Revisited: Trafficked: the trap – part one | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110085/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 02:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110085/</guid><description>Podcast Description The story of a Ukrainian woman who escaped modern slavery in the UK. Annie Kelly reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cotton Capital: Reparations – episode 6 | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110086/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 02:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Revisited: In the final episode of the series, Cotton Capital editor and Guardian journalist Maya Wolfe-Robinson looks at the subject of reparations. What do they mean for communities and descendants of transatlantic enslavement – and what is the Guardian planning to do in its own programme of measures?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cotton Capital: Resistance – episode 5 | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110087/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 02:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Revisited: In the fifth episode in the series, Guardian journalist and Cotton Capital special correspondent Lanre Bakare examines Black Mancunian history, beginning with the 1945 Pan-African Congress that took place in the city and shaped independence movements across Africa. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cotton Capital: The Brazilian connection – episode 4 | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110088/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 02:00:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Revisited: The fourth episode in the Cotton Capital series explores how during the transatlantic slave trade, more enslaved African people were taken to Brazil than any other country. Today, more than half of Brazil’s population identify as Black and there are more Black people in Brazil than any other country except Nigeria. But the country is still grappling with deep structural racism. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.</description></item><item><title>Cotton Capital: The Sea Islands – episode 3 | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110089/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 02:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Revisited: In the third episode in the series, journalist DeNeen L Brown travels to the Sea Islands in the US and meets the Gullah Geechee people – direct descendants of enslaved Africans who picked the distinctive Sea Island cotton prized by traders in Manchester. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cotton Capital: The meaning of Success – episode 2 | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110090/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 02:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Revisited: The second episode in the series follows journalist Maya Wolfe-Robinson as she travels to Jamaica in search of the site of the former sugar plantation Success, once co-owned by the Guardian funder Sir George Philips. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cotton Capital: The bee and the ship – episode 1 | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110091/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 02:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Revisited: The first episode in the Cotton Capital series explores the revelations that the Guardian’s founding editor, John Edward Taylor, and at least nine of his 11 backers had links to slavery, principally through the textile industry. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The wellness-to-conspiracy pipeline | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110092/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 02:00:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110092/</guid><description>Podcast Description For many people, alternative therapies and wellness routines provide comfort and pleasure. For others, they can be a pathway to far-right conspiracies, says author and journalist James Ball. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why were the wildfires in Hawaii so deadly? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110093/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 02:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last week fires tore through the Hawaiian island of Maui, causing devastating destruction in the ancient capital of Lahaina. What happened?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The mystery of the Crooked House fire | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110094/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 02:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110094/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Britain’s wonkiest pub was destroyed in a fire and the ruins demolished, it sparked protests and made headlines around the world – but why?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Bibby Stockholm saga | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110095/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 02:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110095/</guid><description>Podcast Description After removing asylum seekers from the Bibby Stockholm barge on Friday, the government says they will be returned ‘as soon as possible’. Daniel Trilling and Sammy Gecsoyler report. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Uncovering the truth of the Nazi occupation of the Channel Islands | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110096/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 02:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110096/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1940 the German army took over the Channel Islands and built concentration camps on Alderney where hundreds, possibly thousands, of people died. Now a UK government review will attempt to get to the truth of what really happened. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How the search for UFOs reached the US Congress | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110097/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 02:00:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110097/</guid><description>Podcast Description The quest to discover whether or not we’re alone in the universe has become an obsession for many Americans. Some of them are elected officials, reports Adam Gabbatt in Washington DC. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Qur’an burnings in Sweden: who is fanning the flames? – podcast | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110098/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 02:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110098/</guid><description>Podcast Description The act of burning a holy book in Sweden is not of itself illegal. But a spate of burnings has resulted in outrage at home and abroad – and potentially far-reaching consequences. Miranda Bryant reports from Stockholm. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why the rest of the world can’t afford to ignore the coup in Niger | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110099/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110099/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Sahel region, sometimes called Africa’s ‘coup belt’, has just seen another government ousted. Peter Beaumont and Nesrine Malik on what it means for African – and global – security. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The legacy of Sinéad O’Connor | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110100/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Film-maker Kathryn Ferguson and journalist Simon Hattenstone share their memories of Sinéad O’Connor and reflect on her impact on music and society. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How can we escape burnout? | Podcast | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110101/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 02:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Burnout is a serious issue in workplaces across the UK. What can we do to change our working culture in order to prevent it?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Donald Trump’s January 6 indictment | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110102/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110102/</guid><description>Podcast Description The former US president appeared in court on Wednesday charged on four counts related to his efforts to overturn the result of the 2020 election. Hugo Lowell reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rishi Sunak’s anti-green gamble | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110103/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 02:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110103/</guid><description>Podcast Description The prime minister’s announcement of new oil and gas licences in the North Sea this week is a sign he sees electoral advantage in being anti-green. Kiran Stacey reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Life in the UK for one of China’s most wanted | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110104/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 02:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hong Kong activist Finn Lau has vowed to continue his fight for democracy despite the Chinese bounty on his head. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why is Hollywood on strike? (And why Succession's Brian Cox is joining them) | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110105/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 02:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Production on Hollywood films and hit TV shows has ground to a halt. Apart from the stars on the picket line, how is this strike different from other labour disputes?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The novelist who became a war crimes investigator – and uncovered a secret diary - Podcast | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110106/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 02:00:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Victoria Amelina was an award-winning novelist. But after Russian forces invaded Ukraine, she began investigating war crimes – including the disappearance of a much-loved children’s author. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why Nigel Farage’s bank account matters so much | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110107/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Since the politician’s account with Coutts was closed, the story has dominated the news agenda. Does it show that something has gone very wrong in our banking system?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Climate crisis up close: a week of wildfires in Rhodes | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110108/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 02:00:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Holidaymakers on the Greek island of Rhodes found themselves evacuated from hotels and sleeping in school halls as wildfires raged nearby. As they make plans to return home, residents and business owners are counting the cost of what will be an expensive recovery. Rachel Hall reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The class of 2023: the UK’s unluckiest students | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110109/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 02:00:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Many of the students who began their studies under Covid restrictions are now leaving university without knowing their grades. Anna Fazackerley reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Great British motorcycle scam – part two | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110110/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 02:00:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110110/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the concluding part of an investigation into Norton, Simon Goodley reports on a prestigious motorcycle brand that became a vehicle for a multimillion-pound pension fraud. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Great British motorcycle scam – part one | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110111/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 02:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Norton Motorcycles was once one of the most prestigious brands in motorsport. So how did it become the vehicle for a multimillion pound pension fraud that has left investors penniless? Simon Goodley reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why we are all living in a Barbie world – podcast | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110112/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 02:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110112/</guid><description>Podcast Description She may have towered over the toy market for 60 years, but Barbie has never been short of critics. So why is a film about a plastic doll creating such fevered excitement?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Extreme heat: a warning shot from nature | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110113/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 02:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over the last two weeks, many countries have experienced record-breaking temperatures. Guardian reporters based in the UK, US, Italy and Taiwan discuss the fallout. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The World Cup and the future of women’s football | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110114/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 02:00:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110114/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Women’s World Cup kicks off on Thursday. The former England star Karen Carney discusses why this is an opportunity for investment that the sport cannot afford to miss. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Could your clothes be making you sick? | Podcast | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110115/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 02:00:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stain-resistant, wrinkle-proof, hard-wearing – modern clothing can cope with anything. But we know little about the chemicals that go into making it so impressive – or what they could be doing to our health. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Has Britain become a country of shoplifters? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110116/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 02:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shopkeepers complain the number of thefts from stores is soaring. Is the cost of living crisis to blame or organised gangs?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Sun, the BBC and Huw Edwards: the story of a scandal | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110117/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 02:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110117/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a week of frenzied reporting about allegations against the BBC presenter, there are uncomfortable questions for the paper that ran the scoop, reports Jim Waterson. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Will Mark Zuckerberg’s Threads unravel Twitter? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110118/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 02:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110118/</guid><description>Podcast Description Meta has launched what it promises will be a kinder alternative to Twitter. Can it deliver? Dan Milmo reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Putin v Prigozhin: is Wagner too valuable to crush? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110119/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 02:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110119/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Wagner forces turned their guns against Russian forces it led to panic in Moscow. But after the coup was aborted and its leader accused of treachery, it was business as usual for the group’s lucrative Africa operations. Pjotr Sauer and Jason Burke report. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cure or fad? The truth about weight loss drugs | Podcast | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110120/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 02:00:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110120/</guid><description>Podcast Description A new generation of weight loss drugs has caused a stir – offering impressive results. But are they really a silver bullet for the obesity epidemic?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Payback or play? The orcas sinking yachts | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110121/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Since May 2020, there have been hundreds of reports of orcas interacting with boats in the strait of Gibraltar. Philip Hoare reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What the raid on Jenin says about the future of Israel and Palestine | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110122/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 02:00:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110122/</guid><description>Podcast Description The biggest assault on the West Bank in 20 years could herald a new phase of this old conflict, reports Bethan McKernan from Jenin. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Can Biden solve his supreme court problem? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110123/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110123/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last week, the US supreme court ruled in favour of a web designer who does not want to serve gay clients, ended affirmative action and blocked Joe Biden’s student debt forgiveness plan. Sam Levine reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why are so many children refusing to go to school? | Podcast | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110124/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 02:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110124/</guid><description>Podcast Description One in 10 GCSE-year pupils are absent from England’s schools each day, up 70% since before the Covid pandemic. What is going on?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The killing of Nahel – and a week of grief and fury in France | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110125/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 02:00:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Since a 17-year-old boy was shot during a traffic stop, protests have set France ablaze, and exposed deep divisions. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tuvalu – how do you save a disappearing country? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110126/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 02:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110126/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Pacific Islands country could be lost to rising sea levels in just 50 years. Now its citizens have come up with a surprising plan to preserve their nation. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Republican race for 2024: can anyone stop Trump? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110127/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 02:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Despite being embroiled in several legal wrangles that could ultimately land him in jail, Donald Trump has a comfortable lead in the race for the Republican presidential nomination. Joan E Greve reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Guards at Del Monte pineapple farm in Kenya accused of killings | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110128/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 02:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110128/</guid><description>Podcast Description An investigation by the Guardian and the Bureau of Investigative journalism has uncovered claims from villagers in Kenya of violence and even killings linked to guards on a Del Monte pineapple farm. Emily Dugan reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The oil company CEO running the next UN climate change summit | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110129/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 02:00:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110129/</guid><description>Podcast Description The UN’s annual climate conference is being dogged by scandal months before it even begins. Environment editor Damian Carrington reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What the Wagner mutiny means for Ukraine, Russia and Putin | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110130/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 02:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110130/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Russia’s mercenary group marched on Moscow, it seemed to take the world – and Vladimir Putin – by surprise . What does it mean for his grip on power – and for his war?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A violent homicide – and a pioneering act of forgiveness | Podcast | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110131/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 02:00:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110131/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Donald Fields Jr killed his father in an argument, he could have been imprisoned for life. Instead, in a case that might be the first of its kind in the US, he completed a restorative justice programme and was released. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How the Windrush generation shaped British culture | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110132/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 02:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110132/</guid><description>Podcast Description It is 75 years since HMS Empire Windrush docked at Tilbury in Essex. Authors Colin Grant and Patrice Lawrence and publisher Sharmaine Lovegrove reflect on the cultural legacy of that moment and how it has shaped their work. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Britain’s mortgage timebomb | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110133/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 02:00:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110133/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Bank of England is expected to raise interest rates again today, leaving millions of homeowners facing higher costs. Richard Partington reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Held v Montana: the young people fighting for the climate in court | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110134/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 02:00:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dharna Noor reports on the 16 young people taking on the state of Montana in a historic climate case. What could it mean if the plaintiffs are successful?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why police are stepping back from mental health callouts | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110135/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 02:00:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Police spend an estimated 20-40% of their time on mental health calls, according to the College of Policing. Is Humberside police’s ‘Right Care, Right Person’ a better way? Helen Pidd reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The death of the Unabomber: will his dangerous influence live on? – podcast | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110136/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 02:00:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110136/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ted Kaczynski, the Harvard-educated mathematician who ran a 17-year bombing campaign that killed three people, died in prison earlier this month. But his manifesto promoting violent rebellion against the modern world continues to inspire copycat attacks. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Boris Johnson: the damning verdict | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110137/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 02:00:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110137/</guid><description>Podcast Description A committee of MPs has found that Boris Johnson deliberately misled parliament and was part of a campaign to abuse and intimidate them. Peter Walker reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is it time to decriminalise abortion in the UK? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110138/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 02:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110138/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a distressing and controversial case in which a woman was jailed after taking abortion pills after the UK time limit, is it time to change the law?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How Saudi Arabia took over professional golf | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110139/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110139/</guid><description>Podcast Description After months of bitter divisions in the world of professional golf, a major deal has resulted in victory for Saudi Arabia and its bid to influence the future of the sport. Ewan Murray reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The long shadows of Boris Johnson and Nicola Sturgeon | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110140/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 02:00:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110140/</guid><description>Podcast Description The former PM and ex-Scottish first minister were controversial leaders. Now they are both facing disgrace – adding to the turmoil in British politics. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What’s behind the rise in dog attacks? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110141/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 02:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Seven people have been killed by dogs in the UK so far this year. Simon Usborne reports on the worrying increase in attacks. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Prince Harry versus the Mirror | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110142/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 02:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110142/</guid><description>Podcast Description Prince Harry became one of the most senior royals ever to give evidence in an English court this week. Jim Waterson reports from the high court in London where tabloid phone hacking was back under the microscope. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The destruction of the Kakhovka dam | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110143/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 02:00:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110143/</guid><description>Podcast Description The UN has blamed the destruction of the Kakhovka dam on Russia. What impact will the flooding have on the war in Ukraine? Dan Sabbagh reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to develop artificial super-intelligence without destroying humanity | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110144/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 02:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110144/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Altman, the founder of the revolutionary application Chat-GPT, is touring Europe with a message: AI is changing the world and there are big risks, but also big potential rewards. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What is the UK government hiding from the Covid inquiry? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110145/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 02:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110145/</guid><description>Podcast Description The government has launched legal action to prevent the independent Covid inquiry demanding disclosure of thousands of WhatsApp messages. What does it have to hide, asks Aubrey Allegretti. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Our critics’ guide to a summer of music, movies and culture | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110146/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 02:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110146/</guid><description>Podcast Description Guardian culture writers Alex Needham, Ellen E Jones and Michael Cragg make their picks of the best of this summer in arts and culture. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is Manchester City’s dominance of English football fair? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110147/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 02:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110147/</guid><description>Podcast Description Manchester City have added this season’s Premier League title to their collection of honours and are favourites to win the FA Cup and the Champions League. But are they playing fair? Jonathan Liew reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sofas, smiles – and scandal: what’s going on at ITV’s This Morning? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110148/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 02:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110148/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s been a fixture on British TV screens for decades – as has one of its hosts, Phillip Schofield. But now This Morning is in turmoil after he admitted to an ‘unwise, but not illegal’ workplace relationship. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tracking down Ukraine’s abducted children | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110149/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 02:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110149/</guid><description>Podcast Description How did tens of thousands of Ukrainian children end up in Russian re-education camps? Peter Beaumont reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bashar al-Assad’s dark return to the world stage | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110150/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 02:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110150/</guid><description>Podcast Description For almost a decade the murderous actions of the Syrian president meant he was shunned but now he is being embraced by Arab leaders once more. What does this mean for the millions of refugees who fled from his brutal regime?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Murdochs' real-life succession drama | Podcast | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110151/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 02:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110151/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who will take over Rupert Murdoch’s media empire after he dies, and why does it matter? Paddy Manning reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A spying scandal and lots of coffee: how Guardian Australia launched 10 years ago | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110152/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 02:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110152/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a special edition of Full Story, Guardian Australia’s daily podcast, Bridie Jabour speaks to the key players of its launch in May 2013. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Conspiracy theories and chaos: a week watching GB News | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110153/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 02:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110153/</guid><description>Podcast Description GB News launched in 2021 with a mission to disrupt the relatively safe and sedate world of rolling TV news. Heather Stewart spent a week watching the channel to see what it has become today. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How a killing on New York subway exposed a broken system – podcast | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110154/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 02:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110154/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Jordan Neely, a homeless Michael Jackson impersonator, died at the hands of a fellow passenger this month, it shocked the world. But what does it reveal about the city?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is Suella Braverman speeding towards a government exit? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110155/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 02:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110155/</guid><description>Podcast Description Having set herself up as a rival to the prime minister, the home secretary is now facing allegations that she broke the ministerial code. Aubrey Allegretti reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>From pollution to policing – can Sadiq Khan clean up London? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110156/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 02:00:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110156/</guid><description>Podcast Description While training for the marathon, the London mayor developed adult-onset asthma – now he is on a mission to clean up the city’s air. But will his green policies win over voters?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why California is dismantling its death row | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110157/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 02:00:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110157/</guid><description>Podcast Description After decades locked alone in small cages in California’s San Quentin prison, men sentenced to die are now being moved off death row. Sam Levin investigates. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>National Conservatism: a Tory fringe or the party’s future? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110158/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 02:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110158/</guid><description>Podcast Description A conference run by a rightwing American thinktank attracted Tory MPs and influencers this week. Is its Trumpish populist philosophy a taste of where the Conservative party is heading?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Can Imran Khan really take on the Pakistani army and win? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110159/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 02:00:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110159/</guid><description>Podcast Description The former prime minister has blamed the country’s powerful military for his arrest last week, and his supporters have attacked military buildings. With Khan’s home surrounded by police yesterday, has he picked a battle he’s destined to lose?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Has Ukraine’s spring offensive begun? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110160/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 02:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110160/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ukrainian officials claim their forces have retaken land around the eastern city of Bakhmut and shot down Russian missiles targeting Kyiv. Luke Harding reports on the state of the war. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Erdoğan survives, but will Turkish democracy? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110161/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110161/</guid><description>Podcast Description Recep Tayyip Erdoğan, the president of Turkey, has moulded the country in his image during his two decades in power. Now he faces a run-off election to stay in power. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is the UK in the grip of ‘greedflation’? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110162/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 02:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110162/</guid><description>Podcast Description Prices in the UK are continuing to rise on everything from groceries to energy bills and mortgage costs. Meanwhile, some companies are reporting record profits. Richard Partington reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hosting Ukraine’s Eurovision party | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110163/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 02:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110163/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hannah Moore reports from Liverpool’s M&amp;amp;S Bank Arena where Britain is preparing to host the Eurovision song contest on behalf of last year’s winners Ukraine. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The killing of Shireen Abu Akleh – and another ordinary day in the West Bank | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110164/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 02:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110164/</guid><description>Podcast Description A year ago the renowned journalist was shot, but it was far from the only news story in Palestine that day. Kaamil Ahmed looks into the stories Abu Akleh never got to report. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Did distress calls go unanswered in the run-up to a fatal Channel disaster? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110165/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 02:00:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110165/</guid><description>Podcast Description In November 2021 a dinghy crossing from France to the UK overturned, and at least 27 people drowned. Questions are being asked over whether distress calls were effectively ignored in run-up to worst Channel disaster in 30 years. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why ‘godfather of AI’ Geoffrey Hinton thinks humanity at crossroads | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110166/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 02:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110166/</guid><description>Podcast Description His work is at heart of AI revolution, but in an interview with the Guardian’s Alex Hern, Hinton says he now fears the advances he helped usher in could pose an existential threat to humankind. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cotton Capital: the Guardian and reparations | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110167/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 02:00:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110167/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cotton Capital editor and Guardian journalist Maya Wolfe-Robinson looks at the subject of reparations. What do reparations mean for the communities and descendants of transatlantic enslavement – and what is the Guardian planning to do in its own programme of measures?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cost of the crown part 5: the coronation of Charles III | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110168/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 02:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110168/</guid><description>Podcast Description Charles III will be crowned in Westminster Abbey on Saturday in a ceremony steeped in centuries of history. Jonathan Freedland examines what the event means to the modern-day UK. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cost of the crown part 4: calculating the king’s wealth | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110169/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 02:00:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110169/</guid><description>Podcast Description Maeve McClenaghan and the reporting team reach the end of their investigation and make the calculations that reveal the vast personal fortune of King Charles III. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cost of the crown part 3: the hidden history of the monarchy and slavery | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110170/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110170/</guid><description>Podcast Description Documents recently unearthed by historians have shown how the British royal family had ties to transatlantic slavery. Maeve McClenaghan reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cost of the crown part 2: Duchies, diamonds and Dalis | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110171/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 02:00:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110171/</guid><description>Podcast Description Any attempt to understand the extent of royal wealth will need to account for the value of their land and their most valuable treasures. Maeve McClenaghan sets off to uncover what is held by the crown and what belongs to the family privately. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cost of the crown part 1: valuing the royal family | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110172/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 02:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110172/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the first part of an investigative miniseries into royal wealth, Maeve McClenaghan sets off on the trail to uncover how much public money is spent on the Windsors – and what they do in return. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Prince Harry and the return of the phone hacking scandal | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110173/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 02:00:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110173/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Prince Harry’s case over alleged phone hacking by the publisher of the Sun and News of the World reached the high court. Jim Waterson reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Funding, forensics – and a fridge freezer? The investigation into the SNP | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110174/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 02:00:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110174/</guid><description>Podcast Description Just a few months ago the SNP, with Nicola Sturgeon at the helm, looked almost untouchable. Now a fraud investigation into the party has caused that image to dramatically unravel. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why are London’s schools disappearing? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110175/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 02:00:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110175/</guid><description>Podcast Description London schools in areas such as Lambeth and Camden are having to close their doors as pupils leave. Why are numbers dropping so fast – and why does it matter so much?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A bullying politician or snowflake civil servants? The downfall of Dominic Raab | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110176/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 02:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110176/</guid><description>Podcast Description The former deputy prime minister may have resigned but he remains defiant after an inquiry into bullying allegations. What does the scandal tell us about the relationship between ministers and Whitehall?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Embracing a childfree life | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110177/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 02:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110177/</guid><description>Podcast Description Helen Pidd always thought she would have children, but after three unsuccessful rounds of IVF, she reimagines her life with the help of people who are childfree by choice. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Are we facing a summer of sporting protests? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110178/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 02:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110178/</guid><description>Podcast Description High-profile protests at the Grand National and the World Snooker Championships made headlines around the country; the London Marathon could be next. Sean Ingle and Damien Gayle report on what sporting stunts can achieve – and whether the authorities can stop them. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sudan’s warring generals | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110179/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 02:00:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110179/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fighting in Sudan is continuing despite an internationally brokered truce. At the heart of the conflict is a power struggle between two powerful generals in a country permanently in the grip of its military. Nesrine Malik reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The court case pushing Indian democracy to the brink – podcast | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110180/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 02:00:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Critics have long accused Narendra Modi of eroding the world’s biggest democracy. Now, ahead of next year’s general election, his main political rival could be jailed – for defaming the name Modi. What’s going on?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Pentagon leaks: how did US security files end up on Discord? – podcast | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110181/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 02:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110181/</guid><description>Podcast Description Earlier this year, hundreds of top secret Pentagon documents were posted on the social media platform Discord. Manisha Ganguly and Julian Borger report. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why are British audiences suddenly so out of control? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110182/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 02:00:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110182/</guid><description>Podcast Description From fights at the Bodyguard musical to wild drunken antics at comedy clubs and even heckling at the opera, performers and theatre staff say crowds are getting out of hand. What’s going on?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Investigating alleged sexual misconduct at the CBI | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110183/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 02:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110183/</guid><description>Podcast Description Police have launched an investigation into alleged sexual misconduct at the Confederation of British Industry in the wake of a recent Guardian investigation. Anna Isaac reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why has the Labour party turned nasty? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110184/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 02:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110184/</guid><description>Podcast Description The party’s latest ad campaign launches personal attacks on Rishi Sunak. What’s behind its new ruthless approach?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is artificial intelligence getting out of control? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110185/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 02:00:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110185/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hundreds of tech industry leaders have signed a letter proposing a six-month pause on the development of systems more powerful than OpenAI’s GPT-4. Alex Hern reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The ‘nice, ordinary’ family suspected of being Russian spies | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110186/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 02:00:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110186/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a couple and their children moved into a sleepy suburb of Slovenia’s capital, their neighbours thought they seemed very normal. But were they really who they seemed?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Xi Jinping and the battle over China’s memory of the Cultural Revolution | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110187/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 02:00:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110187/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mao’s Cultural Revolution pitted children against their parents and tore at the fabric of China’s society. It’s vital to the understanding of China today, says Red Memory author Tania Branigan. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>‘Peace babies’ and the birth of the Good Friday agreement | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110188/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 02:00:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110188/</guid><description>Podcast Description The generation born after the Good Friday agreement, which brought peace to Northern Ireland, are continuing to reckon with their inheritance. Mother and daughter Anne and Kerrie Patterson explain what it means to them. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Inside Tennessee, America’s most stringent anti-abortion state | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110189/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 02:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110189/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tennessee has an abortion ban so strict that even its Republican sponsors are having doubts about it. Stephanie Kirchgaessner reports on the reality of women’s rights in the state nine months after the supreme court struck down Roe v Wade. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why headteachers are fighting back against Ofsted inspections | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110190/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 02:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110190/</guid><description>Podcast Description The death of headteacher Ruth Perry after a devastating report from schools watchdog Ofsted has prompted a growing backlash. Michelle Sheehy, headteacher of Millfield primary school in the West Midlands, explains why. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The indictment of Donald Trump | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110191/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 02:00:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110191/</guid><description>Podcast Description The former US president will appear in a criminal court in New York City today to answer charges relating to campaign finance offences. Hugo Lowell reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cotton Capital: the bee and the ship – examining the Guardian’s links to slavery | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110192/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 02:00:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110192/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode one of the new Guardian podcast series Cotton Capital explores the revelations that the Guardian’s founding editor, John Edward Taylor, and at least nine of his 11 backers had links to slavery, principally through the textile industry. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How raising the retirement age set France on fire | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110193/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 02:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110193/</guid><description>Podcast Description An attempt to force through an increase in the state pension age brought thousands of protesters out on to the streets and has left Emmanuel Macron facing his biggest crisis yet. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why are British teenagers being locked up in ‘re-education camps’? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110194/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 02:00:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110194/</guid><description>Podcast Description Secretive centres that promise to change the behaviour of wayward western teenagers and young people have been springing up in Somalia. But what really goes on inside?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Who is Humza Yousaf and how will he change Scotland? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110195/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 02:00:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110195/</guid><description>Podcast Description For eight years Nicola Sturgeon towered over Scottish politics. Now there is a new first minister in charge, how will he make his mark?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>‘It’s way beyond just science’: untangling the hunt for Covid’s origins | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110196/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 02:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110196/</guid><description>Podcast Description Three years after much of the world was forced into Covid lockdowns, the precise origins of the virus are still hazy, and the hunt is bringing scientists into confrontation with political forces that many are not prepared for Read more: ‘Being truthful is essential’: scientist who stumbled upon Wuhan Covid data speaks out. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Exposing the myth of Britain’s ‘perfect’ war against Islamic State | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110197/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 02:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110197/</guid><description>Podcast Description The UK government continues to claim that there were no civilian casualties as a result of its bombing campaign against Islamic State militants in Iraq. Emma Graham-Harrison reports from Mosul on the evidence that cannot any longer be ignored. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trafficked: Marta - part four | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110198/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 02:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110198/</guid><description>Podcast Description The story of a Ukrainian woman who escaped modern slavery in the UK. Annie Kelly reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trafficked: the operation – part three | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110199/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 03:00:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110199/</guid><description>Podcast Description The story of a Ukrainian woman who escaped modern slavery in the UK. Annie Kelly reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trafficked: the closed door – part 2 | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110200/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 03:00:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110200/</guid><description>Podcast Description Julia, a Ukrainian woman who escaped modern slavery in the UK, tells the journalist Annie Kelly about the years she was shipped between brothels. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trafficked: the trap – part one | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110201/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 03:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110201/</guid><description>Podcast Description The story of a Ukrainian woman who escaped modern slavery in the UK. Annie Kelly reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Britain’s biggest police force is racist, sexist, and homophobic - can it change? – podcast | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110202/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 03:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110202/</guid><description>Podcast Description A landmark report into the Metropolitan police says discrimination is ‘baked in’ and trust in the force has plummeted. Is it worth trying to fix?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is it time to delete TikTok? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110203/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 03:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110203/</guid><description>Podcast Description Western governments are telling their staff to remove the popular social media app from their work phones amid security fears. Alex Hern reports on why time could be running out for TikTok’s current ownership model. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The accidental journalist who covered the war in Iraq | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110204/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 03:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110204/</guid><description>Podcast Description Twenty years on from the invasion of Iraq, Ghaith Abdul-Ahad and James Meek describe their chance first meeting and their time reporting on the war together. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How Eleanor Williams’ lies tore a town apart and finally unravelled | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110205/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 03:00:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110205/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why did Eleanor Williams, a young woman from a remote coastal town in England, pretend she was a victim of a grooming gang?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jeremy Hunt’s ‘back to work’ budget | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110206/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 03:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110206/</guid><description>Podcast Description The chancellor has put getting Britons back into work at the heart of his plan to grow the UK economy. But the danger signs are still flashing, reports Heather Stewart. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Who will replace Nicola Sturgeon as Scotland’s next first minister? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110207/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 03:00:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110207/</guid><description>Podcast Description The battle to replace Nicola Sturgeon is dividing the SNP and growing increasingly bitter, reports Libby Brooks. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The BBC’s spectacular own goal | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110208/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 03:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110208/</guid><description>Podcast Description A tweet by Gary Lineker led to his suspension by the BBC and set off a weekend of chaos in its schedules. Now with a truce agreed, Archie Bland reports on whether it can hold. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Who blew up the Nord Stream gas pipelines? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110209/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 03:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110209/</guid><description>Podcast Description Months after the covert sabotage mission that has been likened to a spy thriller, the net could be closing in on the perpetrators at the centre of the mystery. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is ‘Stop the boats’ a slogan without a solution? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110210/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 03:00:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110210/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rishi Sunak has promised to stop people crossing the Channel in small boats but his planned law has been called inhumane and unworkable. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Avian flu is decimating wild birds, but could it become a global pandemic? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110211/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 03:00:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110211/</guid><description>Podcast Description It is threatening rare species, and causing havoc for chicken farmers. Now a strain of bird flu has spread to mammals. Could it be a danger to humans?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rupert Murdoch and the lawsuit blowing open Fox News | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110212/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 03:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110212/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rupert Murdoch has been drawn into a defamation lawsuit brought against Fox News for spreading the conspiracy theory that the 2020 US election was rigged. Ed Pilkington reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What have we learned from Matt Hancock’s WhatsApp messages? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110213/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 03:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110213/</guid><description>Podcast Description More than 100,000 of the former health secretary’s phone messages have been leaked. What do they tell us about the way the government handled the pandemic?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The dawn of the four-day week | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110214/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 03:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110214/</guid><description>Podcast Description A growing movement to shorten the working week is gaining supporters, including bosses as well as employees. Heather Stewart reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Israel and the West Bank: a week of rage and rampage | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110215/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 03:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110215/</guid><description>Podcast Description Escalating violence by Israeli settlers in the occupied Palestinian territories is happening amid unprecedented anti-government protests. It’s no coincidence, reports Bethan McKernan. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What’s in the air in East Palestine, Ohio? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110216/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 03:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110216/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a train derailed in a small town in Ohio last month, it shed its toxic load, spewed smoke and set off a political firestorm that is still raging. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What the salad crisis says about Britain | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110217/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 03:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110217/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shoppers have been left staring at empty shelves and advised by their government to eat turnips over tomatoes. But the food shortage might be more serious than it sounds, reports Joanna Partridge. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is the Northern Ireland protocol deal a much-needed win for Rishi Sunak? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110218/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 03:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110218/</guid><description>Podcast Description The protocol led to the collapse of power sharing in Northern Ireland’s assembly – and empty supermarket shelves. So will the prime minister’s Windsor framework solve everything?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rewriting Roald Dahl | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110219/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 03:00:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110219/</guid><description>Podcast Description The latest editions of the author’s books for children have had extensive edits made to update the language for modern sensibilities. Lucy Knight and David Baddiel take a closer look. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Searching for the first casualty of the war in Ukraine | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110220/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 03:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110220/</guid><description>Podcast Description Daniel Boffey reports on the life and death of staff sergeant Denys Tkach, the first soldier to have been killed by Russian forces on the day of the invasion. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why did the search for Nicola Bulley turn so toxic? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110221/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 03:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110221/</guid><description>Podcast Description After the mortgage adviser disappeared TikTok detectives, grief tourists and the media descended. Now her family have hit out at the ‘appalling’ way they have been treated. What went wrong?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The secret world of disinformation for hire | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110222/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 03:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110222/</guid><description>Podcast Description How an undercover investigation revealed a team of Israeli contractors who claim to have manipulated more than 30 elections around the world using hacking, sabotage and automated disinformation on social media. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The new tactics of Britain’s far right | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110223/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 03:00:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110223/</guid><description>Podcast Description Far-right groups are mobilising in towns around the UK where asylum seekers are living in hotels. The protests are spreading – and turning increasingly aggressive. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The true cost of wood-burning stoves | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110224/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 03:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110224/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learning the full extent of the environmental damage caused by wood-burning stoves led Guardian columnist George Monbiot to issue a public mea culpa – and help ignite a raging debate. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Are chatbots coming for your job? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110225/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 03:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110225/</guid><description>Podcast Description A high-stakes race for supremacy in artificial intelligence is playing out between two of the world’s biggest tech companies. Should we be worried or excited? Chris Stokel-Walker reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nicola Sturgeon's resignation: the end of an era for Scotland | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110226/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 03:00:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110226/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Wednesday morning, Nicola Sturgeon called a press conference to announce she would be stepping down as the first minister of Scotland. Severin Carrell reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why is the Prevent counter-terrorism programme review so controversial? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110227/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 03:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110227/</guid><description>Podcast Description The UK scheme has long had its critics, but now even the review looking at how to overhaul it is facing criticism. Why is the debate around Prevent so heated?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why anger is growing in Turkey a week after catastrophic earthquakes | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110228/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110228/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s been an agonising time for survivors in Syria and Turkey – especially those whose relatives and friends are still trapped under rubble. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How a new treatment for diabetes offers hope for millions | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110229/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 03:00:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110229/</guid><description>Podcast Description The development of an ‘artificial pancreas’ could revolutionise the daily lives of people living with type 1 diabetes. Now the technology could be made available to more than 100,000 people in the UK on the NHS. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Could western tanks be decisive in Ukraine? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110230/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 03:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110230/</guid><description>Podcast Description After months of debate and diplomacy, western tanks are finally heading to Ukraine for what promises to be a spring escalation in the fighting. But will they be decisive? Dan Sabbagh and Daniel Boffey report. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Haiti: a country in crisis without an elected government | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110231/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 03:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110231/</guid><description>Podcast Description The last elected Haitian senators left parliament this month. Amid raging gang violence, the country is at breaking point with a health and hunger emergency. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why are more people in the UK turning to private healthcare? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110232/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 03:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110232/</guid><description>Podcast Description The NHS turns 75 this year, but as waiting lists for appointments grow, increasing numbers of patients are looking elsewhere for healthcare. Denis Campbell reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A deadly earthquake in Syria and Turkey | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110233/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 03:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110233/</guid><description>Podcast Description A 7.8-magnitude quake has struck Turkey and Syria, killing at least 2,600 people and razing entire neighbourhoods. Experts say it could not have happened at a worse time. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>After 17 years in prison, will Andrew Malkinson finally clear his name? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110234/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 03:00:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110234/</guid><description>Podcast Description Almost two decades ago Andrew Malkinson was accused of a rape where the victim was left for dead. He has always maintained his innocence and his supporters say the case against him was fatally flawed. Now he hopes new evidence will show he was not guilty. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The children going missing from Home Office hotels | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110235/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 03:00:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110235/</guid><description>Podcast Description More than 200 unaccompanied child asylum seekers have gone missing from hotels used by the Home Office. Mark Townsend reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Strikes, seatbelts and sleaze: Rishi Sunak’s first 100 days as PM | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110236/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 03:00:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110236/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rishi Sunak entered Downing Street promising to calm the markets and stop the scandals, but 100 days in it’s proving a bumpy ride, reports Pippa Crerar. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The scammers forced to steal people’s life savings | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110237/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 03:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110237/</guid><description>Podcast Description ‘Pig butchering’ crypto scams, where victims are wooed for months before being fleeced, are ruining people’s lives. But how are criminal gangs exploiting trafficking victims – and using fake UK firms – to steal millions of pounds?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How Putin’s chef became the second-most powerful man in Russia | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110238/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 03:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110238/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yevgeny Prigozhin went from hot dog seller to the commander of a private army fighting intense battles in Ukraine. But his rapid rise has made him a target, reports Pjotr Sauer. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The code of omertà: how a mafia kingpin evaded police for 30 years | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110239/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 03:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110239/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matteo Messina Denaro was arrested after decades on the run, found hiding in plain sight in Sicily. Lorenzo Tondo and Clare Longrigg report on what it means for the once mighty Cosa Nostra. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What is the teachers strike really about? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110240/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 03:00:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110240/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over the next couple of months, thousands of teachers are due to strike across the UK. What is the government doing in response to their demand for an above-inflation pay increase? Jessica Elgot reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why are women in Britain having to travel hundreds of miles to get an abortion? podcast | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110241/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 03:00:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110241/</guid><description>Podcast Description Record numbers of abortions are being carried out and services are struggling to cope. Why is the system under so much pressure and what toll is it taking on women?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What was behind Jacinda-mania – and why did it end so suddenly? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110242/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 03:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110242/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jacinda Ardern became a progressive icon around the world, but despite winning a rare parliamentary majority in New Zealand and gaining plaudits for her handling of Covid, the outgoing prime minister’s legacy is complicated, says Tess McClure in Auckland. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why is Scotland’s gender reform bill so contentious? | Podcast | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110243/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 03:00:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110243/</guid><description>Podcast Description The bill was supposed to streamline the way that people can apply to change their legal gender. So why has it sparked a constitutional crisis – and become a culture war battleground?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Exposing rainforest carbon credits: why offsetting isn’t working | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110244/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 03:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110244/</guid><description>Podcast Description A Guardian investigation has found that more than 90% of the carbon offsets verified by the company Verra did not reduce deforestation. Patrick Greenfield reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Biden, Trump and the classified documents | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110245/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 03:00:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110245/</guid><description>Podcast Description The discovery of batches of classified documents on Joe Biden’s property presents a headache for the president – but his case is quite different from that of Donald Trump, reports David Smith in Washington. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>David Carrick and the crisis of trust in British policing | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110246/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 03:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110246/</guid><description>Podcast Description The conviction this week of one of Britain’s worst sex offenders in recent history was accompanied by a staggering revelation: he was a serving police officer. Emine Sinmaz and Vikram Dodd report. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why are energy companies forcing their way into people’s homes? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110247/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 03:00:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110247/</guid><description>Podcast Description Energy companies have been granted warrants to forcibly switch customers on to pre-payment meters. What are the consequences for people struggling with their bills?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>China’s deadly coronavirus wave | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110248/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 03:00:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110248/</guid><description>Podcast Description Having spent much of the last three years with some of the world’s most strict Covid restrictions, China’s relaxing of its rules has coincided with a massive wave of infections just as the country prepares to celebrate the lunar new year. Tania Branigan reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Will the UK’s strict new voter ID laws damage democracy? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110249/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 03:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110249/</guid><description>Podcast Description For the first time, voters in May’s local elections will be required to show photo ID before casting their ballot. But as Peter Walker reports, the new rules risk damaging the integrity of elections, not enhancing it. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jailed for life for stealing $14 | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110250/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 03:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110250/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Coulson was imprisoned in California under draconian ‘tough on crime’ laws stemming from the 1990s. Now campaigners are calling for reform, reports Sam Levin. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How a far right assault on Brazil’s democracy failed | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110251/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 03:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110251/</guid><description>Podcast Description The effort to overturn the election of the Brazilian president was thwarted but the attack has shaken an already divided country, reports Tom Phillips. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Prince Harry’s memoir: why has the ‘Spare’ gone rogue? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110252/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 03:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110252/</guid><description>Podcast Description In his explosive memoir he claims Prince William physically attacked him, his family leaked stories about him – and even reveals how he lost his virginity in a field. But why is the prince telling all, and what will it mean for the royal family?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What has Brexit done for Britain? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110253/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 03:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110253/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brexit, Britain was promised, would allow the country to ‘take back control’ – of its economy, its borders and its land. But what has that really meant for people now living with its consequences?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mouldy flats and bidding wars: how did the UK rental crisis get so bad? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110254/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 03:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110254/</guid><description>Podcast Description According to 2021 census data, 5m households in England and Wales are private renting. We ask why renting is getting more expensive and precarious. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Will Donald Trump finally face criminal charges for January 6? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110255/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 03:00:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110255/</guid><description>Podcast Description After interviewing 1,000 witnesses and compiling an 800-page report, the inquiry into the assault on the Capitol is complete. But what will it mean for Donald Trump in 2023 – and his presidential bid?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The arrest of Andrew Tate: the ‘king of toxic masculinity’ | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110256/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 03:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110256/</guid><description>Podcast Description He calls himself a misogynist – and has millions of followers. Now the former kickboxer from Luton turned social media star has been arrested on charges that include human trafficking. What happened?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Can you breathe your way to feeling better? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110257/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 03:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110257/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Guardian’s parliamentary sketch writer, John Crace, and breath coach Rebecca Dennis describe how they have used breathing techniques to help their mental health. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Culture 2023: our picks for film, TV, music and art | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110258/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 03:00:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110258/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Guardian’s arts editor Alex Needham, music and features writer Sam Wolfson, and film critic Ellen E Jones, on what they’re looking forward to this year. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Can I tell you a secret? Episode seven: an update | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110259/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 03:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110259/</guid><description>Podcast Description Revisited: Guardian producer Lucy Hough and reporter Matthew Weaver give an update on the outcome of Matthew Hardy’s appeal. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Can I tell you a secret? Episode six: the winding clock | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110260/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 03:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110260/</guid><description>Podcast Description Revisited: As the years tick by, journalist Sirin Kale speaks to victims and those who know Matthew to ask whether his stalking will ever truly end. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Can I tell you a secret? Episode five: a mother’s love | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110261/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 03:00:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110261/</guid><description>Podcast Description Revisited: Journalist Sirin Kale meets Matthew Hardy’s mother to uncover more about his past – and what may have motivated him to cyberstalk his victims for so long. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Can I tell you a secret? Episode four: a reckoning | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110262/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 03:00:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110262/</guid><description>Podcast Description Revisited: Matthew Hardy’s victims come face to face with him as an attempt is made to stop the torment once and for all. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Can I tell you a secret? Episode three: the man upstairs | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110263/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 03:00:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110263/</guid><description>Podcast Description Revisited: who is Matthew Hardy? Journalist Sirin Kale looks for clues about what motivates this cyberstalker to create chaos and fear in so many people’s lives. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Can I tell you a secret? Episode two: the widening circle | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110264/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 03:00:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110264/</guid><description>Podcast Description Revisited: As the cyberstalker spreads his net wider, anyone could be a target. The fast-changing world of social media creates new opportunities for him to find more victims. But now someone is watching him. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Can I tell you a secret? Episode one: the beginning | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110265/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 03:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110265/</guid><description>Podcast Description Revisited: Guardian journalist Sirin Kale takes us to a small town in the north of England to uncover how one man began a decade of cyberstalking. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How the Guardian covered 2022 | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110266/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 03:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110266/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Guardian’s editor-in-chief, Katharine Viner, talks about how the newspaper covered a year that witnessed war in Europe, three UK prime ministers, the death of the Queen and a winter of industrial strife. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Christmas in Kyiv | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110267/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 03:00:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110267/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kyiv residents this year are facing the holiday season expecting blackouts and missile attacks. Isobel Koshiw reports from Ukraine’s capital. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The career criminal who became a prison correspondent | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110268/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 03:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110268/</guid><description>Podcast Description The late Guardian journalist Eric Allison spent more than two decades uncovering and writing about abuses in the British justice system. But for almost 50 years before that he was a forger and a thief. What made him give up his life of crime?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The bribery scandal rocking the EU parliament | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110269/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 03:00:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110269/</guid><description>Podcast Description Belgian police have seized wads of banknotes worth more than €1m in a series of raids that have plunged the EU parliament into its worst corruption scandal. Jennifer Rankin reports from Brussels. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Three prime ministers and a funeral: Marina Hyde’s political year | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110270/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 03:00:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110270/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Guardian’s award-winning columnist Marina Hyde picks over the political year. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The ‘prince’ and the plot against Germany – podcast | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110271/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 03:00:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110271/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you heard the one about the former paratrooper, politician and ‘prince’ who walk into a hunting lodge and allegedly plot to overthrow the German government? Philip Oltermann in Berlin explains why it was no joke. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>33 hours on the frontline of the NHS | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110272/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 03:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110272/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Covid pandemic has eased, so why is the health service facing its worst winter yet? And how is it coping with endless waiting lists, a staffing crisis and strikes?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The age of extinction: can we prevent an ecological collapse? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110273/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 03:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110273/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Cop15 conference in Canada brings together representatives from all over the world with an urgent mission: preventing the breakdown of Earth’s natural habitats and the extinction of the many species we rely on. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Should you freeze your eggs? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110274/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 03:00:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110274/</guid><description>Podcast Description Since egg freezing became available to anyone who could afford it a decade ago in the UK it has increased tenfold. But are clinics transparent with women about their chances of a successful pregnancy?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Building for end times: the boom in bunkers | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110275/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 03:00:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110275/</guid><description>Podcast Description Threat of nuclear war and a global pandemic have spurred a boom in individuals purchasing survival bunkers, says author Bradley Garrett. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The artists defying Putin’s war on Ukrainian culture | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110276/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 03:00:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110276/</guid><description>Podcast Description From poetry to pop music, Ukrainians are using art to take a stand against Russia – and Putin’s assault on their identity. From dancers to documentary makers, they explain how work they have created in the conflict zone is a weapon of resistance. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why are so many workers going on strike? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110277/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 03:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110277/</guid><description>Podcast Description From posties to paramedics, the list of professions taking industrial action seems to keep growing. But will it lead to better working conditions – or just bring the UK to a standstill?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What’s gone wrong with England’s water? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110278/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 03:00:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110278/</guid><description>Podcast Description More untreated sewage is being pumped into England’s seas and rivers than ever before. Sandra Laville follows the money to find out who is responsible. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The far-right radical in Israel’s new government | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110279/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 03:00:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110279/</guid><description>Podcast Description Itamar Ben-Gvir has spent a lifetime on the fringes of Israeli politics. He was once considered so extreme that he wasn’t allowed to serve in the Israeli army. Now he is the country’s security minister. Bethan McKernan reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Michelle Mone lobbied for PPE Medpro. But was she enriched by its profits? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110280/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 03:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110280/</guid><description>Podcast Description During the early weeks of the pandemic, the government was scrambling to find protective clothing for health workers. The Tory peer recommended one supplier to the government – but how far did her links with it go?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The young people speaking out against the Universal Church of the Kingdom of God | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110281/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 03:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110281/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rachael Reign was an active member of an evangelical Christian church with branches worldwide. It was only after leaving that she came to believe it had exposed her to a ‘horrendous’ ordeal. Maeve McClenaghan reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Imprisoned for being HIV positive | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110282/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 03:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110282/</guid><description>Podcast Description In more than 80 countries, people living with HIV still face criminalisation. We hear from two people who faced criminal charges in the US. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How far could China’s ‘zero Covid’ protests go? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110283/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 03:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110283/</guid><description>Podcast Description China has been rocked by an outpouring of communal anger at the government’s restrictive ‘zero Covid’ lockdown policies. Could the protests develop into something more substantial? Tania Branigan reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The crypto-collapse: inside the crazy world of FTX | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110284/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 03:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110284/</guid><description>Podcast Description The cryptocurrency exchange FTX collapsed earlier this month, leaving billions of dollars unaccounted for. Alex Hern explores what happened and where the money went. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How dangerous is it to live in a damp, mouldy home? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110285/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 03:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110285/</guid><description>Podcast Description The death of two-year-old Awaab Ishak from exposure to mould has shown the consequences of uninhabitable homes. But how many people are living in similarly unhealthy conditions and what can be done to protect their health?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Inside Qatar 2022: the World Cup of politics and protest | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110286/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 03:00:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110286/</guid><description>Podcast Description Football’s governing body Fifa has tried to keep politics out of the World Cup – but there has never been a more political tournament, reports Michael Safi in Doha. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is a second referendum on Scotland’s independence further away than ever? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110287/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 03:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110287/</guid><description>Podcast Description The supreme court has ruled that the Scottish parliament cannot hold a second referendum without Westminster’s approval. Where does that leave the independence movement?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trump v DeSantis: how ex-president’s fan could be his biggest rival | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110288/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 03:00:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110288/</guid><description>Podcast Description Florida governor Ron DeSantis passionately praised the former president – now he is being talked about as a possible presidential candidate himself.. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cop27: another blow to 1.5C? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110289/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 03:00:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110289/</guid><description>Podcast Description At Cop27 in Egypt, negotiations ran 40 hours past the Friday night deadline. Country delegates were able to agree a historic deal on loss and damage, but less progress was made on global fossil fuel emission targets. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Beyond 8 billion: why the world’s population matters | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110290/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 03:00:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110290/</guid><description>Podcast Description The world now contains 8bn people, according to the UN. Hannah Ellis-Peterson reports from India, which is on course to overtake China as the most populous nation. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Excitement, boycotts and rainbow protest: Qatar’s World Cup kicks off | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110291/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 03:00:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110291/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 2022 tournament is finally here. But for more than a decade, disquiet over the Gulf state hosting football’s biggest event has been growing. Four people – with very different perspectives – explain their views. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Autumn statement 2022: it’s going to hurt but will it work? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110292/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 03:00:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110292/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Guardian’s economics editor, Larry Elliott, looks ahead to Jeremy Hunt’s crucial autumn statement, which is set to usher in a new era of austerity, and explains why is likely to fail just like George Osborne’s before it. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Reclaiming Kherson: what Russia’s retreat means for the fight for Ukraine | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110293/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 03:00:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110293/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ukrainians have reacted with jubilation after retaking Kherson city and the region around it. But what did living under Russian occupation do to the area and its people – and is this really the beginning of the end of the war?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is the UK housing market heading for a crash? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110294/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 03:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110294/</guid><description>Podcast Description A steady stream of bad economic news has filtered into Britain’s property market, prompting fears that prices could tumble. But how worried should people be? Rupert Jones reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The mystery of Teesside’s dead crabs | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110295/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 03:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110295/</guid><description>Podcast Description When thousands of crabs started washing up on the beaches of Teesside in north-east England, authorities blamed algae in the water. But the fishers watching their livelihoods disappear weren’t buying it. Joshua Kelly reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cop27: the future is solar, but it won’t be simple | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110296/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 03:00:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110296/</guid><description>Podcast Description As Joe Biden arrives at Cop27 in Egypt, he comes with a good story to tell on America’s transition to renewable energy. But on the ground in rural Indiana where the country’s biggest solar plant is being built, things are getting nasty. Oliver Milman reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Iran’s protest generation on why they won’t be silenced | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110297/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 03:00:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110297/</guid><description>Podcast Description There have been arrests, violence and a rising death toll during more than seven weeks of protests in Iran. Demonstrators across the country – many of whom are students or even schoolchildren – are refusing to back down. What do they want and why are they willing to risk everything to get it?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What the scandal at Manston asylum centre says about our migration system | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110298/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 03:00:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110298/</guid><description>Podcast Description For the last six weeks conditions at a centre housing people who made perilous journeys across the Channel on small boats have been making the headlines. The home secretary, Suella Braverman, has pointed the finger at a ‘broken’ system. But why is the Home Office so often at the centre of a crisis?. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item><item><title>US midterms: is it still the economy, stupid? | Today in Focus</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6225110299/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 03:00:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6225110299/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Democrats have learned hard lessons over the years about what happens when election campaigns neglect the economy, so has the party been strong enough in its messaging for today’s midterm elections? Lauren Gambino reports. Help support our independent journalism at theguardian.com/infocus
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>