<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/just-one-thing-with-michael-mosley/</link><description>Recent content in Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/just-one-thing-with-michael-mosley/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Happiness Special – with Dr Rangan Chatterjee | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460001/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this series of special editions of BBC Radio 4 podcast Just One Thing, Michael Mosley quizzes the world’s leading health experts on the best ways to live well. In this Happiness Special we hear from Dr Rangan Chatterjee - GP, host of successful podcast “Feel Better, Live More” and author of numerous best-selling books including “Happy Mind, Happy Life”.
We hear the top tips that Dr Chatterjee swears by to improve and maintain good mental health and wellbeing.</description></item><item><title>Cold Therapy - Ep 5: Sleep and the Cold | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460002/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460002/</guid><description>Podcast Description There’s a chill in the air as the winter months come around again. But the cold isn’t always something to fight or guard against. With a little bit of care, you can invite the cold into your life - with real benefits for health and mood. In each episode of this new podcast series, Dr Michael Mosley uncovers the science behind a different way you can harness the power of the cold, alongside the very latest research and atmospheric sound design.</description></item><item><title>Cold Therapy - Ep 4: Cold Water Swim | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460003/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460003/</guid><description>Podcast Description There’s a chill in the air as the winter months come around again. But the cold isn’t always something to fight or guard against. With a little bit of care, you can invite the cold into your life - with real benefits for health and mood. In each episode of this new podcast series, Dr Michael Mosley uncovers the science behind a different way you can harness the power of the cold, alongside the very latest research and atmospheric sound design.</description></item><item><title>Cold Therapy - Ep 3: Cold Exercise | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460004/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460004/</guid><description>Podcast Description There’s a chill in the air as the winter months come around again. But the cold isn’t always something to fight or guard against. With a little bit of care, you can invite the cold into your life - with real benefits for health and mood. In each episode of this new podcast series, Dr Michael Mosley uncovers the science behind a different way you can harness the power of the cold, alongside the very latest research and atmospheric sound design.</description></item><item><title>Cold Therapy - Ep 2: Cold Recovery | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460005/</guid><description>Podcast Description There’s a chill in the air as the winter months come around again. But the cold isn’t always something to fight or guard against. With a little bit of care, you can invite the cold into your life - with real benefits for health and mood. In each episode of this new podcast series, Dr Michael Mosley uncovers the science behind a different way you can harness the power of the cold, alongside the very latest research and atmospheric sound design.</description></item><item><title>Cold Therapy - Ep 1: Colder Room | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460006/</guid><description>Podcast Description There’s a chill in the air as the winter months come around again. But the cold isn’t always something to fight or guard against. With a little bit of care, you can invite the cold into your life - with real benefits for health and mood. In each episode of this new podcast series, Dr Michael Mosley uncovers the science behind a different way you can harness the power of the cold, alongside the very latest research and atmospheric sound design.</description></item><item><title>Welcome to Cold Therapy - with Michael Mosley | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460007/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460007/</guid><description>Podcast Description There’s a chill in the air as Dr Michael Mosley uncovers the surprising power of the cold to enhance your health and wellbeing in ways you might not expect.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Listen to Music | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bring on the tunes! In this episode, Michael explores the power of music, from reducing pain to forging strong family relationships. Neuroscientist Dr Psyche Loui from Northeastern University in Boston reveals how just eight weeks of music listening can change activity in the brain, impacting our reward centres in our brain, and why this could be important for healthy ageing. Our volunteer Roberta has a go at “mindful” music listening with an eclectic range of music from Bollywood music to opera.</description></item><item><title>Walk Backwards | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Step out - backwards! The Chinese have a saying that 100 steps backwards are worth 1000 steps forward - and they might be onto something! It may look bizarre to onlookers, but Michael delves into the research and finds some surprising benefits. It’s been used for decades in rehabilitative physical therapy, and recent research reveals that it could even boost memory - by giving your brain a workout! Michael also speaks to biomechanics expert and champion of backwards walking, Professor Janet Dufek from the University of Nevada, Las Vegas, whose research suggests that walking backwards could help with lower back pain.</description></item><item><title>Have a Laugh | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460010/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Laughter really is good medicine. From releasing pain-killing endorphins to improving your memory, laughter can have many benefits on your body and brain - it’s even been shown to boost “gamma” brainwaves, which are associated with higher level brain processes, like learning and memory. In this episode, Michael shares a chuckle with cardiologist Professor Michael Miller from the University of Pennsylvania in the US to discuss how laughter can help your heart health, keep your blood vessels young, and be the antidote to stress.</description></item><item><title>Embrace the Rain | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460011/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get that brolly out! It may feel deeply counter-intuitive - but rainy days could offer a host of health and mood-lifting benefits. Rain improves air quality, literally washing fine particulate pollution away, and rainfall also releases Geosmin, a fragrant compound which is linked with relaxation and increased serotonin levels. What’s more, Professor Michael Terman, from Columbia University in New York, introduces Michael to negative air ions created after rainfall.</description></item><item><title>Reheat Pasta | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Load up on those leftovers - because it’s surprisingly easy to make your bowl of pasta better for you! In this episode, Michael uncovers how reheating carb-heavy foods actually boosts the resistant starch in them. Resistant starch is a healthy carb that can benefit your gut, reduce blood sugar spikes and lower your cancer risk. Dr Darrell Cockburn, Assistant Professor of Food Science from Penn State University, reveals how these carbs can benefit your microbiome.</description></item><item><title>Practise Pilates | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460013/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460013/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s a low-impact, low-intensity exercise that can make you stronger, more flexible, and benefit your posture and balance. It’s proven to reduce lower back pain and it can even enhance your exercise performance! No surprise that tennis star Andy Murray uses it in his training routine. In this episode, Pilates expert Professor Ruth Melo from the University of San Paulo reveals all about the benefits of Pilates on our cardiovascular endurance, core strength and healthy ageing.</description></item><item><title>Breathe Through Your Nose | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Take a nice deep breath in… through your nose. It’s a simple way to get healthier gums, a better memory, and improved lung function. How? Well, it may partly be due to a special molecule called nitric oxide. Michael Mosley speaks to Professor Jon Lundberg from the Karolinska Institute in Sweden who made the fascinating discovery that nitric oxide is produced in your nose and travels to your lungs where it has some surprising benefits, including boosting oxygen uptake and possibly helping you fight off infections.</description></item><item><title>Cook Tomatoes | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tomatoes are packed full of goodness &amp;amp; cooked tomatoes are even better for you! In this episode, Michael reveals how cooking your tomatoes - sautéed, or in a sauce or soup - can reduce your blood fat levels, help your body recover from exercise, and even protect your skin from damage. It’s all to do with a beneficial compound called lycopene which is released under heat. Michael speaks to Professor Richard van Breemen from Oregon State University who reveals his studies on lycopene and why cooked tomatoes can help protect against prostate cancer.</description></item><item><title>Swim | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michael Mosley ventures to his local pool and the sea to explore the unique benefits of going for a swim - from improving memory and mental agility, to boosting longevity. Professor Hirofumi Tanaka, from the University of Texas at Austin, reveals why water-based exercises like swimming are especially good for improving the elasticity of your blood vessels and a new way to exercise in the pool. There really seems to be something special about being in the water that can help your heart, improve joint pain and even boost your brain.</description></item><item><title>Have a Cup of Tea | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michael gets cosy with a cuppa to find out how drinking tea can boost your heart health, reduce stress and may even benefit your bones! With the help of Professor Andrew Steptoe, Head of Behavioural Science at University College London, Michael learns the surprising benefits of ordinary tea. They discuss the benefits of bioactive compounds in tea, including L-theanine and polyphenols. A tasty brew can not only help you recover from stress, it can even benefit your heart health and reduce inflammation…Meanwhile, our volunteer Kit enjoys adding more tea to her life.</description></item><item><title>Stay Young - Ep 5: Stay Strong | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460018/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 08:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michael explores the best way to help you look younger as well as live longer and healthier – revealing how strength training can benefit your waistline, preserve muscle fibres and increase healthy lifespan.
Pumping up your muscles is one of the best ways to protect from the ravages of time and injury. In this episode, Michael speaks to Professor Abigail Mackey from the University of Copenhagen in Denmark, to find out how resistance training can strengthen the connection between your brain and muscles, and keep them looking younger at the cellular level.</description></item><item><title>Stay Young - Ep 4: Stay Feeling Good | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 08:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michael reveals the best food to boost your mood, your energy levels, reduce inflammation and improve your immune system. In this episode, Michael discovers the benefits of fermented foods and their live bacteria. He speaks to Professor Justin Sonnenburg from Stanford University who’s recent clinical trial revealed that eating fermented foods can increase your gut microbiome diversity and reduce inflammation, one of the main drivers of ageing. They discuss the role of your gut bacteria in increasing the activity of key immune cells with knock-on effects across the body, and why a healthy gut microbiome is so important for feeling good.</description></item><item><title>Stay Young - Ep 3: Stay Sharp | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 08:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Want to get the mental sharpness of someone decades younger? Challenging your brain with something difficult, like learning a new language or taking up juggling, can trigger your brain to form new connections, increasing your brain’s white matter and making it more resilient against age-related decline. In this episode, Michael speaks to Dr Rachel Wu from the University of California Riverside who has discovered that learning three new skills at the same time can significantly boost the memory in older adults - so much so that they performed as well as someone 50 years younger in a series of cognitive tests.</description></item><item><title>Stay Young - Ep 2: Stay Looking Young | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460021/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 08:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460021/</guid><description>Podcast Description How a simply dietary change can reduce wrinkles, improve skin texture and slow ageing. In this episode Michael reveals how a daily portion of colourful fruit and vegetables can help retain skin moisture and boost collagen. Carotenoids are compounds that give carrots, mangoes and tomatoes their bright red and orange colour – and they have been shown to boost your skin’s collagen and moisture, improving wrinkles, skin plumpness and texture.</description></item><item><title>Stay Young - Ep 1: Stay Fit | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 08:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Exercise is one of the best things you can do to rejuvenate yourself at the cellular level – but what’s the best way to do it? In this episode, Michael speaks to Associate Professor Matt Robinson from Oregon State University, who has discovered that just a few minutes of high-intensity exercise can help rejuvenate you at the cellular level, by helping restore your mitochondria, your cell’s energy powerhouses. They discuss how exercise has many benefits across your body - from your muscles, to your heart, your brain and even your skin!</description></item><item><title>Welcome to Stay Young - with Michael Mosley | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460023/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 09:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460023/</guid><description>Podcast Description In his new podcast series, Dr Michael Mosley reveals simple things you can do to rejuvenate yourself from the inside out.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Food Special with Tim Spector | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Professor Tim Spector, a leading expert on nutrition and gut health, takes Michael Mosley through his top food and nutrition tips, sharing stories from his life and research along the way. Joined by an audience at the Hay Festival, Michael learns what happened the time Tim convinced his son to eat an ultra-processed food diet for two weeks and the surprising ways your gut influences your immune system. Tim, who is professor in epidemiology at King's College London, shares the shocking moment he realised that even as a doctor, he was on track for major health problems, and how he took control over his diet and his health - and how you can, too.</description></item><item><title>Write It Out | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460025/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460025/</guid><description>Podcast Description When things go wrong, you might think that focusing on the bad and writing about them would make things worse. But in some cases, the opposite seems to be true.
Michael Mosley investigates a technique called “expressive writing”, a simple tip which can have surprising benefits for your health. The idea is to set aside 15 minutes to write about any worries that keep you up at night, showing many benefits - from improving lung function in people with asthma, to improving scores on exams and cognitive tests.</description></item><item><title>Try Some Turmeric | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460026/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Turmeric is a close relative of ginger – it has a similar knobbly root-like stem. The golden-hued powder of turmeric adds colour and flavour to food, but it’s also been linked to some surprising health benefits. As well as helping with wound healing and skin conditions, it’s been linked to better brain health. Michael Mosley speaks to Dr. Benny Antony from the University of Tasmania in Australia who has found that turmeric extract was as effective as ibuprofen to reduce pain levels.</description></item><item><title>Nibble Some Nuts | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460027/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nuts are a rich source of fibre and polyphenols. They are also very high in fats and calories, but studies have shown that eating these bite-sized snacks won’t add to your waistline. These nutrient powerhouses could also help slow-down the ageing process. Research has found that walnut eaters live, on average, over a year longer than those who don’t. What’s more, adding nuts to your diet can help your brain!</description></item><item><title>Lift Some Weights | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lifting weights is obviously great for your strength, but it can also boost your brain power, improve your immune system, and even reverse signs of cellular ageing. Michael enlists Jenny, a self-confessed weight-lifting novice, to try strength training at home using milk bottles and a sturdy rucksack. He speaks to Dr. Teresa Liu-Ambrose at the University of British Columbia, Canada, who has recently found that strength training can lead to better memory.</description></item><item><title>Clean Your Teeth | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460029/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Taking good care of your teeth can prevent tooth decay and boost your oral health - but, surprisingly, the benefits extend well beyond your mouth. Keeping your teeth and gums clean can help your heart and your brain, reducing the risk of diseases from diabetes to dementia. To find out why, Michael Mosley speaks to Dr. Sim Singhrao from the University of Central Lancashire School of Dentistry. She reveals bacteria in your mouth can travel from your gums into your blood causing problems in other organs, including your brain.</description></item><item><title>Put Your Phone Down | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460030/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Most of us in the UK use our phones for over three hours/day! They are incredibly useful - but using them just a little bit less can have big benefits for your health and wellbeing. Studies have shown that reducing your phone use by one hour each day can reduce symptoms of depression and anxiety. It can also increase life satisfaction, reduce smoking and enhance physical activity levels. On top of that, limiting social media use to 30 minutes a day has been found to reduce feelings of loneliness.</description></item><item><title>Choose Red Wine | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460031/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460031/</guid><description>Podcast Description All alcohol is bad for you but if you’re already a drinker, switching out your usual drink with a small glass of red wine could bring surprising benefits to your health - improving blood sugar and fat levels and reducing the risk of diabetes. In this episode, Michael Mosley speaks to Dr Tim Spector, Professor of Epidemiology at King’s College London to find out about the secret ingredient in red wine.</description></item><item><title>Try Tai Chi | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460032/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460032/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you’re looking to add more exercise into your lifestyle why not consider Tai Chi. It’s an ancient Chinese martial art – it’s sometimes called “meditation in motion”. It’s a series of different postures that gently flow into each other in slow movements. One of the big benefits to Tai Chi is that it can significantly enhance the activity of our immune system. And although it looks gentle, it can be a surprisingly good workout!</description></item><item><title>Reach Out | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460033/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460033/</guid><description>Podcast Description It turns out having friends has big benefits for your health. Fascinating research shows social contact can boost your immune system and your brain power. In this episode, Michael Mosley is joined by Professor Pamela Qualter from Manchester University, who explains how reaching out in the simplest of ways - from sending a simple text to helping your neighbours - can significantly reduce loneliness levels, helping you feel more connected and a part of a community.</description></item><item><title>Swap Out Sugar | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460034/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cutting back on free sugars can not only do wonders for your waistline and your oral hygiene, surprising research shows it could also improve your memory and help your brain. But it can be hard to resist those sugar cravings! In this episode, Michael Mosley is joined by Dr Evelyn Medawar from the Max Planck Institute for Human Cognitive and Brain Sciences, who has been studying the effects of our gut microbiome on our eating preferences, and reveals a potential tip to help crack sugar cravings.</description></item><item><title>Sleep Well - Ep 5: Listen to your body | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460035/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 18:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get comfortable, let go of the cares of the day and take a sonic journey with Dr Michael Mosley. In this new sound-filled podcast series, designed to help you drift off, each episode focuses on a scientifically-proven sleep technique and takes a deep dive through some incredible sleep-related bodily mechanisms.
With sleep - because one size doesn’t fit all - you can benefit by listening more to your body and letting go of expectations.</description></item><item><title>Sleep Well - Ep 4: Warm up to cool down | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460036/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get comfortable, let go of the cares of the day and take a sonic journey with Dr Michael Mosley. In this new sound-filled podcast series, designed to help you drift off, each episode focuses on a scientifically-proven sleep technique and takes a deep dive through some incredible sleep-related bodily mechanisms.
Discover a simple hack for the temperature-related, sleep-preparing systems of the body. Plus dilating blood vessels, shapeshifting and taking a hot bath.</description></item><item><title>Sleep Well - Ep 3: Enjoy your bed | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460037/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 18:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get comfortable, let go of the cares of the day and take a sonic journey with Dr Michael Mosley. In this new sound-filled podcast series, designed to help you drift off, each episode focuses on a scientifically-proven sleep technique and takes a deep dive through some incredible sleep-related bodily mechanisms.
There are some simple yet powerful steps you can follow to form new and positive connections around bedtime habits, your bed, and sleep itself.</description></item><item><title>Sleep Well - Ep 2: Use the morning light | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460038/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 18:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get comfortable, let go of the cares of the day and take a sonic journey with Dr Michael Mosley. In this new sound-filled podcast series, designed to help you drift off, each episode focuses on a scientifically-proven sleep technique and takes a deep dive through some incredible sleep-related bodily mechanisms.
The light of the morning can be a powerful ally when it comes to the evening and falling asleep.</description></item><item><title>Sleep Well - Ep 1: Breathe | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460039/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get comfortable, let go of the cares of the day and take a sonic journey with Dr Michael Mosley. In this new sound-filled podcast series, designed to help you drift off, each episode focuses on a scientifically-proven sleep technique and takes a deep dive through some incredible sleep-related bodily mechanisms.
It’s something that the great teachers of meditation and yoga have known about and used for millennia, but science has only really just caught up with: slowing the breath.</description></item><item><title>Welcome to Sleep Well with Michael Mosley | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460040/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 21:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr Michael Mosley introduces his new sound-filled series, designed to help you drift off.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Take a Break | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460041/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460041/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Michael reveals why adding regular breaks to your day can benefit your body, your mind and even your productivity. What’s more, if you allow your mind to wander freely during your breaks - no social media! - the benefits are even greater. Michael speaks to cognitive neuroscientist Professor Moshe Bar from Bar-Ilan University in Tel Aviv to find out exactly what goes on in our brains when we allow our minds to wander, and why it could be a good thing for mood, problem solving and creativity.</description></item><item><title>An Apple a Day | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460042/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460042/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Michael delves into the surprising research on the humble apple, revealing how it can help your heart, gut, and brain. He speaks to Dr Catherine Bondonno from Edith Cowan University in Australia to find out how and why simply eating more apples could reduce risk of dying early by up to 35%! They discuss what apples can do to our gut bacteria and blood vessels to keep them healthy.</description></item><item><title>Read | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460043/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460043/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Michael enters the world of creative fiction to discover how simply reading a story for half an hour a day can bring big benefits to your body and brain - from reducing stress and helping stave off depression, to strengthening your social skills and even helping you live longer! With the help of Professor Raymond Mar from York University in Toronto, Canada, Michael discovers why reading for pleasure could have such a significant impact on overall health and longevity, and delves into research revealing the unique benefits of reading narrative fiction.</description></item><item><title>Meditate | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460044/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Michael uncovers the secret of mindfulness - how just a short mindful meditation a day can enhance your mood, your immune system and your brain. Our willing volunteer Peter has a go at ten days of daily mindfulness practice, and Dr Sara Lazar from Harvard University expertly guides Michael through the mechanisms by which meditation can train your attention, improve working memory, and even rewire your response to physical pain.</description></item><item><title>Enjoy Oily Fish | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460045/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460045/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Michael speaks to nutritional neuroscientist Dr Simon Dyall from the University of Roehampton to get to the bottom of the many benefits behind oily fish and Omega-3s. He finds out how consuming Omega-3 could affect your mood, your brain and even your walking speed! They discuss the different types of oily fish, other sources of Omega-3 fatty acids, revealing why these fatty acids are so important.</description></item><item><title>Drink Coffee | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460046/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Coffee drinkers rejoice! Did you know that a simple cup of coffee can improve your mood, boost your workout and even stimulate your brown fat, helping you burn calories? In this episode, Michael Mosley finds out all the benefits of our beloved bean - with research suggesting that it could help your brain and heart. What’s more, if you time it right, a simple cup of coffee could help you get more out of your workout and could even change the way you break down fat.</description></item><item><title>Dance | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460047/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460047/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Michael gets out his dancing shoes &amp;amp; shines some light on the many benefits of dancing, revealing that dancing has been shown to be BETTER than traditional fitness exercises for improving your muscles, your balance and even the size of your brain. He speaks to professional-ballet-dancer-turned-neuroscientist Dr Julia F Christensen at the Max Planck Institute in Frankfurt, to find out how dancing can improve our balance and coordination, and trigger new connections in our brain, while our volunteer Lorne has a go at adding some disco dancing to her everyday routine.</description></item><item><title>Take a Nap | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460048/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michael reveals how getting some shut-eye during the day could boost your memory and your heart health - and even help your productivity! Research reveals that a simple daily nap could slash your risk of heart attack by half, and have a noticeable impact on your brain, by helping improve your emotional control and boosting memory. In this episode, our volunteer Caroline catches some Zzzs in between work meetings, while nap expert Dr Sara Mednick delves into the different stages of sleep, telling Michael when to nap, and for how long, for the greatest benefit.</description></item><item><title>Eccentric Exercise | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460049/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460049/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Michael reveals how the part of your workout that often feels easier - running downhill after a brutal run up to the peak, or lowering down weights rather than lifting them up - is one of the quickest ways to improve your strength and enhance your workout. It’s the flip side of a lot of movements you’ve already been focused on. To find out more, he speaks to Prof Tony Kay at the University of Northampton who delves into the bizarre benefits of Eccentric Exercise.</description></item><item><title>Eat Beetroot | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460050/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460050/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Michael explores the extraordinary effects of beetroot on your body and brain – from helping lower blood pressure to keeping your brain healthy as you age. He speaks to Professor Andy Jones from the University of Exeter who has found that simply drinking a shot of beetroot juice can improve your endurance during intense exercise by 16%, and finds out why these bright red jewels can have such significant benefits on your heart, your muscles and your brain.</description></item><item><title>Stand Up | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460051/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460051/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are sitting more than ever before - and our sedentary lives are having a big impact on our long-term health. In this episode, Michael stands up to the allure of the couch and reveals the science behind how just standing up - without even doing any exercise - can burn more calories and lower blood sugar levels. With Dr John Buckley, Michael explores how the experience of astronauts in space proves how important the force of gravity is on our bodies - and how standing up can help keep our bones and muscles strong.</description></item><item><title>Drink Water | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460052/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Did you know that even mild dehydration can have damaging effects to your cognition, mood, and physical and mental performance? But drinking litres of plain water every day isn’t necessarily the solution. In this episode, Michael debunks the many myths about how much water we should drink, and enlists the help of Dr Stuart Galloway, Professor of Exercise Physiology from the University of Stirling, to reveal how much water we need, how to avoid the negative effects of mild dehydration, and how drinking water with every meal may even help to lose weight.</description></item><item><title>Think Yourself Stronger | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460053/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pumping iron in the gym is the only way to improve strength, right? Wrong. In this episode, Michael explores the power of the mind to boost strength by up to 24%... Our willing human guinea pig Tom has a go at improving his goal-shooting skills with his mind, and Michael speaks to cognitive neuroscientist Dr Helen O’Shea to reveal how your thoughts can influence your muscles and why it’s surprisingly similar to doing the actual thing.</description></item><item><title>Get Some Houseplants | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460054/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Not only do they look good, but surprising research is revealing the health benefits of houseplants. In this episode, Michael Mosley explores the science, discovers which houseplants have the biggest impact, and reveals just how many you need in a room to feel the effects. Michael speaks to Dr Tijana Blanusa of the Royal Horticultural Society, to explore the science behind how houseplants can not only improve productivity and cognition at work, they can also improve air quality, helping you literally breathe easier.</description></item><item><title>Sing | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460055/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ever noticed how good singing makes you feel? In this episode, Michael is joined by comedian Sindhu Vee to embrace the joys - and health benefits - of singing on the top of your voice. He finds out all about its unique mood-lifting ability and how singing can produce similar effects to cannabis. He speaks to Dr Daisy Fancourt to find out about her research on revealing how singing can boost your immune system and how it could help treat chronic pain.</description></item><item><title>Play Video Games | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460056/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you struggle with multi-tasking, filtering out distractions, and prioritising your to-do list? Believe it or not, video gaming might help. In this episode, Michael Mosley enters the world of gaming to find out how it can benefit our brains! He enlists the help of cognitive neuroscientist Professor Daphné Bavelier to find out how, to Michael’s surprise, video games could actually help improve our vision and what types of features we should look out for when we play.</description></item><item><title>Change Your Mealtimes | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460057/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can’t face cutting down on your favourite foods? In this episode, Michael Mosley speaks to Dr Emily Manoogian from the Salk Institute in California to find out how simply changing when you eat - not what you eat - could help you lose weight, lower your blood pressure and cut your risk of Type 2 diabetes. They reveal what exactly happens when your eating times work against your body’s internal rhythms, and why eating late at night can stop you from going to sleep.</description></item><item><title>Exercise Less, More Often | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460058/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460058/</guid><description>Podcast Description It can be hard to fit a full workout into every day - but it turns out you really don’t need to! In this episode, Michael enlists the help of Marie Murphy, Professor of Exercise and Health at Ulster University, to explore why doing short bursts of exercise can actually be more beneficial than a hard gym session. A brisk 10-minute walk here, taking the stairs there, and it really does add up.</description></item><item><title>Eat Chocolate | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460059/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Could eating two squares of dark chocolate a day really help you reduce your risk of cardiovascular disease - and enhance blood flow to your brain? In this episode, Michael Mosley champions the wonders of chocolate. With the help of Professor Aedín Cassidy at Queen's University Belfast, he reveals the secret ingredients behind the benefits and why we should start to embrace the bitter taste of high cocoa chocolate.</description></item><item><title>Get Some Sun | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460060/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460060/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Michael reveals the power of the sun’s rays to lower blood pressure and improve your mood, bones, muscles and immune system. He challenges TV presenter Mehreen Baig to sunbathe herself healthy, and speaks to Professor Ann Webb at the University of Manchester to shed new light on how going out in the middle of the day is the best way to boost your Vitamin D, and how to do it safely depending on your skin type.</description></item><item><title>Count Your Blessings | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460061/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 12:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Surprisingly simple ways to boost your health and wellbeing - in one easy step.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hot Bath | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460062/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460062/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Michael takes a long soak in the bath, and explores why it might be good for our heart, metabolism and sleep. He speaks to one of the UK’s leading sleep experts, Professor Jason Ellis, Director of the Northumbria Sleep Centre, to find out why a hot bath a couple of hours before bed can help us get to sleep. They discuss the interplay of responses in your brain and body that work together to get your body ready for rest - and why a hot bath one to two hours before bed can help kick start the process… Crucially, it is not the warm, relaxing bath that’s important, but what happens afterwards.</description></item><item><title>Take A Breath | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460063/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460063/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Michael reveals how slowing down and focusing on your breath can have a wide-reaching effect on your body and brain - from reducing pain, to improving concentration. He speaks to psychologist and neuroscientist Professor Ian Robertson, from Trinity College Dublin, who’s discovered how taking just a couple of seconds to control your breath can act as a powerful reset button for your brain.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Stand On One Leg | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460064/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460064/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Michael is reborn as a one legged yogi to reveal why the one leg stance is one the best thing you can do for a longer and more active life. He speaks to Professor Dawn Skelton at Glasgow Caledonian University, to find out what happens to your balance as you get older, why our balance is getting worse with each generation, and how regularly making yourself wobble could help improve your body and your brain.</description></item><item><title>Green Spaces | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460065/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michael explores the science behind the soothing power of nature, revealing how nature not only makes us feel good in the moment, but how it also has a more lasting effect on our stress levels and our mental health. Michael speaks to Professor Ming Kuo at the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign, who has been looking into the surprising ways nature could be having an effect on your immune system and mind.</description></item><item><title>Intelligent Exercises | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460066/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460066/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Michael reveals the best exercises you can do – to help your heart and your brain. He now does press ups every morning – having discovered research that shows being able to do 10 could help you live longer, and doing 40 nearly doubles your protection against heart disease. But strength exercises can do more than just improve your muscle tone and heart. Michael speaks to Professor Damian Bailey at University of South Wales who’s been researching the effects of exercise on your brain.</description></item><item><title>Learn a New Skill | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460067/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460067/</guid><description>Podcast Description From easing your nerves to improving concentration, in this episode Michael explores the hidden brain benefits of taking up a new hobby. He finds out why learning a new skill is one of the best things you can do for mental agility and speaks to Professor Alan Gow at Heriot-Watt University to discover the best - and most fun - ways to keep your brain active, and how taking on a new challenge could help build new connections in your brain, whatever your age!</description></item><item><title>Cold Shower | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460068/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 10:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michael delves into the science of cold water immersion, revealing how just a little bit of physical stress might go a long way to improve your heart health, boost your mood and help keep colds and flu at bay. To find out more, he speaks to Professor Mike Tipton from Portsmouth University who’s been researching exactly what happens in your body when you’re doused with cold water, and why it might have a positive impact on your body and brain, with lasting effects.</description></item><item><title>Eat Some Bacteria | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460069/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 16:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460069/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Michael speaks to expert Kirsten Berding Harold, University College Cork, for all the latest science on all things good bacteria. Our willing human guinea pig Clare has a go making her own kefir at home and Michael has a go at cultivating some healthy bacteria in the form of sauerkraut - which he claims is far simpler to make at home than you might think!</description></item><item><title>Early-Morning Walk | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460070/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michael explores the secret power of early-morning light, revealing the surprising ways it can affect your brain to boost your mood and help get a better night’s sleep. But it’s not just when you go that’s important… He speaks to Marie Murphy, Professor of Exercise and Health at Ulster University, who’s shown how a simple change to the way you walk could cut your risk of heart disease by 20-50%.</description></item><item><title>Welcome to Just One Thing with Michael Mosley | Just One Thing - with Michael Mosley</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8261460071/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 15:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8261460071/</guid><description>Podcast Description If time is tight, what’s the one thing that you should be doing to improve your health and wellbeing? Michael Mosley introduces his new series in which he reveals surprisingly simple tips that are scientifically proven to change your life.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>