<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/2-bears-1-cave-with-tom-segura-bert-kreischer/</link><description>Recent content in 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 13:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/2-bears-1-cave-with-tom-segura-bert-kreischer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Charitable Endeavors | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 216 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260218/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260218/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on 2 Bears, 1 Cave, Bert shares some phone sex tips from his private FaceTime sessions. They try out some new lip stuff that was gifted to Bert from the Philadelphia Flyers. Bert also introduces Tom to the Roast Beef Challenge. Tom and Bert then talk about their experiences at some recent basketball games and a UFC fight, before getting into their latest charitable endeavor involving Habitat for Humanity.</description></item><item><title>Stavros Halkias | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 215 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260217/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260217/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on 2 Bears, 1 Cave, Tom is joined by comedian Stavros Halkias who&amp;rsquo;s here to make the bear cave fat again! They talk about Greece, mafia movies, fat guy math, doing comedy specials in Austin and foreign family members. Tom shares some discoveries about his family history and the duo bond over their appreciation of steaks and dogs, before searching for a new Religious wife for Stavros!</description></item><item><title>2 Bears vs 2 Kelces | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 214 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260216/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260216/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome back to another episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave! This week Tom and Bert throw down a challenge gauntlet for fellow podcasters and football players Jason and Travis Kelce! The Bears discuss the type of competition they&amp;rsquo;d issue to the Kelce brothers and draw lines in the sand between the different communities that would be in their corners. They talk Taylor Swift, the influence of Swifties and the BeyHive, relatable athletes, top 5 female music artists of all time, and even get a call from Pat McAfee!</description></item><item><title>What Kind of Car is Your Wife? | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 213 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260215/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260215/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome back to another episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave. This week, Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer discuss the subtle art of beard dyeing, grooming near the groin, midlife crisis energy and much more! Plus, Bert shares some sober realizations he&amp;rsquo;s had recently while being &amp;ldquo;California sober&amp;rdquo;, and reveals to Tom how he&amp;rsquo;s felt being a little bit lighter. The Bears also debate what type of car their wives are, the greatness of Michael Jordan, gorgeous football players, and discuss why being present is so satisfying.</description></item><item><title>The Bears Are Back | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 212 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome back to another episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave. This week, Bert and Tom are back in the studio for some much needed catching up! They discuss Bert&amp;rsquo;s new healthy habits and then immediately try out nicotine pouches. Tom shares a story about why he&amp;rsquo;s the &amp;ldquo;Master of Finding Missing Items&amp;rdquo; and Bert recollects all the cruise ship insanity from &amp;ldquo;Fully Loaded at Sea&amp;rdquo;. The bears also talk about Bert&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;new girlfriend&amp;rdquo;, not getting enough credit for good deeds, dark algorithms on Instagram, life advice from jacked dudes, taking Tom Segura&amp;rsquo;s family on adventures, and Bert&amp;rsquo;s crush on Josh Hartnett!</description></item><item><title>The Crazy World of Steve-O | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 211 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to another episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave. This week, Bert Kreischer is joined by guest bear Steve-O. They discuss Steve-O’s new special, the start of his entertainment career, his Jackass co-stars, his time in rehab, what it means to be happy, and much more. They also talk on the phone to Mike “Cowhead” Calta, and Dr. Drew Pinsky.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bombing In Front Of De Niro w/ Colin Quinn | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 210 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260003/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave, Colin Quinn joins Tom to discuss some of their most horrific bomb stories. Colin also talks about working at SNL, his favorite (and least favorite) SNL hosts, and some pretty wild Chevy Chase stories. Tom is convinced that drunks ruin shows and Colin wants to pitch a new idea to Bert for his standup. Other topics include: one man shows, “resetting” a bad audience, and how MTV used to be cool.</description></item><item><title>John Stamos Was Bullied For His Looks | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 209 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260004/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260004/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of 2 Bears 1 Cave, John Stamos joins Bert to talk about fame, getting sober, and The Beach Boys. Stamos also opens up about being bullied for his looks and the loss of Bob Saget. The two discuss Don Rickles, the Olsen twins, burning bridges, and the importance of giving it your all. Other topics include: General Hospital, Howard Stern, and family. Tom comes up quite a bit, as well.</description></item><item><title>The Dark Side of Clean Comedy w/ Sam Morril | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 208 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Morril joins Tom Segura for this week’s episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave. They discuss Michael Jordan and the NBA, having to do clean comedy and the dark sides of clean comedians, some of their favorite movies, gambling in Atlantic City, Woody Allen, their writing processes, Tracy Morgan, Tom’s dad Top Dog, Greg Giraldo, Tom’s experience flying with the Blue Angels, and the flight that had to land because a woman had diarrhea on the plane.</description></item><item><title>The Rise of Matt Rife | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 207 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tom Segura is joined by guest bear Matt Rife for this week&amp;rsquo;s episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave. They discuss Matt&amp;rsquo;s meteoric rise to fame, Matt&amp;rsquo;s time on Wild &amp;rsquo;n Out, Netflix comedy specials vs. YouTube comedy specials, crowd work and hecklers, dealing with negative feedback, Matt plans to buy his mom a house, and much more!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What Will Make Bert Less Fat? w/ Layne Norton | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 206 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260007/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Layne Norton is the founder of fitness coaching company BioLayne, a powerlifter, bodybuilder, and author. He joins Tom Segura to discuss powerlifting, bodybuilding, testosterone replacement therapy, stress management, the ketogenic diet, how unhealthy diet soda actually is, why people are obese, and wraps up by discussing Bert Kreischer’s new healthy lifestyle.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>From Hip Hop to Stand-Up w/ Cipha Sounds | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 205 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260008/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave, Cipha Sounds joins Bert as a guest bear to talk about his journey from DJ to stand-up comedian. The two discuss sobriety and how being easy to work with will get you far in this industry. They also talk New York hip hop, the death of Tupac, and Cipha’s new TV show Hip Hop Treasures, which sounds awesome. There’s also a conversation about religious sex and a move called “soaking.</description></item><item><title>Seducing Taylor Swift | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 204 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260009/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260009/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on 2 Bears, 1 Cave, Tom and Bert kick off the episode with their recent interactions with musicians. Bert saw Metallica and Tom&amp;rsquo;s been talking with Oliver Anthony. They go on to talk about some of the biggest names in music: Ed Sheeran, Taylor Swift, and James Hetfield. Bert has a revelation about donating to GoFundMe. Tom and Bert switch lanes into a little sports talk, then baller foods.</description></item><item><title>2 Bears, 2 Great Minds w/ Andrew Huberman &amp; Cory Henry | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 203 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome back to another episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave! This week, Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer are joined by neuroscientist Andrew Huberman and jazz musician Cory Henry. The four of them discuss how music affects the brain, Bert’s recent decision to get healthy, how dopamine works, swimming with great white sharks, Tom’s basketball injury, whether or not Stevie Wonder can sing, anxiety, sleep apnea, sobriety, David Goggins, and much more!</description></item><item><title>Bears vs. Wild Animals | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 202 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260011/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome back to another episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave! This week Tom and Bert discuss which wild animals they could beat in a fight, getting spray tans, seeing Metallica in concert, donating to charity, Kevin Hart&amp;rsquo;s accident, racing, what makes someone a real artist, Taryn Manning, Bert&amp;rsquo;s new diet, and much more!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sober Bert | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 201 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome back to another episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave. This week, Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer discuss their favorite radio shows and podcasts, Scientology, how Peru lost Machu Picchu, what it takes to be an ambassador, and much more! Plus, Bert went to Jazzfest, and saw some of his favorite artists perform, and found some new favorites. Also, Bert is deciding to get sober to help ease his crazy schedule!</description></item><item><title>Episode 200 Spectacular | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 200 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260013/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260013/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s the 200th episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave, and Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer got each other some awesome gifts to celebrate! Tom shows Bert Kevin Leonardo’s infamous “Nair Hair Removal” video, and Bert discusses having Covid 7 times, history, cancel culture, luxury tour buses, and much more!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>I Almost Died | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 199 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260014/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s another week of 2 Bears 1 Cave with the OG bears Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer! They bears start off with sharing how they recently dealt with conflict resolution between them, spray tans, the worst picture of Bert yet, and the Just For Laughs Comedian of the Year award. The bears see if you can cure stinky body parts, they discuss surfing, and Tom shares a story of how he almost drowned.</description></item><item><title>Beer Olympics | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 198 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260015/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we bring you 2 Bears 1 Cave with Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer… in 4K! The bears are back in their Austin den and Bert tells Tom all about The Beer Olympics hosted by Bussin’ With The Boys, surrounded by ELITE athletes like Taylor Lewan, David Bakhtiari, Michael Chandler, and Shane Gillis. Tom then shares with Bert that their overweight producer, Nadav, has been challenged and is training for the NYC Marathon.</description></item><item><title>Wildest Shark Attacks w/ Theo Von | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 197 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260016/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we have a very special 2 Bears 1 Cave with Tom Segura and guest bear Theo Von! They discuss having sunglass options, old school comedians with gimmicks, Matt Rife, and the evolution of getting on TV shows. They talk about Ole Miss and LSU College Football. They discuss how money has the potential to demotivate you and the feeling of making people laugh.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rob Lowe's Incredible Life | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 196 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bert Kreischer is joined by guest bear Rob Lowe on this week’s episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave! Rob discusses being famous in the 80s, growing up with other movie stars in Malibu, golf, watch collecting, transcendental meditation, and much more! He also share stories about Cary Grant, “Unstable,” “The Outsiders,” and “Rumble Fish,” gives advice on making a “first move,” and discusses moving out of L.A. to Santa Barbara.</description></item><item><title>Fun With Chloroform | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 195 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer are back together in the bear cave. They discuss beard grooming, staying in shape, some of their favorites bites and drinks, car accident videos, and much more! They have fun with the FaceApp, give an update on 2 Bears Racing, ponder buying chloroform, and call Dr. Drew for his guidance on it.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Knives and Fights w/ Joel McHale | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 194 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to another episode of 2 Bears 1 Cave with Bert Kreischer and guest bear Joel McHale! They talk about their heads, hair and health along with taking the testosterone plunge. They talk about work ethic, narcissism, auditioning together for The Office and some Bud Light commercials. They share their bad reviews with each other, Bert lost his joke book, and they trade stories about their families. Joel talks a bit about his early career as a college football player, and the two talk about dogs Bert wasn’t allowed to get, funerals and Steve Harvey.</description></item><item><title>Flying Death Traps | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 193 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260020/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s a week of 2 Bears 1 Cave with your favorite bears Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer! They start off with talking about Bert’s distrust in Doctor Quacks, terrifying hot air balloons, Bert’s current struggles that he should discuss with a therapist and some wild food adventures. They discuss their kids, chloroform and fun challenges and what state would be the most fun to move to. They trade stories about their first times with girls, talk about sexual fluidity throughout history and talk about the next possible 2 Bears Live!</description></item><item><title>The Content Machine w/ Kountry Wayne | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 192 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260021/</guid><description>Podcast Description We have another episode of 2 Bears 1 Cave with Bert Kreischer and guest bear Kountry Wayne. Kountry tells us about his 10 kids, growing up selling cocaine, and loving food. They talk about women, Kountry Wayne’s journey, cars and music. Kountry Wayne sheds some light on his content and what it was like to work with Lil’ Boozy and TI. They talk about Kountry’s character “Drip,” how it compares to Bobcat Goldthwait, and how Kountry developed an audience.</description></item><item><title>Bert's Blow Up w/ Ari Shaffir | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 191 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260022/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on 2 Bears 1 Cave we have Tom Segura and guest bear Ari Shaffir! They discuss language, how main landers partake in open defecation and their own human dumps. They discuss some Israeli behaviors, Ari’s YouTube special, singers that fell from grace, and traveling in South America and Australia. They talk about how awesome it would be to be gay, and they discuss Mark Normand’s bachelor party where Bert Kreischer had a bit of a meltdown.</description></item><item><title>Is Squirting Real? | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 190 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260023/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s a classic episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer and Bert gets right into the only thing on his mind at the moment: Squirting isn’t real. They talk about some weird fan interactions they’ve had and how they interact with celebrities they admire. They discuss taking chances on certain jokes, tough languages, releasing movies in China, and learning how to say very cool things in Arabic.</description></item><item><title>Plus-Size Accommodations w/ Tim Dillon | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 189 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260024/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s another episode of 2 Bears 1 Cave with Tom Segura and guest bear Tim Dillon! Tim explores what his political platform would be for 2024, North Korean way of life, and what murder feels like, allegedly, and the Austin serial killer. They discuss wildly inappropriate politicians, Tim’s new book, and how horrible cruises are. They discuss accommodations for fat people, trans racial folks, and Tim Dillon’s incredible ability for creating great content.</description></item><item><title>The Machine Premiere | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 188 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260025/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s another week of 2 Bears 1 Cave with the OG bears Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer! Bert&amp;rsquo;s movie &amp;ldquo;The Machine&amp;rdquo; just came out and you should go see it in theatres! They talk about the making of the movie, Tom surprising Bert at the premiere, fun stories about working with Iva Babić, Mark Hamill, Arnold Schwarzenegger and Mark Wahlberg. Bert recalls how good some famous people at the premiere were great at interacting with people, and how it&amp;rsquo;s completely different from Joe Rogan&amp;rsquo;s energy, there own energy and Jason Mamoa.</description></item><item><title>Flooring It w/ Ryan Blaney | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 187 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260026/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260026/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on 2 Bears, 1 Cave Tom Segura is here to talk to his guest bear, American professional stock car racer who competes full time in the NASCAR Cup Series driving the #12 Ford Mustang for Team Penske, Ryan Blaney! Tom learns about how Ryan got into pro racing, Ryan learns about Tom’s love of cars, and Ryan shares some hilarious Michael Jordan stories. Ryan shares the differences between the different skill levels of racing, racer Josh Williams who walked across the track in protest, touring routines, Talladega Nights, and how they hung out in Daytona at the Indy 500.</description></item><item><title>Make Hollywood Fun Again w/ Kevin Smith | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 186 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260027/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260027/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s 2 Bears 1 Cave with Bert Kreischer and guest bear, cult classic director, producer and podcaster, Kevin Smith! The bears discuss the business of podcasting, how Kevin experimented with live shows, and The Machine. They talk about a new chapter of Hollywood, Ben Affleck, and Kevin opens up about his recent mental breakdown. They share insights about workaholism, family life overlapping with their work, pop tarts, doing cocaine on accident and heart attacks.</description></item><item><title>The Dream Team w/ Ryan Sickler | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 185 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260028/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260028/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s another episode of 2 Bears 1 Cave with Tom Segura and guest bear, comedian and podcaster, Ryan Sickler! They talk about how wild the stories on Sickler&amp;rsquo;s patreon is, discuss sex parties and share their most embarrassing sports moments. They share wild stories of Larry Bird talking trash, the Dream Team, and OJ Simpson. They talk about famous athletes with AIDs, freak athletes, trade coach stories and discuss athletes who smoke and party.</description></item><item><title>The Monarchy Sucks w/ Jim Jefferies | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 184 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260029/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260029/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on 2 Bears 1 Cave Bert Kreischer welcomes guest bear Jim Jefferies! They discuss serial killers, Australia, and a having a bad sense of smell. They discuss Brad Pitt, Austin Butler, Tom Holland and accents. They discuss Jim’s new TV show and try to see how well Bert would do on it. They discuss the Royal Family, the comedy terrorist, top tier American and foreign comedians, and Jimmy Carr’s attempted cancelation.</description></item><item><title>Women Have It Good w/ Yannis Pappas | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 183 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260030/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tom Segura is joined by guest bear Yannis Pappas on this week’s 2 Bears, 1 Cave. They discuss the old times, speeding, homelessness, exclusivity and wait for things, their experiences in therapy, and how Yannis is cheating on his therapists, and very cool guys Greg Hardy, Ray Rice, Woody Allen, and Bernie Madoff. Yannis also shares the story of how he got shot, and his experience recovering from it.</description></item><item><title>Testosterone Bears | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 182 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260031/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260031/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s another classic episode of 2 Bears 1 Cave with Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer. Bert is trying to update his wardrobe, how much weight change affects looks, and if it has the potential to change a fat comedian’s act. Tom injects Bert with (doctor prescribed) testosterone, the discuss what tattoos they’re going to get on their newly ripped bodies, and how jacked some athletes used to be. They discuss plane crashes, health and longevity,</description></item><item><title>Crazy Ex-Girlfriends w/ Big Jay Oakerson | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 181 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260032/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to another episode of 2 Bears 1 Cave with Tom Segura and guest bear Big Jay Oakerson! Go check out his new comedy special “Dog Belly” on YouTube right now! Tom and Jay talk about the chaotic Ari Shaffir, the shameless Bert Kreischer, and the confident Kevin Hart. They trade stories about TSA encounters, Jay shares stories about coming up with Kevin Hart, getting broken up with and getting caught cheating.</description></item><item><title>Rise of the Comedians | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 180 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260033/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260033/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s a classic episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer! The bears talk about touring in Latin America, men getting dressed, and how much Bert loves Testosterone. They talk about Fast and the Furious franchise, naming a standup special, The Machine movie. They reminisce about cutting each other’s hair and try to figure out if they’d get hair transplants.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bert’s Biggest Fears | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 179 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260034/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer are back together in the bear cave for this episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave! They discuss flying on private jets, Bert’s experience getting pranked by Andrew Schulz on Flagrant, both of their biggest fears, funny family stories, filming comedy specials, hanging with NFL players, and more! Plus, they watch a clip of Machine Gun Kelly confronting Sam Tripoli research patron saints for Tom to choose, and reveal some of their favorite comedians.</description></item><item><title>Chrissy New Glasses w/ Chris Distefano | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 178 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260035/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Go catch Chris at The Theater at MSG in NYC on September 23rd. Get tickets at https://chrisdcomedy.com/tickets.
Chris Distefano joins Tom Segura as a guest bear in Bert Kreischer’s place this week! Tom and Chris discuss, Chrissy’s new look, weight loss, the effects of social media, Chris’ new show “Super Maximum Retro Show”, and much more! Chris also shares some hilarious stories about his dad, Tampa Tony, meeting Steven Tyler and Phil Collins, as well as a wild story about an argument Chris witnessed.</description></item><item><title>Bonus: Live from MGM Grand in Las Vegas | 2 Bears, 1 Cave | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260036/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260036/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode of 2 Bears 1 Cave was filmed in front of a live audience of MGM Rewards Members at the MGM Grand in Las Vegas. It&amp;rsquo;s a bonus episode of 2 Bears 1 Cave live on Saint Paddy&amp;rsquo;s Day! We start with a dental update from Tom, Bert reveals his affinity for HBCU Cheerleading videos, and Bert expresses how no one can love Tom like Bert does. They discuss their testosterone usage, Taylor Lewan from Bussin&amp;rsquo; with the Boys invites Bert to Beer Olympics, and Bert talks about Ila jokes he had removed from his Netflix Special Razzle Dazzle.</description></item><item><title>Losing Your Virginity w/ Adam Devine | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 177 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260037/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adam Devine joins Bert Kreischer in Tom Segura’s place for this week’s episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave. Bert and Adam discuss Mardi Gras, losing their virginity, making movies, improvising, their career goals, working with Danny McBride, Zac Efron, and Pete Davidson, doing edibles and mushrooms, and much more!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Awful Radio Shows w/ David Cross | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 176 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260038/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260038/</guid><description>Podcast Description We got special guest bear David Cross guest-bearing with Tom Segura this week. Go Catch David on “The Worst Daddy In The World Tour” and get tickets at officialdavidcross.com
They discuss how important it is to pick the person you bring on comedy tours with you so they can eat the leftovers you don’t like. They trade morning radio horror stories, H. Jon Benjamin, Brendon Walsh, Mr. Show with Bob and David, and the Increasingly Poor Decisions of Todd Margaret.</description></item><item><title>TikTok Fiasco w/ Howie Mandel | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 175 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260039/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260039/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week’s episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave Bert Kreischer is joined by Howie Mandel in Tom Segura’s place. They discuss Howie’s TikTok fiasco, watching yourself on TV, how Bert Orders takeout, Julius Caesar, their worst haircut stories, and more! Throughout, the two come up with jokes, and Bert wraps up the episode by running them by his wife LeeAnn.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Daily Stoic w/ Ryan Holiday | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 174 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260040/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to another episode of 2 Bears 1 Cave with Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer! Today, Ryan Holiday fills in as a guest bear! Ryan Holiday is the best-selling author of &amp;ldquo;Trust Me, I&amp;rsquo;m Lying&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;The Obstacle is The Way&amp;rdquo;, and other famous books. Tom and Ryan discuss the origins of philosophy, the four cardinal virtues, and their significance to obtaining, and maintaining, a prosperous lifestyle. They relive their days as struggling artists and share their mutual, yet individual experiences in becoming famous for their respective art.</description></item><item><title>Dana's World w/ Dana Carvey | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 173 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260041/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bert Kreischer is joined by Dana Carvey sitting in for Tom Segura on this week’s 2 Bears, 1 Cave. Dana and Bert discuss Dana’s upbringing, his lesser known films, their mutual fear of flying, “Wayne’s World,” their health, Johnny Carson, luck and success, Winston Churchill and Hunter S. Thompson’s indulgent days and much more!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sexual Athlete w/ Adriana Chechik | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 172 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260042/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260042/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s a special episode of 2 Bears 1 Cave with Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer and special guest cub, Adriana Chechik! Adriana tells us a little bit about her recent back injury at Twitch Con, some differences between her personal and professional sex life, and tips to prep for back action. The bears ask Adriana about BTS scenes on sites, Only Fans advice, her career as a stripper, how to prep for a DP and how to deal with newcomers.</description></item><item><title>Bears Guide To Life | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 171 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260043/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer unite for another episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave! The bears talk about how Tom tried surfing, Bert embarrassing Tom in front of Tony Hawk, and embracing doing activities while touring. They discuss people that eat bad food while unhealthy, Testosterone replacement therapy, and how every dude should be getting their clothes tailored. They try to figure out how to make their fans live forever, where they would disappear after they retire from standup comedy, and talk about being really into cars.</description></item><item><title>You're Not A Skater! w/ Tony Hawk | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 170 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260044/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260044/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Tony Hawk joins Bert Kreischer as a guest bear! Bert starts the episode off by letting his daughters ask Tony questions, then Bert and Tony get into surfing, skate injuries, the relationship between comedy and skating, Tom’s basketball injury, the best old school skaters, Bert’s new movie “The Machine,” and much more!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Laugh Hard w/ Louis C.K. | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 169 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260045/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260045/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s 2 Bears, 1 Cave and Bert Kreischer welcomes guest bear Louis CK! They discuss growing up, faith, and David Goggins. They trade their views on living and dying, testing amusement park rides, and old commercials and TV shows. Bert educates Louis on quicksand content, Louis recalls making Patrice O’Neal and David Letterman laugh, and Bert asks when Louis changed his comedy style. Louis talks about his fall from the peak and live streaming his next comedy special from MSG on his website.</description></item><item><title>Body Hacks w/ Andrew Huberman | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 168 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260046/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260046/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s another episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura and guest bear, Professor Andrew Huberman! They talk about Huberman’s rough and tough upbringing, psychedelics, and cannabis. Huberman gives some insight on brain function, tobacco use, supplements, and performance enhancement drugs. They discuss clean training, teaching while podcasting, explaining the need for sun light and good sleeping habits. They discuss importance of appearance, getting obsessed with stuff like Joe Rogan, and cold plunges.</description></item><item><title>I Will Out Live You! | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 167 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260047/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome back to another episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave! This week Tom and Bert share their wildest stories of visiting Europe, discuss why South Africa got mad at Bert, their feelings about money and success from comedy, what the most successful actors have in common and more! They wrap up by pondering how long Bert will live, which leads into a conversation about their fathers.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Drugs All Day | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 166 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260048/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy new year and welcome back to 2 Bears 1 Cave with Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer! They talk about surgeries, Tom translates Bert&amp;rsquo;s plane conversation, and Kurt Cobain. The Jewish community reacts to Bert&amp;rsquo;s Hitler cup, Bert shares a story about his wife, and the bears trade accidental smuggling stories. They describe their perfect day of drugs, discuss Bert&amp;rsquo;s self awareness, and fitness. Bert then pitches Tom one of his best ideas: 2 Bears 1 Coach, where they interview coaches like Jimmy Johnson, Coach Prime and Phil Jackson.</description></item><item><title>The Hottest Instagrams | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 165 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260049/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260049/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s another week of 2 Bears 1 Cave with Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer! We start with Bert learning about numbers in other languages, they talk about countries they would run away to, and Bert really considers starting an Only Fans page. Tom then shows Bert a WILD loophole some Instagram models found and they look up the girlfriends of George Clooney, Chris Hemsworth, Henry Cavil. They talk about Nate Diaz and freak athletes like Barry Sanders and Charlie Ward.</description></item><item><title>Jacked w/ Kumail Nanjiani | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 164 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260050/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260050/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on 2 Bears 1 Cave, Bert Kreischer welcomes guest bear Kumail Nanjiani. They discuss Kevin Hart, writers rooms they&amp;rsquo;ve been on, and all the different scenes in standup. Kumail talks about growing up in Pakistan, starting in comedy, and being cool on film sets. Kumail talks about the Chicago comedy scene, Silicon Valley and Portlandia. They discuss acting, Saturday Night Live, Kumail getting JACKED, and Welcome to Chippendales on Hulu.</description></item><item><title>Important Message To Fans | 2 Bears, 1 Cave Ep. 163 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260051/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260051/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s another episode of 2 Bears 1 Cave with Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer! This week, the bears talk about scamming dentists and address fans that don&amp;rsquo;t like hearing the bears talk about nice things. They also talk about how awesome the movie Belly is, how jacked Method Man is, work out competitions and confrontations they&amp;rsquo;ve had with people in public. They talk about scary flights they&amp;rsquo;ve been on, and Bert demands credit for bringing Aaron Rodgers into their circle of friends.</description></item><item><title>WILD Conspiracy Theories! w/ Yannis Pappas | 2 Bears, 1 Cave - Ep. 162 | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260052/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260052/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Tom Segura is joined by Yannis Pappas in Bert Kreischer’s place. They discuss how Yannis got talked into softening his water, how Tom feels about meeting fans, Chris Rocks current material, chartering jets vs. flying coach, weird ways people get aroused, the SNL writer who threatened to boycott the show over Dave Chappelle hosting, annoying politically correct terms, Kanye West, the Ukraine situation, the wildest conspiracy theories, Donald Trump, Herschel Walker, and more!</description></item><item><title>Ep. 161 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260053/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bert Kreischer finally recovered from all of his surgeries and joins Tom Segura to discuss their taste in adult videos. They discuss Adriana Chechik breaking her back, Bhad Bhabie, and if Bert should start an Only Fans account. Tom educates Bert on Tyga, Travis Scott and Woah Vicky. Bert shares his theory on little people, the bears discuss herpes, pregnancy scares, as well as hernias. They review some of the best hair transplants among celebrities, female celebrities that aged gracefully, and private jets.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 160 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Quentin Tarantino | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260054/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bert Kreischer is still recovering from his heart surgeries so Tom Segura asked Quentin Tarantino to step in as a guest bear! Go check out Quentin’s new book “Cinema Speculation” and his podcast “The Video Archives!” Quentin discusses his new book, the journey of green lighting Pulp Fiction as well as the decisions made for casting. Tom asks Quentin about accents in Inglorious Bastards, Michael Parks in Kill Bill, and the “Top Gun is Gay” monologue.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 159 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Neal Brennan &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260055/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Neal Brennan joins Bert Kreischer in Tom Segura’s place for this episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave. Neal and Bert discuss how much different comedians make, Neal’s Mark Twain speech, tour busses, SNL, representation in comedy, Chappelle’s Show, Trevor Noah, how they edit their stand-up specials, Neal’s new Netflix special “Blocks,” and much more!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep. 158 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260056/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260056/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s another week of 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer and it is a WILD episode! Sober October is over and it’s Berty Boy’s birthday! The Bears discuss their favorite comics and throw shade at every comedian that’s slighted them, they discuss the tragic news about Takeoff from Migos, and then Tom reveals possibly the BEST birthday gift ever for Bert! The bears then discuss Diddy’s wild Halloween interaction with actor from the show Power, Michael J.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 157 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260057/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Halloween! It&amp;rsquo;s another week of 2 Bears 1 Cave with Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer and it&amp;rsquo;s the last day of #SoberOctober! They discuss how unbelievably cool comedian Dean Delray is, the bears&amp;rsquo; fashion choices, and lies they spread about each other. Bert discusses opening for Louis CK and nearly ruining the show, they talk about a heckler who threw a beer at a comedian on stage, and Bert shares a review from a fan posted on Instagram.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 156 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260058/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260058/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s another week of 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer! They talk about Tiger Woods, their kids playing sports, and what it takes to become an elite athlete. They try to figure out how they can raise freak athletes, discuss sports families, and debate if 2 Bears Racing is going to participate in the great Gumball 3000.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep. 155 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260059/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260059/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;rsquo;re halfway through Sober October and Bert Kreischer tells Tom Segura how he&amp;rsquo;s disgusted with drinking now, the bears look at their sleep and recovery from Whoop, and Tom shares some VERY cool auto-generated art of Bert made by artificial intelligence software. Tom talks about his recent incredible ayahuasca experience, Bert shares how often he thinks about death, and how bummed Bert is that he is madly in love with his wife LeeAnn.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 154 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Greg Fitzsimmons | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260060/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Greg Fitzsimmons is a stand-up comedian, writer, producer, and radio host. He joins Tom Segura, in Bert Kreischer’s place for this week’s episode of “2 Bears, 1 Cave.” They discuss their old acting classes, getting to know adult performers, going shooting with Joe Rogan, “American Psycho,” “The Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power,” cultural appropriation in media, method acting, and much more!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep. 153 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Duncan Trussell | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260061/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Duncan Trussell joins Tom Segura in Bert Kreischer’s place for this week’s “2 Bears, 1 Cave.” They discuss the new Armie Hammer documentary, Vlad the Impaler, North Korea, UFOs, Mos Def, Ted Bundy, and the Mari Aoki phenomenon. They also swap stories about “relieving themselves” on airplanes.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep. 152 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Joe Rogan | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260062/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260062/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s another episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura and we have guest bear Joe Rogan! We talk about Joe beating Enny in arm wrestling right before cameras started rolling, how athletic Bert Kreischer actually is, and the parameters for Sober October this year. The bears talk about Mark Zuckerberg going on Joe Rogan Experience, failed attempts at canceling Joe, some wild videos on Instagram, and famous mobsters and hitmen.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 151 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260063/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260063/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s another week of 2 Bears 1 Cave with Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer! Bert interviews Tom about his inspirations for fitness, sex, comedy and his perspective on funding your own projects. They discuss pioneers in the standup comedy world like Dane Cook and Louis CK, Bert shares what he learned about history on his trip to Italy, and how Jesus definitely wasn&amp;rsquo;t white. They try to see if they can name all the presidents, they call Dr.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 150 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260064/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260064/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s another week of 2 Bears 1 Cave with Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer! The bears talk about torturing their kids with singing, Hank Williams, and more on Andrew Tate. They discuss hazing, the gayest things they&amp;rsquo;ve ever done, and women&amp;rsquo;s safety on college campuses. Tom shares what makes him laugh about violent videos, the bears share the fattest they&amp;rsquo;ve ever been and getting in shape. The bears wrap up with discussing Sober October and the birthday gift-off.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 149 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260065/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260065/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s another week of 2 Bears 1 Cave with Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer! Bert discusses how he dresses like a child, Nadav is a genius, and his daughter going off to college. Tom talks about going to college with Prince Fielder, Bert talks about the differences between him and his daughters, and the bears discuss Andrew Tate getting cancelled. They talk about Bert&amp;rsquo;s knack for promoting, protesting the Garth Brooks concert for YMH Live 8, coffee makers, Bert&amp;rsquo;s trip to Italy, and then Bert runs Tom through his &amp;ldquo;power&amp;rdquo; questions.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 148 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260066/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer are back together in the Bear Cave this week! They talk about why Bert’s given up “adult films,” how he is stimulating himself now, sounding, Manti Te’o, and the new Armie Hammer documentary “House of Hammer.” Bert reacts to Tim Dillon’s comments about him from YMH Live 8, and Bert shares the story of the time he modeled nude on “Trip Flip.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep. 147 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Whitney Cummings &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260067/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260067/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s another episode of 2 Bears 1 Cave! This episode we are joined by comedian, actor, producer, and fellow podcaster, Whitney Cummings! Bert and Whitney start off the show discussing stories about fellow comedian Demetri Martin, then tragically interrupt themselves into discussing palindromes, ambigrams, onomatopoeias, and luxury watches&amp;hellip;? These bears are all over the place! Whitney talks about breaking into her neighbor&amp;rsquo;s house, Bert talks about stealing lawn jockeys as a kid.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 146 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Andrew Santino &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260068/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome back to 2 Bears 1 Cave! This episode we&amp;rsquo;re joined by actor, producer, and fellow comedian Andrew Santino. Bert &amp;amp; Andrew start us off discussing why Adam Ray ruined the comedy basketball league, and Santino&amp;rsquo;s new movie &amp;ldquo;Me Time&amp;rdquo; with Kevin Hart and Mark Wahlberg. They discuss each others&amp;rsquo; favorite tequilas, and Bert talks about why he&amp;rsquo;s switching from his old favorite, Tito&amp;rsquo;s. Bert makes Santino take his blood pressure, then they wrap talking about their personal experiences working out with famous bodybuilders Thor Bjornsson and Martin Ford.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 145 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260069/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer share stories about pregnancy scares, discuss the overturning of Roe v. Wade, find out about the history of orphanages, and revisit the PLASTT subreddit. Bert raves about the Oculus, which he just tried thanks to Brian Simpson, and a conversation about exes prompts the Bears to question which one of them is easier to fall in love with. They wrap up by discussing tequila, which Bert has officially switched to from vodka.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 144 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260070/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer are together in the bear cave again for this episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave. Bert starts off by discussing his fall the night before. and they watch a video of the incident. They also talk about queerbaiting in Thor: Love and Thunder, Daniel Craig, playing red rover, why Bert thought he might have to have a broken jaw, and Tom’s experience with a shady dentist.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 143 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260071/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer are back together in the bear cave for this week’s episode! Bert recaps his Fully Loaded tour with Dave Attell, Shane Gillis, Big Jay Oakerson, Taylor Tomlinson, and many more comics. They also discuss Tom’s appearance on The Late Show With Stephen Colbert, working out with Mark Bell, the Ron White episode of 2 Bears, and Bert’s upcoming trip to Italy. Tom then tells Bert about his experience donating to a Starlight Children’s Foundation, which prompts a conversation about donating to charity.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 142 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Mark Bell | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260072/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260072/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week’s episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave, Tom Segura is joined by lifter, podcaster, and entrepreneur Mark Bell. Tom and Mark discuss weight lifting injuries, Mark’s extreme weight loss, Tom’s workout routine on the road, improving sleep, squatting 1,000+ lbs, diet, motivation, using PEDs and more! Mark and Tom share the story of how they became friends, they talk about how to help Bert Kreischer “be less fat,” and Tom also reveals the time he was most nervous speaking in front of an audience.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 141 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Ryan Sickler | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260073/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260073/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s 2 Bears 1 Cave with a sick Tom Segura and guest bear Ryan Sickler! The bears talk about Michelin Star restaurants, Tom&amp;rsquo;s mom&amp;rsquo;s gifts, and Brad Pitt. They talk about how sick they get on the road, people who dip chewing tobacco, the 30 For 30 doc on Street Basketball, and Bill Clinton.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep. 140 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Sal Vulcano &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260074/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260074/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s another week of 2 Bears 1 Cave and Bert Kreischer welcomes his guest bear Sal Vulcano! They talk about performing on cruises, compare friendships, and gambling. They talk about how Sal grew up, how Impractical Jokers blew up, and surviving the pandemic. They discus their flaws, having fun bombing past podcast appearances, and why no one should get a full set of new teeth. They talk about the infamous George Brett story dumping in his pants, Bert describes his own misfired dumps, and Sal has a hard time comprehending any of it.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 139 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Danny Brown | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260075/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260075/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s 2 Bears 1 Cave with Tom Segura and guest bear (from YMH Studios&amp;rsquo; The Danny Brown Show) Danny Brown! Danny talks to Tom about watches, getting his identity stolen, and things he learned from hanging out with Insane Clown Posse. They talk about how Danny got into podcasting, his move to Austin, traveling and performing in different countries, and Ninja from Die Antword trying to pick him up.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 138 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Ron White | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260076/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome back to 2 Bears, 1 Cave! This week Bert Kreischer is on dialysis and Tom Segura sits down with guest bear Ron White! The bears talk about how Ron used Ayahuasca to stop drinking, Ron getting arrested for drug smuggling, and the Blue Collar Comedy Tour. They trade standup comedy stories, discuss retirement, and some advice on love and happiness!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep. 137 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Yannis Pappas | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260077/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260077/</guid><description>Podcast Description We got guest bear Yannis Pappas joining Tom Segura this week! Go check out his standup comedy special &amp;ldquo;Mom Love&amp;rdquo; on YouTube! The bears discuss celebrity culture, standup comedy youtube specials, and fat football coaches like Stan Van Gundy and Mark Mangino. They find an article wondering why Bert Kreischer takes his shirt off all the time, describe what it feels like for your jokes to not work on stage, and appreciate everything Jewish people have done for society.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 136 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260078/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Another episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer! This week the two talk about Bert’s love of the band Wilco, how they each pitch this podcast to people who haven’t listened to it, and a promising new product Bert wants to be affiliated with. They discuss being fathers, buying gifts for their crew on the road, how they both got into sneaker culture, and why they ever became friends in the first place.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 135 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260079/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260079/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s another week of 2 Bears 1 Cave with Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer! They talk about how wild it&amp;rsquo;s been to be friends with Joe Rogan as his career has grown, they take the original racist test that Bert found, and they discuss serial killers and where they went wrong. They talk about how Joey Diaz blew up a group text, getting stuck on a huge email thread with hundreds of other comedians, and Tom tries on his cream leather jacket for Bert.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 134 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260080/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260080/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of “2 Bears, 1 Cave,” Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer discuss hatmaking, Bert’s experience hanging with Christy Mack, Tom’s ad campaign he did with Jared Fogle, athletes who cheat on their spouses, Melissa Villasenor and Selena Gomez’ “chola” SNL sketch, and more. The Bears also take a test to see if they’re racist, and the results may surprise you!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep. 133 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Bert Kreischer &amp; Chris Distefano | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260081/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris Distefano AKA Chrissy Specials joins Bert Kreischer this week fresh off of his new Netflix special &amp;ldquo;Speshy Weshy!&amp;rdquo; They discuss drinking, check in with Christina P to ask about her Netflix special Mom Genes, and side effects. Bert and Chris discuss their friendship with Tom, the early days of Joe Rogan, and old school comedy legends like Dave Attell, Colin Quinn and Jerry Seinfeld. They talk about how they got to where they are in comedy, being dads, and finding a work/life balance.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 132 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Mark Normand &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260082/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260082/</guid><description>Podcast Description We have a special guest bear joining Bert Kreischer today&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s Mark Normand! They talk about iconic standup comedy sets from black comedians, prescription pills, and Bert getting hurt on his Travel Channel show. They trade stories about first experiences with drugs, alcohol and sex. They discuss their sex lives, cultures from all over the world, a bartender Bert was attracted to the night before, and being diverse on accident.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 131 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260083/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260083/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week&amp;rsquo;s episode of &amp;ldquo;2 Bears, 1 Cave,&amp;rdquo; Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer discuss Bert&amp;rsquo;s inability to keep a secret, jigsaw puzzles, racing Caeleb Dressel, why Bert should be a Speedo spokesperson, and &amp;ldquo;Jackass Forever.&amp;rdquo; Bert recalls partying with Johnny Knoxville in the 90s, and the two FaceTime Steve-O
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep. 130 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260084/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260084/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave, Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer discuss finding your personal style and take a look at the style of celebrities such as Lenny Kravitz, Jason Momoa, Ben Affleck, and Jack Black. They also talk The Neck Boys, getting rest on tour, Logan Paul&amp;rsquo;s pro wrestling debut, vacationing in Medellin, Kodak Black, and more. Plus, Bert introduces Tom to his new favorite game: Wordle.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 129 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260085/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260085/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s Tom Segura&amp;rsquo;s birthday, and Bert Kreischer, once again, topped their previous birthday gifts to each other. He got him a race car for 2 Bears Racing! The Bears call Matt Farah of &amp;ldquo;The Smoking Tire,&amp;rdquo; who advised Bert on the purchase. He gives Tom and Bert a full run down of the car&amp;rsquo;s specs. The Bears then swap stories of other meaningful gifts they&amp;rsquo;ve given to people, and get emotional discussing Bert&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Wait Staff Raffle&amp;rdquo; where he would give comedy club staff the chance to win money at his shows.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 128 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260086/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260086/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week&amp;rsquo;s episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave, Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer discuss stem cell treatments, hanging with DJ Premier in New York, Will Smith slapping Chris Rock at the Oscars, and the ways Walter Matthau and Michael Jordan bet. Also, Bert thinks he&amp;rsquo;s turning into Kanye West, which prompts a discussion about how he would react if LeeAnn started dating John Mayer.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep. 127 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260087/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260087/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week&amp;rsquo;s episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave, Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer discuss why Tom got into an altercation at a dog park, Kodak Black getting shot, Jenna Jameson&amp;rsquo;s illness, Kevin Hart&amp;rsquo;s Gucci pants, and Tom&amp;rsquo;s experiences at the Buffalo Bills facility and Chef Jose Andres&amp;rsquo; restaurant Jaleo. Josh Potter was just on tour with Bert, this leads the Bears to compare and contrast how the two of them tour.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 126 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260088/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome back to another episode of 2 Bears 1 Cave with Bert Kreischer and Tom Segura! The bears start off the show talking about being bullies and being bullied in school. Who do you think was a bigger bully, Tom or Bert? Then they review shows and specials they’ve recently seen, like Dave Chappelle’s Home Team: Earthquake’s “Legendary”, Anthony Jeselnik’s “Fire in the Maternity Ward”, Ali Wong’s “Don Wong”, and Bert’s favorite: “A Made Homecoming”.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 125 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260089/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260089/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week&amp;rsquo;s episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave, Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer discuss Bert&amp;rsquo;s experience watching Tyler Perry&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;A Madea Homecoming,&amp;rdquo; Britney Spears&amp;rsquo; insane Instagram posts, W. Kamau Bell&amp;rsquo;s new docuseries &amp;ldquo;We Need to Talk About Cosby,&amp;rdquo; and David Spade&amp;rsquo;s episode of 2 Bears. Bert tells the story of going to a strip club in Austin with his crew the night before, and Tom and Bert talk about &amp;ldquo;Yo!</description></item><item><title>Ep. 124 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260090/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260090/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s another episode of 2 Bears 1 Cave! Bert starts the episode off comparing himself to minor league and Olympian athletes. What a surprise! Do you think Bert could challenge Caeleb Dressel at swimming? Israel Adesanya at fighting? What if they were both drunk? Tom tries talking about the new Chevrolet Corvette, 2 Bears Racing, and his genuine love for other people’s fear, but Bert moves onto his favorite politician, Saparmurat Niyazov, talks about commissioning a statue of himself, and/or Tom Segura in pure bronze, and how excited he is for 2 Bears Racing!</description></item><item><title>Ep. 123 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260091/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260091/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on 2 Bears, 1 Cave, Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer discuss what they think Bert&amp;rsquo;s daughter&amp;rsquo;s college experience will be like due to Bert&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;party guy&amp;rdquo; persona, their tastes in fashion and art, and Bert&amp;rsquo;s process of perfecting his stand-up routine. Bert shares a joke he wrote about Joe Rogan and Neil Young, and The Bears discuss their nicknames and brainstorm which rappers have the best nicknames.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 122 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260092/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260092/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on 2 Bears 1 Cave, Bert Kreischer opens with what it&amp;rsquo;s like visiting Austin, and how much he loves playing games with Tom Segura&amp;rsquo;s kids. Also, Tom&amp;rsquo;s kids give Bert a new nick name: Fat Sticks. The bears talk about standup comedy all over the world, they try to figure out the perfect outfit for Bert&amp;rsquo;s next special, and we go down the female golfer rabbit hole.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 121 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260093/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260093/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s another week of 2 Bears 1 Cave with Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer out of the new Austin set and we get into hypotheticals about hooking up with relatives! We get an update on the weight loss challenge with Nadav, talk about Ben Askren and the Jake Paul fight, and Bert tries to figure out his price for getting knocked out by a professional fighter. How much should Bert get to be in a boxing ring with Israel &amp;ldquo;Stylebender&amp;rdquo; Adesanya?</description></item><item><title>Ep. 120 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; David Spade | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260094/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260094/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s another week of 2 Bears 1 Cave, and we have guest bear David Spade joining Tom Segura! Spade has all sorts of questions as he just started an SNL themed podcast co-hosted by Dana Carvey called &amp;ldquo;Fly On The Wall.&amp;rdquo; David tells Tom about getting on Saturday Night Live with Rob Schneider and what it was like to be a writer/performer on the cast back then. They talk about Tommy Boy, Chris Farley, Kevin Nealon, Gap Girls, and a horror story involving Eddie Murphy.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 119 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260095/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer are finally recording out of the new set and Bert almost immediately ruins it. Bert fantasizes which celebrities he&amp;rsquo;d date, the bears discuss the Buffalo Bill&amp;rsquo;s insane game and the incredible 2 Bears cleats that Gabe Davis wore during a game. The bears try doing some inspirational social media posts, we get an update on #TheMachine movie, Bert shares his Covid episode and a screen grab from his nest cam after he had sex.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 118 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260096/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260096/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s another episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer and Bert thinks he&amp;rsquo;s finally going to move to Austin! Will Enny and Nadav move in with him? Then, the bears decide to completely change and rebuild Nadav. Is he up for the challenge? Tom shares how he got into doing standup comedy and Bert reveals he doesn&amp;rsquo;t listen when people answer his questions.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 117 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Ari Shaffir | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260097/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260097/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s another week of 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura and with special guest bear, Ari Shaffir! We analyze some of Carrot Top&amp;rsquo;s wild Instagram posts and ask Ari how he got banned from social media. They talk about how important change is to your life and some fans who are surprised when comedians don&amp;rsquo;t care about their feelings. Ari tells us about his time at J school, Tom shows Ari a heavy clip from YMH Live and an OG clip known as &amp;ldquo;Man VS Jar.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 116 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260098/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260098/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s another episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer, and Bert is having a rough time recovering from the previous episode. Bert went into a deprivation tank loaded and had a day of polar plunges and packed saunas and marvels at his incredible genes. With that, they talk about ayahuasca which cause Bert to have a panic attack mid-thought. The bears discuss sleep, touring styles, disc golfers, and E-sports gamers.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 115 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260099/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260099/</guid><description>Podcast Description A truly special episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer where they try do as many vices in the span of a little over an hour. Bert and Tom celebrate their power by lighting cigars and Bert tries to compare himself to Dwayne &amp;ldquo;The Rock&amp;rdquo; Johnson. They try to come up with the premise to a movie that The Rock would do with them&amp;hellip; would you watch it?</description></item><item><title>Ep. 114 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260100/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260100/</guid><description>Podcast Description 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer are back in Austin and we try to figure out if Bert is the most self absorbed person Tom knows. Is he a lot? Bert tries to convince Enny to let him smoke cigars in his house and Bert reveals how he incentivized his tour bus to motivate his weight loss. He describes his day working out with Joe Rogan at the Onnit gym, and the bears make Nadav compare and contrast their stand up shows.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 113 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260101/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260101/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s another week of 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer, this time out of Bert studio in Los Angeles! Bert shares he&amp;rsquo;s been on a fasting mimicking cleanse diet and shares his incentivized weight loss routine on tour. They go on to discuss at the physique of jacked celebrities like Michael B. Jordan, Chris Pratt, Kumail Nanjiani and how Jason Momoa does it the best way.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 112 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260102/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Time to hang out in the cave with the 2 bears: Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer! Bert starts this episode with deciding he&amp;rsquo;s going to drink today, and figured it&amp;rsquo;s not fair only uppity non-woke women get to be called Karen&amp;hellip; he wants to figure out names for the rest of the spectrum of dumb people. Are you a Liam? We watch the classic viral video of the girl getting hit in the head with a shovel and see what the ladies are up to today.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 111 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260103/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260103/</guid><description>Podcast Description 2 Bears, 1 Cave has partnered with the one and only Mache to bring to you a custom 2 Bears, 1 Cave shoe! Preorders for this one of a kind shoe begin this Friday, 12/17 at 11am EST and will only be open for 72 hours when the window closes Monday, 12/20 at 11am EST. So head on over to https://machecustoms.com this weekend to preorder a custom 2 Bears, 1 Cave shoe designed by Mache!</description></item><item><title>Ep. 110 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260104/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Become a paid channel member of YMH to experience an AD-FREE version of the show here : https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCYIgiXwJck_Pb5Nj-wIrsqg/join SPONSORS: - Go to https://LIQUIDIV.COM and use code BEARS at checkout and get 25% off ANYTHING you order. &amp;ndash; Go to https://Saatva.com/theshit to get $200 off your mattress! - Head on over to https://Stance.com and enjoy the color and comfort of a life less ordinary… with Stance. - Go to https://HELLOTUSHY.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 109 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260105/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260105/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Head on over to https://Stance.com and pick out whatever styles you like. Enjoy the color and comfort of a life less ordinary… with Stance. - Go to https://ShipStation.com and use the code CAVE to get a 60 day free trial - To start comparing quotes and simplify insurance-buying, check out Policygenius: https://policygenius.com/2BEARS1CAVE. Thanks to Policygenius for sponsoring this video! - Get 15% off your first order, free shipping, and a 100% satisfaction guarantee, when you go to https://MeUndies.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 108 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260106/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260106/</guid><description>Podcast Description CHICAGO! Come see Tom live on his birthday, April 16! Presale starts this Wednesday at 10am local time. Get tickets at https://www.ticketmaster.com/event/04005AE7FAE32A7B and use code EVERYWHERE SPONSORS: - Go to https://EstablishedTitles.com/BEARS to become a Lord today and get 10% off. - Go to https://3Chi.com and use code BEARS at checkout to receive 5% off your order - Go to https://WHOOP.com and use code “CAVE” at checkout to save yourself 15% off today.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 107 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260107/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260107/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Download the DraftKings Sportsbook app now, use promo code BEARS, bet ONE DOLLAR on either team to score and win ONE HUNDRED DOLLARS IN FREE BETS. - Earn your bragging rights with Zingeroo by going to https://apps.zingeroo.com/2Bears - Head on over to https://Stance.com and pick out whatever styles you like. Enjoy the color and comfort of a life less ordinary… with Stance. - Head to https://PolicyGenius.com/CAVE to get started right now.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 106 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260108/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260108/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Get an extra $50 off sitewide, on top of their Biggest Sale of the Year when you go to https://Kamikoto.com/CAVE and use the offer code CAVE - Go to https://3Chi.com and use code BEARS at checkout to receive 5% off your order - Get three extra months free at https://ExpressVPN.com/CAVE - Go to https://Squarespace.com for a free trial and when you’re ready to launch, use the offer code BEARS to save 10% off your first purchase of a website or domain - Go to https://WHOOP.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 105 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260109/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Become a paid channel member of YMH to experience an AD-FREE version of the show here : https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCYIgiXwJck_Pb5Nj-wIrsqg/join SPONSORS: - Get 25% off when you go to https://LiquidIV.com and use code BEARS at checkout - Be the big winner this holiday season with a gift from MVMT. Go to https://MVMT.COM/CAVE! Join the MOVEMENT! - Go to https://saatva.com/theshit for $200 off your order - Go to https://GetSuperLeaf.com/bears and use promo code BEARS for 40% off your entire order for the month of November - Go to https://ShipStation.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 104 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260110/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260110/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Go to https://3Chi.com and use code BEARS at checkout to receive 5% off your order - Go to https://WHOOP.com and use code “CAVE” at checkout to save yourself 15% off today. - Get your first visit absolutely free at https://forhims.com/bears. - Get 20% Off + Free Shipping at https://Manscaped.com/BEARS - Get 10% off your first month of online therapy at https://BetterHelp.com/BEARS. - Visit https://SimpliSafe.com/bears for 20% off your entire new system and your first month of monitoring service FREE, when you enroll in Interactive Monitoring.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 103 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260111/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260111/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Head to https://PolicyGenius.com/CAVE to get started right now. Policygenius. When it comes to insurance, it’s nice to get it right. - Go to https://saatva.com/theshit for $200 off your order - Visit https://mudwtr.com/bears to support the show and use BEARS at check out for $5 off - Go to https://birddogs.com enter promo code “BEARS” and they’ll throw in a free Birddogs Whistle Tip Football. - Go check out https://AdamAndEve.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 102 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260112/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260112/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Go to https://3Chi.com and use code BEARS at checkout to receive 5% off your order - Get three extra months free at https://ExpressVPN.com/CAVE. - Go to https://WHOOP.com and use code “CAVE” at checkout to save yourself 15% off today. - Go to https://HelloFresh.com/CAVE14 and use code CAVE14 for up to 14 free meals plus free shipping! - Get 25% off when you go to https://LiquidIV.com and use code BEARS at checkout It&amp;rsquo;s another episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer out of Austin and we&amp;rsquo;re getting decadent!</description></item><item><title>Ep. 101 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260113/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260113/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Go to https://Squarespace.com for a free trial and when you’re ready to launch, use the offer code BEARS to save 10% off your first purchase of a website or domain - Start building better habits for healthier, long-term results. Sign up for your trial at https://Noom.com/BEARS. - Get 15% off your order at https://BuyRaycon.com/bears - Go to https://WHOOP.com and use code “Bears” at checkout to save yourself 15% off today.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 100 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260114/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260114/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Go to https://3Chi.com and use code BEARS at checkout to receive 5% off your order - Get 25% off when you go to https://LiquidIV.com and use code BEARS at checkout - Go to https://WHOOP.com and use code “Bears” at checkout to save yourself 15% off today. - Get your first visit absolutely free at https://forhims.com/bears. - Go to https://ShipStation.com and use the code CAVE to get a 60 day free trial - Go to https://HelloFresh.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 99 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Ari Shaffir &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260115/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260115/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Go to https://EstablishedTitles.com/BEARS to become a Lord today and get 10% off. - Go to https://babbel.com and use promo code BEARS for an extra three months of Babbel FREE. - Head to https://PolicyGenius.com/CAVE to get started right now. Policygenius. When it comes to insurance, it’s nice to get it right. - Go to https://WHOOP.com and use code “Bears” at checkout to save yourself 15% off today. - Get 20% Off + Free Shipping at https://Manscaped.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 98 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260116/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260116/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Go to https://3Chi.com and use code BEARS at checkout to receive 5% off your order - Go to https://saatva.com/theshit for $200 off your order - Get three extra months free at https://ExpressVPN.com/CAVE. - Go to https://WHOOP.com and use code “Bears” at checkout to save yourself 15% off today. - Go to https://HelloFresh.com/CAVE14 and use code CAVE14 for up to 14 free meals plus free shipping! - Find your Starbucks Tripleshot Energy online or at your local store - Download the DraftKings app now and use code &amp;ldquo;BEARS&amp;rdquo; to get a FREE shot at MILLIONS in total prizes with your first deposit!</description></item><item><title>Ep. 97 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Dr. Drew &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260117/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260117/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Start building better habits for healthier, long-term results. Sign up for your trial at https://Noom.com/BEARS. - Get an extra $50 off sitewide, on top of their Biggest Sale of the Year when you go to https://Kamikoto.com/CAVE and use the offer code CAVE - Go to https://Squarespace.com for a free trial and when you’re ready to launch, use the offer code BEARS to save 10% off your first purchase of a website or domain - Get 15% off your order at https://BuyRaycon.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 96 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Roy Wood Jr. | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260118/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260118/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Go to www.3Chi.com and use code BEARS at checkout to receive 5% off your order - Go to www.BlueChew.com to try it for FREE when you use our promo code BEARS at checkout and just pay $5 shipping. - Go to www.BlendersEyewear.com and enter promo code BEARSVIP to get 15% off - Get your Bud Light Retro Summer Tie Dye Variety Pack at www.budlight.com/delivery or pick it up at your local neighborhood grocery, convenience or liquor store - Go to www.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 95 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260119/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260119/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Head to https://PolicyGenius.com/CAVE to get started right now. Policygenius. When it comes to insurance, it’s nice to get it right. - Go to https://WHOOP.com and use code “Bears” at checkout to save yourself 15% off today. - Go to https://MillerLite.com/CAVE to find delivery options near you. It&amp;rsquo;s Miller Time. - Go to https://BlackRifleCoffee.com/BEARS today to get the new Cold Brew Packs. -Save 35% by going to https://BeamTLC.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 94 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260120/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260120/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Get 25% off when you go to LIQUIDIV.com and use code BEARS at checkout - Go to Squarespace.com for a free trial and when you’re ready to launch, use the offer code BEARS to save 10% off your first purchase of a website or domain - Go to vuori.com/bears to get 20% off your first purchase and enjoy free shipping on any U.S. orders over $75 - Go to BuyRaycon.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 93 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260121/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260121/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Get Bud Light Seltzers delivered right to your door by going to https://budlight.com/delivery. - Go to https://saatva.com/theshit for $200 off your order. - Sign up for your trial at https://Noom.com/BEARS. - Get three extra months free at https://EXPRESSVPN.com/CAVE. - Go to https://WHOOP.com and use code “Bears” at checkout to save yourself 15% off today. - Subscribe today and you’ll save 35% by going to https://beamtlc.com/BEARS. - Go to https://TommyJohn.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 92 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260122/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260122/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Go to https://EstablishedTitles.com/BEARS to become a Lord today and get 10% off. - Get your Bud Light Seltzer delivered right to your door by going to https://budlight.com/delivery. - Go https://3Chi.com and use code BEARS at checkout to receive 5% off your order. - Visit https://ritual.com/BEARS to get 10% off during your first 3 months. - Go to https://ShipStation.com, click on the microphone at the top of the page, and type in CAVE to get a 60-day free trial.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 91 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Brendan Schaub | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260123/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260123/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Go to https://Squarespace.com for a free trial and when you’re ready to launch, use the offer code BEARS to save 10% off your first purchase of a website or domain - Go to https://Whoop.com and use code &amp;ldquo;Bears” at checkout to save yourself 15% off today. - Head to https://PolicyGenius.com/cave to get started right now. Policygenius. When it comes to insurance, it’s nice to get it right.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 90 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Marc Maron | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260124/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260124/</guid><description>Podcast Description The second leg of the I&amp;rsquo;m Coming Everywhere Tour is here! Go to https://TomSegura.com/tour and use code TOMMY to access the pre-sale this Wednesday, July 21st at 10am. Take advantage of this opportunity and get your tickets before they sell out! SPONSORS: - Go to https://BlueChew.com and get your first month FREE when you use our promo code BEARS at checkout, just pay $5 shipping. - Go to https://LiquidIV.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 89 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Cassius Marsh | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260125/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Come see Tom Segura on tour in Chicago at Credit 1 Arena April 15th! Go to https://TomSegura.com/tour and use code TOMMY to access the pre-sale this Wednesday, July 14th at 10am. Take advantage of this opportunity and get your tickets before they sell out! SPONSORS: - Use code BEARS for 50% off 2 or more pairs at https://ShadyRays.com. - Go to https://Whoop.com and use code &amp;ldquo;Bears” at checkout to save yourself 15% off today.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 88 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Anthony Jeselnik | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260126/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260126/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Go to https://saatva.com/theshit for $200 off your order. - Purchase at https://BlackRifleCoffee.com/BEARS and use code: BEARS at checkout for 20% off your purchase and your first coffee club order! - Get 10% off your first 3 months at https://Ritual.com/BEARS - Join the MVMT and get 15% off today with free shipping and free returns by going to https://MVMT.com/CAVE - Get 15% off your order at https://BuyRaycon.com/bears - Get 20% off your first order at https://TommyJohn.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 87 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Greg Fitzsimmons | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260127/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260127/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Purchase at https://BlackRifleCoffee.com/BEARS and use code: BEARS at checkout for 20% off your purchase and your first coffee club order! - Get your first visit absolutely free at https://ForHims.com/bears - Get the retro summer tie dye variety pack for a limited time this summer! You can get them delivered right to your door by going to https://BudLight.com/delivery or pick it up at your local neighborhood grocery, convenience or liquor store - To start comparing quotes and simplify insurance-buying, check out Policygenius: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 86 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Felipe Esparza | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260128/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260128/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Use code BEARS for 50% off 2 or more pairs at https://ShadyRays.com. - Go to https://LiquidIV.com and use the code BEARS for 25% off anything you order! - Get 20% Off + Free Shipping at https://Manscaped.com/BEARS - Go to https://Vuori.com/BEARS and receive 20% off your first purchase, free shipping on any U.S. orders over $75, and free returns. - Go to https://Whoop.com and use code &amp;ldquo;Bears” at checkout to save yourself 15% off today.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 85 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Mark Normand | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260129/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260129/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Go to https://Squarespace.com for a free trial and when you’re ready to launch, use the offer code BEARS to save 10% off your first purchase of a website or domain - Go to https://Whoop.com and use code &amp;ldquo;Bears” at checkout to save yourself 15% off today. - Get an extra three months of ExpressVPN for free at https://ExpressVPN.com/CAVE - Get 15% off your order at https://BuyRaycon.com/bears - Go to https://Public.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 84 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Godfrey | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260130/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260130/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tickets for The Berty Boy Relapse World Tour are on sale now at https://bertbertbert.com! SPONSORS: - Use code BEARS for 50% off 2 or more pairs at https://ShadyRays.com. - Get your first visit absolutely free! Go to https://forhims.com/bears. - Get $10 Off Your First Pair of Feetures when you go to https://feetures.com/CAVE. - Get 20% Off + Free Shipping at https://Manscaped.com/BEARS. - Visit https://ritual.com/BEARS to get 10% off during your first 3 months.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 83 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Ethan Klein | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260131/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260131/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Go to https://saatva.com/theshit for $200 off your order. - Go to https://BlueChew.com and get your first month FREE when you use our promo code BEARS at checkout, just pay $5 shipping. - To start comparing quotes and simplify insurance-buying, check out Policygenius: https://www.policygenius.com/cave. Thanks to Policygenius for sponsoring this video! - You can get all the different flavors of Bud Light Seltzer delivered at https://budlight.com/delivery or pick it up at your local neighborhood grocery, convenience or liquor store - Get 15% Off and Free Shipping at https://MeUndies.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 82 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Steve-O &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260132/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260132/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Go to https://GetShuffle.app/bears to download shuffle and start posting for a chance to win a new iPhone - Go to https://Squarespace.com for a free trial and when you’re ready to launch, use the offer code BEARS to save 10% off your first purchase of a website or domain - Go to https://vuoriclothing.com/BEARS and receive 20% off your first purchase, free shipping on any U.S. orders over $75, and free returns.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 81 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Brian Simpson | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260133/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Go see when Brian Simpson is performing comedy in your town here: https://www.briansimpsoncomedy.com/ SPONSORS: - Go to https://ShadyRays.com and use Code: BEARS for 50% off 2 or more pairs - Buy One, Get One Free. - Go to https://Feetures.com/CAVE to get $10 off your first pair! - Go to https://Whoop.com and use code &amp;ldquo;Bears” at checkout to save yourself 15% off today. - Get an extra three months of ExpressVPN for free at https://ExpressVPN.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 80 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Ryan Sickler &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260134/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260134/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Go to https://Keeps.com/BEARS to get your first month of treatment for free! - Get 20% Off and free shipping at https://Manscaped.com/BEARS - Get 15% off your order at https://BuyRaycon.com/bears - Go to https://Whoop.com and use code &amp;ldquo;Bears” at checkout to save yourself 15% off today. - Go to https://Public.com/2BEARS to download the app and get a free slice of stock when you join! - Get 20% off your first monthly box when you sign up at https://boxofawesome.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 79 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Josh Potter | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260135/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Check out Josh&amp;rsquo;s new YouTube channel here: https://youtube.com/channel/UCpREVmHBIx4QIQLA5ZUx0wA SPONSORS: - Go to https://Saatva.com/theshit to save $200 on your order - Go to https://us.pandora.net/Bears to start shopping or find a store near you. - Head to https://Policygenius.com right now to get started. When it comes to insurance, it’s nice to get it right. - Go to https://www.shipstation.com, click on the microphone at the top of the page, and type in CAVE for a 60-day free trial.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 78 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260136/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260136/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Go to https://GetSuperLeaf.com/BEARS and enter code BEARS for 20% off - Go to https://Feetures.com/CAVE to get $10 off your first pair! - Go to https://Keeps.com/BEARS to get your first month of treatment for free! - Go to https://vuoriclothing.com/BEARS and receive 20% off your first purchase, free shipping on any U.S. orders over $75, and free returns. - Check out https://FIVERR.com and use code CAVE to receive 10% off your first order - Go to https://Whoop.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 77 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260137/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260137/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Go to https://Watchgang.com/BEARS and use code BEARS for 20% off your first purchase - Go to https://us.Pandora.net/Bears and if you shop online or in-store between 4/22 and 4/26 you will receive a bonus gift with your $150 Pandora jewelry purchase – a limited edition, sterling silver bangle. - Get 15% off your order at https://BuyRaycon.com/bears - Get 20% Off and free shipping at https://Manscaped.com/BEARS - Get 10% off your first 3 months at https://Ritual.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 76 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260138/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260138/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Visit https://mudwtr.com/bears/ to support the show and use code BEARS at check out for $5 off. - Go to https://Feetures.com/CAVE to get $10 off your first pair! - Go to https://Squarespace.com for a free trial and when you’re ready to launch, use the offer code BEARS to save 10% off your first purchase of a website or domain - Get an extra three months of ExpressVPN for free at https://ExpressVPN.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 75 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260139/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260139/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Go to https://Saatva.com/theshit to save $225 on your order - Go to https://Watchgang.com/BEARS and use code BEARS for 20% off your first purchase - Go to https://TommyJohn.com/BEARS to get 15% off your first order. - Head to https://Policygenius.com right now to get started. When it comes to insurance, it’s nice to get it right. - Go to https://www.shipstation.com, click on the microphone at the top of the page, and type in CAVE for a 60-day free trial.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 74 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Andrew Santino &amp; Bobby Lee | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260140/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260140/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS; - Go to https://hellofresh.com/cave12/ and use code cave12 for 12 free meals, including free shipping! - Visit https://mudwtr.com/bears/ to support the show and use code BEARS at check out for $5 off. - Go to https://vuoriclothing.com/BEARS/ and receive 20% off your first purchase, free shipping on any U.S. orders over $75, and free returns. - Go to https://hellotushy.com/BEARS/ to get 10% off your order and FREE shipping. - Head to https://brightcellars.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 73 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260141/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260141/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Go to https://Watchgang.com/bears and use code BEARS for 20% off your first purchase - Grab the Bud Light Seltzer Out of Office Variety pack for a very limited time only at a store near you! - Go to https://Feetures.com/CAVE to get $10 off your first pair! - Get 20% Off and free shipping at https://Manscaped.com/BEARS - Get 10% off your first 3 months at https://Ritual.com/BEARS - Head to https://Policygenius.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 72 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260142/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260142/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get your own custom handshake from the #HandshakeKing on cameo: https://www.cameo.com/handshakeking15 SPONSORS: - Go to https://Squarespace.com for a free trial and when you’re ready to launch, use the offer code BEARS to save 10% off your first purchase of a website or domain - Grab the Bud Light Seltzer Out of Office Variety pack for a very limited time only at a store near you! - Go to https://BlueChew.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 71 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260143/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260143/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Head to https://Policygenius.com right now to get started. When it comes to insurance, it’s nice to get it right. - Go to https://www.shipstation.com , click on the microphone at the top of the page, and type in CAVE for a 60-day free trial. - Go to https://BearbottomClothing.com and use code BEARS to get free shipping on your first order Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer talk about Bert&amp;rsquo;s obsession with candy and predictable repeated tooth loss, the unnerving images of &amp;ldquo;My Feet Are Killing Me,&amp;rdquo; and get inspiration for their secret handshake from a video of Wake Forest football player, Cortez Lewis.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 70 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260144/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260144/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Go to https://Saatva.com/theshit to save $225 on your order - Go to https://Feetures.com/CAVE to get $10 off your first pair! - Get your first visit absolutely free at https://ForHims.com/bears - Get 15% off your order at https://BuyRaycon.com/bears - Go to https://BearbottomClothing.com and use code BEARS to get free shipping on your first order - Go to https://FitVineWine.com to order online for delivery straight to your door - Get 15% off plant orders of $100 with promo code CAVE at https://Bloomscape.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 69 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260145/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260145/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Get 20% Off and free shipping at https://Manscaped.com/BEARS - Get 10% off your first 3 months at https://Ritual.com/BEARS - Go to https://VuoriClothing.com/BEARS and get 20% off your first purchase plus free shipping on U.S. orders over $75 - Go to https://FitVineWine.com to order online for delivery straight to your door - Head to https://Policygenius.com right now to get started. When it comes to insurance, it’s nice to get it right.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 68 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260146/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260146/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Get the new Bud Light Seltzer Lemonade delivered at https://BudLight.com/delivery - Get your first visit absolutely free at https://ForHims.com/bears - Get an extra three months of ExpressVPN for free at https://ExpressVPN.com/CAVE - Go to https://HelloFresh.com/cave10 and use code cave10 to get 10 free meals free plus free shipping! - Go to https://TommyJohn.com/BEARS to get 15% off your first order. Bert Kreischer and Tom Segura discuss the differences between raising girls and boys, road rage, their 2 Bears, 1 Sapp Super Bowl live show, Lil Nas X, Fans Only creators, and Hilaria Baldwin&amp;rsquo;s accent controversy.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 67 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260147/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260147/</guid><description>Podcast Description Miss out on 2 Bears, 1 Sapp LIVE? It&amp;rsquo;s available at https://livestream.ymhstudios.com/ RIGHT NOW! SPONSORS: - Receive $10 Off Your First Pair of Feetures when you go to http://feetures.com/CAVE - Go to https://www.shipstation.com , click on the microphone at the top of the page, and type in CAVE for a 60-day free trial. - Re-shop your home and auto insurance today at https://www.policygenius.com/ Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer start off this episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave by discussing the time Bert&amp;rsquo;s spent in Rome.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 66 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260148/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260148/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you ready for the Big Game on February 7th?! Come hang out with the bears and special guest Warren Sapp as they watch both teams face off in the final game of the season. Get tickets at https://livestream.ymhstudios.com SPONSORS: - Get the new Bud Light Seltzer Lemonade delivered at https://BudLight.com/delivery - Get your first visit absolutely free at https://ForHims.com/bears - Go to https://Squarespace.com for a free trial and when you’re ready to launch, use the offer code BEARS to save 10% off your first purchase of a website or domain - Get 15% off your order at https://BuyRaycon.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 65 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260149/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260149/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you ready for the Big Game on February 7th?! Come hang out with the bears and special guest Warren Sapp as they watch both teams face off in the final game of the season. Get tickets at https://livestream.ymhstudios.com SPONSORS: - Go to https://Feetures.com/CAVE to get $10 off your first pair! - Get 10% off your first 3 months at https://Ritual.com/BEARS - Head to https://Policygenius.com right now to get started.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 64 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260150/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260150/</guid><description>Podcast Description Become a paid channel member of YMH to experience an AD-FREE version of the show here : https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCYIgiXwJck_Pb5Nj-wIrsqg/join SPONSORS: - Go to https://Saatva.com/theshit to save $225 on your order - Download the DraftKings app and use code BEARS to get a free shot at millions of dollars in total prizes! - Get 20% Off and free shipping at https://Manscaped.com/BEARS - Go to Squarespace.com for a free trial and when you’re ready to launch, use the offer code BEARS to save 10% off your first purchase of a website or domain - Get an extra three months of ExpressVPN for free at https://ExpressVPN.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 63 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260151/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260151/</guid><description>Podcast Description Did you miss partying with the bears this New Years Eve? You still have until January 11 to catch all the action at https://ymhstudios.com/livestream SPONSORS: - Get your first visit absolutely free at https://ForHims.com/bears - Get 10% off your first 3 months at https://Ritual.com/BEARS - Download the World Series of Poker app and use promo code WSOPBEARS for ONE MILLION bonus chips when you sign up. - Head to https://Policygenius.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 62 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Dr. Drew &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260152/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260152/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you ready to party with the bears this New Years Eve? Head over to https://ymhstudios.com/livestream and get your tickets now! SPONSORS: - Get your first visit absolutely free at https://ForHims.com/bears Dr. Drew Pinsky fills in for Tom Segura and hangs out with Bert Kreischer as guest-bear on 2 Bears 1 Cave this week! They give Tom a call to check in on how he&amp;rsquo;s doing, Bert confesses to lying to his therapist, and they give a call to a guy that texted Bert as a wrong number&amp;hellip; Brandon seems pretty cool!</description></item><item><title>Ep. 61 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Whitney Cummings &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260153/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260153/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you ready to party with the bears this New Years Eve? Head over to https://ymhstudios.com/livestream and get your tickets now! Become a paid channel member of YMH to experience an AD-FREE version of the show here : https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCYIgiXwJck_Pb5Nj-wIrsqg/join SPONSORS: - Buffalo Trace. This is damn good whiskey - Go to https://Talkspace.com or download the Talkspace app and use promo code BEARS for $100 off your first month. - New U.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 60 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Christina P &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260154/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260154/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Head to https://Policygenius.com right now to get started. When it comes to insurance, it’s nice to get it right. - Go to https://Kamikoto.com/CAVE and use offer code CAVE for an extra $50 off - Get 20% Off and Free Shipping at https://Manscaped.com/BEARS - Get an extra three months of ExpressVPN for free at https://ExpressVPN.com/CAVE - Go to https://Squarespace.com for a free trial and when you’re ready to launch, use the offer code BEARS to save 10% off your first purchase of a website or domain - Go to https://Whoop.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 59 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260155/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260155/</guid><description>Podcast Description Become a paid channel member of YMH to experience an AD-FREE version of the show here : https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCYIgiXwJck_Pb5Nj-wIrsqg/join SPONSORS: - You can try ShipStation FREE for 60 days when you use offer code CAVE at https://ShipStation.com - Go to https://Kamikoto.com/CAVE and use offer code CAVE for an extra $50 off - Get your first visit absolutely free at https://ForHims.com/bears - Go to https://Vuori.com/BEARS and get 20% off your first purchase plus free shipping on U.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 58 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260156/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260156/</guid><description>Podcast Description Become a paid channel member of YMH to experience an AD-FREE version of the show here : https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCYIgiXwJck_Pb5Nj-wIrsqg/join SPONSORS: - Go to https://EstablishedTitles.com/BlackFriday and get a Lordship Title and have another Title for free. - Go to https://Mugsy.com/2bears to get 20% off sitewide, today only for Cyber Monday! - Go to https://Whoop.com/bears to get your first month free - Go to https://Feetures.com/CAVE to get $10 off your first pair!</description></item><item><title>Ep. 57 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260157/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260157/</guid><description>Podcast Description Become a paid channel member of YMH to experience an AD-FREE version of the show here : https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCYIgiXwJck_Pb5Nj-wIrsqg/join SPONSORS: - Head to Policygenius.com right now to get started. When it comes to insurance, it’s nice to get it right. - Go to Kamikoto.com/CAVE and use offer code CAVE for an extra $50 off - Get your first visit absolutely free at ForHims.com/bears -Go to NoDaysWasted.co/BEARS30 and use code BEARS30 at checkout for 30% off and free shipping in the US.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 56 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260158/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260158/</guid><description>Podcast Description Become a paid channel member of YMH to experience an AD-FREE version of the show here : https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCYIgiXwJck_Pb5Nj-wIrsqg/join SPONSORS: - Get an extra three months of ExpressVPN for free at ExpressVPN.com/CAVE - Go to Whoop.com and enter “BEARS” at checkout to save 15% - Get 20% off your order at BuyRaycon.com/bears! - Go to Vuori.com/BEARS and get 20% off your first purchase plus free shipping on U.S. orders over $75 - Get 20% off your first order when you use promo code BEARS at BubsNaturals.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 55 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260159/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260159/</guid><description>Podcast Description Become a paid channel member of YMH to experience an AD-FREE version of the show here : https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCYIgiXwJck_Pb5Nj-wIrsqg/join SPONSORS: - You can try ShipStation FREE for 60 days when you use offer code CAVE. - Get your first visit absolutely free at ForHims.com/bears - Get 20% Off and Free Shipping at Manscaped.com/BEARS - Go to Whoop.com and enter “BEARS” at checkout to save 15% Bert Kreischer is back in the cave with Tom Segura for this episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 54 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Tim Dillon | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260160/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260160/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Go to EstablishedTitles.com and enter BEARS at checkout to get 10% off. - Go to Squarespace.com for a free trial and when you’re ready to launch, use the offer code BEARS to save 10% off your first purchase of a website or domain - Go to Whoop.com and enter “BEARS” at checkout to save 15%. - Go to Vuori.com/BEARS and get 20% off your first purchase plus free shipping on U.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 53 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Ryan Sickler | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260161/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260161/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Head to Policygenius.com right now to get started and see what weirdly specific amount they could save you - Get your first visit absolutely free at ForHims.com/bears -Go to NoDaysWasted.co/BEARS and use code BEARS at checkout for 20% off and free shipping in the US. - Get 20% Off and Free Shipping at Manscaped.com/BEARS - Go to Feetures.com/CAVE to get $10 off your first pair! - Go to Talkspace.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 52 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260162/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260162/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tommy and Brent are doing standup together at the Rose Bowl on 10/28! Get your tickets at https://www.2bears1bowl.com/ Did you miss the XXL event of the year: 2 Bears 1 Cave LIVE!? You still have time to watch it. Get tickets here: https://ymhvirtual.com/ SPONSORS: - Get an extra three months of ExpressVPN for free at ExpressVPN.com/CAVE - Go to Whoop.com and enter “BEARS” at checkout to save 15% - Go to MugsyJeans.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 51 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260163/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260163/</guid><description>Podcast Description Grab tickets to the XXL event of the year: 2 Bears 1 Cave LIVE! October 15! Get tickets here: https://ymhvirtual.com/ SPONSORS: - You can try ShipStation FREE for 60 days when you use offer code CAVE. - Get your first visit absolutely free at ForHims.com/bears - Get 15% Off and Free Shipping at MeUndies.com/BEAR - Get 20% Off and Free Shipping at Manscaped.com/BEARS - Go to Whoop.com and enter “BEARS” at checkout to save 15% Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer start off this episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave by discussing the recent presidential debate and getting hyped for their tennis match.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 50 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260164/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260164/</guid><description>Podcast Description Grab tickets to the XXL event of the year: 2 Bears 1 Cave LIVE! October 15! Get tickets here: https://ymhvirtual.com/ SPONSORS: - Saatva.com/theshit for $225 off your order - Go to Squarespace.com for a free trial and when you’re ready to launch, use the offer code BEARS to save 10% off your first purchase of a website or domain - Go to Whoop.com and enter “BEARS” at checkout to save 15%.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 49 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260165/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260165/</guid><description>Podcast Description Grab tickets to the XXL event of the year: 2 Bears 1 Cave LIVE! October 15! Get tickets here: https://ymhvirtual.com/ SPONSORS: - If you’re a homeowner, head to Policygenius.com right now to get started and see what weirdly specific amount they could save you - Buffalo Trace. This is damn good whiskey - Get your first month free at ForHims.com/bears - Go to Whoop.com and enter “BEARS” at checkout to save 15%.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 48 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bobby Lee | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260166/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260166/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Get an extra three months of ExpressVPN for free at ExpressVPN.com/CAVE - FitVine Wine has partnered with the Navy SEAL Foundation to create a limited edition co-branded Red Zinfandel variety and is giving away 2 limited edition Navy SEAL Foundation Luminox watches. Go to FitVineWine.com/luminox-giveaway to enter. - Get 15% off your order at BuyRaycon.com/bears! - Go to Squarespace.com for a free trial and when you’re ready to launch, use the offer code BEARS to save 10% off your first purchase of a website or domain - Go to Whoop.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 47 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; LeeAnn Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260167/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260167/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - You can try ShipStation FREE for 60 days when you use offer code CAVE. - Get your first visit absolutely free at ForHims.com/bears - If you’re a homeowner, head to Policygenius.com right now to get started and see what weirdly specific amount they could save you - Go to hellotushy.com/BEARS to get 10% off your order -Download the DraftKings app and use code BEARS to get a free shot at millions of dollars in prizes with your first deposit!</description></item><item><title>Ep. 46 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260168/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260168/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: -Sign up at PeacockTV.com to start streaming new episodes of A.P. BIO now. -Go to EstablishedTitles.com and enter BEARS at checkout to get 10% off. -Get 20% Off and Free Shipping at Manscaped.com/BEARS -Go to fitvinewine.com to order online for delivery straight to your door -Get 15% off your order at BuyRaycon.com/bears! -Go to NoDaysWasted.co/BEARS and use code BEARS at checkout for 20% off and free shipping in the US.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 45 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260169/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260169/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - If you’re a homeowner, head to Policygenius.com right now to get started and see what weirdly specific amount they could save you - Go to EstablishedTitles.com to become a Lord today and enter BEARS at checkout to get 10% off. - Get your first visit absolutely free at ForHims.com/bears - For a limited time, get 15% off your order at BuyRaycon.com/bears! - Go to Whoop.com and enter “BEARS” at checkout to save 15%.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 44 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260170/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260170/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Go to EstablishedTitles.com to become a Lord today and enter BEARS at checkout to get 10% off. - For 20% off your first order, visit mackweldon.com/bears and enter promo code: BEARS - Get 15% off your order at BuyRaycon.com/bears! - Go to Squarespace.com for a free trial and when you’re ready to launch, use the offer code BEARS to save 10% off your first purchase of a website or domain - Go to Whoop.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 43 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260171/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260171/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Try ShipStation FREE for 60 days when you use offer code CAVE. Get started at ShipStation.com today! - Go to fitvinewine.com to order online for delivery straight to your door - Go to hellotushy.com/BEARS get 10% off your order - Get an extra three months of ExpressVPN for free at ExpressVPN.com/CAVE - Get 20% off your order and free shipping in the US at NoDaysWasted.CO/BEARS and use promo code &amp;ldquo;BEARS” at checkout.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 42 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260172/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260172/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Get 20% Off + Free Shipping at Manscaped.com/BEARS. - Head over to NoDaysWasted.CO/BEARS and use promo code &amp;ldquo;BEARS” at checkout to get 20% off your order and free shipping in the US.. Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer start off this episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave by discussing Bert&amp;rsquo;s want for a British hype man. Tom then plays a clip of LeeAnn finding out about Bert&amp;rsquo;s barehanded wiping for him, before discussing that their friends, including Joe Rogan and Joey Diaz, are moving.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 41 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260173/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260173/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Head to Policygenius.com right now to get started on finding the best home insurance for you. - Go to forhims.com/bears for a free online visit. - Go to hellotushy.com/BEARS get 10% off your order Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer start off this episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave by discussing how Bert&amp;rsquo;s perfected day drinking. They discuss their current favorite reality shows, and Tom shares a cool video of an Ed Asner look-a-like with Bert.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 40 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260174/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260174/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - Get 15-percent off your order at BuyRaycon.com/bears! - Want wine that has less sugar but doesn&amp;rsquo;t comprimise on ABV or flavor? Head over to FitVine.com and try it out Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer start off this episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave by calling NFL Hall of Famer Warren Sapp. Warren suggests that the Bears and him start a podcast. Tom and Bert then discuss their excitement over the idea and what guests they would like to have on.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 39 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260175/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260175/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - You can try ShipStation FREE for 60 days when you use offer code CAVE. - Go to forhims.com/bears for a free online visit - Receive $10 Off Your first pair of Feetures by going to feetures.com and using the code BEARS. - Go to drinkLMNT.com/BEARS and check out their electrolyte variety pack! Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer start off this episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave by discussing Bert&amp;rsquo;s drinking the night before, during which he sent text messages to Tom and Nadav about the 1972 Miami Dolphins.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 38 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260176/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260176/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave, Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer discuss Bert&amp;rsquo;s recent drive-in movie theater tour, wiping barehanded, and Bert&amp;rsquo;s foot race with his tour bus driver, Ron. Bert also reveals that he has started eating ice cream. A lot of ice cream. Tom and Bert then look at a Amazon review for Kool-Aid written by a fan, and Tom reveals new Kool-Aid inspired merch!</description></item><item><title>Ep. 37 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260177/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260177/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer start off this episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave by eating Krispy Kreme donuts. They give Russell Peters a call to discuss Hinduism, which Bert is interested in possibly joining. They also discuss how often they brush their teeth, celebrities with fake teeth and fake hair, planking, Trinidad James, and Bert&amp;rsquo;s daily caloric intake. Bert and Nadav also talk out their differences.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep. 36 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260178/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260178/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer start off this episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave by discussing why they would make a good couple, and Bert pitches a new show idea. They give Nikki Glaser a call to run the idea by her. Bert also reveals how much Kool-Aid he consumes in a day. The bears also taste test various sodas, talk about their favorite sneakers, and explore new religions.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 35 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260179/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260179/</guid><description>Podcast Description SPONSORS: - See how much you can save by re-shopping your home insurance rates at Policygenius.com - Use Code: BEARS for 50% off 2 or more pairs at ShadyRays.com - Buy One, Get One Free - Get started with your first month free! Go to ForHims.com/bears. - Go to WHOOP.com and enter “BEARS” at checkout to save 15%. Sleep better, recover faster, and train smarter - Go to hellotushy.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 34 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260180/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer start off this episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave by discussing their hair loss and weight gain over the years. Tom shares YMH All-Star Robert Paul Champagne&amp;rsquo;s cool new content with Bert. Then Bert breaks down his new favorite commercial. They also discuss losing their virginity, decaf coffee, men&amp;rsquo;s wigs, 85 South, and UTIs. Also, the 2 Bears baseball caps are available sooner than you think!</description></item><item><title>Ep. 33 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260181/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260181/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get tickets to Tom Segura&amp;rsquo;s Charity Zoom Event here: https://givebutter.com/lls-tom-segura Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer start off this episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave by to rebrand the infamous hashtag coined by Tom all those years ago. Tom suggests three new options to replace it. They also discuss Bert&amp;rsquo;s most recent discovery: Nadav has red hair! Who knew? Tom shares a story of touring Dr. Dre&amp;rsquo;s old house, which leads Bert to pitch a show in which they would tour celebrity houses and guess whose it is.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 32 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260182/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260182/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave, Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer discuss the viral &amp;ldquo;Karen in Central Park&amp;rdquo; video, Jimmy Fallon&amp;rsquo;s blackface controversy, the best Superbowl teams, and if they would take on Jason Bateman as a lover. The bears also take calls from Ari Shaffir and Whitney Cummings to have them weigh in on these topics.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep. 31 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260183/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260183/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bert Kreischer and Tom Segura are back in the cave once again. Bert has a new perspective on Karl Malone. Tom and Bert then start going doing lists to see which alt comics don&amp;rsquo;t know them, which leads them to a more fun conversation on which black comedians don&amp;rsquo;t know them. We even call up black expert Neal Brennan to weigh in! We find out Tom’s experience driving a McLaren after he gives the Kreischer girls a ride.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 30 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260184/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260184/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave, Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer discuss Michael Jordan and &amp;ldquo;The Last Dance&amp;rdquo; documentary, dipping, and seeing Nirvana in concert. Bert issues an apology to people struggling with addiction, and the two of them debate the greatest all-time college football teams. Who&amp;rsquo;s in YOUR top five? Let us know in the comment section below!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep. 29 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260185/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260185/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave, Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer discuss Adele&amp;rsquo;s weight loss, Bert&amp;rsquo;s sober days, and college pranks. Tom shares the infamous &amp;ldquo;1 Man, 1 Jar &amp;quot; video with Bert. They also call Dr. Drew to discuss the possibility of nicotine fighting Coronavirus. The two of them wrap up by eating the world hottest pork rind. What&amp;rsquo;s the spiciest thing YOU&amp;rsquo;VE eaten? Let us know in the comment section below!</description></item><item><title>Ep. 28 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260186/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260186/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave, Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer discuss Bert&amp;rsquo;s sobriety, the period of time in which people became attractive, and what the two of them are going to do after the quarantine is over. The two of them talk to Ryan Sickler, Dr. Drew Pinsky, and Joey Diaz on the phone. Tom also shares Norman Summerton&amp;rsquo;s poutine video with Bert. What do YOU like on YOUR poutine?</description></item><item><title>Ep. 27 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260187/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 22:26:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260187/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave, Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer discuss vulgar tweets, how their parents differ, and music they hate. They also take a look at Bert&amp;rsquo;s surprise birthday video for Tom. What&amp;rsquo;s the best present YOU&amp;rsquo;VE ever been given?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep. 26 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260188/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260188/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave, Bert Kreischer decides he&amp;rsquo;s going to try to listen. Does he succeed? Tom Segura tells him about getting blacked out, playing football, and getting into stand-up. Bert shares stories about browning in his pants. Tom then calls Dr. Drew and asks about Bert&amp;rsquo;s health. Tom and Bert wrap up by sharing what they learned about each other this episode. When was the last time YOU browned in your pants?</description></item><item><title>Ep. 25 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260189/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260189/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave, Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer discuss how they&amp;rsquo;re spending the quarantine, Bert&amp;rsquo;s weight gain, and Drake. Bert graces us with his singing and freestyle abilities, and discusses his Adam Sandler interview mishap. The bears also talk to comedian Ian Bagg, 90 Day Fiance producer Dan Adler, and sports analyst Pat McAfee. How are YOU passing time during the quarantine? Let us know in the comment section below!</description></item><item><title>Ep. 24 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260190/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260190/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 2 Bears Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer are back in the cave this week and it&amp;rsquo;s a real special one. It starts off with Bert showing off his latest homage to Wood on social media. Is he good enough at photoshop to keep people from reversing what he put up? We then get into Kristen Bell and Dax Shepard, alleged slander on Sean William Scott, smearing brown on your significant other&amp;rsquo;s nose, and some amazing raps written by Bert and performed by Tom.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 23 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260191/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260191/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 2 Bears are back in the Cave this week for ANOTHER extra episode to help you stay safe at home! First, remember to check out Bert Kreischer&amp;rsquo;s special &amp;ldquo;Hey Big Boy&amp;rdquo; and Tom Segura&amp;rsquo;s special &amp;ldquo;Ball Hog&amp;rdquo; on Netflix now! The bears start off with sharing a drinking game someone made on Bert&amp;rsquo;s podcast habbits called &amp;ldquo;Bertus Interruptus.&amp;rdquo; Can you survive it? Then Tom shares his story behind his new &amp;ldquo;Wash Your Hands&amp;rdquo; merch and the story of contacting the widow of the famed &amp;ldquo;Wood&amp;rdquo; who most of you have seen via text messages.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 22 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260192/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260192/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s wild times, but the bears are back together in the cave! This time to celebrate Tom Segura&amp;rsquo;s new Netflix special &amp;ldquo;Ball Hog!&amp;rdquo; With the current state of the world, Tom had to cancel all of the press he was going to do to promote it, so his best friend/bear Bert Kreischer steps in to try and recreate all the different interviews he would have had to do! What would Stephen Colbert have asked?</description></item><item><title>Ep. 21 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260193/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260193/</guid><description>Podcast Description The two bears, Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer, reunite in the cave today to celebrate Bert&amp;rsquo;s new Stand-Up Netflix special &amp;ldquo;Hey Big Boy&amp;rdquo; that becomes available to watch on Netflix March 17, 2020 on St. Patrick&amp;rsquo;s Day! We first get into seeing exactly how much worse Bert looks now from when he taped his special (3-ish months apart). It&amp;rsquo;s WILD. We get into both tom and Bert doing press for their upcoming specials (Tom&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Ball Hog&amp;rdquo; comes out March 24, 2020).</description></item><item><title>Ep. 20 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260194/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260194/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave Tom Segura surprises Bert Kreischer by having the Stanley Cup brought into the studio and they learn about its history together! The two of them also revisit the idea of becoming dandies. The question &amp;ldquo;what is the youngest age you would date&amp;rdquo; is also explored. What&amp;rsquo;s the youngest you would go?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep. 19 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260195/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260195/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 2 Bears, Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer are back in their 1 Cave today. Bert just got off the road, how is he doing? Tom and Bert are starting to realize they have no hobbies, so they start to entertain the idea of starting one. Will Bert become a Dandy? Will Bert buy a car on the podcast? These are all hobbies discussed. Plus, Tom and Bert look into joining a secret society.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 18 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260196/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 21:26:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260196/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 2 Bears, Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer are back in their 1 Cave! First we must discuss, what could be breaking news: Bert had a heart attack last night?! TMZ is trying to confirm! Then, Tom and Bert discuss the Ari Shaffir tweet about Kobe Bryant. Then we get on to the Super Bowl half time show! Jennifer Lopez and Shakira look absolutely incredible! Which one would you rather fill up?</description></item><item><title>Ep. 17 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260197/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260197/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of 2 Bears, 1 Cave, Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer discuss things they learned from their fathers, their feelings about over emotional people, and their new weight loss challenge. Tom also shares a cool story about about a guy who was not nice to his mom. What did YOU learn from your dad? Who do YOU think will win this weight loss challenge?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep. 16 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260198/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260198/</guid><description>Podcast Description What do the 2 Bears get up to in the cave this week? First, Tom and Bert show off hats that they&amp;rsquo;re not sure if they can sell or not, but if guys like them, we&amp;rsquo;ll figure something out! Then we get on the subject of Tom&amp;rsquo;s new found love for speaking Spanish on podcasts! Is it all a rouse? What&amp;rsquo;s the ACTUAL reason? Bert has some ideas! Bert then tells us about his spiritual healer.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 15 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260199/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260199/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bert Kreischer is burning his mouth on an Uncrustable while Tom Segura laughs. That’s how this episode of 2 Bears 1 Cave begins. The only way to follow that is with a history lesson. Plus, we find out about Tom’s parenting misstep and about what a miracle Bert’s kids are alive and haven’t been taken away. There’s a quick call from Joey Diaz and the Bears reminisce about Bert’s old sex show.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 14 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260200/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260200/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, on 2 Bears 1 Cave, Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer talk about what they’re thankful for. After Tom’s “Toast” video with Sam Adams dropped, it got the Bears to thinking about what they should give thanks for this holiday season. We get a sample of Bert’s award winning impressions, interactions with alcoholics and some wild stories about “apologies.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep. 13 - 2 Bears 1 Cave 2 w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260201/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260201/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today&amp;rsquo;s 2 Bears 1 Cave the music video that shook the internet to it&amp;rsquo;s core is first seen by Bert Kreischer. This episode was recorded right as Tom Segura dropped his legendary music video and we get Bert&amp;rsquo;s first reaction to seeing it for the first time. Plus, Tom has just shot his NETFLIX special as Bert is gearing up to shoot his.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep. 12 - 2 Bears 1 Cave 2 w/ Bert &amp; LeeAnn Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260202/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260202/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on 2 Bears 1 Cave, Tom Segura is still on his Euro-tour and couldn&amp;rsquo;t attend this recording. However, Bert Kreischer brought Mama-Bear LeeAnn. If you thought Bert was safe from being checked for an hour straight just because Tom wasn&amp;rsquo;t there, GUESS AGAIN. We first get into Bert&amp;rsquo;s recent weight loss. He actually legit looks good, but everyone (including himself) knows it won&amp;rsquo;t last too long. We get into the inner working of Bert and LeeAnn&amp;rsquo;s marriage.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 11 - 2 Bears 1 Cave 2 w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260203/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260203/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tom Segura is appearing from Europe via hologram and Bert Kreischer is very down in weight! It&amp;rsquo;s 2 Bears 1 Cave! Do you have wild hiking thoughts? Is making out cheating? These questions and more are answered. Plus, an appearance by Whitney Cummings after a &amp;ldquo;viewing&amp;rdquo; sparks some questions. Bert and Tom talk about So Over October with Christina P and LeeAnn Kreischer, and we ask &amp;ldquo;Who cooks ONE egg?</description></item><item><title>Ep. 10 - 2 Bears 1 Cave 2 w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260204/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2019 02:32:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260204/</guid><description>Podcast Description Now you can text both Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer on the &amp;ldquo;Community&amp;rdquo; app! Just like Sebastian and Ashton Kutcher and your other favorite celebrities. The Bears reminisce about some awkward moments of charity. We learn about Bert and LeeAnn&amp;rsquo;s first date, plus Jet Skis to Catalina, flying planes and Corvettes. Tom (818) 275-5526 Bert (323) 208-0844
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep. 09 - 2 Bears 1 Cave 2 w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260205/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2019 19:56:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260205/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 2 Bears are back in the 1 Cave and Sober October is almost at the half way point. The wheels are coming off in some ways and we find out if Bert&amp;rsquo;s family would be sad if he left us. Did you know you can text P. Diddy and other celebrities now? We put it to the test. Plus Spear Fishing, Private Jets and is Bert the Master of Impressions?</description></item><item><title>Ep. 08 - 2 Bears 1 Cave 2 w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260206/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260206/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sober October has begun and Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer are both handling the 1st week differently. Bert talks about flying sober and has a reminder about flying with Ric Flair. Tom has been having a lot of fun at the range - John Wick style. After WHOOP readings there is a small distraction looking at pretty women, then Bert calls Dr. Drew for a medical related question. Dr.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 07 - 2 Bears 1 Cave 2 w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260207/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260207/</guid><description>Podcast Description Greg Louganis hates Bert Kreischer. Tom Segura gets the scoop from Bert as he rehashes his time on reality TV show &amp;ldquo;Reality Bites Back.&amp;rdquo; The conversation shifts to one of the cast members on Bert&amp;rsquo;s season who created the craziest comedy class in all of history, so crazy that it caused Doug Stanhope to write an eviscerating blog about it. Tom and Bert need to settle a bet so they call their wives.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 06 - 2 Bears 1 Cave 2 w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260208/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260208/</guid><description>Podcast Description The show begins with Bert recapping his weekend in Atlantic City, NJ after riding his bike there from Philadelphia, PA. This episode also has a &amp;ldquo;special&amp;rdquo; appearance from both wives, Christina P and LeeAnn. Plus, a brand new challenge that will assuredly sweep the internet.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep. 05 | 2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260209/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260209/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s the dance video that has swept the nation and warmed the hearts of everyone. Everyone except one of the two bears. Tom Segura confronts Bert Kreischer about what he REALLY thought about his dance video and his plans for a rebuttal. Is a &amp;ldquo;Dance-Off&amp;rdquo; going down in the cave in the future?? Plus, there was an overwhelming amount of theme song submissions, the Bears listen to a few and decide on what the winner will be.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 04 - 2 Bears 1 Cave 2 w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260210/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260210/</guid><description>Podcast Description Between Tom and Bert, who do you think has dated a more &amp;ldquo;diverse&amp;rdquo; group of women? This brings both Bears to share intimate sexy stories about their wives. Who would you pick for Tom and Bert&amp;rsquo;s second wives? Both have somewhat of an idea and we even hear about Bert&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;coma fantasy.&amp;rdquo; Tentacle stuff, Down-Blousing and Bert as a Politician? It&amp;rsquo;s all inside The Cave!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep. 03 - 2 Bears 1 Cave 2w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260211/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260211/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Bears are back in the cave and Bert just got back from Bali just in time to see his career implode! Tom and Bert also discuss there show &amp;ldquo;Buzzed&amp;rdquo; that never saw the light of day, even though it was so much fun. The traveling has been extensive for these two, and Bert also recaps his trip to Australia where audiences clamored to meet the fattest working comedian today.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 02 - 2 Bears 1 Cave 2w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260212/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260212/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer are back for Episode 2 of 2 BEARS 1 CAVE! The two best friends get right into the stories, discussing Ralphie May, Joy Koy, Greg Giraldo and Jim Norton. Plus, Tom recaps all of his Theo trolling from the past few months. Who would be at the ultimate comedian slumber party? Bert&amp;rsquo;s daughter is starting to drive, which is getting dicey, and everything wraps up in a strip club.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 01 - 2 Bears 1 Cave 2w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260213/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260213/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s the debut of the biggest Super Podcast to date! 2 BEARS 1 CAVE! Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer have joined forces inside the YMH studios to get together as best friends and talk about anything and everything! Tom and Bert compare themselves to other duos, and some unsavory characters from WW2! It&amp;rsquo;s the morning time, will Bert have a drink? How about once Hannah appears? She seems to have inside knowledge on Bert&amp;rsquo;s vices.</description></item><item><title>2 Bears 1 Cave w/ Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer Intro | 2 Bears, 1 Cave with Tom Segura &amp; Bert Kreischer</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8484260214/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 21:29:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8484260214/</guid><description>Podcast Description A brand new podcast is coming out of YMH Studios with Tom Segura and Bert Kreischer! Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to rate, review, and subscribe!
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>