<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/categories/behind-the-tech-with-kevin-scott/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 15:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/categories/behind-the-tech-with-kevin-scott/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Bill Gates, Co-chair, Bill &amp; Melinda Gates Foundation</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500052/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500052/</guid>
        <description>BILL GATES: It was stunning, it was mind blowing. After the biology question I had them type in, “What do you say to a father with a sick child?” And it gave this very careful, excellent answer that was perhaps better than any of us in the room might have given. And so, it was like, wow, what is it – what is the scope of this thing? Because this is way better.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Rana el Kaliouby, Founder of Affectiva, Deputy CEO of Smart Eye, and Emotion AI Pioneer</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500051/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500051/</guid>
        <description>RANA EL KALIOUBY: Empathy and emotions are at the center of how connect and communicate as humans, and our emotional experiences drive our decision making, whether it’s a big decision or a small decision. It drives our learning, our memory. It drives this human connection.
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone. Welcome to Behind the Tech. I’m your host, Kevin Scott, Chief Technology Officer for Microsoft.
In this podcast, we’re going to get behind the tech.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Tobi Lütke: CEO and Founder, Shopify</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500050/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500050/</guid>
        <description>TOBI LÜTKE: I operate under the fundamental assumption that all companies are terrible, that – all of the ones ever created, which you know, like, some people don’t love me saying this, but like I think, to me, this is actually inspiring because, boy, building companies is worth it. Like, it’s like, I mean, all innovation around us is like – it comes from companies. It comes from journeys, it comes from – like entrepreneurships and builders getting together.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Year in Review 2022</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500049/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500049/</guid>
        <description>KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone. Welcome to Behind the Tech. I’m your host, Kevin Scott, Chief Technology Officer for Microsoft.
In this podcast, we’re going to get behind the tech. We’ll talk with some of the people who have made our modern tech world possible and understand what motivated them to create what they did. So, join me to maybe learn a little bit about the history of computing and get a few behind-the-scenes insights into what’s happening today.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Randall Munroe: XKCD Cartoonist, Author, &amp; Physicist</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500048/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500048/</guid>
        <description>RANDALL MUNROE: Then fell into doing comics where I can spend all day diving into some rabbit hole, and then draw comics about it. And then the next day, move on to a different thing. I found a way to grab all the candy in the candy store.
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone. Welcome to Behind the Tech. I’m your host, Kevin Scott, Chief Technology Officer for Microsoft.
In this podcast, we’re going to get behind the tech.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Sam Schillace: Deputy CTO, Microsoft</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500047/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500047/</guid>
        <description>SAM SCHILLACE: Find the thing you feel kinda guilty about being paid for and do the hell out of it. Like if you feel kind of guilty that you’re getting paid to do something it probably means you’re really good at it, and it’s fun for you, and if people are willing to pay for it, just go do the heck out of it.
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone. Welcome to Behind the Tech.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Simone Giertz: Inventor, entrepreneur &amp; robotics enthusiast</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500046/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500046/</guid>
        <description>SIMONE GIERTZ: in making and building things it’s like, when you start, you think that there’s, like, one right way of doing it and it’s like, no, there’s a hundred different ways of doing it. And maybe five of those are really good and 40 of those are really bad. But it’s like you can – there are so many different ways to – to skin a cat. But why would you want to skin a cat?</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Phil Spencer: CEO, Microsoft Gaming</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500045/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500045/</guid>
        <description>PHIL SPENCER: There was something magical about that feedback loop of actually seeing customers use the product that you had built that just, again, reinforced the whole loop about if you can spend more time in the creation on the things that really matter to your customers, you get so much more value out of that.
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone. Welcome to Behind the Tech. I’m your host, Kevin Scott, Chief Technology Officer for Microsoft.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - David Baszucki: Co-Founder and CEO, Roblox</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500044/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500044/</guid>
        <description>DAVID BASZUCKI: Time and time again, I think we try to solve things or figure them out ourselves rather than take a step back and think through, could the community do this better than us if we gave them the tools and the functionality?
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone. Welcome to Behind the Tech. I’m your host, Kevin Scott, Chief Technology Officer for Microsoft.
In this podcast, we’re going to get behind the tech.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Alexis Ohanian: Reddit Co-Founder and CEO of 776</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500043/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500043/</guid>
        <description>HOOK: I hoped people would say, “I read it on Reddit.” I don’t think anyone to date has, but that was the dream.
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone. Welcome to Behind the Tech. I’m your host, Kevin Scott, Chief Technology Officer for Microsoft.
In this podcast, we’re going to get behind the tech. We’ll talk with some of the people who have made our modern tech world possible and understand what motivated them to create what they did.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Irma Olguin: CEO &amp; Co-Founder of Bitwise Industries</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500042/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500042/</guid>
        <description>IRMA OLGUIN: I know that technology generally has a bad rap for, like, gentrification and those types of things and the effect on neighborhoods. But when you literally skill the folks who are from those neighborhoods into these jobs, they get to turn around and give back to their neighborhoods.
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone. Welcome to Behind the Tech. I’m your host, Kevin Scott, Chief Technology Officer for Microsoft.
In this podcast, we’re going to get behind the tech.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Neal Stephenson, Award-winning science fiction author</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500041/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500041/</guid>
        <description>NEAL STEPHENSON: I think I’m a little bit of a freak, even among writers. I hear other writers talking about self-discipline and writers block and the struggle. It’s not like that for me. I mean, I don’t mean to be egotistical or anything like that, but at no point in my career have I ever felt as though I were inflicting some kind of discipline on myself. It’s just what I like to do.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Dr. Daniela Rus, Director of MIT Computer Science and AI Lab</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500040/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500040/</guid>
        <description>DANIELA RUS: I believe that we can stretch ourselves and go to a different stage, where we think about soft robots that are inspired in shape by the animal kingdom with its form diversity, by the natural world, with its form diversity, and even by the built environment. Because then, we would have so much more potential for applications.
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone. Welcome to Behind the Tech. I’m your host, Kevin Scott, Chief Technology Officer for Microsoft.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Year in Review 2021</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500039/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500039/</guid>
        <description>KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone. Welcome to Behind the Tech. I’m your host, Kevin Scott, Chief Technology Officer for Microsoft.
In this podcast, we’re going to get behind the tech. We’ll talk with some of the people who have made our modern tech world possible and understand what motivated them to create what they did. So, join me to maybe learn a little bit about the history of computing and get a few behind-the-scenes insights into what’s happening today.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Dr. Steven Pinker: Psychologist, psycholinguist and author</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500038/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500038/</guid>
        <description>STEVEN PINKER: It isn’t as if this universe contains some force called progress. That’s kind of mystical. In fact, if anything, the universe tries to grind us down. It’s constantly throwing pandemics at us, and – and natural disasters and entropy, things wearing down, and falling apart and rotting. To the extent that life gets better, it’s only because people have applied their ingenuity to try to make it better. We’ve invented antibiotics and vaccines, and intergovernmental organizations, and liberal democracies.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Justine Ezarik: Digital influencer, author, and actress</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500037/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500037/</guid>
        <description>[MUSIC]
JUSTINE: Everyone’s like, oh, like, have goals and stick to them. And I don’t believe that at all. I mean, I think it’s great to have goals, but I think if you stray from that goal, you could potentially find something way better.
[MUSIC]
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone. Welcome to Behind the Tech. I&amp;rsquo;m your host, Kevin Scott, Chief Technology Officer for Microsoft.
In this podcast, we&amp;rsquo;re going to get behind the tech.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Dr. Peter Lee: Microsoft Research &amp; Incubations</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500036/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500036/</guid>
        <description>[MUSIC]
PETER LEE: What we’re seeing today is that more and more, what we do, and even just to survive as a civilization depends on researchers and scientists being able to get drawn in and solve problems, respond to crises, help us become hopefully more resilient to the future. And that sort of crisis response science, I think, is getting to be incredibly important. And it won’t work if society doesn’t trust what we’re doing.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Steven Bathiche: Microsoft Technical Fellow</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500035/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500035/</guid>
        <description>[MUSIC]
STEVIE BATHICHE: A big part of invention, engineering, product development is managing complexity, and moving complexity around, in fact. Like, if you think about, high level, what we can do and if you understand the different systems and the different disciplines, you can effectively move complexity around where it’s hard in one area, but not so hard in another area.
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone. Welcome to Behind the Tech. I&amp;rsquo;m your host, Kevin Scott, Chief Technology Officer for Microsoft.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Chase Jarvis: Entrepreneur, artist and photographer</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500034/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500034/</guid>
        <description>[MUSIC]
CHASE JARVIS: I believe that it’s our job as adults to unlearn a lot of those constraints that school and career counselors and parents and often people who meant really well for us, you know, that they placed on us so that we can reach our true potential.
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone. Welcome to Behind the Tech. I&amp;rsquo;m your host, Kevin Scott, Chief Technology Officer for Microsoft.
In this podcast, we&amp;rsquo;re going to get behind the tech.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Dr. David Baker: Director of the Institute for Protein Design, University of Washington</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500033/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500033/</guid>
        <description>[MUSIC]
DAVID BAKER:
Generally, in engineering and biology, if you want to solve a problem, you go look in nature for a protein that already does something similar, and then you modify it a bit. The relationship between sequence and structure has been really mysterious, but now we can actually design proteins with intent to do new things. So, I think it’s just getting to be very exciting.
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Kimberly Bryant: CEO &amp; Founder of Black Girls Code</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500032/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500032/</guid>
        <description>[MUSIC]
KIMBERLY BRYANT: I think we need more organizational support, not just at Black Girls Code, but any organization that’s doing this work as a nonprofit. We can’t do it alone. So for me, it’s always about how can we have this magnified effort of different organizations that are all working collectively to elevate girls in the STEM fields, and particularly in computer science?
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone. Welcome to Behind the Tech.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Ashley Llorens: Artificial intelligence and robotics</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500031/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500031/</guid>
        <description>[MUSIC]
ASHLEY LLORENS: Can we start to set some audacious goals around enabling as many people as possible on the planet to live a long, healthy life, creating an atmosphere of shared prosperity, and what is the role of AI in doing that? To me, these big societal narratives should be at the top level of abstraction in terms of what we’re talking about. And then everything else is derived from that.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Jacob Collier and Ben Bloomberg: Bonus Episode</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500030/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500030/</guid>
        <description>JACOB COLLIER:
I can imagine a world where there’s some kind of creative feedback from human to AI where the human gets a cool idea based off something that the human could never have imagined. If it generates ideas or makes space, then humans will fill it and that’s cool. That’s exciting.
[MUSIC]
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone. Welcome to Behind the Tech. I&amp;rsquo;m your host, Kevin Scott, Chief Technology Officer for Microsoft.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Jacob Collier &amp; Ben Bloomberg: Grammy award-winning duo</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500029/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500029/</guid>
        <description>JACOB COLLIER: Honestly, I think mastery is a myth. I don’t think it exists. I think that no ideas are ever finished or new. Everything is just recombined. And I love that. Because it means that we get to be artists rather than inventors. We can paint with what we know. And so I guess my job as a musician has been to learn as much as I possibly can.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Dr. Mae Jemison: Astronaut, engineer, physician and educator</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500028/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500028/</guid>
        <description>MAE JEMISON: 100 Year Starship is about making sure the capabilities for human interstellar flight exists within the next 100 years. Capabilities, not building a starship or launching a starship, but having the capabilities. And the reason for that was the challenge that it requires, right? The radical leaps in knowledge that are required. We can’t ease up on this.
[MUSIC]
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone. Welcome to Behind the Tech. I’m your host, Kevin Scott, Chief Technology Officer for Microsoft.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Behind the Tech: 2020 Year in Review</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500027/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500027/</guid>
        <description>[MUSIC]
KEVIN SCOTT: I think it’s really important for all of us to sort of share our stories because, you know, there are interesting lessons in there. But maybe most importantly, understanding each other a little bit better shows us how I do honestly believe that we are vastly, vastly more similar than we are different, and that sometimes, these stereotypes that we have of each other are just obstacles that stand in the way of each of us achieving our full potential.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Oren Etzioni, PhD: CEO of Allen Institute for AI</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500026/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500026/</guid>
        <description>[MUSIC]
OREN ETZIONI: Whose responsibility is it? The responsibility and liability has to ultimately rest with a person. You can’t say, “Hey, you know, look, my car ran you over, it’s an AI car, I don’t know what it did, it’s not my fault, right?” You as the driver or maybe it’s the manufacturer if there’s some malfunction, but people have to be responsible for the behavior of the machines.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Charlie Stross: Award-winning sci-fi author</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500025/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500025/</guid>
        <description>CHARLIE STROSS: You know the difference between a pessimist and an optimist? The pessimist, the glass is half empty. The optimist, the glass is half full. The engineer, the glass is twice the size it needs to be. And the visionary, okay, we need to figure out how to fill this bigger glass.
KEVIN SCOTT: (Laughter) Indeed.
[MUSIC]
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone. Welcome to Behind the Tech. I&amp;rsquo;m your host, Kevin Scott, Chief Technology Officer for Microsoft.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Daphne Koller, PhD: CEO and founder of insitro</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500024/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500024/</guid>
        <description>[MUSIC]
DAPHNE KOLLER: I think one of the very, very thin silver linings around this very dire situation that we find ourselves in is that there is, I hope, a growing appreciation among the general public for what science is able to do for us today and how much of that ability rests on decades of basic science work by many, many people.
[MUSIC]
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone. Welcome to Behind the Tech.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Tom-Daniel: Neuroscientist and bioengineer</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500023/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500023/</guid>
        <description>[MUSIC]
Tom Daniel: Therein lies the massive fundamental difference between sort of synthetic systems and living systems. It&amp;rsquo;s that ability to be plastic, and in part, we built systems that aren&amp;rsquo;t going to change, on purpose. We don&amp;rsquo;t want them to change. Heaven forbid should my car decide, you know, “Nah, I&amp;rsquo;m not going to do what you say, you know? I&amp;rsquo;m sorry, Hal, I can&amp;rsquo;t do that.”
[MUSIC]
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Drew Endy: Bioengineering Pioneer</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500022/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500022/</guid>
        <description>[MUSIC]
DREW ENDY: We&amp;rsquo;ve inherited this stuff, which is three plus billion years old, going on four billion years old. It&amp;rsquo;s pretty sophisticated. You lift the lid on it and understand how it&amp;rsquo;s working. It&amp;rsquo;s unbelievable, right, the layers of sophistication and the architecture and how things appear to have been selected to perform. I mean, it&amp;rsquo;s stunning.
[MUSIC]
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone. Welcome to Behind the Tech. I&amp;rsquo;m your host, Kevin Scott, Chief Technology Officer for Microsoft.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Dr. Eric Horvitz: Chief Scientific Officer, Microsoft</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500021/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500021/</guid>
        <description>ERIC HORVITZ: I think that we know so little even today and there’s so much possible, that I think our grandkids will live in a very different world where biology will have played a major role in almost everything that’s being touched, including the materials that we build systems from. And so, I’m very excited about the possibilities.
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone. Welcome to Behind the Tech. I&amp;rsquo;m your host, Kevin Scott, Chief Technology Officer for Microsoft.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Kevin Scott: Reprogramming the American Dream</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500020/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500020/</guid>
        <description>[MUSIC]
KEVIN SCOTT: We&amp;rsquo;re not on some sort of inexorable path where we&amp;rsquo;re building these technologies and like things are going to unfold in this very particular way that it&amp;rsquo;s not inclusive. Like we get to choose our future, and I think if we make careful choices that that future can be like very, very inclusive.
[MUSIC]
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone. Welcome to Behind the Tech. I&amp;rsquo;m your host, Kevin Scott, Chief Technology Officer for Microsoft.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Stanford University Professor, technologist, and researcher in AI</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500019/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500019/</guid>
        <description>[MUSIC]
PERCY LIANG: At the end of the day, you know, we&amp;rsquo;re computer scientists building, you know, systems for the world, and I think humans make mistakes. They have fallacies, they have biases, they&amp;rsquo;re not super transparent sometimes, and why inherit all these when, maybe, you can design, you know, a better system? And I think computers, already, clearly have many other advantages that humans don&amp;rsquo;t have.
[MUSIC]
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Chris Urmson: CEO of Aurora – Autonomous Driving</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500018/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500018/</guid>
        <description>[MUSIC]
SCOTT URMSON: People talk about Silicon Valley engineers being risk-takers. I think it’s actually the opposite. It’s the realization that if you go and try one of these things and you’re actually good at what you do, if it fails, it fails. You’ll have a job the next day at somewhere else, right? And you’ll have this wealth of experience that people will value.
[MUSIC]
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone. Welcome to Behind the Tech.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Behind the Tech: 2019 Year in Review</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500017/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500017/</guid>
        <description>[MUSIC]
KEVIN SCOTT: All of us every day should be asking, like, how is it that the thing that I&amp;rsquo;m doing right now is going to positively accrue to the overall social good. Like, if you can&amp;rsquo;t answer that question in an affirmative way, then maybe you&amp;rsquo;re doing the wrong damn thing.
[MUSIC]
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone. Welcome to Behind the Tech. I&amp;rsquo;m your host, Kevin Scott, Chief Technology Officer for Microsoft.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Danny Hillis: Inventor, entrepreneur, scientist</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500016/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500016/</guid>
        <description>[MUSIC]
DANNY HILLIS: Social media is, you know, was never by itself, the thing that was going to, you know, advance humanity, nor is it the thing that&amp;rsquo;s going to destroy humanity it’s actually a tool that we&amp;rsquo;re going to learn to use with time like we learn to use fire.
[MUSIC]
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone. Welcome to Behind the Tech. I&amp;rsquo;m your host, Kevin Scott, Chief Technology Officer for Microsoft.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - danah boyd: Researcher, activist, tech scholar</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500015/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500015/</guid>
        <description>[MUSIC]
danah boyd: The only reason I applied was that this boy in my class told me that it was a program for men, it was not for girls. And I was, like, &amp;ldquo;Hmfft,&amp;rdquo; I&amp;rsquo;m going to go. (Laughter.) It was very simple. And, you know, that kept happening, where when people told me I didn&amp;rsquo;t belong, I just became determined to stay.
[MUSIC]
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone. Welcome to Behind the Tech.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Neha Narkhede: Author, entrepreneur and cofounder of Confluent</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500014/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500014/</guid>
        <description>NEHA NARKHEDE: So you know, why we wanted to open source it is this was an observation we made is, you know, this trend that you know technology companies are going to essentially be defined in software, you know, not just use more software, but literally all the actions and decisions in a company happen through software. It&amp;rsquo;s going to be a trend.
[MUSIC]
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone. Welcome to Behind the Tech.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Sam Altman: Entrepreneurial prodigy, Y Combinator President and OpenAI CEO</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500013/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500013/</guid>
        <description>SAM ALTMAN: You know, the two strategies to succeed in life are you either go super deep in one field of knowledge, or you go extremely broad. And I&amp;rsquo;ve always been going extremely broad and find the connections, and sort of be good at the intersection.
[MUSIC]
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone. Welcome to Behind the Tech. I&amp;rsquo;m your host, Kevin Scott, Chief Technology Officer for Microsoft.
In this podcast, we&amp;rsquo;re going to get behind the tech.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Bill Coughran: Human-Centered AI</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500012/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500012/</guid>
        <description>BILL COUGHRAN: What I&amp;rsquo;ve always done in the last many years is give you my advice as a leader inside a company, but then I will also give you my advice as an individual. And I think, to me, that&amp;rsquo;s been one of the things that I think has bonded people to me over the years.
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone. Welcome to Behind the Tech. I&amp;rsquo;m your host, Kevin Scott, Chief Technology Officer for Microsoft.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Fei-Fei Li: Human-Centered AI</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500011/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500011/</guid>
        <description>FEI-FEI LI: (VOICEOVER) Whenever humanity creates a technology as powerful and potentially useful as AI, we owe it to ourselves and our future generation to make it right.
[MUSIC]
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone. Welcome to Behind the Tech. I&amp;rsquo;m your host, Kevin Scott, Chief Technology Officer for Microsoft.
In this podcast, we&amp;rsquo;re going to get behind the tech. We&amp;rsquo;ll talk with some of the people who have made our modern tech world possible and understand what motivated them to create what they did.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Surya Ganguli: Innovator in artificial intelligence</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500010/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500010/</guid>
        <description>SURYA GANGULI: (VOICEOVER) A lot of people, of course, listening to your podcast and out there in the world have become incredibly successful based on the rise of digital technology. But I think we need to think about digital technology now as a suboptimal legacy technology. To achieve energy efficient artificial intelligence, we&amp;rsquo;ve really got to take cues from biology.
[MUSIC]
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone. Welcome to Behind the Tech. I&amp;rsquo;m your host, Kevin Scott, Chief Technology Officer for Microsoft.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Reid Hoffman: Investor, author &amp; entrepreneur</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500009/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500009/</guid>
        <description>REID HOFFMAN: (VOICEOVER) Prior to going to China, when I go other places from Silicon Valley, I would say, &amp;ldquo;Oh, you&amp;rsquo;re in slow motion, like, you&amp;rsquo;re moving slowly.&amp;rdquo; Because one of the things we&amp;rsquo;ve really learned here in Silicon Valley is that speed and speed to scale really, really matters.
You go to China and you go, &amp;ldquo;Oh, we&amp;rsquo;re in slow motion.&amp;rdquo;
[MUSIC]
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone. Welcome to Behind the Tech.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Jaron Lanier: Father of Virtual Reality, Renaissance man</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500008/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500008/</guid>
        <description>JARON LANIER: (VOICEOVER) I&amp;rsquo;m worried about where we are right now. I just feel like our present Internet is destroying societies and democracies and economies. I think it&amp;rsquo;s bringing down civilization. It&amp;rsquo;s bad. We really screwed this thing up.
[MUSIC]
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone. Welcome to Behind the Tech. I&amp;rsquo;m your host, Kevin Scott, Chief Technology Officer for Microsoft.
In this podcast, we&amp;rsquo;re going to get behind the tech. We&amp;rsquo;ll talk with some of the people who have made our modern tech world possible and understand what motivated them to create what they did.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Dio Gonzalez: Mixed Reality is becoming part of our day-to-day life!</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500007/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500007/</guid>
        <description>DIO GONZALEZ: (VOICEOVER) And so they made us draw lines, not even curved lines, it was just straight lines. And they explained us how to do it. Like, you find the formula, then you program it, and then tah-dah, lines. (Laughter.)
And that was like my &amp;ndash; like &amp;ldquo;ah-hah&amp;rdquo; moment and my mind exploded….
But that part, when we were able to draw pictures, that&amp;rsquo;s when I&amp;rsquo;m like, &amp;ldquo;That&amp;rsquo;s it, I&amp;rsquo;m in.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Wences Casares: Betting on Bitcoin in a big way</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500006/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500006/</guid>
        <description>WENCES CASARES (VOICEOVER): I cannot change it nobody can change it &amp;ndash; not government, no company. So, that&amp;rsquo;s one thing. And the other one is it&amp;rsquo;s uncensorable. Nobody can keep you from acquiring Bitcoin. Nobody can keep you from sending Bitcoin to anyone, and nobody can keep you from holding Bitcoin.
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone. Welcome to Behind the Tech. I&amp;rsquo;m your host, Kevin Scott, chief technology officer for Microsoft. In this podcast, we&amp;rsquo;re going to get behind the tech.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Danielle Feinberg: Pixar’s Academy Award-winning Computer Scientist</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500005/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500005/</guid>
        <description>[MUSIC]
DANIELLE FEINBERG: You know, on WALL-E it&amp;rsquo;s towards the end and we&amp;rsquo;re racing to beat the clock to get it done in time. And all of a sudden, the director says, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m so sorry, but I&amp;rsquo;ve realized that if I make this critical change in the story, that it&amp;rsquo;s going to make it a better film. And I know it means you guys are going to have to throw some of this out and start over.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Judy Estrin: Co-creator in Developing Internet-Engineer, Entrepreneur &amp; Executive</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500004/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500004/</guid>
        <description>JUDY ESTRIN: (Voiceover) Right now, so much of what is going on in the industry is driven by the values of scale and speed. It is about maximizing growth. It is about maximizing connectivity. What about thinking about what we&amp;rsquo;re losing in those values. There&amp;rsquo;s nothing wrong with growth, but not at the expense of humanity.
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi, everyone. Welcome to Behind the Tech. I&amp;rsquo;m your host, Kevin Scott, Chief Technology Officer for Microsoft.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Andrew Ng: Influential Leader in Artificial Intelligence</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500003/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500003/</guid>
        <description>ANDREW NG: With the rise of technology often comes greater concentration of power in smaller numbers of people&amp;rsquo;s hands, and I think that this creates greater risk of ever-growing wealth inequality as well. To be really candid, I think that with the rise of the last few ways of technology, we actually did a great job creating wealth in the East and the West Coast, but we actually did leave large parts of the country behind, and I would love for this next one to bring everyone along with us.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Alice Steinglass: Code.org Expanding Access to Computer Science</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500002/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500002/</guid>
        <description>ALICE STEINGLASS: (Voiceover) It was an 8086. At the time, 8086 was already out of date, but I had one. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t until about senior year in high school when I realized what I could do with it. I have a little brother, and so I made it so that when he tried to log into the computer, it would just beep really loudly. And then it would put up this huge ASCII warning error that was like &amp;ldquo;Intruder, intruder.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Behind The Tech with Kevin Scott - Anders Hejlsberg: A Craftsman of Computer Language</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308500001/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308500001/</guid>
        <description>ANDERS HEJLSBERG: (VOICEOVER) Surely. Anything can be done here. Look at this diagram. I just drew it for you. Just go and make it so, right?
No, coding is hard and it continues to be hard, and code gets bigger and bigger and bigger but our brains are not getting any bigger, and this is largely a brain exercise.
KEVIN SCOTT: Hi everyone. Welcome to Behind the Tech. I&amp;rsquo;m your host, Kevin Scott, Chief Technology Officer for Microsoft.</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
