<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Keep it Positive, Sweetie on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/keep-it-positive-sweetie/</link><description>Recent content in Keep it Positive, Sweetie on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 07:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/keep-it-positive-sweetie/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>In This New Season with Megan Ashley | Keep it Positive, Sweetie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3183680001/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3183680001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season 3 Episode 2 | Oftentimes when people get in the limelight, they hide their love for God and only acknowledge Him publicly during their acceptance speeches. But today&amp;rsquo;s guest loves God publicly and proudly. I invited Megan Ashley on the show to discuss her faith and how she&amp;rsquo;s navigating this new season in her life post her divorce and life after Know For Sure podcast. Get your notes ready because Megan preached a good WORD!</description></item><item><title>Father's Day with Kirk Franklin | Keep it Positive, Sweetie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3183680002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3183680002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season 3 Episode 1 | We&amp;rsquo;re kicking season 3 off with the one and only, Kirk Franklin. Not only is he one of my favorite artists, but his music helped me during some of the toughest seasons of my life. In this episode you get to learn about the man behind the mega hits &amp;ndash; and he should high key be a comedian. We talk about everything from his upbringing, his new documentary, his career and so much more.</description></item><item><title>Where There's a Will, There's a Way with Will Packer | Keep it Positive, Sweetie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3183680003/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3183680003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season 2 Episode 10 | For our season finale, I sat down with my family and super producer, Will Packer. He&amp;rsquo;s such a great conversationalist, so much so, that he started interviewing me. We talked about everything from our early beginnings in the business, THE Oscar&amp;rsquo;s moment, the strike and much more. Thank y&amp;rsquo;all so much for tuning in this season! I love y&amp;rsquo;all and don&amp;rsquo;t forget to keep it positive, sweetie!</description></item><item><title>Positive Outcomes | Keep it Positive, Sweetie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3183680004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3183680004/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, I&amp;rsquo;m watching your video submissions for Positive Outcomes letters and y&amp;rsquo;all told me ALL of your business! Thank you for trusting KIPS to be a safe space. I just want to let you know that I love you guys and I see you. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to keep it positive, Sweetie.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Still I Rise with Gocha Hawkins-Haynes | Keep it Positive, Sweetie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3183680005/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3183680005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season 2 Episode 8 | This week I sat down with my longtime friend Gocha, who has been through a lot and has turned her life around. Gocha is a walking testimony with a story to tell and spreads positivity wherever she goes. She&amp;rsquo;s turned her trials into triumph, becoming a successful entrepreneur, opening a few restaurants and now even franchising them. God has had his hand on her and will continue to keep blessing her.</description></item><item><title>The Entertainment Biz- Seasons of Uncertainty w/ Shornell &amp; Manny | Keep it Positive, Sweetie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3183680006/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3183680006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season 2 Episode 7 | Everyone knows it takes a village to pull off production. There are so many departments such as glam, costume design, crafty and more who work to bring your favorite shows and movies to life. I&amp;rsquo;m so grateful for my hairstylist, Shornell and MUA Manny who work with me on set. The pandemic and the SAG-AFTRA strike hit a lot of us in the industry very hard.</description></item><item><title>Becoming a Bawse with Kimberly Blackwell | Keep it Positive, Sweetie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3183680007/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3183680007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season 2 Episode 6 | This week Kimberly Blackwell joined me on the couch and we caught up like the cameras weren&amp;rsquo;t rolling. Sometimes you meet people unexpectedly and you hope they are as dope as they seem online; Kim was that and so much more. We talked about ALL of the things such as being hyper independent women, love and friendships, and entrepreneurship. She blessed me with a good word and I hope y&amp;rsquo;all catch it.</description></item><item><title>Creating a Life of Longevity with Kenny Burns | Keep it Positive, Sweetie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3183680008/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3183680008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season 2 Episode 5 | This week&amp;rsquo;s guest and I go WAY back! I&amp;rsquo;ve invited my big brother Kenny Burns on the show. We talk about navigating the entertainment industry, networking, how to keep your integrity and so much more. To watch his trajectory for well over a decade has been beyond inspiring. Make sure you pay attention because he is dropping some gems.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Heart to Heart with Dinorah Peña | Keep it Positive, Sweetie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3183680009/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3183680009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season 2 | Episode 4. When I met this week’s guest, I had no idea how much my life would change. KIPS Gang has requested my manager, Dinorah Peña on the show since season 1 and now she’s on the couch! Not only is she my manager, but she is my sister and my friend. We dive deep in this episode discussing our careers, faith, healing through issues with parents, and more.</description></item><item><title>Help Is On The Way with Kountry Wayne | Keep it Positive, Sweetie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3183680010/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 14:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3183680010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season 2 Episode 3 | I’m so excited to welcome my friend and Praise This co-star Kountry Wayne to the couch! We talked about his experience growing up, his past life as a drug dealer, his love for God, road to success and so much more. Make sure you buy his new book “Help Is on The Way: Stay Up and Live Your Truth” and watch his Netflix special ” A Woman’s Prayer”.</description></item><item><title>More Than What Meets The Eye with Eva Marcille | Keep it Positive, Sweetie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3183680011/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3183680011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season 2 Episode 2 | This week, I am sitting with the talented and beautiful, Eva Marcille! Many of you may know her as America’s Next Top Model or from the many TV shows she’s been in, but she’s so much more than what meets the eye — a true beauty on the inside just as much as she is on the outside. Get ready and grab your tissues as we dive deep and get deep with Eva.</description></item><item><title>Higher is Waiting with Tyler Perry | Keep it Positive, Sweetie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3183680012/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3183680012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season 2 Episode 1 | Welcome back SWEETIES! I am so excited to have my big brother, boss, and one of my biggest inspirations, Tyler Perry, on the couch. Ya’ll have no idea how monumental this moment is for me — for US! We talked about everything from his upbringing, to fear, my man issues and more! Get your notebook out for these notes, because he dropped so many gems.</description></item><item><title>Dating Women of My Caliber | Keep it Positive, Sweetie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3183680013/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 07:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3183680013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season 1 Episode 11 | As we bring this season to an end, I invited my brother Cyhi on the show to discuss dating a woman of my caliber. Over the years, Cyhi and I have had countless talks about dating, love and relationships. I appreciate his perspective because he gives it to you straight, no chaser. Join us on the couch to listen to our raw and unfiltered conversation.</description></item><item><title>Sisterhood | Keep it Positive, Sweetie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3183680014/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 07:00:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3183680014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season 1 Episode 10 | This week I have my sistas on the couch. Join us as we talk about sisterhood, love, relationships, boundaries and much more. I pray that all of the women out there have a village of women that supports and pours into them like mine, because I truly don&amp;rsquo;t know what I&amp;rsquo;d do without my girls. Get into the kiki that I had with my girls @raiyonda @ninacemonewright @loveari_2112 !</description></item><item><title>My Salvation Story | Keep it Positive, Sweetie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3183680015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 07:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3183680015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season 1 Episode 9 | So many of you have shared how my love for God has been inspiring and I wanted to share my salvation story with you. We all have our own journey in our faith walk and one is not greater than the other. It’s never too late to draw nearer to God. My hope is that this episode blesses you real good and encourages you to strengthen your bond with Him.</description></item><item><title>Purging Season | Keep it Positive, Sweetie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3183680016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3183680016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season 1 Episode 8 |While purging is very necessary to get rid of dead weight and start anew, the process isn’t always easy. You can know that you need to do the right thing, but the right decision doesn’t always feel pleasant. Letting go of people and things that you love and that have been in your life for some time can be very lonely. Join me on the couch as I talk about how I’m going through and growing through this purging season in my life.</description></item><item><title>Navigating Anxiety | Keep it Positive, Sweetie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3183680017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3183680017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season 1 Episode 7 | In today&amp;rsquo;s society, we are going through so much and a lot of us are going through it alone and in silence. Our anxiety has gotten worse since the pandemic and we&amp;rsquo;re coping the best we know how. Come join my therapist @delenazimmermantherapy and I on my couch as we discuss how to navigate anxiety. Y&amp;rsquo;all get a glimpse into our therapy sessions and let me tell you&amp;hellip;Delena keeps it REAL and gets me right together!</description></item><item><title>Soft Life | Keep it Positive, Sweetie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3183680018/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3183680018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season 1 Episode 6 | OK now, KIPS gang. If you didn’t already know it, I am in my soft life era, like FR FR. I have chosen to live more in my feminine and do the things that feel good, alleviate stress, bring me joy, glorify God and create an environment for me to thrive. It can be as simple as running a bath for myself, listening to worship music, sipping a glass of champagne in lounge wear, or time with my closest girls.</description></item><item><title>Love The Way God Intended | Keep it Positive, Sweetie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3183680019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3183680019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season 1 Episode 5 | Y&amp;rsquo;all I feel like this is my year for LOVE. I am ready for my man, my man, my man! So often, we start dating someone and God is nowhere to be found. If we gon do this thing, I need it be rooted in Jesus&amp;rsquo; name&amp;hellip;okay!!! Come join me on the couch with my pastors Shameka Daniels and Dr. Dharius Daniels of Change Church in Atlanta and New Jersey as they keep it real and spicy with me!</description></item><item><title>Dating In Your 40's | Keep it Positive, Sweetie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3183680020/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 07:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3183680020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season 1 Episode 4 | Whew chile the ghetto! Dating in today’s society is HARD, especially with social media and all of the apps. But dating in your 40’s seems to be even harder. Is it just me?! Ladies, the older we get, the more we know ourselves, therefore we know exactly what we want and don’t want. Our tolerance for BS is very low. Come join me on the couch as I share some of my dating stories, the good and the bad and much more.</description></item><item><title>Body Count with Jasmin "Watch Jazzy" Brown | Keep it Positive, Sweetie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3183680021/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 07:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3183680021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season 1 Episode 3 | Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about SEX, baby &amp;ndash; cause some of us want a freak in the morning and a freak in the evening 👀 Ladies, is it just me, or are you also tired of how society shames you for your body count, or how men oftentimes use it against you? I mean let&amp;rsquo;s be real, most of our thoughts and mindset around sex are just plain-old antiquated, in my opinion.</description></item><item><title>Get to Know Me | Keep it Positive, Sweetie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3183680022/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 07:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3183680022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season 1 Episode 2 | Whew, this is a lot! For years I have remained guarded and have only shared the pieces of me that I felt safe to do so. But for some reason, this year I felt God calling me to be vulnerable and most importantly, be safe being myself in every room. I&amp;rsquo;m excited (and nervous) to share my heart with you and I&amp;rsquo;m glad to be here, at my most rawest, realest, and confident.</description></item><item><title>Survivor's Remorse with Isaac Carree | Keep it Positive, Sweetie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3183680023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 07:00:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3183680023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season 1 Episode 1 | Survivor&amp;rsquo;s remorse is when a person has feelings of guilt because they survived a life-threatening situation when others did not. The truth is, that same type of guilt can bleed into our day to day lives as we experience our own ascension and those we love perhaps are still figuring things out &amp;ndash; and sometimes even making us feel bad for how much we have accomplished.</description></item><item><title>Trailer | Keep it Positive, Sweetie | Keep it Positive, Sweetie</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3183680024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 23:08:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3183680024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to keep it Positive, Sweetie!
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>