<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Trump&#39;s Trials on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/tags/trumps-trials/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Trump&#39;s Trials on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 20:52:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/trumps-trials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>&#39;The boss is not going to leave under any circumstances&#39; | Trump&#39;s Trials</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/5894800001/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 20:52:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/5894800001/</guid>
        <description>Podcast Description This week, Scott Detrow and NPR political editor/correspondent Domenico Montanaro discuss leaked confidential videos of two former Trump lawyers and what those videos could mean for the Georgia election interference case. Plus a new development in the January 6 case. Their guest is NYU&amp;rsquo;s Melissa Murray. Topics include: -The potential consequences of leaked videos in court — and the court of public opinion
-Trump lawyer Sidney Powell admitting she &amp;lsquo;didn&amp;rsquo;t know much&amp;rsquo; about election fraud.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Why lawyers say &#39;never write anything down&#39; | Trump&#39;s Trials</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/5894800002/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 17:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/5894800002/</guid>
        <description>Podcast Description On this inaugural episode of Trump&amp;rsquo;s Trials, host Scott Detrow and NPR political editor/correspondent Domenico Montanaro break down this week&amp;rsquo;s testimony from former President Donald Trump and his daughter Ivanka in the New York civil fraud case brought against the Trump Organization. This week&amp;rsquo;s guest is NYU&amp;rsquo;s Melissa Murray. Topics include: -Arguments in the New York case so far
-Whether Donald Trump actually cares if he loses -Why Trump sounded a lot different on the witness stand this week than he has in the past — while Ivanka, notably, did not</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Welcome to Trump&#39;s Trials | Trump&#39;s Trials</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/5894800003/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 21:57:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/5894800003/</guid>
        <description>Podcast Description NPR&amp;rsquo;s Scott Detrow hosts a weekly discussion about the latest courtroom drama, testimony, and legal maneuvering in the criminal and civil cases facing former President Donald Trump — and what it all means for American democracy — with analysis from NPR political editor/correspondent Domenico Montanaro.
Sign up for sponsor-free episodes and support NPR&amp;rsquo;s political journalism at plus.npr.org. Email the show at trumpstrials@npr.org
Transcript </description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
