<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Trump's Trials on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/trumps-trials/</link><description>Recent content in Trump's Trials on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 17:41:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/trumps-trials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Jack Smith's big gamble | Trump's Trials</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5894800007/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 17:41:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5894800007/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Trump&amp;rsquo;s Trials, host Scott Detrow and Domenico Montanaro are joined by former Deputy Assistant Attorney General Harry Litman. This week&amp;rsquo;s focus: the January 6th federal election interference case. Prosecutor, Special Counsel Jack Smith, made an unusual move, and sidestepped the appeals court and went straight to the Supreme Court to answer a fundamental question at the heart of the case:. Can presidents be criminally prosecuted for crimes they are allegedly committed while in office?</description></item><item><title>Should the Jan 6 trial be televised? Trump and many journalists say yes | Trump's Trials</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5894800006/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 17:27:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5894800006/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Trump&amp;rsquo;s Trials, host Scott Detrow and Domenico Montanaro are joined by NPR Justice Correspondent Carrie Johnson. We focus on the January 6th federal election interference case led by special counsel Jack Smith. The case is scheduled to go to trial in March in Washington, D.C., and it might be coming to a TV near you. Yes, Trump and some media outlets are requesting cameras in the courtroom.</description></item><item><title>Trump's trials are about to collide with the political calendar | Trump's Trials</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5894800005/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 17:08:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5894800005/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Trump&amp;rsquo;s Trials, guest host Miles Parks and Domenico Montanaro look at how one judge, Aileen Cannon, could be slow-walking the federal classified documents case in Florida. Delays in that case could impact the three other criminal trials Trump is facing — and put legal and political calendars ahead of the 2024 race on a collision course. Plus an update from the Georgia election case and the gag order from the New York civil fraud case.</description></item><item><title>Why gag orders against Trump haven't stopped his attacks | Trump's Trials</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5894800004/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 18:38:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5894800004/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Scott Detrow and NPR political editor/correspondent Domenico Montanaro discuss gag orders in multiple cases against President Donald Trump and his attempts to weaponize them politically. Plus an update in the New York Civil trial and a Colorado case you might&amp;rsquo;ve missed. They&amp;rsquo;re joined by NPR justice correspondent Carrie Johnson. Topics include: - Gag orders in the federal election case and the New York civil fraud trial - The legal and political challenges of implementing gag orders on Trump</description></item><item><title>'The boss is not going to leave under any circumstances' | Trump's Trials</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5894800001/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 20:52:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5894800001/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Scott Detrow and NPR political editor/correspondent Domenico Montanaro discuss leaked confidential videos of two former Trump lawyers and what those videos could mean for the Georgia election interference case. Plus a new development in the January 6 case. Their guest is NYU&amp;rsquo;s Melissa Murray. Topics include: -The potential consequences of leaked videos in court — and the court of public opinion
-Trump lawyer Sidney Powell admitting she &amp;lsquo;didn&amp;rsquo;t know much&amp;rsquo; about election fraud.</description></item><item><title>Why lawyers say 'never write anything down' | Trump's Trials</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5894800002/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 17:17:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5894800002/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this inaugural episode of Trump&amp;rsquo;s Trials, host Scott Detrow and NPR political editor/correspondent Domenico Montanaro break down this week&amp;rsquo;s testimony from former President Donald Trump and his daughter Ivanka in the New York civil fraud case brought against the Trump Organization. This week&amp;rsquo;s guest is NYU&amp;rsquo;s Melissa Murray. Topics include: -Arguments in the New York case so far
-Whether Donald Trump actually cares if he loses -Why Trump sounded a lot different on the witness stand this week than he has in the past — while Ivanka, notably, did not</description></item><item><title>Welcome to Trump's Trials | Trump's Trials</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5894800003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 21:57:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5894800003/</guid><description>Podcast Description NPR&amp;rsquo;s Scott Detrow hosts a weekly discussion about the latest courtroom drama, testimony, and legal maneuvering in the criminal and civil cases facing former President Donald Trump — and what it all means for American democracy — with analysis from NPR political editor/correspondent Domenico Montanaro.
Sign up for sponsor-free episodes and support NPR&amp;rsquo;s political journalism at plus.npr.org. Email the show at trumpstrials@npr.org
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>