<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Jumpers Jump on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/jumpers-jump/</link><description>Recent content in Jumpers Jump on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 07:06:02 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/jumpers-jump/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>EP.161 - CASSIE STODDART TRUE CRIME STORY, DARK RUDOLPH THEORIES, &amp; JUSTIN BIEBER KARDASHIAN THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350157/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 07:06:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350157/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 161 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Being legally blind, Justin Beiber yummy video theory, Dicyanian aura glasses, Leave the earth behind movie symbolism, Courtney Kardashian kid theory, Cassie Stoddart true crime story, Vegas tesla tunnels, Elf movie theory, P Diddy industry conspiracies, Rudolph Reindeer theory, Reindeer red nose theory, Young thug trial, Chinese bear meme, Coincidences in dreams, GTA 6 causing violence, naked and afraid experience and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.160 - DARK CHRISTMAS THEORIES, TAYLOR SWIFT THEORY &amp; HOME ALONE DEVIL THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 02:58:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 160 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Being high on life, Dark Christmas theories, Quarantine theories, Gambling theories, Adulting &amp;amp; having kids, Skinwalker pretends to be dog, Adam &amp;amp; Eve theory, Dog &amp;amp; owner theory, Hamster murder stories, Home Alone devil theory, Taylor swift theory, Time travel, Genghis Khan, Knowledge, Free will, Getting over embarrassment and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.159 - ETTA SMITH UNSOLVED MYSTERY, SPONGEBOB BRAIN SWITCH THEORY &amp; PAPA LEGBA URBAN LEGEND | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:47:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 159 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Living in third person, Transfigure short film, Garth Brooks tour date murder theory, Shakira dissed by casio, Papa Legba urban legend, Etta Smith unsolved mystery, Filipino slang combines word, Spongebob brain theory, Wayside school vs scott pilgrim theory, Bands using holograms to perform, Spongebob flower cloud theory, Depression showed through cartoons, Funny fan interactions, Making money clipping up our podcast, How beats by dre got popular, Athletes saying &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m going to Disneyland&amp;rdquo;, Wearing VR for a week straight and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.158 - DARK HUNGER GAMES THEORIES, AI MURDER STORY &amp; FORTNITE THEORIES | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 04:18:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 158 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Lil Uzi demonic theory, Real Nightlock berries, Gavin at Lil Uzi concert, Bad pr training, Dark Hunger Games theories, Mr. Beast theories, AI murder story, Mario Kart mandela effect, Core Memories theory, Home Alone mandela effect, Fortnite theories, Our cards getting compromised, Karma &amp;amp; cancel culture, Mindsets, Meaning to life, Losses &amp;amp; wins, Being a better person and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.157 - PHILIPPINES ASWANG URBAN LEGEND, EVIAN WATER THEORY &amp; TIKTOKER GOES TO PRISON | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350004/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:56:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 157 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Jumpers Jump basketball buzzer-beater, Breakfast theory, Wu yong ning stuntman story, Filipino urban legend Maria Labo, Tiktoker in prison story, Microbiomes sending brain signals, Evian water theory, Water laced in New York, Drinking too much water, Having similar experiences to everyone else, Family scent, UFC champion has weakness, Jeremy Lin documentary, Nepobabies and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.156 - MYSTERY OF LORETTO CHAPEL, ATTACK ON TITAN THEORIES &amp; DARK CASE OF ADAM GRAHAM | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350005/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 23:18:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 156 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Stories with tmi, Torture methods, The Mystery of Loretto chapel, Miracles, Recurring dreams &amp;amp; nightmares, Dark case of Adam Graham, Crazy revenge story, Frontier justice, Attack of Titan ending theories, 30 Million money murderer, Pyramid schemes, Scam stories/top finesses, Tyson fury theory, Pacquiao vs Margarito fight, Karma, Keep and Peel UFC skit, Tom Brady theory, Brain capacity, Fame and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.155 - MATTHEW PERRY CONSPIRACY, MICHAEL JACKSON NEVERLAND THEORY &amp; LIGHTS OFF PARANORMAL GAME | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 04:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 155 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Party side missions, Social media affecting real life, Matthew Perry death conspiracy, Pickering dungeon lore, Santa Clause serial killer backstory, Michael Jackson neverland theory, Island Boys theory, Lights on Lights off paranormal game, Teacher abusing her power, Going viral now vs the past, Tory Lanez Roc Nation theory, Pleasure island cartoon, Drake disses Bobbi Althoff, Terrifier 2 reaction, Finding your role in life and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.154 - DEMONIC ZODIAC THEORY, REAL LIFE CLOWN KILLER &amp; DARK CHICKEN JOKE ORIGIN | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350007/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 02:56:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 154 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Halloween lore, Demonic Zodiac theory, Ancestor theories, Soul &amp;amp; personality, Dark chicken joke origin, Mr.Krabs theory, First blood phenomenon, Real life clown killer story, Clown origin, Iconic yellow characters, Rappers &amp;amp; the industry, Cancel culture, Elmer dead body story, Why Halloween is dying, 4 mile effect, Outgrowing your parents, Our personal Halloween stories and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.153 - REAL EXORCISM STORIES, WORLD'S MOST HAUNTED DOLL, &amp; THE AMMONS HOUSE HAUNTING | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 153 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Anneliese Michel exorcism, The Ammons house haunting, Paranormal activity at Gavin&amp;rsquo;s house , Let me out doll, Third man syndrome phenomenon, Philippines black spirit story , Carlos&amp;rsquo; paranormal doctor story, Exorcism movie actor injury , Atheist ghost story, Logan Paul vs Dillion Danis fight theory, Manny Pacquiao creed son, Jesus tattoo contradiction, Handling negative comments, Manifesting stuff into our apartment, Not taking life too seriously, NFL industry plant theory and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.152 - CRAZY DRAKE ALBUM THEORY, DARK ATHLETIC TACTICS &amp; THE SATELLITE THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350009/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 01:25:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 152 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Crazy Drake album theories, Concerts, Music legends, Toronto culture, Gavin &amp;amp; Charan slap boxing, Funny club fight story, Fight at our sister&amp;rsquo;s graduation, Psychology test on hidden personality traits, Overthinking &amp;amp; taking risks, Being in Flow state, Dark athletic tactics, Taylor Swift and Travis Kelce theory, Rice Gum Doja Cat story, Satanic celebrities, Why God created satan, Satellite theory, Specific manifestations and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.151 - LIL TAY FAKE DEATH THEORY, CRAZY IRL STREAMER STORY &amp; THOUSAND YARD STARE THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350010/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 21:03:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 151 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Perspective as a creative, Rick Ruben&amp;rsquo;s job for artists, Lil Tay hidden message in song, Country music predictions, Rorochan_1999 streamer story, Girls take jewelry off dead body, thousand yard stare theory, Why villains always get out of jail, Ye interactions with Kim, Using airpods to track a persons location, How news cameraman never die, Filming a documentary gone wrong, Sewer system civilization, Indian street food is clean , Using our feet more on a daily basis, Mayweather vs 50 cent beef, with great power comes great responsibility and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.150 - CRAZY FILIPINO GHOST STORIES, DARK MANIFESTATION THEORY &amp; SPIRITUAL REALMS | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350011/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 01:39:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 150 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Gavin&amp;rsquo;s true family ghost stories, Latched by a demon in the Philippines, Dark manifestations, Spiritual beings, Tarot card readings, Monkey paw stories, Being connected to the spiritual realm, Faith and religion, Planet of the Apes, Vampire folklore, Courage the cowardly dog theory, Barbie Wizards of Oz theory, Freedom and discipline, Asap rocky Miley Cyrus Mandela effect, Carlos is from a different dimension, Celebrity &amp;ldquo;pizza party&amp;rdquo; theories, Confidence and body language, Identity switch, Muay thai and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.149 - BANNED SOUR PATCH KIDS AD, SALLIE HOUSE HORROR STORY &amp; CHILDHOOD TOYS THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 01:18:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 149 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Importance of personality, Taekwondo compared to Muay Thai, Banned sour patch kids ad, Yuri Lipski blue hole death, Sallie house horror story, People swam in a pool with a dead body, Slang from influencers, Cancel culture in korea, Key to having a successful clothing brand, Car accident traumas, How do you know your potential, Don&amp;rsquo;t live a boring life, Your circle determines who you are, Why stop signs are red, Childhood Toys theory, Deeper meaning to life, training for other podcasts and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.148 - FIRST EVER EXORCIST, JINN FOLKLORE STORY &amp; SCIENTIST WHO SOLD THEIR SOUL | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350013/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 02:58:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 148 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Mind to muscle theories, Cursed family horror story, First ever exorcist performed, Jinn folklore story, Scientist who sold their soul, Crazy allergic reaction transformation, Slim fast tea, Entrepreneur delayed dopamine, Real life purge, Rich and poor life, The Village movie, The promised neverland, Camp rock exposed, Generational movie effects, First world problems, Advice for youth, Funny icks, Proving people wrong and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.147 - DARK MEANING OF NICKELODEON, ALIENS ON MARS THEORY &amp; MOUNTAINS SHAPED AS PEOPLE | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:56:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 147 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Being dehydrated, Holiday 7 deadly sins theory, Fake being famous app, Jesus as the first influencer, CNE gambling games, Schizophrenia is different for everyone, Fish spa tragedy, Guinea pig movie, Born evil vs taught evil, Grocery store finesses, Fight vs flight moments, School system hasn&amp;rsquo;t changed, Millionaire not paying at restaurant story, Mutating your body, Tiktok hunger games, Not knowing how much is in your bank account, Life is a video game, Black mirror episodes and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.146 - TOP HAT DEMON STORY, DARK PERFECT WORLD THEORY &amp; EGO DEATHS w/ EMSON | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350015/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 20:31:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 146 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Meant to be moments, Life is frequency, Sleep paralysis, Top hat man demon, Ghost frequency theory, Think and grow rich, Manifestation, Perfect world theories, Death and eternity, Being delusional, Being in the spotlight, Faith in God, Ego deaths, Purpose with intent, Speaking to your soul, Last days on earth, Wasted time, Movie influences and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.145 - UFO SIGHTING IN AFRICA, THE JOKER THEORY &amp; THE MARY VINCENT SURVIVAL STORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350016/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 20:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 145 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: The biggest UFO sighting in Africa, The inner smile theory, Mary Vincent true crime story, Filipinos and their anxiety, Blue raspberry theory, Girls trying to deflate your ego, Blue beam project holograms, Pringles can&amp;rsquo;t call itself chips, The antichrist, Rick and Morty apocalypse party, Calling out your friends, Living life under protective parents, Joker was the hero in the dark knight, Does it take evil to beat evil, Being easily influenced into bad things and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.144 - GIRL SURVIVES 1600 FT DROP, HAWAII WILDFIRE THEORY &amp; DRAKE SZA THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 03:08:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 144 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Down bad moments, Hawaii wildfire theory, Direct energy weapons, Black mirror parody, Drake Sza theory, Profession that cheats most, Eminem mandela effect, How to react to a bully, Antarctica theory, Epcot theory, Recurring dreams, Story of Jonah, They cloned Tyrone movie, Girl who survived 1600 ft drop, Racism and world peace and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.143 - MONTGOMERY BRAWL INCIDENT, TUPAC STILL ALIVE THEORY CONFIRMED &amp; SAN PEDRO HAUNTING | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350018/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 20:01:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 143 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Why do we speak english, The montgomery brawl incident, Hidden message in Oreo&amp;rsquo;s, Women being chased by bear, San Pedro haunting, Influencers acting in movies, Jake Paul vs Nate Diaz was fixed, Talking to animals, Prime drink theory, Social media making people depressed, Drake&amp;rsquo;s impact on Toronto, New Tupac theory, Being delusional about your dreams, Bradley Martyn fighting everyone, Rappers doing humiliation rituals and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.142 - BARBIE MOVIE THEORY, TRAVIS SCOTT BIBLICAL THEORY &amp; ETHAN'S TRUE GHOST STORIES | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350019/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 17:22:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 142 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Barbie movie theories, Lil uzi pink tape, Travis Scott biblical theory, Living if the world was ending, Productivity and making money, God is water theory, Aliens confirmed, Superheroes theory, Controversy sells, The Others movie, Ethan&amp;rsquo;s true ghost stories, Jim Jones origin, Passion gives you purpose, Toxicity of team sports, Bucktee stories and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.141 - MONKEY PAW URBAN LEGEND, KIDS SURVIVE 40 DAYS IN JUNGLE &amp; HOWIE MANDEL HELD HOSTAGE | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350020/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 19:02:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 141 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Howie Mandel held hostage theory, Monkey paw urban legend, 4 kids survive the amazon rainforest for 40 days, The toxic lady story, God leading you down your path, Rolls Royce garbage trucks, Unknown hiker urban legend, Near death experience on gondola, Reading the notes on our notes app, Falling into glacier lake, Girls almost sign their life away, African lion safari, Sushi body ritual, Uber finesse, Don&amp;rsquo;t rush your life, getting revenge and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.140 - AIRPLANE LADY GONE MISSING, CHEATING DEATH THEORY &amp; DEMONOLOGY STORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:53:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 140 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Gavin&amp;rsquo;s drunk story, Carlos&amp;rsquo; canon event, Airplane lady gone missing, Project blue beam, Sound of Freedom, Nostalgia and childhood stories, Demonology stories, Celtic rituals, Banned movie, Cheating death theory, Solidifying yourself in history, GOATS, Life lessons from movies vs people, Looks vs personality, Ai friends, Smart city and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.139 - WOMEN SEES GHOST ON PLANE, SPLIT PERSONALITY DISORDER, &amp; MICHAEL RUBINS MYSTERIOUS PARTY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 21:35:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 139 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: New guest Django, Gavin&amp;rsquo;s hallucinations while being sick, Having split personality disorder, The greatest performer of our generation, Women claims person isn&amp;rsquo;t real on flight, Michael Rubin hosts all white party for elites, Influencer kills 12 people while driving at high speeds, Getting more then one tattoo, Do you step into changing people&amp;rsquo;s timeline, Growing up in different environments, having direction for your goals, abnormal lessons, Damar Hamlin incident and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.138 - MICHAEL JACKSON SPOTTED ON BOAT, &amp; HAUNTED TATTOO SHOP, GHOST HUNTER DOPPELGANGERS | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:36:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 138 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Michael Jackson still alive, Chef gets possessed, Ghost hunters find their doppelgangers, The haunted tattoo shop, Vlogger who hated women, Fake moon pictures on phones, Spiderman canon event theory, interrupting the timeline, Being able to take a joke, Ja Morant chips story, Would you go looking for ghosts, how to get out of awkward situations, Kanye has ghost writer and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.137 - TITANIC SUBMARINE THEORIES, CRAZY GEOCACHE DEATH STORY &amp; HOODED WOMAN WITH NO FACE | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 00:06:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 136 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Titanic submarine theories, The Simpsons predictions, Black Mirror stories, Crazy geocache death stories, Pokemon Go kidnapping, Canadian witch animal ritual, Cargo Cult story, Mythologies, Woman consciousness in monkey, The shadow game ritual, Japanese demonic rituals, Hooded woman with no face, True art and interpretations and much more!
Follow the podcast: @JumpersPodcast Follow Carlos: @CarlosJuico Follow Gavin: @GavinRutaa Check out the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>EP.136 - SPENDING 100 DAYS UNDERWATER, TAYLOR SWIFT ROYAL FAMILY THEORY, FAMILY FEUD MURDER CASE | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350025/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 19:43:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 136 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Deliverances in the church, Taylor Swift and royal family theory, 100 days underwater reverses a guy&amp;rsquo;s age, Being gullible is a superpower, Family feud murder case, Guy exposes himself on TV by rapping, Twitch streamer catches a ghost, Kids growing up too fast, Hospital scenario about morals, Fighting for love, All news channels having the same script, What is actually &amp;ldquo;meant to be&amp;rdquo; and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.135 - HELLO KITTY MURDER CASE, CRAZY ALIEN FOOTAGE &amp; HOMELESSMAN SURVIVES OFF TINDER DATES | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350026/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 02:56:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 135 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Children&amp;rsquo;s books and influences, Caillou theory, The colour theory, Future of technology theories, Technology outage prediction, Archetypes of people, Disney princess universe connected theory, Alexis Avila case, Our canon events, Homeless man survives off tinder dates, Hello kitty murder case, Crazy Alien footage and much more!
Follow the podcast: @JumpersPodcast Follow Carlos: @CarlosJuico Follow Gavin: @GavinRutaa Check out the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>EP.134 - RED DOOR GHOST GAME, CEREAL TESTOSTERONE THEORY &amp; CARLOS HEARS VOICES STORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350027/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 22:04:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 134 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Boomers vs Gen-Z, 9/11 true crime attempts, Project sunshine, Spiderman was a 6.5/10, Red door yellow door ghost game, Carlos&amp;rsquo; crazy spirit story, Hanging man ghost story, Speaking tongues in church, cereal theory, Apple pro vision theory, Overcoming social anxiety, prom story and much more!
Follow the podcast: @JumpersPodcast Follow Carlos: @CarlosJuico Follow Gavin: @GavinRutaa Check out the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>EP.133 - CHILDREN'S BOOK MURDER MYSTERY, SPIDERMAN POSSESSED THEORY &amp; TIKTOK HIGH THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350028/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 02:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 133 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Streetwear talks, Time travel evidence, Adopted child actually grown woman, Spiderman possessed theory, Kardashian ancestor curse, Character and childhood bring ups, Picture perfect theories, Tiktok high theory, Children&amp;rsquo;s book murder mystery, Minority theories, Jeffery Epstein, Tedtalk slip up and much more!
Follow the podcast: @JumpersPodcast Follow Carlos: @CarlosJuico Follow Gavin: @GavinRutaa Check out the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>EP.132 - GUARDIANS OF THE GALAXY THEORIES, CALLING OUT ALEX WASSABI TO BOX, &amp; OUR CRAZY DREAM STORIES | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350029/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 22:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 132 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Meaning of car accident dreams, Seeing the same person in all your dreams, Indiana Jones theory, Smelling flowers randomly story, Guardians of the Galaxy groot theory, Working on yourself before anything else, Getting into a fight at the club, Guardians poster predicted who dies in the movie, Carlos almost getting finessed for shoes, Boy&amp;rsquo;s reflection in the mirror moves, calling out Alex Wassabi and Guava Juice to box, Top G is not a fighting champion, influencing kids through tv shows, changing the evil narrative to good and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.131 - CRAZY VOODOO CURSES, BALENCIAGA MISSING PERSON THEORY &amp; MR. KRABS SOLD HIS SOUL | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350030/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 16:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 131 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Gavin manifesting his dream car, History repeats royal car accident, Crazy uncovered news stories, Balenciaga missing person theory, Knocking on wood theory, Treadmill and Bowling origins, Pyramids theory, Voodoo curses, LeBron satanic pregame ritual, Faith and spirituality, Killer clowns comeback, Bee movie theories, Jeff Bezos tweet, Mr. Krabs sold his soul and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.130 - WILL ROBOTS TURN ON HUMANS, ENERGIZER BUNNY MANDELA EFFECT &amp; CONTROVERSIAL A.I TREND | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350031/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 130 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Robots turning on humans, What Youtube will become in the future, Energizer bunny mandela effect, Fergie lyrics mandela effect, Peanut butter jelly time backstory, A.I trend sparks controversy, Being grateful for life, Parents being our first superheros, Social media aka digital clubs, Carlos&amp;rsquo; love for the zoo, what if there was no evil on earth and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.129 - AI DRAKE THEORY, HAUNTED KUKATASHI STORY &amp; CARLOS' EGG CLEANSE GONE WRONG | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350032/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 22:45:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 129 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Carlos&amp;rsquo; egg cleanse gone wrong, Rituals and meanings, End of the world theories, Demon trapped in boulder released, Asian superstitions, Drinking and confidence, End goals and influence, Life path and reincarnation, Kill Bill Sza theory, AI Drake theory, Ghost stories and much more!
Follow the podcast: @JumpersPodcast Follow Carlos: @CarlosJuico Follow Gavin: @GavinRutaa Check out the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>EP.128 - HIDDEN SYMBOLS IN LOGOS, MARIO PLUMMER THEORY, &amp; THE BRIAN WELLS MYSTERY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350033/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:17:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 128 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Heroes turning into villains, Yellow Jackets TV show, Masonic symbols in logos, Ayahuasca and frog slime trips, Benjamin Franklin murderer theory, Why Mario is a plummer, No name vs normal brand theory, Pasquale pizza theory, The mystery of Overtun bridge, The Brian Wells case, Deleted Kanye SNL speech, cosplaying in public and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.127 - HAUNTED JAPAN RITUAL GAME, FILIPINO URBAN LEGEND &amp; CRAZY CARTOON THEORIES | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350034/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 22:26:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 127 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: AI theories and predictions, Juico theory, Haunted Japan ritual game, Crazy reddit horror stories, Filipino urban legend, Lofi girl theories, Matrix theory, Spongebob theory, Donald Duck theory, Japanese halloween rally story, Minecraft stories and much more!
Follow the podcast: @JumpersPodcast Follow Carlos: @CarlosJuico Follow Gavin: @GavinRutaa Check out the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>EP.126 - STRANGEST SUPERSTITIONS, DONALD TRUMP TIME TRAVEL THEORY, &amp; REDDIT PARANORMAL VIDEOS | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350035/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 22:02:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 126 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Our trip to LA, Effects of Chlorophyll, Fake hand experiment, New Gen vs Old Gen problems, Donald Trump son theory, Bible predicts end of days, Paranormal videos on reddit, Crazy superstitions around the world, Keannu Reeves ghost lookalike, Whistling calls spirits, Millionaire off a bank glitch, Disneyland trip and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.125 - ASIAN GHOST STORIES W/ YOUTUBE LEGENDS JUSTKIDDINGFILMS &amp; TIM CHANTARANGSU | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350036/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 00:20:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 125 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Asian representation, Our inspirations, Ghost stories, Placebo effect, Old Asian psychics, Feng shui, Manifesting success, Journey as young creators, Egotism, Our end goals, Comfort is the enemy of success, Price of fame and much more!
Follow the podcast: @JumpersPodcast Follow Carlos: @CarlosJuico Follow Gavin: @GavinRutaa Check out the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>EP.124 - JOSH'S HIDDEN FAMILY TREASURE, BIRTHDAY RITUAL THEORY &amp; NEIGHBORHOOD GHOST STORIES | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350037/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 23:45:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 124 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Childhood games and stories, A slug that paralyzed a man, Puss in Boots Theory, Coco theory, Everything Everywhere all at once theory, How to break bad news to homies, Josh&amp;rsquo;s hidden family treasure, Our neighborhood ghost stories, Birthday ritual theory, Crazy Life theories and much more!
Follow the podcast: @JumpersPodcast Follow Carlos: @CarlosJuico Follow Gavin: @GavinRutaa Check out the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>EP.123 - THE TRAGIC CASE OF BEAUTY BLOGGERS, CRAZY LAWS IN NORTH KOREA &amp; DREAMWORKS UNIVERSE THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350038/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 23:03:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 123 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Crazy North Korea Laws, The new ChatGPT5, Live Animes, Meth banshee story, Homeless people interactions, Switching to someone else&amp;rsquo;s body, Instagram murder mystery, Shrek &amp;amp; Kung Fu Panda theory, Paranormal toy in Mexico, Experiencing life, our favourite WWE wrestlers and much more!
Follow the podcast: @JumpersPodcast Follow Carlos: @CarlosJuico Follow Gavin: @GavinRutaa Check out the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>EP.122 - DEMONIC BRAZIL CARNIVAL, REINCARNATION STORY &amp; RATATOUILLE THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350039/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 01:08:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 122 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: The greatest athlete of all time, Demonic Brazil carnival, Ancestor theories, Teen couple murders parent, The most dangerous things in the world, Cursed diamond relic, Foot shape meanings, Ratatouille theory, How perfection is objective, Relationship tests, Kylie Jenner Sanpaku theory and much more!
Follow the podcast: @JumpersPodcast Follow Carlos: @CarlosJuico Follow Gavin: @GavinRutaa Check out the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>EP.121 - CURSED JAPANESE POEM, OLDBOY MOVIE PLOT TWIST &amp; SUNGLASSES | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350040/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 01:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 121 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: What is an industry plant, Old Boy crazy plot twist, Haunted red ribbon story, Cursed Japanese Poem, Sunglasses theory, Abandoned town with 400 life-sized dolls, Society and the school system, Celebrity lighting theory, Last person on the planet question, Finding your purpose in life and much more!
Follow the podcast: @JumpersPodcast Follow Carlos: @CarlosJuico Follow Gavin: @GavinRutaa Check out the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>EP.120 - SKIN WALKER ENCOUNTER, LEBRON NUMEROLOGY THEORY &amp; OUTERBANKS THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350041/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 03:37:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 120 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Following your gut, Gavin&amp;rsquo;s negative intuition, Woody Harrelson going off script in SNL, AI celebrity voices, The elevator game, Hacks to not be cancelled, Lebron numerology theory, Man who went to jail on purpose, Outerbanks theory, Crazy healing stories and much more!
Follow the podcast: @JumpersPodcast Follow Carlos: @CarlosJuico Follow Gavin: @GavinRutaa Check out the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>EP.119 - COLORS TRIGGER CHAKRA THEORY, KUYANG URBAN LEGEND, &amp; CELEBRITY GLITCHES CAUGHT ON CAMERA | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350042/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 22:20:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 119 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Fish committing credit card fraud, fast food controlling humans with colors, Japanese man turning into a dog, Chupacabra has been found, Kuyang urban legend, Celebrities glitches caught on camera, Spirituality used as a secret weapon, Pets gaining conscious, Mirrors used as portals, Heart monitor exposes cheater, and much more!
Follow the podcast: @JumpersPodcast Follow Carlos: @CarlosJuico Follow Gavin: @GavinRutaa Check out the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>EP.118 - WHERE THE DEVIL LIVES THEORY, CRAZY CHEATING STORY, &amp; AI IS AFTER US THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350043/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 01:25:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 118 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Water conspiracy, Time Traveller Millionaire Story, AI predicting people theory, doppelganger ghost story, Vatican secrets, Hollow Earth theories, Alien Theories, Sinkholes popping up around the world, Portals Theory, John Wick killed his wife theory, and much more!
Follow the podcast: @JumpersPodcast Follow Carlos: @CarlosJuico Follow Gavin: @GavinRutaa Check out the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>EP.117 - AI BECOMING SELF-AWARE, DISNEY PRINCESS THEORY, REAL ANGEL CAUGHT ON CAMERA | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350044/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 21:02:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 117 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: AI becoming self-aware, Disney princess mental disorder theory, Dark symbolism at the Grammys, Full moon theory, Real angel caught on camera, Reincarnation story, Poker face movie plot twist, Hippies have superpowers, Humans smarter than AI, Girl who cries crystals, numerology coincidences and much more!
Follow the podcast: @JumpersPodcast Follow Carlos: @CarlosJuico Follow Gavin: @GavinRutaa Check out the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>EP.116 - KOREAN PHYSICAL 100 THEORY, SERBIAN DANCING LADY, &amp; DARK HARRY POTTER THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350045/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 23:05:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 116 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: SpongeBob Mandela Effects, Year of the Cat 2023 Theory, Snapchat Theory, Crazy ring camera footage, Dark Harry Potter Theory, Michael Jordan Mandela Effect, Haunted Hat man story, Pokémon Mandela effect, Boy trapped in shipping container story, bio energetics, Serbian Dancing Lady and much more!
Follow the podcast: @JumpersPodcast Follow Carlos: @CarlosJuico Follow Gavin: @GavinRutaa Check out the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>EP.115 - ANNABELLE DOLL IS BACK, GUY PRETENDS TO BE SERIAL KILLER, THREE LITTLE PIGS MANDELA EFFECT | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350046/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 21:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico, Gavin Ruta on episode 115 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Ally Lotti and Juice World, Being trapped with 1 gorilla or 20 black mambas, New Puss and Boots theory, Creepy fortune cookie story, Three little pigs mandela effect, Baseball interview mandela effect, Monkey doll is named Anabelle, Robert doll puts women in hospital, Boys tresspass olympic park story, Why the color purple is rare, Rapper video game, and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.114 - SPECIAL GUEST TRISTAN TATE, DISCORD MURDER STORY, &amp; CRAZY PUSS AND BOOTS THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350047/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 21:07:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico, Gavin Ruta, and special guest Tristan Tate on episode 114 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Andrew Tate theories, Do or Die mentality, Secret cameras in Airbnbs, Man who&amp;rsquo;s cursed by witch doctor, Mom who cyberbullied own daughter, Puss and boots Theory, Toy Story Theory, Triangle Plot twist movie, Midsommar movie, Carlos almost starting street fight, Cancelled Netflix shows conspiracy, and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.113 - DARK DISNEY GLOVES THEORY, DRAKE MANDELA EFFECT, &amp; HOTEL SKINWALKER STORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350048/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 20:47:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 113 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Being El Chapo&amp;rsquo;s son, The dumbest bank robber in the world, Hidden message behind Mickey Mouse gloves, Drake mandela effect, Horror in screen 9, Cereal box theory, Grand Canyon theory, Skinwalker story, past life study, GTA and its influence on kids, and much more!
Follow the podcast: @JumpersPodcast Follow Carlos: @CarlosJuico Follow Gavin: @GavinRutaa Check out the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>EP.112 - EXPOSED RAPPER CLONING, HAUNTED VENTRILOQUIST STORY, &amp; DARK PINOCCHIO THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350049/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 20:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 112 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Asap Rocky exposes rapper clones, Rejection Theory, Glitch in Matrix reddit stories, Coffee Theory, Pinocchio Theory, Third Eye Theories, Michael Jackson Phobia, Isekai worlds, Advice for heartbreak, xxxtentacion studied cults, and much more!
Follow the podcast: @JumpersPodcast Follow Carlos: @CarlosJuico Follow Gavin: @GavinRutaa Check out the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.ly/JumpersJumpYT Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>EP.111 - ANDREW TATE ARREST THEORY, MISSING TIKTOKER MYSTERY, &amp; VACATION GHOST STORIES | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350050/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 21:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 111 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Tate brothers arrested, Simpsons predict Andrew Tate, Tory Lanez arrested theory, New pill given to prisoners, Tiktoker spots giant and goes missing, Alice in Borderland explained, Vacation ghost stories, Kanye can&amp;rsquo;t be cloned, Birth control theory, Fake shopper story, Minecraft map that is banned in several countries, and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.110 - CHRISTMAS THEORIES, STRANGER THINGS MANDELA EFFECT, &amp; TIKTOK MURDERERS | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350051/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 110 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Would you give your friends your riches, Home Alone Theory, The Grinch Theory, Christmas Theories, Dark Balenciaga Theories, The Swimmers Movie, Two types of manifesting, Sarah Boone Tiktok Murder Story, People in Pool Ghost Story, Invisible man movie, Stranger Things Mandela Effect, and much more!
Thanks to our sponsors! Right now - NetSuite is offering a one-of-a-kind special financing program.</description></item><item><title>EP.109 - AI GENERATED ART TREND, LIVING IN A SIMULATION &amp; BLEEDING HOUSE MYSTERY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350052/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 18:08:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 109 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Living in a simulation, Mentally vs Physically living in a simulation, Christmas level backrooms, Wednesday Addams theory, The &amp;ldquo;Bleeding House&amp;rdquo; mystery, Walking Dead theory, Disturbing AI art generator, ChatGPT for school, AI simulates evolution, Mr.Beast using Neurolink, Glitches in the matrix, and much more!
Thanks to our sponsors! Right now - NetSuite is offering a one-of-a-kind special financing program.</description></item><item><title>EP.108 - INFLUENCER MURDER STORY, HAUNTED TIMEOUT DOLLS, &amp; SECRET KANYE HIDDEN | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350053/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 17:40:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 108 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Cursed Timeout dolls, Blueface Chrissean Theory, Smiling man story, Island that ages people faster, Bermuda Triangle Theory, Weinstein Karma Theory, Secret Hidden Kanye, Knives Out 2, Why 2016 was a good year Theory, Santo Nino scary story, Carlos&amp;rsquo; dream story, and much more!
Thanks to our sponsors!
&amp;ldquo;Looking for a last minute gift?</description></item><item><title>EP.107 - MAN SURVIVED UNDERWATER, HAUNTED MCDONALDS STORY, &amp; 2022 MANDELA EFFECTS | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350054/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 15:44:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 107 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: The Donald Duck Killer, Orbiter Nine story, New Mandela Effects, Sign of Apocalypse footage, One Mind consciousness Theory, Rick and Morty Theory, Dark Mcdonalds story, Barney horror episode, Man with upside down face story, Social Media Theories, Devil Theory, 127 hours survival story, and much more!
Thanks to our sponsors!</description></item><item><title>EP.106 - MOST HAUNTED CEMETERY STORY, DARK MARILYN MONROE THEORY, &amp; NEW MANDELA EFFECTS | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350055/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 18:34:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 106 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Ariana Grande experience with demons, Marilyn Monroe theory, JFK and Abraham Lincoln similarities, CERN hidden rituals, Spongebob mandela effect, Krabby patty formula exposed, Risky business mandela effect, &amp;ldquo;The Menu&amp;rdquo; movie, &amp;ldquo;Exam&amp;rdquo; the movie, Ellen Degeneres family tree, and much more!
Thanks to our sponsors!
Try BlueChew FREE when you use our promo code Jumpers at checkout&amp;ndash;just pay $5 shipping.</description></item><item><title>EP.105 - ANDREW TATE EXPOSED, REAL MATRIX THEORY, &amp; USING NUMEROLOGY FOR RICHES | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350056/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 17:45:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico, Gavin Ruta, and special guest GG33 on episode 105 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: How gg33 helped Golden State Warriors win championships, How celebrities use Numerology for success, why Kanye and Kim Kardashian were doomed, gg33 Exposing Andrew Tate, Spiritual meanings of numbers, Birth dates of most attractive people, Titanic Theory, Real Matrix Theory, Birth dates destined for riches, How numbers predict life and important events, How to use numerology to get rich, JFK Theory, Facebook Theory, Rolex Theory, Chinese Zodiac, Astrology theories, and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.104 - CRAZY DRAKE "HER LOSS" THEORY, TAKEOFF'S DEATH PREDICTED, &amp; KANYE ILLUMINATI THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350057/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 16:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 104 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Drake steals flow on &amp;ldquo;Her Loss&amp;rdquo; album, Takeoff&amp;rsquo;s death coincidences, Sanpaku Eyes, Kanye Jesus contracts, Dojacat black eye theory, Ritual in a movie, Talking to Takeoff after his death, Drake disses X again, VR game that kills you, 1092paradise cursed website, and much more!
Thanks to our sponsors!
Right now, go to https://BUYRAYCON.</description></item><item><title>EP.103 - KOBE LOGO MEANING, MUHAMMAD ALI'S INCONIC PIC BACKSTORY, &amp; HEADLESS GHOST STORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350058/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 16:42:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 103 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: The meaning of Kobe&amp;rsquo;s Logo, The real backstory of the Muhammad Ali inconic picture, Technology to relive memories, Never chase a red butterfly story, Canada investing in insect food, Headless ghost jumping rope story, Being born great, Mosquitos with numbers on them, Battleships mandela effect, Mary statue crying blood, and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.102 - HALLOWEEN SPECIAL, MILK ANXIETY THEORY, &amp; DARK ORIGIN OF MUFFIN MAN | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350059/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 13:58:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 102 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Exorcisms, Ventriloquist who sold his soul, Craziest Game of Thrones Theory, The Night Clown Story, Muffin Man Dark Origin, Charli D&amp;rsquo;amelio Theory, Numerology, Mckinney Manor Haunted House, Milk Conspiracy, The Knowing Movie, Zombie Jeffery Dahmer, and much more!
Thanks to our sponsors!
Get 20% Off and Free Shipping with the code [JUMPERS] at Manscaped.</description></item><item><title>EP.101 - END OF THE WORLD THEORY, PARROT SOLVES MURDER MYSTERY, &amp; WHISTLING MAN URBAN LEGEND | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350060/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 17:39:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico, Gavin Ruta, and special guests on episode 101 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Dark truth about the industry, End of days theory, Meeting other influencers, Hallucinating with ping pong balls, Bjork stalker story, Squidward is deaf theory, Fiona is a cannibal theory, Shein messages on tags, Importance of friends, Urban legend El Sibon, The reset button, Fairly odd parents theory, frat party experience, and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.100 - JEFFREY DAHMER, DARK HORROR THEORIES, &amp; EVIL MOTHER STORY (Ft. ALL GUESTS) | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350061/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 22:40:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico, Gavin Ruta, and special guests on episode 100 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Our favorite moments, What to do on a first date, Jeffrey Dahmer, Our thoughts on the afterlife, Pearl Horror Movie, Phone Addiction Theory, How to impress a crush, Guys x Girls debates, Near death experiences, Mother who held daughter captive story, Sixth Senses, Things we did out of character to impress, Embarrassing confessions, Funniest personal stories, and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.99 - HAUNTED DOLL OF UNITED KINGDOM, SECRET LOGO MEANINGS, &amp; SPONGEBOB SANDY THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350062/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 99 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Spongebob Sandy Theory, History repeating itself Theory, Guy who escaped police with a teddy, Dark origin of Barber poles, Hidden meanings in popular logos, Starbucks Theory, Jay Z time travel Theory, Simulations, New York Theory, and much more!
Keep things smooth and fresh with Manscaped. Get 20% off + free shipping with the code JUMPERS at manscaped.</description></item><item><title>EP.98 - TWITCH CONTROVERSY, CHINA BANS TIME TRAVEL, &amp; THE AARON RAMSEY CURSE | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350063/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 22:01:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 98 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Recent Twitch drama, Twitch vs Rumble drama, The Aaron Ramsey curse, Abraham Lincoln predicts his death, Dark Monsters Inc. theory, Andrew Tate still secretly on tiktok, Fruit of the Loom mandela effect, China bans time travel, Devil of Swansea story, Ghosts trapped in art forms, The root of all evil, and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.97 - HAUNTED DUDLEY TOWN MYSTERY, THE DEADLIEST FILM, &amp; KARDASHIAN CURSE DARK ORIGIN | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350064/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 01:26:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 97 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Music industry planning artists death Theory, Dancing with the devil story, Food Theories, Ray Jay Theory, The barbarian story, Illegal pp size, The man who never pooped, Mcdonald’s Theory, Elvis Presley, Christopher Nolan is trying to save the world theory, Dudley Town Unsolved Haunting, and much more!
Upgrade your wardrobe with True Classic.</description></item><item><title>EP.96 - PRINCESS DIANA THEORY, RAPPER DEATH COINCIDENCES, &amp; INCREDIBLES THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350065/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 23:54:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 96 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Rolling loud got everyone sick, Rappers death coincidences, Princess Diana theory, Queen Elizabeth is still alive, Through the fire and flames story, AI generated messages, People manifest the future, Lil Tay and XXXtentacion theory, Fast food agenda, God&amp;rsquo;s Plan music video theory, having blind faith, gaining confidence, and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.95 - WAKING UP FROM THE MATRIX, WOKE THEORIES, &amp; CHILD WHO PRAYED TO THE DEVIL | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350066/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 20:24:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 95 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Big Hero 6 Theory, Japanese Mirror Experiment, Iluminati hidden website, Project High Jump, Agartha Theory, Woke thoughts/theories, Olive Theory, Beetles Theory, Manifestation Reality Theory, Mark Zuckerberg is an Alien, Eyes vs Legs, Real Life Suicide Squad, and much more!
Get 15% off your Raycon order, at BuyRaycon.com/jumpers
Keep things smooth and fresh with Manscaped.</description></item><item><title>EP.94 - THE MOST UNLUCKY MAN IN THE WORLD, HAUNTED ROBERT DOLL, &amp; THE CASE OF STEPHEN HAWKING | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350067/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 16:56:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 94 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: The most unlucky man in the world, The haunted Robert Doll, Different dimensions of our conscious theory, Haunted house in LA, The silent twins story, The KFC curse, Reaction to a fans ghost story, The mysterious case of Stephen Hawking, relationship advice, and much more!
Download the DraftKings Sportsbook app NOW and use promo code JUMPPOD to get TWO HUNDRED DOLLARS in FREE bets INSTANTLY when you place a five-dollar bet on any football game!</description></item><item><title>EP.93 - THE NASUBI TRAGEDY, YUBA UNSOLVED MYSTERY, &amp; ASIAN GHOST STORIES | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350068/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 93 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Ninja Turtles Theory, Alex Wasabi vs KSI Theory, Elon Musk Theory, Princess Peach Theory, Exorcist girl video, Nasubi Story, The little albert fear theory, Yuba County 5 Unsolved Mystery, Cloning humans, and much more!
Head to Policygenius.com to get your free life insurance quotes and see how much you could save.</description></item><item><title>EP. 92 - ALBUM COVER PREDICTS 9/11, DARK BEYONCE ALBUM THEORY, &amp; CRAZY GHOST STORIES | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350069/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 21:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 92 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Toronto&amp;rsquo;s concert curse, Album cover predicts 9/11 tragedy, Beyonce&amp;rsquo;s album cover predicts the end of the world, Music producer&amp;rsquo;s crazy ghost story, our favourite childhood disney movies, J-Cole&amp;rsquo;s dark sample, The ghost in the chair story, Woodstock 99&amp;rsquo;, Liking other girls posts while in a relationship, High School Musical hot takes, and much more!</description></item><item><title>EP.91 - REAL PARANORMAL STORIES, SIMPSONS MANDELA EFFECT, &amp; PROJECT SERPO | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350070/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 91 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Helping your friends out of toxic relationships, Carlos&amp;rsquo; aunt&amp;rsquo;s ghost stories, Project Serpo, real men in black, organism 46B in Antarctica, chamber inside Mount Rushmore, Malaysian Ghost Story, new hex city, Justin Beiber is a reptile, real paranormal stories, and much more!
FREE travel packs with your first purchase. At athleticgreens.</description></item><item><title>EP.90 - EXPOSING ANDREW TATE, TELL SNEAKO BOX ME, &amp; MALAYSIAN GHOST STORIES | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350071/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 90 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Polo G Theory, Nle Choppa spiritual side, Exposing Andrew Tate, Sneako says Canadians are weak, Lady gaga theory, Terasita Basa Ghost Story, Malaysian Ghost Story, Smile dog cursed image, India sacred artifacts story, Yeezy runners theory, and much more!
Head to Policygenius.com to get your free life insurance quotes and see how much you could save.</description></item><item><title>EP.89 - DARK MINIONS THEORY, HAUNTED AIRBNB STORY, &amp; MEGAN FOX THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350072/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 15:56:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 89 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Dark Minions Theory, Robots giving birth, King Tut Mandela Effect, Pac Man Theory, Ouiji Board story, our haunted airbnb vlog, Megan Fox MGK theory, Barney Theory, psychic abilities, and much more!
FREE travel packs with your first purchase. At athleticgreens.com/JUMPERS
Follow the podcast: @JumpersPodcast Follow Carlos: @CarlosJuico Follow Gavin: @GavinRutaa Check out the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>EP.88 - CELEBRITY ILLUMINATI THEORIES, CERN DIMENSIONS, &amp; KURT COBAIN THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350073/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 19:38:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 88 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Kylie Jenner&amp;rsquo;s kid name, Pete Davidson theory, The Kurt Cobain mystery, Kanye and Taylor&amp;rsquo;s beef, Kendrick and J-Cole exposing the illuminati, CERN and July 5th, Wizard of Oz mandela effects, our haunted airbnb experience, and much more!
Head to Policygenius.com to get your free life insurance quotes and see how much you could save.</description></item><item><title>EP.87 - REAL CONJURING STORIES, ANNABELLE HAS ESCAPED, &amp; GAVIN CAUGHT ON FIRE | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350074/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 87 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Japanese haunted beach picture, Our Ghost Tunnel Vlog, Going to a Haunted airbnb, Goat Theory, Blemy creatures, Star wars Mnadela Effect, The True Conjuring Stories, Annabelle escaping, and much more!
As a listener of this podcast, you’ll get $100 off of your first month at Talkspace.com Just use the code JUMPERS</description></item><item><title>EP.86 - TIM MCLEAN STORY, BANNED POKEMON EPISODE, &amp; MICHAEL JORDAN THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350075/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 86 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Michael Jordan retiring theory, Mrs.Puff criminal theory, Timmy Turner theory, banned porygon pokemon episode, Tim Mclean story, leaping lawyer urban legend, dark web stories, real life compared to minecraft, e-sports teams, and much more!
Get 20% off with free shipping at manscaped.com, and use our code JUMPERS Head to GO.FACTOR75.com/JUMPERS120 &amp;amp; use code JUMPERS120 to get $120 off.</description></item><item><title>EP.85 - STRANGER THINGS THEORIES, NILE'S GHOST CANYON, &amp; RELATIONSHIP LIFE HACKS | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350076/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 16:31:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 85 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Language frequency theories, Filipino drill music, Project Montauk, Stranger Things Theories, Squid Game season 2 Theories, How you can sue Morbius, Relationship Life hack with food, La Pascilita Horror Story, Nile&amp;rsquo;s Ghost Canyon, Psychology theories, and much more!
Athletic Greens is going to giving our listeners a FREE 1 year supply of immune-supporting Vitamin D AND 5 FREE travel packs with your first purchase.</description></item><item><title>EP.84 - JAMISON FAMILY MYSTERY, DRAKE ALBUM THEORY, &amp; REAL PORTAL CAUGHT ON CAMERA | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350077/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 84 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Drake&amp;rsquo;s new album, the Jamison family mystery, Castle Huska story, real portal caught on camera, creature found running behind a google car, the &amp;ldquo;Headless Valley&amp;rdquo;, Johnny Kim story, comparing yourself to others, and much more!
​​Get 15% off your first order by going to CUTSCLOTHING.COM/ JUMPERS. Head to Policygenius.com to get your free life insurance quotes and see how much you could save</description></item><item><title>EP.83 - HAUNTED WHISPER GAME, MALAYSIAN AIRLINES UNSOLVED MYSTERY, &amp; FINLAND IS FAKE THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350078/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 17:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 83 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Everything everywhere all at once theories, Disney Secret island, the Haunted Whisper Game, Malaysian airlines secrets revealed, Finland is fake theory, English speaking Gorilla&amp;rsquo;s final message to the world, trying personality illusions, and much more!
Match with your dedicated therapist today at talkspace.com, and use promo code JUMPERS during sign-up to get $100 off your first month.</description></item><item><title>EP.82 - WILLY WONKA THEORY, DARK MR.KRABS THEORY &amp; SHUTTER ISLAND STORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350079/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 17:23:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 82 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Lying is a superpower, Shutter Island story, Willy Wonka and Charlie theory, &amp;ldquo;Kimmy&amp;rdquo; the movie, Mr.Krabs using addictive drug in patties, scammer saving lives, whisper game at the club, angel of death story, and much more!
Check out the awesome hoodies and polos at Rhoback.com and use code JUMPER for a generous 20% off your first order.</description></item><item><title>EP.81 - WILL SMITH CHRIS ROCK THEORY, THE AMAZON KILLER &amp; SUBCONSCIOUS DATING SECRETS | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350080/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 16:54:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on Episode 81 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: The Will Smith &amp;amp; Chris Rock Theory, The Snail Debate, Chipmunks vs Squirrels, The Amazon Killer, Adam Sandler Theory, Philosophical thoughts, The Loud Sneeze theory, John Wick &amp;amp; Boondock saints theory, subconscious dating secrets and much more! Head to GO.FACTOR75.com/jumpers120 and use code jumpers120 to get $120 off. ​​Get 15% off your first order by going to CUTSCLOTHING.</description></item><item><title>EP.80 - BOB ROSS THEORY, CANDY LADY STORY &amp; ESCAPING PRISON WITH A RAINCOAT | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350081/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 23:41:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 80 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Bob Ross&amp;rsquo; mysterious paintings, the Texas &amp;ldquo;Candy Lady&amp;rdquo; story, human hair in our bread, 2 brothers escaping Alcatraz, hypnosis vs hacking, Big Hero live action, scammers being exposed, Moon Knight theory, and much more!
Head to GO.FACTOR75.com/jumpers120 and use code jumpers120 to get $120 off. ​​Get 15% off your first order by going to CUTSCLOTHING.</description></item><item><title>EP.79 - DYATLOV PASS UNSOLVED MYSTERY, NEVADA TAN KILLER &amp; BIRTH MONTH THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350082/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 19:43:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 79 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Birth months with the most cheaters, Nevada Tan Killer story, living as a double agent, Toronto unsolved mystery, Woman in the ceiling story, Dyatlov pass unsolved mystery, Evil eye, Daniel Neilson story, and much more!
That’s $100 off at talkspace.com, promo code jumpers. ​​Get 15% off your first order by going to CUTSCLOTHING.</description></item><item><title>EP.78 - THINKING MAN MANDELA EFFECT, JUNKO FURUTA STORY &amp; GREEN LINE RELATIONSHIP THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350083/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 19:06:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 78 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: All in one fade machine, the green line relationship test, the thinking man Mandela effect, ET Mandela effect, the Church of the iron rod, coffin confessor, how our souls decide how we look, our upcoming Egypt trip, and much more!
Check out the awesome hoodies and polos at Rhoback.com and use code JUMPER for a generous 20% off your first order.</description></item><item><title>EP.77 - PEKO-CHAN HORROR STORY, ROCKEFELLER UNSOLVED MYSTERY &amp; HAUNTED JAPANESE TRAIN | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350084/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 17:35:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 77 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: cutting out negative energy, Nelson Rockefeller Unsolved Mystery, Quantum Jumping, Astral projecting, Japanese train station horror story, Manifesting height, Peko-chan Horror story, mushroom theories, and much more!
Don’t wait and check your low-interest loan rate today at UPSTART.com/JUMPERS Check out the awesome hoodies and polos at Rhoback.com and use code JUMPER for a generous 20% off your first order.</description></item><item><title>EP.76 - DARK FUTURE THEORIES, REVERSE MANDELA EFFECTS &amp; CRAZY PRISON ESCAPE STORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350085/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 16:23:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 76 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Hypnotic Mandela Effect, Batman Mandela Effect, The Beatles reverse Mandela Effect, Ed Sheeran Theory, multiverse theories, futuristic theories, and much more! Look for Every Man Jack at Target, Walmart, Amazon, or everymanjack.com
Follow the podcast: @JumpersPodcast Follow Carlos: @CarlosJuico Follow Gavin: @GavinRutaa Check out the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.ly/JumpersJumpYT Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>EP.75 - THE NIGHT STALKER STORY, CRAZY FROG MANDELA EFFECT &amp; APPS YOU DIDN'T KNOW EXISTED | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350086/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 19:37:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 75 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: the Richard Ramirez story, the crazy frog Mandela effect, crazy apps that got deleted, the bucket list Mandela effect, influencers being the new cult leaders, Carlos&amp;rsquo; tattoo story, being motivated to succeed and much more!
Look for Every Man Jack at Target, Walmart, Amazon, or everymanjack.com Match with your dedicated therapist today at talkspace.</description></item><item><title>EP.74 - BUNNY MAN MYSTERY, THE WINDOW GHOST GAME &amp; COWBOY VS ALIENS MANDELA EFFECT | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350087/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 20:14:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 74 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: the Bunny Man story , the cowboy vs aliens Mandela effect, the picture ghost game, the window ghost game, how to tell if your house is being targeted, tattoos that you can&amp;rsquo;t get, a place where murder is legal and much more!
Follow the podcast: @JumpersPodcast Follow Carlos: @CarlosJuico Follow Gavin: @GavinRutaa Check out the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>EP.73 - HAUNTED ELEVATOR GAME, ELISA LAM UNSOLVED MYSTERY, &amp; A BUG WE’VE ALL EATEN | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350088/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 16:08:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 73 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Unsolved Mystery of Elisa Lam, Last thing on minds before death, most disgusting animals, two pretty best friends theory, Batman Theory, skinwalkers, Haunted elevator game, and much more! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.72 - MOST DANGEROUS KIDS TOYS, BLUE BABY GHOST GAME &amp; CAT IN THE HAT THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350089/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 71 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: the Hannah Montana card game , blue baby ghost game, Cat in the Hat theory, Get Out hidden meanings, Catcher in the Rye theories, teacher and student story, craziest rap bars in history and much more!
Follow the podcast: @JumpersPodcast Follow Carlos: @CarlosJuico Follow Gavin: @GavinRutaa Check out the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>EP.71 - NEW MANDELA EFFECTS, ELVIS IS ALIVE THEORY &amp; TESTING MY SISTER'S BOYFRIEND | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350090/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 22:58:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 71 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Big brother duties, Elvis is alive Theory, Kardashian Theory, Hunger games mandela effect, Avril lavinge mandela effect, DB Cooper unsolved mystery, evolution of streetwear and much more!
Follow the podcast: @JumpersPodcast Follow Carlos: @CarlosJuico Follow Gavin: @GavinRutaa Check out the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.ly/JumpersJumpYT Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>EP.70 - COCA-COLA MANDELA EFFECT, TURNING RED THEORIES, &amp; THE FOUR CORNER GAME | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350091/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 16:40:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 70 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: The biggest gym hack in the world, Coca-Cola Mandela effect, The cursed four corner game, the Kanye documentary, the ghost story of the grandma in the reflection , babysitting clown story, the Euphoria season 2 ending, cheating in the talking stage, and much more!
Follow the podcast: @JumpersPodcast Follow Carlos: @CarlosJuico Follow Gavin: @GavinRutaa Check out the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>EP.69 - HAUNTED STORIES, ILLEGAL BABY NAMES, &amp; THE ORIGIN OF ABGS | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350092/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 69 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: the lucky cat origin, illegal baby names, asian stereotypes, origin of abgs, holy cross burn phenomenon, Bahamas lighthouse theory, haunted stories, highschool advice, and much more!
Follow the podcast: @JumpersPodcast Follow Carlos: @CarlosJuico Follow Gavin: @GavinRutaa Check out the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.ly/JumpersJumpYT Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>EP.68 - BAHAMAS GHOST SIGHTING, HOTEL PARANORMAL STORIES, &amp; DIFFERENT TYPES OF DEJA VU | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350093/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 17:42:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 68 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Carlos&amp;rsquo; vacation ghost story, Bahamas paranormal sighting, Nassau ghost mystery, the different types of Deja Vu, meaning of hand gestures in different countries, living in the moment, cheating in school and much more!
Follow the podcast: @JumpersPodcast Follow Carlos: @CarlosJuico Follow Gavin: @GavinRutaa Check out the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.ly/JumpersJumpYT Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>EP.67 - PSYCHOPATH BEHAVIOUR, THE LOST BOYS UNSOLVED MYSTERY &amp; INTROVERT VS EXTROVERTS | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350094/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 17:38:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 67 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Psychopath behaviours, is being a Jack of All Trades bad?, The unsolved Canadian mystery of The Lost Boys of Pickering, Alien Theories/sightings, introvert vs extroverts, and much more!
Get 20% Off + Free Shipping @MANSCAPED by going to https://manscaped.com/jumpers or use the code &amp;ldquo;JUMPERS&amp;rdquo; at Manscaped.com! #sponsored
Follow the podcast: @JumpersPodcast Follow Carlos: @CarlosJuico Follow Gavin: @GavinRutaa Check out the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>EP.66 - ALL OF US ARE DEAD THEORIES, THE TINDER SWINDLER, &amp; MIND CONTROL TECHNOLOGY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350095/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 66 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Our Mount Rushmore of Youtubers, All of Us Are Dead zombie theories, mind control technology, the Tinder Swindler scam on Netflix, Tiktok solving a murder mystery, the Bermuda Triangle of Romania, the sample drill rap scene and much more!
Follow the podcast: @JumpersPodcast Follow Carlos: @CarlosJuico Follow Gavin: @GavinRutaa Check out the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>EP.65 - DREAM SYMBOLISMS, THE RAT KING THEORY, &amp; HOW LOVE CAN KILL | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350096/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 65 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Gavin&amp;rsquo;s crazy death dream, the Unsent Project, How love can kill, The first night effect, Rat King theory, Monsters inc Theory, Moana Theory, Pokemon Theory, and stories of our fight experiences.
Follow the podcast: @JumpersPodcast Follow Carlos: @CarlosJuico Follow Gavin: @GavinRutaa Check out the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.ly/JumpersJumpYT Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>EP.64 - BRITNEY SPEARS MANDELA EFFECT, CRAZY FOOD THEORIES, &amp; PRETTY WOMEN EFFECT | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350097/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 64 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: The Britney Spears Mandela effect, How sugar rushes are actually a myth, Jesus Christ Mandela effect, illegal islands that you can&amp;rsquo;t visit , pretty women theory, different love languages, how to approach a girl and much more!
Follow the podcast: @JumpersPodcast Follow Carlos: @CarlosJuico Follow Gavin: @GavinRutaa Check out the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>EP.63 - CRAZY PERSONALITY THEORIES, FILIPINO MARVEL THEORY, &amp; SOCIAL MEDIA THEORIES | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350098/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 16:29:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 63 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: The index/middle finger theory, personality theories, Filipino created Marvel theory, our last meals on death row, CES robot, Gen Z role models theory, fake vs reality, and much more!
Follow the podcast: @JumpersPodcast Follow Carlos: @CarlosJuico Follow Gavin: @GavinRutaa Check out the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.ly/JumpersJumpYT Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>EP.62 - EUPHORIA THEORIES, NICKELODEON FOOT THEORY, &amp; BOOTS POPSICLE MANDELA EFFECT | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350099/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 62 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Season 1 Euphoria theories, Dan Schneider&amp;rsquo;s foot fetish, how the boots popsicle never existed, how a book predicted the 2020 events 40 years ago, snowflake shapes, peeing in a pool theory, funny bathroom stories and much more!
Follow the podcast: @JumpersPodcast Follow Carlos: @CarlosJuico Follow Gavin: @GavinRutaa Check out the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>EP.61 - OMICRON THEORIES, SECRET BEHIND STARBUCKS ADVERTISING, JAPANESE RED ROOM CURSE | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350100/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 61 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: getting coronavirus, Omicron variant theories, why Starbucks misspells everyones name, secret marketing strategies by big corporations, hackers getting more advanced, the Japanese red room curse, importance of mindset in life, and much more!
Follow the podcast: @JumpersPodcast Follow Carlos: @CarlosJuico Follow Gavin: @GavinRutaa Check out the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.ly/JumpersJumpYT</description></item><item><title>EP.60 - JOHN'S TRUE GHOST STORIES, JONESTOWN MASSACRE, &amp; METAVERSE THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350101/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and special guest John Dasilva on Episode 60 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss The Jonestown Massacre, Jim Jones and popular cults, John&amp;rsquo;s real paranormal experiences in Guyana, Metaverse Theory, Elon musk Theory, Ghost stories working security at haunted places, and much more! Check out the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.ly/JumpersJumpYT Follow the podcast: @JumpersPodcast Follow Carlos: @CarlosJuico Follow Gavin: @GavinRutaa Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>EP.59 - MARK ZUCKERBERG EXPOSED, CRAZY POKEMON THEORY, &amp; THE BEATLES THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350102/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Josh Nugent on Episode 59 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss: Clones in the music industry Theory, Time travelers caught on tape, Mark Zuckerberg&amp;rsquo;s secrets exposed, Monsters Inc Theory, William Shakespeare Theory, Spiderman, The Beil Cyphers, and much more! Check out the podcast on YouTube: https://bit.ly/JumpersJumpYT Follow the podcast: @JumpersPodcast Follow Carlos: @CarlosJuico Follow Gavin: @GavinRutaa Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>EP.58 - CHRISTMAS THEORIES, MICHAEL JACKSON DAVE DAVE THEORY, CANDY-CANE GHOST STORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350103/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350103/</guid><description>Podcast Description JUMPERS JUMP CHRISTMAS SPECIAL!! Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 58 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: A bunch of Christmas theories, meaning of Christmas lights, dark origin of Frosty the Snowman, true crime Christmas stories, Michael Jackson is still alive theory, candy cane ghost story, getting caught trying to finesse, and much more! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.57 - FILIPINO KARAOKE THEORY, SPIRITUAL REALM THEORY, &amp; MANIFESTING SUCCESS | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350104/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and special guest Jbalwaysfresh on Episode 57 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss: jamiels success (millionaire cuts), how jamiel built his barber career, advice on determination, filipino karaoke song theory, filipino dark magic, paranormal filipino stories, simulation theory, old finch road ghost story, and much more! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.56 - SPIRITUAL EGG CLEANSE RITUAL, JEFFREY EPSTEIN CASE, &amp; JAPANESE BLOODY MARY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350105/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 56 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Doing an egg cleanse ritual, Japanese Bloody Mary story, name theories, Jeffrey Epstein case, how people cheat in casinos, and much more! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.55 - HAUNTED COW HEAD STORY, ZIMBABWE ALIEN SIGHTING, &amp; URBAN LEGENDS | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350106/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 03:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350106/</guid><description>Podcast Description ump in with Carlos Juico and special guest Denzel Vincent on Episode 55 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss the Denver Airport Theory, Japanese hauntings, Zimbabwe Alien phenomenon, The cursed Cow Head story and much more! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.54 - CURSED PALLBEARING RITUAL, RATATOUILLE THEORY &amp; ADDAMS FAMILY SUPERHUMAN THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350107/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 02:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on episode 54 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Jumpers 1 Year Anniversary, cursed vietanmese children game, ratatouille theories, Adam&amp;rsquo;s family superhuman theory, showing your family your significant other, and much more! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.53 - SERIAL KILLER STORIES, HAUNTED DOLL ISLAND, &amp; CURSED WINCHESTER HOUSE | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350108/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 03:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and special guest Deno on episode 53 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss: Serial killers that are roaming free, Haunted doll island in Mexico, SPC&amp;rsquo;s, The cursed Winchester maze house, Blue ghost tunnel vlog, and much more! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.52 - ASTROWORLD FESTIVAL DISSCUSSION, HAUNTED HOSPITAL, RAP INFLUENCE ON THE YOUTH | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350109/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 17:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on Episode 52 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss the tragic events that happened at Astrofest, the devil&amp;rsquo;s role in rap, haunted doctor story, spirits, creative blocks &amp;amp; many more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.51 - CURSED FRUIT DOLL STORY, REAL DEATH GAMES, &amp; MR BEAN THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350110/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 06:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and special guest Josh Nugent on Episode 51 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss the power of the mind, Ghost footage of Manchester, Real death games of Russia, Solipsim Theory, Secret inventor of the Internet Theory, Mr. Bean Theory, Simulations Theories, Tupac Theory, Josh&amp;rsquo;s cursed fruit doll story, Brain in a jar Theory and much more! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>EP.50 - HAUNTED DORA DOLL, THE THREE KINGS RITUAL, SCARY HALLOWEEN DECORATIONS | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350111/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 04:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on Episode 50 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss the three kings ritual, Halloween decoration story, Ronald O&amp;rsquo;Bryan story, Saebyok Squid Game theory, the haunted dora doll &amp;amp; many more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.48 - CURSED BACKROOM DREAMS, DABABY THEORY, SLEEP PARALYSIS EXPERIENCES | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350112/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 05:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on Episode 46 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss the Dababy theory, rituals for the Illuminati, cursed dreams, our experience of going into a haunted tunnel, sleep paralysis story &amp;amp; many more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.46 - SQUID GAME THEORIES, BANSHINSABA URBAN LEGEND, PARANORMAL ACTIVITY STORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350113/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 05:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on Episode 46 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss all the Squid Game theories, the Banshinsaba urban legend, paranormal activity story at the park, sacred tattoos, biggest scams in the world &amp;amp; many more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.47 - THE AFTERLIFE THEORY, MANIFESTATION, &amp; USING ANPHANTASIA w/ Emson Mallari | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350114/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 03:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and special guest Emson Mallari on Episode 47 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss The IPhone Conspiracy, The Afterlife Theory, Manifestation, Oracle&amp;rsquo;s Alien prophecy, The Lightbulb Theory, using Aphantasia, Drake vs Kanye, reliving past lives, and much more! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.44 - AMELIA EARHART THEORY, NINJA'S GOING EXTINCT, NINJA TURTLES PTSD THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350115/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 07:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on Episode 44 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss Ninja&amp;rsquo;s and how they are going extinct, the mysterious case of Amelia Earhart, acting in a movie, TNMT PTSD theory, scariest escape rooms &amp;amp; many more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.43 - DARK NARUTO THEORY, DISNEY PIXAR THEORIES, &amp; ALIEN PANDEMIC THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350116/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 23:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Denzel Vincent on Episode 43 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss The Diary of a Wimpy kid Theory, Rick and Morty Theory, Naruto Theory, Finding Nemo Theory, Monsters Inc Theory, Incredibles Theory, Reddit conspiracy theory, Alien pandemic Theory and much more! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.42 - DRAKE MENTIONED OUR THEORY ON CLB, DISNEY AND THE ILLUMINATI, &amp; DONDA THEORIES | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350117/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 02:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on Episode 42 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss how Drake used our theory in his newest album CLB, Donda theories, early retirement, the Aladdin theory, Suite Life on Deck theories &amp;amp; many more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.40 - LIZARD URBAN LEGEND, ANIMAL CROSSING THEORY, &amp; MONEY VS HAPPINESS | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350118/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2021 20:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350118/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on Episode 40 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss why Lizards kiss the ground at sunset, animal crossing purgatory theory, money doesn&amp;rsquo;t buy happiness, instagram followers, Carlos&amp;rsquo; toxic trait &amp;amp; many more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP. 39 - ALMOST RECRUITED BY A CULT, OUIJA BOARD GHOST STORY, &amp; DISNEY VS SHREK THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350119/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 02:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Josh Nugent on episode 39 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss crazy Costco marketing theory, Ouiji boards, weird foods we&amp;rsquo;ve ate, Josh almost being recruited by a cult, Shrek and Lord Farquad Theory, computers predicting the future, and much more! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.38 - DEEP MEANING OF DREAMS, OLYMPIC GAMES THEORIES, &amp; SECRETS OF MARKETING | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350120/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 01:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350120/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on Episode 38 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss the different meaning of our dreams, Olympic games theories, secrets of marketing, facing fears, taking compliments &amp;amp; many more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP 37 - THEORIES OF LIFE, SECRETS TO LIVING HAPPY, &amp; DARK SCOOBY DOO THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350121/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 03:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and special guest Deno on episode 37 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss theories on life, secrets on how to live a happy life, Marvel conspiracy, cheating in sports, dark Scooby doo theory, atomic bombs, and much more! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.36 - KANYE WEST THEORIES, SPIRITED AWAY THEORY, &amp; MR.MIME IS ASH'S REAL DAD | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350122/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 03:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350122/</guid><description>Podcast Description Go to https://www.upstart.com to lower your monthly payments today! Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on Episode 36 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss about the Kanye West and David Bowie theory, how Spirited Away talks about prostitution, Ash&amp;rsquo;s real dad in Pokemon, finding yourself, old Youtubers we used to watch &amp;amp; many more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP. 34 - CONTROLLING THE WEATHER, SPONGEBOB SCHOLAR THEORY, &amp; CRAZY PLACEBO EFFECT | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350123/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 06:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350123/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on Episode 32 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss about Shamans drinking reindeer urine, wristband &amp;amp; plant placebo effect, spongebob scholar theory, doing what makes you happy, being street smart &amp;amp; many more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP. 33 - JOSH'S ALIEN ENCOUNTER, MIND-BLOWING SIMULATION THEORY, &amp; SECRETS OF THE MIND | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350124/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2021 03:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and special guest Josh Nugent on Episode 33 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss our lives being predicted by AI, lost ancient technology theory, professional slap fights, Josh&amp;rsquo; ufo experience, secrets of the mind, mind-blowing simulation theory, the law of correspondence, and much more! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.32 - TUPAC REINCARNATION THEORY, CALLING PARANORMAL NUMBERS, &amp; GHOSTS PULL PRANKS | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350125/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 02:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on Episode 32 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss the Tupac reincarnation theory, haunted places in Toronto, near death experiences, ghosts pulling pranks on us, calling paranormal numbers &amp;amp; many more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP. 31 - BABYSITTING A GHOST, CANNIBAL TRIBE IN PHILIPPINES, &amp; SHREK THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350126/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 21:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and special guest Robbyn Deleon on Episode 31 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss finding yourself as a creative, how to start your own podcast, life as a Filipino superstitions, Robbyn&amp;rsquo;s ghost encounters, Backyardigans Theory, Shrek Theory, and much more! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.30 - MARIO COLLECTING SOULS, SPONGEBOB KARATE METAPHOR, &amp; DANA WHITE PUPPET THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350127/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 17:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on Episode 30 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss the Mario coin theory, Spongebob karate metaphor, Mcgregor and Dana White theory, Neuralink, voice acting &amp;amp; many more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP. 29 - MJ NICK FURY'S DAUGHTER, LOKI DEATH THEORY &amp; ALL MARVEL THEORIES - JUMPERS JUMP EP. 29 | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350128/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 00:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350128/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and special guest Luca Perch on episode 29 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss all Marvel Theories: MJ Nick Fury&amp;rsquo;s daughter theory, Loki suicide theory, Vision worthy theory, Spiderman theory, Thor Groot theory, Hulk theory, and much more! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.28 - CURSED KLEENEX AD, OLIVIA RODRIGO THEORY, HAVING A CLONE &amp; YAO MING THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350129/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 21:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350129/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on Episode 28 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss the cursed Japanese Kleenex Ad, Olivia Rodrigo theory, Yao Ming being made in a lab, having a clone, Mr.112Dirtbag video, different fighting styles, &amp;amp; many more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP. 27 - HIDDEN CULT SYMBOLS, DARK ALADDIN THEORY, &amp; THIRD EYE THEORY - JUMPERS JUMP EP. 27 | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350130/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 05:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350130/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and special guest Josh Nugent on Episode 27 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss the Blood Moon, third eye pineal gland theory, secret free mason symbols in media, the Aladdin post apocalyptic theory, and much more! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP. 26 - RAPPER PREDICTING CORONAVIRUS, AMERICAN MURDER GHOST STORY &amp; DISCORD CATFISH | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350131/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 11:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on Episode 26 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss the rapper who predicted coronavirus, the American murder ghost story, rapper deep fakes, randonauting with friends, Disneyland ghosts, the discord catfish, &amp;amp; many more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP 25 - DARK SIMULATION THEORY, GHOST RENDER THEORY, &amp; PANDEMIC CONSPIRACY - JUMPERS JUMP EP. 25 | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350132/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 21:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350132/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and special guest Deno on episode 25 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss following your dream career, proof we&amp;rsquo;re in a simulation, ghost rendering theory, pandemic conspiracies, black mirror plots, and much more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.24 - ONLYFANS HORROR STORY, DISASSOCIATION &amp; EGG THEORY, DARK WEB GAME SHOWS | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350133/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 04:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on Episode 24 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss disassociation, the egg theory, onlyfans horror stories, dark web game shows, Phineas and Ferb theories, water on Mars theory, &amp;amp; many more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.23 - JOSH SAW HIS PAST LIFE, ANNUNAKI THEORY, &amp; JAPAN'S TOMB OF JESUS | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350134/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 02:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and special guest Josh Nugent on Episode 23 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss moving to Mars, The ancient sumerians, Annunaki Theory, Winnie the pooh theory, Adrenachrome cults, Josh&amp;rsquo;s reincarnation story, and Japan&amp;rsquo;s Jesus Theory. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.22 - HACHISHAKUSAMA URBAN LEGEND, JUSTIN TRUDEAU THEORY, &amp; AFTERLIFE/GUARDIAN ANGEL | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350135/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 12:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on Episode 22 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss the urban legend Hachishakusama, what happens in the afterlife, guardian angels, Justin Trudeau theory, the meaning of monster energy drink, dark childhood nursery rhymes, &amp;amp; many more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP 21 - ALIENS MADE HUMANS THEORY, DARK WEB STORIES, &amp; MOON LANDING CONSPIRACIES - JUMPERS JUMP EP. 21 | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350136/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 23:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350136/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and special guest Josh Nugent on Episode 21 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss stories of our abandoned school, human origin theory, only fans hustle, pyramids around the world, buried treasure of the Philippines, and much more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.20 - VALENTINES DAY ORIGIN , "WHITE LADY" GHOST, ADRENOCHROME THEORY, SLEEP DEMONS | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350137/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 09:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on Episode 20 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss the origins of Valentines Day, Graveyard possession story, Adrenochrome theory, the meaning of birthmarks, childhood stories, &amp;amp; sleep demons. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.19 - CRAZY EASTER THEORY, PSYCHEDELIC THEORIES, &amp; CREATING CLOTHING BRANDS | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350138/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 05:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350138/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and special guest Jetlag. On this episode we discuss: creating a clothing brand, the Easter Mushroom theory, secrets of the Vatican, Alien sightings, and much more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.18 - HALLOWEEN THEORY , "TENT LADY" URBAN LEGEND, CRAZY DMT TRIPS &amp; VAMPIRES | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350139/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 23:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on Episode 18 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss the origins of Halloween, Old Finch road stories, &amp;ldquo;Tent Lady&amp;rdquo; urban legend, DMT trips with similar experiences, NFT&amp;rsquo;s, &amp;amp; vampires. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP. 17 - NOSTRADAMUS PROPHECY, TIME TRAVELER ON CAMERA, &amp; PROJECT MONTAUK CONSPIRACY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350140/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 04:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350140/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and special guest Myles V on Episode 17 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss real alien sightings, Footage of inside the pyramids, Nostradamus prophecies, time travelers caught on camera, Project Montauk conspiracy, mind control, and chasing goals &amp;amp; overcoming obstacles. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.16 - CRAZY DENVER AIRPORT THEORY, THE ILLUMINATI, TWIN FLAME, LILO &amp; STITCH THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350141/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 15:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on Episode 16 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss the Denver Airport , Jim Carey trying to expose the Illuminati, finding your twin flame, vodoo dolls, &amp;amp; different cartoon theories. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP. 15 - SURVIVING SCHOOL KNIFE ATTACK, DORA EXPLORA THEORY, ZOMBIE VIRUS | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350142/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 02:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350142/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and special guest Logan King on Episode 15 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss Logan&amp;rsquo;s surviving a school knife attack story, Dora the explorer theory, Nazi experiments, Pineal gland theory eye of Horus theory, The Regular Show theory, and more. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.14 - WANDAVISION THEORY, LIL UZI PINK DIAMOND CONSPIRACY, RUNNING FROM THE POLICE | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350143/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 07:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350143/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on Episode 14 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss the Wandavision theory, the reason why Lil Uzi got the pink diamond on his head, predicting technology in the future, running from the police, &amp;amp; the biggest lessons we learned during quarantine. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP. 13 - THE TESLA THEORY, GIANTS FOUND ON EARTH, &amp; RJAY'S GHOST STORIES | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350144/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 03:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350144/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and special guest Ryan Jay on Episode 13 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss the Nikola Tesla Theory, evidence of giants found on earth, alien theories, Ghost stories, and theories about holiday traditions. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP. 12 - CRAZY LION KING THEORY, WHY WE GET DEJA VU &amp; SANPAKU EYE SUPERSTITION | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350145/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 20:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350145/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on Episode 12 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss why we get &amp;ldquo;Deja Vu&amp;rdquo;, the Lion King theory, palm readings, sanpaku eyes, &amp;amp; dream hopping. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.11 - DRAKE MICHAEL JACKSON THEORY, THE KRABBY PATTY FORMULA, &amp; STREETFIGHTS | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350146/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 04:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350146/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and special guest Charan Charles on Episode 11 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss childhood street fights, the Kanye diss track Sicko Mode Theory, Drake Michael Jackson Theory, the Krabby patty secret formula, &amp;amp; the Michael Jordan Theory. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.10 - SEEING ALIENS IN 2021, TIME TRAVELLING THEORIES, &amp; CRAZY NEW YEARS EVE STORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350147/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 22:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350147/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on Episode 10 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss seeing &amp;ldquo;aliens&amp;rdquo; in the sky, the titanic time travel theory, crazy firework story during New Years Eve, our 2021 predictions , &amp;amp; our childhood crushes. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.9 - DA VINCI CODE THEORY, AUNT'S GHOST STORY 2, &amp; THE AFTERLIFE w/ Sophia Lorenzo | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350148/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350148/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and special guest Sophia Lorenzo on Episode 9 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss the afterlife, the illuminati, finding your passion, demon possessions, the Da Vinci Code Theory, Max and Ruby theory, the Stoned ape theory, Carlos&amp;rsquo; Aunt&amp;rsquo;s ghost hotel story, and Multiverse theories. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.8 - CRAZY DISCOVERY IN THE PYRAMIDS, BEING IMMORTAL, &amp; APPLE IPHONE THEORY | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350149/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 18:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350149/</guid><description>Podcast Description SHOW LESSJump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on Episode 8 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss crazy discoveries found in the pyramids, being immortal, the Dan Bilzerian theory, the dangers of social media , &amp;amp; being voice actors. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.7 - END OF THE WORLD, DARK DISNEY THEORIES, &amp; JOSH'S GHOST STORIES | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350150/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 03:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350150/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and special guest Josh Nugent on Episode 7 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss the stories about our abandoned elementary school, the end of the world, dark Disney/Pixar theories, &amp;amp; Josh&amp;rsquo;s encounters with spirits. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.6 - HOLLOW EARTH THEORY, DARK NURSERY RHYMES, &amp; PREDICTING THE FUTURE | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350151/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 00:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350151/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on Episode 6 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss the Hollow Earth theory, the truth about nursery rhymes, what will the future look like, &amp;amp; the secret about different frequencies. #JumpersJump Carlos Juico https://www.instagram.com/carlosjuico&amp;hellip; Juico Studios https://www.instagram.com/juicostudio&amp;hellip; Gavin Ruta https://www.instagram.com/gaviinsgone/ Sober Society https://www.instagram.com/sobersocietyy/ Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.5 - CHRISTMAS THEORY, SECRETS OF THE DEEP SEA, &amp; ALIEN INVASIONS | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350152/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 00:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350152/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on Episode 5 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss reliving past memories, Illuminati Christmas theory, what&amp;rsquo;s secrets are in the deep sea, &amp;amp; consciousness through psychedelics. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.4 - THE DARK WEB, HIGH AT THE DENTIST, &amp; MORE GHOST STORIES - EP. 4 | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350153/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 02:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350153/</guid><description>Podcast Description SHOW MOREJump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on Episode 4 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss nostalgic tv shows/games, theories of the Illuminati, the Dark Web, being high at the dentist, &amp;amp; unlocking creativity. #JumpersJump Carlos Juico https://www.instagram.com/carlosjuico&amp;hellip; Juico Studios https://www.instagram.com/juicostudio&amp;hellip; Gavin Ruta https://www.instagram.com/gaviinsgone/ Sober Society https://www.instagram.com/sobersocietyy/
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.3 - SIMULATION THEORIES, MY HITMAN ANCESTOR, &amp; MEANINGS BEHIND DREAMS - JUMPERS JUMP EP. 3 | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350154/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 03:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350154/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on Episode 3 of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss growing up filipino, Carlos&amp;rsquo; infamous ancestor, simulation theories, and the meanings behind dreams.
Watch us on Youtube: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCRFF8xw5dg9mL4r5ryFOtKw?view_as=subscriber Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.2 - ALTERNATE DIMENSIONS, DARK TV SHOW THEORIES, &amp; MYTHICAL CREATURES | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350155/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 22:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350155/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico &amp;amp; Gavin Ruta on Episode 2 of Jumpers Jump. This episode we discuss a Christmas Psychedelic Origin Theory, Dark TV Show Cartoon Theories, The Mandela Effect, Alternate Dimensions, and Stories of Finding Mythical Creatures. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP.1 - YOUTUBE HOLES, GHOST STORIES, &amp; SUPERSTITIONS - JUMPERS JUMP EP. 1 | Jumpers Jump</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5882350156/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 02:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5882350156/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jump in with Carlos Juico and Gavin Ruta on the first ever episode of JUMPERS JUMP. This episode we discuss topics such as falling into Youtube holes, experiences with real ghost encounters, personal superstitions, and manifesting success. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>