<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Thoma Bravo's Behind the Deal on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/thoma-bravos-behind-the-deal/</link><description>Recent content in Thoma Bravo's Behind the Deal on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 09:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/thoma-bravos-behind-the-deal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How the Flexera Carve-Out Revolutionized IT Management | Thoma Bravo's Behind the Deal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5422850021/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5422850021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Thoma Bravo Managing Partner Seth Boro gives an inside look at how the firm can hit the ground running after a platform carve-out investment. Thoma Bravo helped build out Flexera back in 2008, exited in 2011, and is now back for more with a controlling stake as of 2020. Flexera is a company that provides customers with the ability to map their IT spend to better optimize their IT estate.</description></item><item><title>Beyond the ConnectWise Transformation with Mike Hoffmann and Jason Magee | Thoma Bravo's Behind the Deal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5422850020/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5422850020/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Beyond the Deal mini-sode, Thoma Bravo Partner Mike Hoffmann and ConnectWise CEO Jason Magee sit down, and go beyond their business partnership. They chat about their top business role models, their first jobs, and what they’re reading.
For more information on Thoma Bravo&amp;rsquo;s Behind the Deal, visit https://www.thomabravo.com/behindthedeal Learn more about Thoma Bravo: https://www.thomabravo.com/ Visit ConnectWise&amp;rsquo;s website: https://www.connectwise.com/
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How Thoma Bravo Partnered with Founder-Led ConnectWise to Transform the MSP Industry | Thoma Bravo's Behind the Deal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5422850019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5422850019/</guid><description>Podcast Description ConnectWise is an industry-leading robust platform of software built for technology solutions providers (TSPs) to run their entire as-a-service business. Their solutions help managed service providers (MSPs) outsource their help desk, billing, and other IT services to small and medium-sized businesses so that they can focus on their products, not IT problems.
Thoma Bravo Partner Mike Hoffmann sits down with ConnectWise CEO Jason Magee to discuss their partnership and the importance of a shared vision when taking a founder-led business to the next level.</description></item><item><title>Beyond the J.D. Power Transformation, with Scott Crabill and David Habiger | Thoma Bravo's Behind the Deal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5422850018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5422850018/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Beyond the Deal mini-sode, Thoma Bravo Managing Partner Scott Crabill and J.D. Power President and CEO David Habiger’s conversation goes deeper than just their business partnership. The two give insight into their career paths, what failure has taught them, and where they might be today if they weren’t in business together.
For more information on Thoma Bravo&amp;rsquo;s Behind the Deal, visit https://www.thomabravo.com/behindthedeal Learn more about Thoma Bravo: https://www.</description></item><item><title>How J.D. Power Uses Data to Drive the Auto Industry Forward | Thoma Bravo's Behind the Deal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5422850016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5422850016/</guid><description>Podcast Description J.D. Power has nearly 80% name recognition for its awards, but its data business is the real hidden gem. In this episode, Thoma Bravo Managing Partner Scott Crabill sits down with J.D. Power’s CEO David Habiger to discuss how the company is bringing together the fragmented auto industry, and how Thoma Bravo has partnered with J.D. Power on acquisition strategy, merging two world-class companies, and flattening organizational structure. The conversation then broadens to include what it was like to navigate a merger during a global pandemic and how to put the right people in the right leadership positions.</description></item><item><title>Beyond the Syntellis Carve Out, with A.J. Rohde and Flint Brenton | Thoma Bravo's Behind the Deal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5422850014/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5422850014/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Beyond the Deal mini-sode, Thoma Bravo Senior Partner A.J. Rohde and Syntellis CEO Flint Brenton’s conversation continues outside the bounds of their partnership. The two discuss tough customer calls, their favorite software sectors, and who they’re rooting for this season in the NBA.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Behind the Deal is Back for Season 2 | Thoma Bravo's Behind the Deal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5422850002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5422850002/</guid><description>Podcast Description For even more inside looks at some of the firm’s biggest deals, Thoma Bravo’s Behind the Deal returns for Season 2. This season, Thoma Bravo partners will sit down with portfolio company CEOs from acquisitions like J.D. Power, ConnectWise, and Syntellis to give a behind the scenes look at some of the carve outs, acquisitions and mergers that have helped make Thoma Bravo the world’s largest tech-buyout firm.</description></item><item><title>How Syntellis Grew from a Software Carveout to a Successful Standalone Company | Thoma Bravo's Behind the Deal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5422850001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5422850001/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the Season Two premiere, a behind-the-scenes journey with Thoma Bravo Senior Partner A.J. Rohde to discuss our deal to acquire and carve out Syntellis, a performance management software business, from its parent company, Kaufman Hall Software. By partnering with Madison Dearborn, Thoma Bravo crafted a strategic business plan to carve out Syntellis into a standalone company.
A.J. speaks with Syntellis CEO Flint Brenton, a five-time successful software CEO, about how Flint ultimately became the leader of Syntellis after a breakfast meetup in a small Californian diner, and how their shared Midwestern sensibility has led to a successful partnership, ultimately selling Syntellis to Roper Technologies in 2023.</description></item><item><title>How Orlando Bravo Helped Build the World’s Largest Software Buyout Firm | Thoma Bravo's Behind the Deal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5422850003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5422850003/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the Season One finale of Thoma Bravo’s Behind The Deal, Thoma Bravo Partner Andrew Almeida connects with Thoma Bravo Founder and Managing Partner Orlando Bravo who shares his stories of success and trial and error in building Thoma Bravo. In the interview, Andrew helps listeners get to know Orlando beyond the dealmaking, as he shares inspiring stories about his mentors Carl Thoma and Marcel Bernard, tactics for staying positive and pragmatic in the face of problems, and how he applies the lessons from being a parent to his professional career.</description></item><item><title>How AppOmni Seized the SaaS Security Market Opportunity | Thoma Bravo's Behind the Deal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5422850004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5422850004/</guid><description>Podcast Description AppOmni is a leader in securing SaaS applications. In this episode, Thoma Bravo Partner Tre Sayle talks with AppOmni Co-founder and CEO Brendan O’Connor about how AppOmni has tripled in size in the year since their partnership with the Thoma Bravo Growth team began.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How a Merger Helped Veriforce Grow to Five Times Its Size | Thoma Bravo's Behind the Deal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5422850005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5422850005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Veriforce is a global provider of contract management software for industrial markets. In this episode, Thoma Bravo Partner Hudson Smith speaks with Veriforce CEO Colby Lane about how Veriforce expanded to almost five times its original size in under five years by an acquisition process that brought Veriforce together with PEC Safety.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How Circle CVI - a Niche Category Leader in Healthcare - Has Grown with Private Equity | Thoma Bravo's Behind the Deal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5422850006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5422850006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Circle CVI is the global leader in cardiac imaging solutions used by some of the world’s leading hospitals and physicians. In this episode, Thoma Bravo Partner Carl Press speaks with Co-Founder and CEO Greg Ogrodnick about how Thoma Bravo backed Circle CVI, a category leader in a small but very growing category of healthcare, and how their one year partnership has flourished as a result.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How Quorum Overcame Adversity Through Private Equity | Thoma Bravo's Behind the Deal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5422850007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5422850007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Quorum’s suite of software solutions for the oil, gas, and renewable energy sectors is designed to cover each area of their business - from planning, operations, accounting, measurement, transportation, and logistics. Thoma Bravo Partner Tara Gadgil speaks with former Quorum CEO Gene Austin about their partnership and how they weathered the storm of the global pandemic by continuing to invest in their product and serve it’s customers effectively in a difficult time.</description></item><item><title>How Leadership Transformed the Culture of Conga | Thoma Bravo's Behind the Deal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5422850008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5422850008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Thoma Bravo Managing Partner Holden Spaht tells the story of how CEO Noel Goggin turned Conga into a market leader for commercial operations transformation by focusing on company culture and customers.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How Majesco Brings the Speed of Private Equity to Transform the Insurance Business | Thoma Bravo's Behind the Deal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5422850009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5422850009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Majesco is a leader in providing technology and software solutions for the life, property, and casualty insurance business. In this episode, Thoma Bravo Senior Partner AJ Rohde speaks with Majesco CEO Adam Elster about how the company partnered with Thoma Bravo to use the speed of private equity to expedite the digitization of the insurance industry.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How Apryse Achieves Fast Growth and High Margins | Thoma Bravo's Behind the Deal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5422850010/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5422850010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Apryse is a leading provider of document processing technology for developers and enterprises. On this episode of Thoma Bravo’s Behind The Deal, Apryse CEO Cassidy Smirnow and Thoma Bravo Operating Partner Kristin Weston reflect on how Cassidy has led the company through a total rebrand and has achieved accelerated growth with high margins as a result.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How SailPoint Keeps Business Identities Safe | Thoma Bravo's Behind the Deal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5422850011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5422850011/</guid><description>Podcast Description SailPoint Co-Founder and CEO Mark McClain speaks with Thoma Bravo Managing Partner Seth Boro about how they forged a relationship that led to Thoma Bravo’s first ever IPO of a portfolio company, and eventually acquiring SailPoint twice over the course of a decade.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How ABC Fitness Keeps Your Gym Running | Thoma Bravo's Behind the Deal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5422850013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5422850013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Thoma Bravo Managing Partner Scott Crabill details how ABC Fitness quadrupled their client base after Thoma Bravo acquired the fitness technology company in 2018, and then discusses how ABC’s go-to-market strategy was transformed and taken to the next level with ABC Fitness CEO Bill Davis.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Welcome To Thoma Bravo’s Behind the Deal | Thoma Bravo's Behind the Deal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5422850012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5422850012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join Orlando Bravo, founder and managing partner of Thoma Bravo - one of the largest software investors in the world - for stories behind some of its biggest and most dynamic acquisitions.
From Orlando Bravo: “At Thoma Bravo, we partner with great technology companies to help them do even greater things. Over the past 20 years, the firm has acquired or invested in more than 420 companies, and behind every one of these deals is a unique story, and that’s what this podcast is all about.</description></item></channel></rss>