<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dan Carlin's Hardcore History: Addendum on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/dan-carlins-hardcore-history-addendum/</link><description>Recent content in Dan Carlin's Hardcore History: Addendum on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 00:20:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/dan-carlins-hardcore-history-addendum/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>EP27 More Steppe Stories | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History: Addendum</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4506780001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 00:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4506780001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Huns, Mongols, Turks, Scythians and other nomadic steppe tribes are longtime interests of Dan&amp;rsquo;s. In this show he interviews historian Kenneth W. Harl who specializes in the study of those fascinating peoples. 1. Empires of the Steppes: A History of the Nomadic Tribes Who Shaped Civilization by Kenneth W. Harl 2. China Marches West: The Qing Conquest of Central Eurasia by Peter C. Perdue
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP26 Dig This! | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History: Addendum</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4506780002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4506780002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Daniele Bolelli the fabulous host of “History on Fire” and I fanboy out over archaeology. We had some inexplicable audio problems at times with the recording, so hopefully that doesn&amp;rsquo;t detract from the greatness of the guest.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP25 The Long View | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History: Addendum</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4506780003/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 02:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4506780003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan tries focusing a much wider historical lens on perennial human issues like war, land ownership, immigration, ethnicity, environmental worries and the double-edged sword that is human inventiveness. 1. Agricola and Germania by Tacitus 2. A Most Dangerous Book: Tacitus&amp;rsquo;s Germania from the Roman Empire to the Third Reich by Christopher B. Krebs
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP24 Manifesting the Muse with Rick | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History: Addendum</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4506780004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 04:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4506780004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rick Rubin joins Dan to discuss human creativity. This unusual show evolves as it goes though and by the end covers a wide array of subjects and topics. By the end it isn&amp;rsquo;t even clear who is asking questions and who is answering them. 1. “Broken Record” with Rick Rubin and Malcolm Gladwell https://www.pushkin.fm/podcasts/broken-record 2. “Tetragrammaton” podcast with Rick Rubin https://tunein.com/radio/Tetragrammaton-with-Rick-Rubin-p3496748/ 3. “From Cyrus to Alexander: A History of the Persian Empire” by Pierre Briant 4.</description></item><item><title>EP23 Boxing with Ghosts | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History: Addendum</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4506780005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 02:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4506780005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ready for an argument? Like Dan&amp;rsquo;s quote voice? Waiting to hear Dan discuss boxing? Then you&amp;rsquo;ve hit the trifecta. Boxing expert Mike Silver and Dan discuss whether today&amp;rsquo;s modern fighters could compete with those of yesteryear. 1. The Arc of Boxing: The Rise and Decline of the Sweet Science by Mike Silver 2. The Night the Referee Hit Back: Memorable Moments from the World of Boxing by Mike Silver 3.</description></item><item><title>EP22 The Fabulous Bill Barrett | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History: Addendum</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4506780006/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 02:05:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4506780006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bill Barrett has been the voice of Dan Carlin’s podcasts since they began in 2005. In this retrospective Dan looks back at samples of Bill’s catalog of work.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP21 Hollandansandbrook | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History: Addendum</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4506780007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 03:36:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4506780007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tom Holland and Dominic Sandbrook stop by to continue the conversation with Dan that began on their own podcast The Rest is History. 1. “Rubicon” by Tom Holland 2. “Dominion” by Tom Holland 3. “Persian Fire” by Tom Holland
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP 20 A Republic Lost at Sea | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History: Addendum</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4506780008/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 00:57:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4506780008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Professor Barry Strauss and Dan talk about Cleopatra, Mark Antony, Julius Caesar, Augustus Caesar and a host of historical luminaries in a tale worthy of Shakespeare as the Roman Republic goes down with the ships at Actium. Show Notes: 1. “The War That Made the Roman Empire: Antony, Cleopatra, and Octavian at Actium” by Barry Strauss 2. “The Art of War” by Sun Tzu 3. Dan Carlin’s Hardcore History “Death Throes of the Republic”</description></item><item><title>EP19 Asymmetrical Perspectives | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History: Addendum</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4506780009/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 03:23:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4506780009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Author, actor and senior fellow at the Modern War Institute Max Brooks joins Dan to discuss asymmetrical warfare and related societal issues. 1. &amp;ldquo;On War&amp;rdquo; by Gen. Carl von Clausewitz 2. “The Art of War” by Sun Tsu 3. &amp;ldquo;War and Anti-War: Survival at the Dawn of the 21st Century” by Alvin and Heidi Toffler
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP18 Iranian Interconnections | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History: Addendum</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4506780010/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 01:44:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4506780010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Iranian-born historian John Ghazvinian&amp;rsquo;s new book is about the history of the U.S.-Iranian relationship. He and Dan discuss coups, oil, religion, history, arms deals, Shahs, U.S. presidents and wars. 1. “America and Iran: A History, 1720 to the Present” by John Ghazvinian.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP17 Engineering Victory with Elon | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History: Addendum</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4506780011/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 08:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4506780011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Elon Musk and Bill Riley from SpaceX join Dan to discuss the underappreciated role of science and engineering in war. As you might imagine, military aircraft feature prominently in the conversation. 1. The Wages of destruction by Adam Tooze2. The Art of War by Sun Tzu 3.The Wages of Destruction: The Making and Breaking of the Nazi Economy by Adam Tooze
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP16 Powers Thrones and Dan Jones | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History: Addendum</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4506780012/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2021 20:22:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4506780012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Historian Dan Jones’ specialty is the Middle Ages. Dan Carlin adores the Middle Ages. Normans anyone? 1. Powers and Thrones: A New History of the Middle Ages by Dan Jones 2. The Templars: The Rise and Spectacular Fall of God&amp;rsquo;s Holy Warriors by Dan Jones 3. The Wars of the Roses: The Fall of the Plantagenets and the Rise of the Tudors by Dan Jones 4. The Plantagenets: The Warrior Kings and Queens Who Made England by Dan Jones 5.</description></item><item><title>EP15 The Supernova Coda | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History: Addendum</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4506780013/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 03:55:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4506780013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Author Ian W. Toll who has written extensively on the Pacific Theater in the Second World War joins Dan to put the finishing touches on the Supernova in the East subject matter. 1. Pacific Crucible: War at Sea in the Pacific, 1941–1942 by Ian W. Toll 2. The Conquering Tide: War in the Pacific Islands, 1942–1944 by Ian W. Toll 3. Twilight of the Gods: War in the Western Pacific, 1944-1945 by Ian W.</description></item><item><title>EP14 The Game of War | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History: Addendum</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4506780014/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 00:51:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4506780014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan discusses his background in miniature wargaming and then talks to one of the architects of a popular Second World War themed video game about the genre, its development, growth and challenges. 1. War Games through the Ages 3,000BC to 1,500AD by Donald F. Featherstone 2. How to Play War Games in Miniature: A Forgotten Wargaming Pioneer Early Wargames by Joseph Morschauser
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP13 Gladwell and the Bomber Mafia | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History: Addendum</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4506780015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 00:33:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4506780015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Revisionist History host Malcolm Gladwell joins Dan to discuss the development of U.S. precision bombing ideas, Curtis LeMay and the firebombing of Japanese cities.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP12 Wolf Pack Hunting with Hanks | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History: Addendum</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4506780016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 18:45:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4506780016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tom Hanks joins Dan to talk about his new Second World War naval-themed film “Greyhound”. This is an hour-long conversation with two fans of History geeking out over the past.” Show Notes:
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP11 Toronto Redux | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History: Addendum</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4506780017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 01:25:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4506780017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Description: Canadian television personality, radio and podcast host Jeff Marek takes over the show and interviews Dan. Show Notes:
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP10 Strangelove Whisperings | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History: Addendum</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4506780018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 01:48:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4506780018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Description: In a world that can sometimes be obsessed with the current threat du jour, author Fred Kaplan reminds us that one of the all-time great threats to us all hasn&amp;rsquo;t gone anywhere. Notes:
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP9 Glimpses of Olympias | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History: Addendum</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4506780019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 05:35:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4506780019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Description:Philip II of Macedonia and his son Alexander the Great are two of the most impressive figures in history. Few could contend with either man. One woman held her own with both of them. Alexander&amp;rsquo;s mother Olympias. Notes:
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP8 Caesar at Hastings | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History: Addendum</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4506780020/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 03:51:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4506780020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Description: Could militaries separated by ten centuries compete on a battlefield? In this alternative history experiment two armies that successfully invaded Britain a millennium apart are matched. Which side would you bet on? Show Notes:
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP7 Hardcore History On Fire | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History: Addendum</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4506780021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 21:22:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4506780021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan and History on Fire host Danielle Bolelli do a crosscast together about Nazis, political spectrums, U.S. Presidents they want back and some other stuff. Basically it&amp;rsquo;s a typical phone call between these two guys that an audience gets to hear for once. Show Notes: Mein Kampf by Adolf Hitler
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP6 On The Vietnam War with Sir Max | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History: Addendum</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4506780022/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 00:53:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4506780022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Description: This show comes in two parts, an overview of the Vietnam War era by Dan, followed by a conversation with famed writer, historian and war correspondent Sir Max Hastings about his experience in Vietnam and his new book on the Vietnam War. Show Notes:
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP5 Nightmares of Indianapolis | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History: Addendum</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4506780023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 17:56:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4506780023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Description: Imagine actual people living for real through the plot of several disaster and survival movies combined. That&amp;rsquo;s what the crew of the USS Indianapolis experienced after it was torpedoed at the very end of the Second World War. Show Notes: 1. &amp;ldquo;In Harm&amp;rsquo;s Way: The Sinking of the U.S.S. Indianapolis and the Extraordinary Story of Its Survivors&amp;rdquo; by Doug Stanton 2. &amp;ldquo;The Unthinkable: Who Survives When Disaster Strikes - and Why&amp;rdquo; by Amanda Ripley This episode is brought to you by Audible</description></item><item><title>EP4 Exposing the Hart of The Great War | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History: Addendum</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4506780024/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 22:32:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4506780024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan and the British Imperial War Museum&amp;rsquo;s famed First World War historian Peter Hart talk about one of their favorite mutual interests&amp;hellip;World War One. The Last Battle: Victory, Defeat, and the End of World War I by Peter Hart The Great War: A Combat History of the First World War by Peter Hart Gallipoli by Peter Hart The Somme: The Darkest Hour on the Western Front by Peter Hart Somme Success: The Royal Flying Corps and the Battle of The Somme 1916 by Peter Hart Jutland, 1916: Death in the Grey Wastes by Nigel Steel and Peter Hart Defeat at Gallipoli by Nigel Steel and Peter Hart Tumult in the Clouds: British Experience of War in the Air, 1914-18 by Nigel Steel and Peter Hart Bloody April: Slaughter in the Skies Over Arras, 1917 by Peter Hart Fire and Movement: The British Expeditionary Force and the Campaign of 1914 by Peter Hart The 16th Durham Light Infantry in Italy 1943-1945 by Peter Hart Passchendaele: The Sacrificial Ground by Peter Hart 1918: A Very British Victory by Peter Hart The Heat of Battle: The 16th Battalion Durham Light Infantry : The Italian Campaign, 1943-1945 by Peter Hart At the Sharp End: The 2nd Battalion Royal Norfolk Regiment 1939-1944 by Peter Hart Voices from the Front: The 2nd Norfolk Regiment: From Le Paradis to Kohima by Peter Hart This episode is brought to you by Audible</description></item><item><title>EP3 A Four-Star Conversation | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History: Addendum</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4506780025/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2018 00:36:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4506780025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan talks about history, war and philosophy (and where those three subject might converge) with Four-Star General and former U.S. Air Force Chief-of-Staff Merrill McPeak. Books: Roles and Missions by General Merrill A. McPeak The Vietnam Chapters: Air Combat in Southeast Asia by General Merrill A. McPeak Below The Zone by General Merrill A. McPeak Hangar Flying by General Merrill A. McPeak
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP2 Rome Through Duncan's Eyes | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History: Addendum</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4506780026/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 23:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4506780026/</guid><description>Podcast Description History podcasting legend Mike Duncan and Dan talk about Mike&amp;rsquo;s new book on the pivotal early era of Rome&amp;rsquo;s road from Republic to Empire.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EP1 Imperial Germany vs Nazi Germany | Dan Carlin's Hardcore History: Addendum</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4506780027/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 03:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4506780027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dan once said that he thought Germany&amp;rsquo;s First World War military was superior to Nazi Germany&amp;rsquo;s Wehrmacht. He is often asked to elaborate, so he does in this show (note:this “pilot” show was previously posted on YouTube) Notes: The Pity Of War: Explaining World War I by Niall Ferguson The Wages of Destruction: The Making and Breaking of the Nazi Economy by Adam Tooze Inside the Third Reich by Albert Speer Panzer Leader by Heinz Guderian (post war memoirs) Blood, Tears and Folly: An Objective Look at World War II by Len Deighton</description></item></channel></rss>