<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>COMMONS on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/commons/</link><description>Recent content in COMMONS on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 09:58:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/commons/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CULTS 9 - Romana’s Reign | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 09:58:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Romana Didulo, the self-proclaimed Queen of Canada, is unlike almost any other cult leader Canada has ever seen. In an incredibly short amount of time, she’s been able to gain a mass following, despite her absurd claims and alarming rhetoric.
At various points, she’s claimed to be a political leader, a monarch, an interdimensional being communing with aliens, and so much more. She’s urged her followers to take up arms and execute migrants on sight.</description></item><item><title>CULTS 8 - The Eye of the Pyramid | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 09:04:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Multi-level marketing isn’t based on rational business logic. It’s not even built on irrational business logic. It’s ideology. It’s faith.
MLMs have become such a ubiquitous part of North American life that their tenets are rarely ever questioned. The sector holds enormous political sway. Millions of people join, leave and rejoin every year, almost all of them ending up poorer for the experience.
And to call it a cult is not just a cute turn of phrase.</description></item><item><title>CULTS 7 - Hey #Bossbabe! | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 08:58:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nearly 1.4 million Canadians and almost 50 million Americans are involved in multi-level marketing. And that sheer volume of people makes it a near certainty that you’ve encountered MLMs in your life somehow.
The promise of financial freedom can be an intoxicating lure. But MLMs, like so many other cultish enterprises, are about more than just money. They’re about transcendence.
And in their wake, they often leave behind ruined livelihoods and broken lives.</description></item><item><title>CULTS 6 - Being a Blackmore | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 08:31:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mary-Jayne Blackmore is one of the oldest children of Winston Blackmore, the most famous polygamist in Canada.&amp;nbsp;
For decades, her family has been the subject of intense media and legal scrutiny because of her father’s 27 wives and 150 children. Their lives have been dissected in documentaries and in court testimony.
The name Blackmore has become synonymous with either faith-based persecution by the state or with cult-like religious fundamentalism that victimizes girls and women.</description></item><item><title>CULTS 5 - Alien Superstar | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 08:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750005/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1973, a French motorsports journalist claimed to have been visited by a UFO that revealed to him the secret origins of humanity. For the next half-century, the man known as Raël would go on to create a new faith with tens of thousands of adherents all around the world.&amp;nbsp;
The media have portrayed the Raelians as not just a cult, but a strange phantasmagoria of extraterrestrials, orgies and clones.</description></item><item><title>CULTS 4 - The Cult Wars | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 08:37:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750006/</guid><description>Podcast Description An explosion of new spiritual movements in the 1970s led to the creation of an entirely novel academic field. But right from the beginning, the discipline was riven asunder.
The Cult Wars have been raging for decades. They’re fought not only in academic journals and conference seminars, but in the press, the courts and in legislative assemblies. And their battles continue to have enormous consequences.
Featured in this episode: Michael Kropveld, Stephen A.</description></item><item><title>CULTS 3 - MKUltra | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 07:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750007/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the 1960s and 70s, there was a fear that cult leaders were brainwashing young people into joining their new, strange movements. But is it even possible to “brainwash” anyone?
At a psychiatric hospital in Montreal, one mad scientist, with the help of the CIA, tried to find out.
Featured in this episode: Alison Steel, Lisa Ellenwood
To learn more:
Brainwashed by Michelle Shephard, Lisa Ellenwood &amp;amp; Chris Oke on CBC Podcasts</description></item><item><title>CULTS 2 - Brother XII | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 07:34:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750008/</guid><description>Podcast Description The story of Brother XII still fascinates and even frightens some people in and around Nanaimo.
He’s often called the Devil of De Courcy Island for good reason.
Brother XII prophesied about the coming apocalypse. But instead, his story would presage something different. He was a forerunner of the strange, new religions that would sweep over the western world.
Featured in this episode: Bill Miner, Justine Brown
To learn more:</description></item><item><title>CULTS 1 - Speak in Tongues | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 07:42:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750009/</guid><description>Podcast Description As organized religion declines in countries like Canada, we’ve experienced an explosion of what some call religious movements and what others call cults.
The idea of cults has become an omnipresent part of our discourse. But what even is a cult? And why have we become so intrigued by these groups?
And the language of cults has moved beyond just religion into so many different spheres — everything from fitness, to politics, to work.</description></item><item><title>The End of Canadaland | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750010/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 07:50:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Support us now! Click here:&amp;nbsp;canadaland.com/join
The first episode of Canadaland was published ten years ago today. If we were to announce this is the last episode of Canadaland, no one would be surprised.
Journalism in Canada is in a fight for its life. You can have an impact. Head to&amp;nbsp;canadaland.com/join&amp;nbsp;to become a supporter today.&amp;nbsp;
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Introducing our new season… Cults | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750011/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 16:34:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750011/</guid><description>Podcast Description The word cult gets tossed around&amp;nbsp;a lot. The label gets applied to everything from doomsday religions, to wellness fads, to online conspiracies.
Uncovering the stories of both devotees and dissenters, this season of COMMONS will go beyond the true crime cliches and will make you question everything you thought you knew about cults.
Our new season launches on October 18th.
Canadaland Supporters can listen to the first episode a week early!</description></item><item><title>Bonus - Game Misconduct | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 07:03:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750012/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this bonus episode, COMMONS producer Jordan Cornish sits down with Jashvina Shah to talk about her book, Game Misconduct: Hockey's Toxic Culture and How to Fix It.&amp;nbsp;
Featured in this episode: Jashvina Shah
To learn more:
Game Misconduct Hockey's Toxic Culture and How to Fix It by Evan F. Moore and Jashvina Shah
“No, this is not a watershed moment for hockey” by Jashvina Shah in The Globe and Mail&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>Bonus - Overtime | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750013/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 07:02:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750013/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this bonus episode, COMMONS producer Jordan Cornish sits down with host Arshy Mann to discuss our recent season on hockey.&amp;nbsp;
If you value this podcast, Support us! You’ll get premium access to all our shows ad free, including early releases and bonus content. You’ll also get our exclusive newsletter, discounts on merch, tickets to our live and virtual events, and more than anything, you’ll be a part of the solution to Canada’s journalism crisis, you’ll be keeping our work free and accessible to everybody.</description></item><item><title>HOCKEY 7 - Blood on the Ice | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 07:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Derek Boogaard made his living pummeling people on the ice. But outside the arena, he was soft-spoken and kind.
Fighting was just his job. But it would end up taking everything from him.
Hockey fights, and the numerous blows to the head that players have to endure, have become a moral crisis at the very heart of the sport. And the NHL is doing everything they can to deny the science and allow this gladiatorial combat to continue.</description></item><item><title>HOCKEY 6 - The Problem Hockey Won’t Name | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 07:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750015/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Hockey Canada scandal has become one of the biggest stories in the country. And now, hockey appears to be in the middle of a reckoning. But this isn’t the first time. There was another moment, just like this one.
Back then, people tried to warn the hockey world — they were ignored. And even today, the sport won’t name the very specific issue they face.&amp;nbsp;
Hockey has a gang rape problem.</description></item><item><title>HOCKEY 5 - The Boys from Brampton | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mike Danton was playing in the Stanley Cup playoffs for the St. Louis Blues. And at the same time, he was trying to hire a hitman to kill his agent, David Frost.
Danton’s arrest and conviction would become one of the biggest hockey scandals of all time. But this is not just some salacious true crime story.&amp;nbsp;
It’s an extreme example of everything that’s wrong with hockey culture; hazing and abuse, sexual misconduct and the adult men who control the lives of teenage boys for their own monetary gain.</description></item><item><title>HOCKEY 4 - The Lonely End of the Rink | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 07:02:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Justin Davis was never a superstar. He was a journeyman player, one of tens of thousands, chasing the dream. And at almost every step, when hockey gave him something, it would also take something away.
Hockey exacts a heavy toll on many boys and young men — on their minds and their bodies. And then they’re told not to talk about any of it outside the locker room.</description></item><item><title>HOCKEY 3 - Iced Out | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750018/</guid><description>Podcast Description The NHL likes to call Willie O’Ree the Jackie Robinson of hockey. And no one can deny how significant it was when he became the first Black player on the ice in an NHL game in 1958.&amp;nbsp;
But what the league doesn’t like to talk about is what happened next.&amp;nbsp;
Because after O’Ree, the NHL didn’t admit another black player for sixteen years. So did the NHL resegregate? And why don’t we talk about the experiences of the players who broke hockey’s second colour line?</description></item><item><title>HOCKEY 2 - The Birth of Black Hockey | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 11:02:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Of the estimated 7000 people who have played in the NHL only around 100 of them have been Black. That’s an absurdly low number compared to any other major North American sports league.
But what makes that statistic especially shocking is the fact that the modern game has its roots with Black players on Black teams.
The Coloured Hockey League wasn’t just a sideshow to the main event of white hockey.</description></item><item><title>HOCKEY 1 - The Best Game You Can Name | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 11:04:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hockey is a hell of a lot of fun. But right now, the sport is going through a reckoning. Allegations of racism, corruption, sexual misconduct and so much more are rocking the game to its core.
But the truth is that in Canada, hockey is more than just a sport. It’s a civic religion, with a billion dollar business attached to it.
Over the next seven episodes, COMMONS will be digging into the cult of hockey, scrutinizing its doctrines and exposing its secrets.</description></item><item><title>Introducing our new season… Hockey | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750021/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 11:00:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Love it or hate it, hockey is inescapable in Canada. But the sport has a dark side.
From violence and racism on the ice, to corruption, cover-ups and abuse off of it. In the latest season of COMMONS, host Arshy Mann and producers Jordan Cornish and Noor Azrieh will be bringing you stories from inside the cult of hockey.
Our new season launches on May 24th.
If you’re a Canadaland supporter, you can get access to episodes a week early!</description></item><item><title>BONUS: Cory Doctorow knows why monopolies are killing art | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 10:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750022/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the last season we sat down with Cory Doctorow, co-author of Chokepoint Capitalism: How Big Tech and Big Content Captured Creative Labor Markets and How We'll Win Them Back, to find out how the music industry has become dominated by monopoly power. In this bonus episode, we’re bringing you Arshy’s full interview with Cory, complete with all the nitty gritty details around how and why musicians continue to get screwed by Spotify, music labels, ticketmaster and more.</description></item><item><title>Bonus - Do Not Pass Go | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 07:05:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750023/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this bonus episode, COMMONS producer Jordan Cornish sits down with host Arshy Mann to talk about the grocery CEOs testifying at Parliament, their thoughts about the Monopoly season coming to an end, and what listeners can do to make change.
Sponsors: USW, Free Lunch, Gardisil&amp;nbsp;
If you value this podcast, Support us! You’ll get premium access to all our shows ad free, including early releases and bonus content.</description></item><item><title>Monopoly 17 - Food Fight | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 08:03:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750024/</guid><description>Podcast Description A Loblaws, or any other, modern-day supermarket, is many things.&amp;nbsp;
It’s a temple of abundance. A place where a consumer has more choice than the greatest kings, emperors and pharaohs had in their lifetimes.&amp;nbsp;
It’s a tech platform, tracking our every taste, transaction and even ailment.
And it’s an ideological arena. Where everyday Canadians and grocery CEOs are battling over what’s to blame for our declining standard of living.</description></item><item><title>Monopoly 16 - Amazon’s Empire | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750025/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 09:59:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750025/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Big Tech companies have ushered in a new era of global monopoly. And the most influential, the most powerful of all of them, is Amazon.
In this episode, we focus in on two of the fundamental pillars of Amazon’s dominance: its online marketplace and its cloud computing arm.
And a former Amazon VP speaks out.
Featured in this episode: Matt Stoller, Brad Stone (Bloomberg), Dana Mattioli (Wall Street Journal), Tim Bray</description></item><item><title>Monopoly 15 - Movie Monster | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750026/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 08:05:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750026/</guid><description>Podcast Description “I love the smell of monopoly in the morning”
“Forget it, Jake, it’s Cineplex”
“The competition commissioner once tried to test me. I ate his liver with some fava beans and a nice Chianti”
“Life is like a box of anti-competitive cinema chains that allegedly use their 75% market share to bully their competition, limit consumer choice and charge obscene junk fees. You never know what you’re going to get.</description></item><item><title>Monopoly 14 - Where the Sidewalk Ends | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750027/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 08:05:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Google, one of the world’s great tech monopolies, wanted to make a “smart city,” full of sensors and robots and self-driving cars.
Toronto, one of the world’s most insecure cities, wanted a big tech firm to put it on the innovation map.
What resulted was not exactly a match made in heaven.
Featured in this episode: Josh O’Kane (Globe and Mail), Kurtis McBride
To learn more:
Sideways: The City Google Couldn’t Buy by Josh O’Kane</description></item><item><title>Monopoly 13 - The Irvings | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 08:05:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750028/</guid><description>Podcast Description For almost a century, the Irving family has run New Brunswick like a personal fiefdom. They own the newspapers, the industry, and, according to some, even the government. So how does a single family come to so thoroughly dominate an entire province? And what happens when that family starts to fracture and split apart at the seams?
Featured in this episode: Bruce Livesey (Thieves of Bay Street).
To learn more:</description></item><item><title>Monopoly 12 - Overdrawn | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750029/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 08:05:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Not only do the Big Five banks get away with charging exorbitant fees for basic services. Not only do they block any competitors by controlling Canada’s payment infrastructure. Not only are they totally entwined with the federal government.&amp;nbsp;
But the Big Five banks are about to get even bigger.
Featured in this episode: Colin Deacon, Keldon Bester, Alex Vronces
To learn more
“How blocked mergers foiled banks' ambitions — and forced the Big Six to innovate” by James Bradshaw in The Globe and Mail</description></item><item><title>Monopoly 11 - Flight Risk | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750030/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 08:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750030/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s been a hard few years for Canadian air passengers. And while no one blames the airline oligopoly for COVID or winter storms, air travellers have had to put up with a lot.
But Canada has consumer protections to make sure that when something goes wrong, there’s a fair process in place to make sure everyday Canadians don’t get screwed over, right? Right??!
Featured in this episode: Gábor Lukács, John Gradek</description></item><item><title>Monopoly 10 - The Way the Music Died | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750031/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 08:05:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750031/</guid><description>Podcast Description ♩♪ A long, long time ago, I can still remember
How the music used to pay my bills
I knew that if I got my break
That I could be as big as Drake
And then I could stop shopping at No Frills ♩♪
♩♪ But Spotify, it’s nearly killed us
Ticketmaster’s ground us to dust
The companies got too large
Now monopolies are in charge ♩♪
♩♪ And the record labels I fear the most</description></item><item><title>MONOPOLY 9 - Diamonds of Attawapiskat | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750032/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 08:05:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750032/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode was originally published on December 21, 2021.&amp;nbsp;
Attawapiskat has become famous across Canada and around the world. Not for the natural beauty that surrounds it, or for the Cree culture of the people who live there. Instead, it’s become a byword for the toxic legacy of Canadian colonialism.
But while Attawapiskat faced crisis after crisis, the community was sitting on a literal diamond mine run by the world’s most famous mining company.</description></item><item><title>Monopoly 8 - Raining Cats and Dollars | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750033/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 08:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750033/</guid><description>Podcast Description When you look at your pet, you probably see an adorable furball that you’d do anything for. A private equity firm sees dollar signs.
Ever so quietly, faceless, big money firms have been consolidating Canada’s veterinary clinics. And vets are just the beginning.
Featured in this episode: Michael Mossop, Denise Hearn
To learn more
“Inside the corporate dash to buy up dentists’ offices, veterinary clinics and pharmacies” in The Globe and Mail by Chris Hannay</description></item><item><title>Trailer: COMMONS | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750034/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 08:30:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750034/</guid><description>Podcast Description COMMONS is a documentary podcast that proves Canada is anything but boring. Each season, host Arshy Mann guides you through the country’s dark underbelly, bringing you stories about crime, corruption and all manner of misdeeds.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>CANADALAND #725 The Rogers Family Compact | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750035/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 08:05:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750035/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode was originally published on November 1st, 2021.&amp;nbsp;
Who are the Rogers family? How did they get so powerful? Why have they turned against one another? And what does it matter?&amp;nbsp; We've spent a week immersed in Rogers history to bring you this unofficial narrative of Canada's telecom overlords.
Further reading:
Kelly Pullen’s 2014 story in Toronto Life on the “ruthless” power struggle at Rogers: https://torontolife.com/from-the-archives/edward-rogers-the-man-who-would-be-king/
Ted Rogers’ last interview, with Alan Gregg: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Monopoly 7 - Canada’s Competition Cop | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750036/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 08:05:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Support us at www.commonspodcast.com
Matthew Boswell is the Competition Commissioner. And he's the last man trying to stand in the way of the mega-merger between Rogers and Shaw.&amp;nbsp;
But even he acknowledges that Canada's antitrust laws aren't just inadequate — they're weighted in favour of the monopolists.
A frank discussion with Canada's top competition cop.
Featured in this episode: Matthew Boswell
Credits: Arshy Mann (Host and Producer), Jordan Cornish (Producer), Noor Azrieh (Producer), André Proulx (Production Coordinator)</description></item><item><title>Monopoly 6 - The Urge to Merge | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750037/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 08:05:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rogers and Shaw are getting ready to tie the knot. But before they can consummate their less-than-holy union, they have to get the approval of Canada’s competition tribunal and the federal government. And even though most Canadians would find this union highly objectionable, it’s likely to be approved.
Because for 150 years, Canadian politicians have been talking out of both sides of their mouths. They claim they want to promote competition.</description></item><item><title>Monopoly 5 - Against the WIND | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750038/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 08:05:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750038/</guid><description>Podcast Description WIND Mobile, now known as Freedom, was a small company that tried to break through Canada’s telecom oligopoly. It did not have an easy ride.&amp;nbsp;
WIND faced numerous hurdles from regulators, it was subjected to dirty tricks from the telecom oligopoly, and was eventually sold to Shaw. But it also helped lower cell phone rates and brought in unlimited data and U.S. roaming, changing the wireless market permanently.</description></item><item><title>Monopoly 4 - Teleconned | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 08:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750039/</guid><description>Podcast Description They’re the most hated companies in the country. And yet, they’re unavoidable.&amp;nbsp;
The telecom oligopoly seems to rule Canada’s economy with an iron fist. Canadians are paying more and more for our cell phones, cable and internet.&amp;nbsp;
So how was it that we ended up in this situation? And was it inevitable that things would get so bad?
Featured in this episode: Ben Klass, Dwayne Winseck, Keldon Bester, Dale Eisler</description></item><item><title>Monopoly 3 - The Hudson’s Bay Company | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750040/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 08:05:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, it’s a department store where you might go to buy perfume or cookware. But the Hudson’s Bay Company was Canada’s first, and its most powerful, monopoly.&amp;nbsp;
It grew from a largely insignificant enterprise into one of the most dominant forces in North America.
The story of the HBC reveals just how deeply embedded monopoly is in Canada’s very fabric.&amp;nbsp;
Featured in this episode: Stephen R. Bown, Jean Teillet</description></item><item><title>Monopoly 2 - Big Milk | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750041/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 08:03:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Some say that they’re a shadowy group that are the true power behind our elected officials, wielding enormous influence that they use to either benefit their friends or crush their enemies.
Others claim that they’re a bulwark against oligopolies, ensuring that rural Canada doesn’t turn into an empty, corporatized hellscape.
But what’s not up for debate is that Big Milk is a big deal.
Featured in this episode: Marlene Haley, Justin Ling, Bruce Muirhead</description></item><item><title>Monopoly 1 - Lost in the Supermarket | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750042/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 08:37:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Canadians are being squeezed at every end. When it comes to cell phone bills, grocery bills, housing, entertainment, we’re all paying more than ever before.
But a small number of companies that dominate their industries are reaping in enormous profits.
This season of COMMONS we’ll be digging into all of the monopolies, oligopolies and cartels that dominate our lives. And for our first stop, we head to the supermarket.</description></item><item><title>Introducing our new season… Monopoly | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750043/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 07:25:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750043/</guid><description>Podcast Description From broadband to banking to blueberries (yes, even blueberries), life in Canada is ruled by monopolies. In the latest season of COMMONS, host Arshy Mann and producers Jordan Cornish and Noor Azrieh will bring you the stories of how these monopolists bullied their way to the top, strangled their rivals, and cornered their markets with help from the government.
Our new season launches on November 9th. If you’re a Canadaland supporter, you can listen to the first episode now!</description></item><item><title>Introducing our new series: Ratfucker | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750044/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 12:40:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Meet David Wallace, political fixer. After decades in the game he says he’s getting out, telling all, and dumping his files in public. The result is the viral "Klondike Papers" theory of conspiracies, conservatives, and cults. But are the allegations true? And why is he really implicating himself, and so many others? A wild, true story.
Series launches October 31st.
Subscribe now (link).
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>WAR 8 - Who Pays the Price? | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750045/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 09:37:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Afghanistan has endured more than four decades of almost ceaseless war. But since the Taliban takeover, Afghans have been abandoned by the global community and are now facing an unprecedented humanitarian crisis.
What was all of this for? And is Afghanistan destined for yet another cycle of violence?
Featured in this episode: Rangina Hamidi, Mohsin Amin, Stephen M. Saideman
To learn more:
“Americans nurtured Afghanistan’s economy. Now they’re gutting it” by Mohsin Amin in The Washington Post</description></item><item><title>WAR 7 - The Long, Slow Death | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750046/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 09:23:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stuart Langridge was a model soldier. But when he returned from a tour in Afghanistan, his family noticed that something was off. He was suffering from PTSD. But instead of providing him the treatment he needed, Stuart was punished and humiliated by the Canadian Forces. Like too many Afghan veterans, Stuart ended up taking his own life. And when his parents began to ask questions about what had happened to their son, the Canadian military went to war against them.</description></item><item><title>WAR 6 - Tortured Pasts | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750047/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 07:19:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750047/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Afghan Detainee scandal became the defining story of Canada's war in Kandahar. It exposed Canada's complicity and direct involvement in war crimes. And it helped fuel the insurgency that eventually brought down the Afghan government.
Despite repeated denials by senior government and military officials, there's evidence that many Canadians knew they were sending Afghans to be tortured.
So why did so few people do anything to stop it?</description></item><item><title>WAR 5 - The Narcokings of Kandahar | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750048/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 09:04:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750048/</guid><description>Podcast Description During the Afghan War, it was clear who the enemy was. The Taliban were a group of religious zealots who harboured terrorists, killed with fervour and enslaved women.
But then why did so many Afghans join with the Taliban during the years that Canada was fighting in Kandahar?&amp;nbsp;
And if the Taliban were our enemies, who exactly were our friends and allies? In many cases, they were torturers, rapists and murderers themselves.</description></item><item><title>WAR 4 - Medusa | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750049/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 09:42:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Operation Medusa has become the most celebrated battle in recent Canadian history. It was hailed as a stroke of military genius that may have vanquished the Taliban once and for all.&amp;nbsp;
But the soldiers and commanders on the ground have a different story to tell. A rushed battle. Flawed intelligence. And generals putting political considerations ahead of Canadian lives.&amp;nbsp;
And even though Canada had defeated the Taliban on the battlefield, that didn't mean they were winning the war.</description></item><item><title>WAR 3 - Tarnak Farms | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750050/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 07:37:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bill Wilson and Chris Kopp were two of the first Canadian soldiers deployed to Afghanistan.
One night in April 2002, they were at a training exercise at Tarnak Farms, Osama Bin Laden's old hideout outside of Kandahar.
All of a sudden, they see a blast, and chaos surrounds them. What happens next would change their lives &amp;mdash; and the Canadian military&amp;nbsp;&amp;mdash; forever.
&amp;nbsp;
Featured in this episode: Chris Kopp, Bill Wilson, Michael Friscolanti, Eugene Lang</description></item><item><title>WAR 2 - Lords of War | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750051/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 09:53:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750051/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the days after 9/11, Canada joined in the invasion and occupation of Afghanistan. Right away, it became painfully obvious that we didn't understand the country, its people, or its history.
That would have profound consequences.&amp;nbsp;
Within months, Canadian special forces were participating in secret operations at the behest of some of the most sinister men in the country.
Our actions in the early days of the war would go on to endanger the lives of Afghans and Canadian soldiers alike in the years to come.</description></item><item><title>WAR 1 - Last Plane Out of Kabul | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750052/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750052/</guid><description>Podcast Description The War in Afghanistan was Canada's longest war. More than 40,000 Canadian troops served. And countless Canadian civilians went to work in the country. But after twenty years, billions of dollars and hundreds of thousands of lives lost, Afghanistan is worse off than before.
When the Taliban marched into Kabul last August, the world watched as Afghans clung to planes in an attempt to escape. We bring you the true story of the end of one of the forever wars through the eyes of the people who were there.</description></item><item><title>Introducing our new season… War | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750053/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Narcolords in league with the government. Hundreds of millions of dollars that vanish into thin air. Arrogant decision-making that leads to the deaths of Canadians and Afghans alike. This season of COMMONS will bring you the war stories that Canada wants you to forget.
First episode drops March 30, 2022.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>MINING 8 - The Crying of Lot 8 | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750054/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750054/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2007, the small Guatemalan village of Lote Ocho, Spanish for Lot 8, was burned to the ground by military, police and security for a Canadian-owned mine. Eleven women claim they were raped during the evictions.
A few years later, a prominent community activist is murdered in broad daylight by the head of security for the mining company.&amp;nbsp;
These are just some of the many crimes that Canadian mining companies have been accused of committing in this region over the last 60 years.</description></item><item><title>MINING 7 - Barrick and the Cruelty of Gold | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750055/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750055/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;nbsp;
Papua New Guinea is a part of the world that few Canadians ever think about. But for the people of Porgera, their lives have been shaped by the decisions of Canadian companies.
It's hard to wrap your head around the atrocities that people in Porgera have suffered over the last thirty year. Environmental devastation. Murder as a matter of course. Hundreds of women and girls who have been raped.</description></item><item><title>MINING 6 - Diamonds of Attawapiskat | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750056/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Support us at www.commonspodcast.com&amp;nbsp;
Attawapiskat has become famous across Canada and around the world. Not for the natural beauty that surrounds it, or for the Cree culture of the people who live there. Instead, it's become a byword for the toxic legacy of Canadian colonialism.
But while Attawapiskat faced crisis after crisis, the community was sitting on a literal diamond mine run by the world's most famous mining company.</description></item><item><title>MINING 5 - The North’s Giant Monster | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750057/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Support us at www.commonspodcast.com&amp;nbsp;
&amp;nbsp;
A monster has been haunting the North.
Giant Mine may be a big reason why Yellowknife exists. But for seven decades, it's been a unique source of suffering for the people in the region.
Three stories from this uniquely haunted place: the damage it did when it opened, the bloodiest labour dispute in Canadian history, and the toxic legacy that may remain for thousands of years.</description></item><item><title>MINING 4 - The Westray Disaster | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750058/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Support us at www.commonspodcast.com
Twenty-six men were working underground when an explosion tore through the Westray Mine in Nova Scotia. Their friends and colleagues went into the wreckage to try to save them.
The story of Westray is one of managerial malice and the heroism of everyday people. But why is it that governments let this happen over and over again, at the expense of so many lives?</description></item><item><title>MINING 3 - Before Bitcoin, Bre-X | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750059/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 13:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Support us at commonspodcast.com
A tiny Canadian mining company discovers the largest gold deposit in human history. But when the company's chief geologist falls out of a helicopter over the Indonesian jungle, it was all revealed to be a mirage.
Bre-X was a national obsession that made many overnight millionaires. It also happened to be the biggest fraud in the history of mining.&amp;nbsp;
But questions still remain. Why did no one go to jail?</description></item><item><title>MINING 2 - Life and Death in Asbestos, QC | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750060/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Support us here: http://commonspodcast.com/
For a century, Canada was one of the world's leading exporters of asbestos, most of it mined from the small town of Asbestos, Quebec. But during that time, governments and corporations in Canada did everything they could to hide the fact that asbestos is deadly.
They went to extraordinary lengths &amp;mdash; secret organ smuggling, corporate-supervised police torture &amp;mdash; to keep the ugly truth from the world.</description></item><item><title>MINING 1 - The Myth of the Klondike | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750061/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750061/</guid><description>Podcast Description When gold was discovered in the Yukon, 100,000 people desperately tried to make it to a small patch of land in one of the most remote environments on the continent. Few made it all the way.&amp;nbsp;
The Klondike Gold Rush was many things: a media conspiracy, a ponzi scheme, a land grab. But above all, it was a humanitarian disaster that stretched over much of the Pacific Northwest.</description></item><item><title>Introducing our new season… Mining | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750062/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 10:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stories about the dirty business of Canadian mining.
First episode drops October 13, 2021.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Introducing The White Saviors | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750063/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 07:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over 25 years, WE built a golden brand by inspiring children to rally around their charismatic leader. But behind the scenes, employees experienced a cult-like culture and a troubling blur of charitable and commercial activities. In the aftermath of a national scandal, thousands of donors and volunteers (and dozens of &amp;lsquo;celebrity ambassadors') are left wondering where the money went, and whether the savior industry creates a constant need for victims.</description></item><item><title>REAL ESTATE 8 - The Last White Rajah | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750064/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750064/</guid><description>Podcast Description The destruction of Borneo's rainforests has been called the greatest environmental crime of our time. But journalists and NGOs have long alleged that one man, Abdul Taib Mahmud, has benefitted from that destruction to the tune of billions of dollars. If that's true, it's one of the worst acts of corruption in the modern era.
And for over a decade, those same campaigners have argued that Taib's empire isn't limited to Malaysia.</description></item><item><title>REAL ESTATE 7 - The Ballad of Eddy Haymour | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750065/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 10:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eddy Haymour has been called a lot of things in his life. Immigrant success story. Kidnapper. Terrorist. Folk Hero.
But the long saga of Eddy Haymour is at its heart a story of obsession. About a man who became consumed by his dreams for a piece of land. And about a government equally determined to stop him at any cost.
Featured in this episode: Omar Mouallem, Greg Crompton</description></item><item><title>REAL ESTATE 6 - Canada’s Biggest Slumlord | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750066/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 10:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750066/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Toronto Community Housing Corporation is the biggest landlord in Canada, and the second biggest in all of North America.&amp;nbsp;
But government after government has allowed social housing in Toronto to fall apart. It's not just the buildings that they've let rot. It's also our moral obligation to the most vulnerable in our society.
&amp;nbsp;
Featured in this episode: Joe Fiorito, John Sewell, Susan Gapka
&amp;nbsp;
To learn more:</description></item><item><title>REAL ESTATE 5 - Oka | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750067/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 10:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750067/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Oka Crisis was the biggest military confrontation on Canadian soil in more than a century. On its face, it was about a golf course expansion. But for the Mohawks who took up arms, it was the culmination of a centuries-long fight for recognition of their sovereignty and their land.
&amp;nbsp;
Featured in this episode: Thaioroni&amp;oacute;hte Dan David, Loreen Pindera, Geoffrey York (Globe and Mail)
&amp;nbsp;
To learn more:</description></item><item><title>REAL ESTATE 4 - City of Glass | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750068/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 10:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Real estate mania is at an all time high in this country. And in no place is this more true than in Vancouver. But nobody can even agree on what went wrong.&amp;nbsp;
Have snooty property owners, overreaching bureaucrats, and gutless politicians allowed the housing supply to dwindle to nothing?&amp;nbsp;
Or has a network of transnational criminals turned Vancouver into a narco-capital built on dirty money?
&amp;nbsp;
Featured in this episode: Frances Bula, Sam Cooper, Lindsey Murphy, Jesse Donaldson</description></item><item><title>REAL ESTATE 3 - Terminal City | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750069/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 09:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vancouver is obsessed with real estate. But what most people don't realize, is that it's been this way from the beginning.&amp;nbsp;
Three stories of the swindlers, segregationists and profiteers that made Terminal City what it is.
&amp;nbsp;
Featured in this episode: Jesse Donaldson, Jordan Stanger-Ross, Michael Abe, Stephen Learey
&amp;nbsp;
To learn more:
Land of Destiny: A History of Vancouver Real Estate by Jesse Donaldson
Landscapes of Injustice: A New Perspective on the Internment and Dispossession of Japanese Canadians edited by Jordan Stanger-Ross</description></item><item><title>REAL ESTATE 2 - The Last Man in Africville | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750070/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Africville was one of Canada's oldest Black settlements, a proud community of more than 400 people. And then the City of Halifax decided to utterly obliterate it.&amp;nbsp;
There was one man who simply refused to leave. Eddie Carvery may not have been the best man for the job. But for half a century, he has never stopped fighting for his home.&amp;nbsp;
&amp;nbsp;
Featured in this episode: Eddie Carvery, Jon Tattrie</description></item><item><title>REAL ESTATE 1 - The Bridle Path | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750071/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750071/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Bridle Path is one of the most exclusive neighbourhoods in Canada, home to the ultra-wealthy and the famous. But behind their locked gates, some of Canada's elite try to scheme their way into even greater wealth on the property market &amp;mdash; not always legally. &amp;nbsp;And their ambitions have a way of becoming problems for the rest of us.&amp;nbsp;
Featured in this episode: Kozeta Izeti, Norma Walton
NOTE: The original version of this episode contained an additional story, which we will publish separately.</description></item><item><title>Introducing our new season… Real Estate! | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750072/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stories about Canada's real estate obsession.&amp;nbsp;
The first episode drops on April 28, 2021.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>THE POLICE 10 - Portapique | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750073/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 10:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Almost a year after the worst mass shooting in modern Canadian history, Nova Scotians are still in the dark about what exactly happened. A gunman, dressed in an RCMP uniform, driving an RCMP cruiser killed 22 people.
In the months since, the Mounties have been short on answers. And it's left people wondering whether they have something to hide.
&amp;nbsp;
Featured in this episode: Stephen Maher, Paul Palango, Sandra McCulloch</description></item><item><title>THE POLICE 9 - Northern Patrol | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750074/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 11:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750074/</guid><description>Podcast Description For three decades, much of Northern Ontario has been engaged in an unprecedented experiment in policing. It's called the Nishnawbe-Aski Police Service. And the idea is simple: the old, colonial cops shouldn't be policing Indigenous territory. Instead, Indigenous people should police themselves.
Featured in this episode: Kyle Edwards, Christian Leuprecht
To learn more:
&amp;ldquo;Inside the impossible work of Canada's biggest Indigenous police force&amp;rdquo; by Kyle Edwards in Maclean's</description></item><item><title>THE POLICE 8 - The G20: Fortress Toronto | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750075/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 11:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750075/</guid><description>Podcast Description When John and Susan Pruyn came to Toronto, they were hoping to protest against the G20 and then spend some time with their daughter. Instead, they would be caught up in a whirlwind of police misconduct with few precedents in Canadian history.
Featured in this episode: Jesse Rosenfeld, John Pruyn, Susan Pruyn, Sarah Pruyn.
Jesse Rosenfeld is a Toronto born journalist who has covered the Middle East since 2007.</description></item><item><title>THE POLICE 7 - The G20: Conspiracy | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750076/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 12:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750076/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the first of a two-part series on the G20, two mysterious strangers start volunteering with activist networks in southern Ontario. It's all part of one of the biggest undercover police operations in Canadian history.
&amp;nbsp;
To learn more:
&amp;ldquo;Unmasked: Searching for lessons in Toronto's 2010 G20 debacle&amp;rdquo; by Andrea Bennett in Maisonneuve
&amp;ldquo;How police infiltrated groups planning G20 protests&amp;rdquo; by Adrian Morrow and Kim Mackrael in The Globe and Mail</description></item><item><title>THE POLICE 6 - Who Killed Myles Gray? | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750077/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Myles Gray was an unarmed man who died after seven Vancouver police officers beat him mercilessly. Half a decade after he died, not only does his family not have justice, they don't even know the names of the people who killed him.
&amp;nbsp;
Featured in this episode: Bethany Lindsay (CBC Vancouver), Harsha Walia (B.C. Civil Liberties Association), Ronald MacDonald (Independent Investigations Office of B.C.)&amp;nbsp;
&amp;nbsp;
To learn more:</description></item><item><title>THE POLICE 5 - Toronto’s Finest | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750078/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 08:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750078/</guid><description>Podcast Description A Toronto police officer shoots and kills two Black men and is accused of beating another, all within a five-year span. He's never found guilty of committing a crime. And he continues to rise through the ranks.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Featured in this episode: Bruce Livesey, Howard Morton, Andr&amp;eacute; Marin, Leora Shemesh&amp;nbsp;
&amp;nbsp;
To learn more:
&amp;ldquo;Above The Law&amp;rdquo; by Bruce Livesey in BuzzFeed News
&amp;ldquo;Defence lawyer alleges Toronto officers diverted 7 kilos of meth into her client's car&amp;rdquo; by Betsy Powell in The Toronto Star</description></item><item><title>THE POLICE 4 - Starlight Tours | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750079/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 10:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Even as a teenager, Neil Stonechild was an inspiration to his friends. And then one day, he was found frozen to death outside of Saskatoon. He was last seen alive in the back of a police cruiser. Thirty years later, we know some of what happened to him. But we still don't have justice.&amp;nbsp;
Featured in this episode: Jeffrey Crowe, Donald Worme, Susanne Reber
&amp;nbsp;
To learn more:</description></item><item><title>THE POLICE 3 - Dirty Tricks | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750080/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 14:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750080/</guid><description>Podcast Description A teenage boy and his friends start robbing banks in Toronto. A future Prime Minister is deported from Montreal. A Black Panther in Baltimore goes to prison for four decades. And the RCMP is split apart by the biggest scandal in the force's history.&amp;nbsp;
At the heart of it all is one man. He calls himself the General.
&amp;nbsp;
Featured in this episode: Ricky Atkinson, David Austin, Robin Philpot, Lennox Farrell, Gary Cristall</description></item><item><title>THE POLICE 2 - The Secret History of the RCMP | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750081/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 09:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Support us: canadaland.com/join
The RCMP is one of the most famous police forces in the world &amp;mdash; the red serge and stetson hat are practically synonymous with Canada. But that image obscures the profound power the Mounties have held throughout Canadian history. And the dark legacy of ethnic cleansing and genocide at their core.
Featured in this episode: Jean Teillet, Sean Carleton, Steve Hewitt
To learn more:
The North-West Is Our Mother: The Story of Louis Riel's People, the M&amp;eacute;tis Nation by Jean Teillet</description></item><item><title>We Need Your Support | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750082/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Canada is a big, interesting, and complicated place and COMMONS is committed to bringing you thoughtfully crafted and illuminating stories that will challenge everything you think you know about this country.
This past year, we have brought you stories from all across the country. We told your stories about some of Canada's most powerful families. We launched an emergency season to cover the COVID-19 crisis in long-term care. And right now, we're taking a hard look at how the police operate in this country.</description></item><item><title>THE POLICE 1 - Julian Fantino | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750083/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 08:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Julian Fantino may be the most famous cop in Canadian history. He was the chief of four different police forces. And for decades, he was one of the most influential voices in law enforcement. But during his rise, people critical of the police had a way of finding themselves in the crosshairs. They were smeared, surveilled, intimidated and arrested.
The police are a singularly powerful institution in this country.</description></item><item><title>Introducing our new season... | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750084/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stories about the power that police wield in Canada, and about the lengths they're willing to go to hold on to it. First episode drops Wednesday, October 14.
&amp;nbsp;
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>PANDEMIC 12 - The Most Dangerous Story | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750085/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 10:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Support us at commonspodcast.com
In the final episode in our series about the COVID-19 pandemic and the crisis in long-term care, we’re going to tell you a different kind of story. A story of hope. About how the people we treat as disposable, can have lives of joy and dignity. And about one place where they were given exactly that.
COMMONS: Pandemic is currently focusing on how COVID-19 is affecting long-term care in Canada.</description></item><item><title>PANDEMIC 11 - It Didn’t Have To Be Like This | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750086/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 08:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Support us at commonspodcast.com
Four months after the first outbreak in a Canadian nursing home, over 7000 long-term residents have died of COVID-19. But if you look at the news or social media or our political debates, it seems like we’ve already moved on. Maybe that’s because it feels like this kind of tragedy was inevitable during a pandemic. It wasn’t. And we know that because in some places in Canada, politicians and public health officials made decisions that saved hundreds, if not thousands of lives.</description></item><item><title>PANDEMIC 10 - Burn It Down | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750087/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 09:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Support us at commonspodcast.com
Jonathan Marchand is one of the thousands of young disabled people living in long-term care. But Marchand doesn’t want to fix the system. He doesn’t think it can be reformed. Marchand is an abolitionist. For a century and a half, Canada has hidden away disabled people in institutions where they were neglected and abused. Is long-term care just the latest incarnation of this dark history?</description></item><item><title>PANDEMIC 9 - Mend the World | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750088/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 10:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Support us at commonspodcast.com
After a stroke left him locked in his own body, Rabbi Ronnie Cahana has found ways to lead an incredibly full life. Then the pandemic came. It swept through Quebec, leaving a trail of devastation. Today, Rabbi Cahana is one of the thousands of Quebeckers left stranded in the middle of one of the worst disasters in modern Canadian history.
COMMONS: Pandemic is currently focusing on how COVID-19 is affecting long-term care in Canada.</description></item><item><title>PANDEMIC 8 - Hunger Strike | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750089/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 06:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Support us at commonspodcast.com
Innis Ingram’s mother is his hero. But today, she’s living in one of the worst hit long-term care homes in Ontario. She has a terminal illness. Dozens and dozens of people around her have died, including her friend and roommate. And she’s had minimal human contact for three months. But even though he can’t be there with her, Innis is determined to get her the care she needs.</description></item><item><title>BONUS: The Honest Fakery of Wrestling | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750090/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Support us at commonspodcast.com
We take a break from our PANDEMIC season with an extended interview with Damian Abraham, a guest from our episode about Canada's wrestling dynasty, The Harts. Damian explains the art of juggling the real and the fake, wrestling's dying language and how Canadians helped build World Wrestling Entertainment.
Damian Abraham is the host of Turned Out A Punk Podcast, the creator and host of The Wrestlers, and a member of Toronto hardcore band, Fucked Up.</description></item><item><title>PANDEMIC 7 - The Frontline | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750091/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 07:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Support us at commonspodcast.com
Long-term care workers are in the vanguard in the war against COVID-19. They’re not the kinds of workers who get movies or TV shows made about them. In fact, their stories are rarely told. But not only are they battling heroically against this pandemic. They’re fighting for recognition and respect within a system built to marginalize them. COMMONS: Pandemic is currently focusing on how COVID-19 is affecting long-term care in Canada.</description></item><item><title>PANDEMIC 6 - Northwood | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750092/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 07:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750092/</guid><description>Podcast Description $5/month for-adree COMMONS by clicking here.
Over the last two months, Nova Scotians have endured tragedy upon tragedy. The worst mass murder in modern Canadian history. A helicopter crash and the death of a Snowbirds’ pilot. And all the while, COVID-19 ravaged the biggest long-term care home in Atlantic Canada.
COMMONS: Pandemic is currently focusing on how COVID-19 is affecting long-term care in Canada.
Featured in this episode: Jennifer Henderson (Halifax Examiner), Janice Keefe</description></item><item><title>PANDEMIC 5 - Shirley and Tracy | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750093/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 09:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Here's where you can support us: commonspodcast.com
Tracy Rowley lost her surrogate mother to COVID-19 in a long-term care facility. But she’s determined that Shirley Egerdeen doesn’t become just another statistic. Tracy’s suing the company that runs the home. But one of the strangest things in this story is exactly who owns them.
COMMONS: Pandemic is currently focusing on how COVID-19 is affecting long-term care in Canada.
Featured in this episode: Tracy Rowley, Sherina Harris (HuffPost Canada), Emma Paling (HuffPost Canada), Zaid Noorsumar To learn more:</description></item><item><title>PANDEMIC 4 - Ontario Reaps its Dividends | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750094/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over 1700 Ontarians have already been killed by COVID-19. And the vast majority of them died in long-term care. But if you live in a private, for-profit home, you’re much more likely to die from this virus. The for-profit long-term care industry is politically powerful and deeply entrenched. Is this their moment of reckoning?
COMMONS: Pandemic is currently focusing on how COVID-19 is affecting long-term care in Canada.</description></item><item><title>PANDEMIC 3 - McKenzie Towne | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750095/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 06:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750095/</guid><description>Podcast Description The McKenzie Towne Continuing Care Centre has experienced the deadliest COVID-19 outbreak in Alberta. But some people say that their loved ones were killed by neglect at McKenzie Towne long before the pandemic even began.
COMMONS: Pandemic is currently focusing on how COVID-19 is affecting long-term care in Canada.
Featured in this episode: Breanne Sinclair, Shauna Parks
To learn more:
“'I'm numb': families beg for help as care home outbreak spreads” by Timm Bruch in CTV News Calgary</description></item><item><title>PANDEMIC 2 - When the Plague Came | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750096/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 06:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why did Commons drop everything and focus in on long-term care? Because the vast majority of deaths are happening in those homes. Because we should have known that was going to be the case, but we let it happen anyways. And because the level of suffering, isolation and trauma happening in long-term care today is almost too much for us to face up to.
Featured in this episode: Nathan Stall, Jane Meadus</description></item><item><title>PANDEMIC 1 - 33 Dead in Dorval | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750097/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 06:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750097/</guid><description>Podcast Description They were found abandoned in the facility. The conditions were described as “akin to a concentration camp.” Within two weeks, over thirty of them would be dead. The story of the Résidence Herron in Dorval, Quebec is a national shame — and a preview of the carnage still to come.
COMMONS: Pandemic is currently focusing on how COVID-19 is affecting long-term care in Canada.
Featured in this episode: Aaron Derfel (Montreal Gazette)</description></item><item><title>An emergency season: PANDEMIC | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750098/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 04:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750098/</guid><description>Podcast Description COVID-19 has upended everything, and forced us to change plans. From here on out, COMMONS will be bringing you stories about the people and institutions most impacted by the pandemic. And first up is long-term care. If you or someone you know have any stories about Canada’s long-term care system, get in touch with us at arshy@canadalandshow.com.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>RADICALS 3 - The Last Pandemic | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750099/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 12:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750099/</guid><description>Podcast Description It began as a mysterious disease from a far off place. It turned into the deadliest plague humanity has faced since the Black Death. AIDS has ravaged and reshaped us in so many ways. But in Canada, the battle against AIDS wasn’t just a fight against a virus. It was a fight against a system that didn’t care if some people lived or died.
Featured in this episode: Gary Kinsman, Darien Taylor, John Kozachenko</description></item><item><title>RADICALS 2 - They Buried Her Heart at Wounded Knee | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750100/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 16:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750100/</guid><description>Podcast Description There have been books and songs and plays written about Anna Mae Aquash. But she was no folk hero — she was flesh and blood. A young Mi'kmaq woman who took up arms against the United States government, Anna Mae was a revolutionary. But when she was found murdered in the South Dakotan countryside, it tore her movement apart. It took thirty years to find out who pulled the trigger.</description></item><item><title>RADICALS 1 - Nazi Island in the Sun | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750101/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 11:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750101/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s one of the most audacious plots in North American history. Turn a Caribbean island nation into a criminal state — then use the money to fund Neo-Nazis and Klansmen across Canada, the US and Europe. The scariest part? They almost pulled it off. Featured in this episode: Stewart Bell (Global News)
To learn more:
Bayou of Pigs: The True Story of an Audacious Plot to Turn a Tropical Island into a Criminal Paradise by Stewart Bell</description></item><item><title>Our new season: RADICALS | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750102/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our new season is about the people on the extremes. The activists, the terrorists, and the revolutionaries who took things right to the edge for what they believe in... for good or for ill.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Introducing: Cool Mules | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750103/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 04:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750103/</guid><description>Podcast Description A new investigative series about the cocaine smuggling ring inside Vice Media.
To hear episode 2 right now, subscribe to Cool Mules. Or get all six episodes ad-free for $5/month by clicking here.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>DYNASTIES 9 - The Harts | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750104/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 12:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750104/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Harts are Canada’s first family of professional wrestling and one of the most famous dynasties the country has ever produced. And sure, wrestling is scripted. But what happens when reality begins to invade that fiction? The story of the Harts is one of triumph and tragedy that transcends the world of pro wrestling. Featured in this episode: Damian Abraham, Omar Mouallem
To learn more:
Wrestling With Shadows by Paul Jay</description></item><item><title>DYNASTIES 8 - The Regans | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750105/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 11:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gerald Regan was the premier of Nova Scotia, the founder of a powerful political dynasty, and one of the most prolific sexual predators in Canadian political history. Even after his death last November, few in the establishment are willing to recognize, let alone reckon with, his crimes. This episode contains graphic depictions of sexual violence and won’t be suitable for all listeners.
Featured in this episode: Stephen Kimber, Maggie Rahr</description></item><item><title>DYNASTIES 7 - The Olands | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750106/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 11:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750106/</guid><description>Podcast Description For 150 years, the Olands have been one of Canada’s most prominent brewing dynasties, the makers of Moosehead Beer. But in the last decade, they’ve made the news for much darker reasons. Richard Oland was murdered in 2011. And police and prosecutors believe that he was killed by his only son. Featured in this episode: Greg Marquis
To learn more:
Truth &amp; Honour: The Oland Family Murder Case that Shocked Canada by Greg Marquis</description></item><item><title>DYNASTIES 6 - The Desmarais | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750107/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 11:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750107/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Desmarais family is by far the most influential Canadian dynasty of the last half-century. But if you don’t live in Quebec, chances are you haven’t even heard of them. Paul Desmarais had Prime Ministers and Premiers in his pocket and billions of dollars at his disposal. He wasn’t just a Laurentian elite; he was the Laurentian emperor. Featured in this episode:
Robin Philpot (Derrière l'État Desmarais: Power)</description></item><item><title>DYNASTIES 5 - The Sahotas | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750108/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 08:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750108/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Sahotas are Vancouver’s most notorious slumlords. For decades they’ve let their buildings rot, leaving their tenants to live in filth and desolation. But the Sahotas are not like any other dynasty you’ve ever heard of. Their story is far stranger, and far darker, than anything you can imagine.
Featured in this episode: Jen St. Denis, Christopher Cheung (The Tyee), Sam Dharmapala
To learn more:
“For low-income residents in Vancouver, a different kind of real estate crisis” by Wendy Stueck and Mike Hager in The Globe and Mail</description></item><item><title>DYNASTIES 4 - The Rizzutos | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750109/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 06:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750109/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Rizzutos are Canada’s first family of crime. For decades, they dominated Montreal’s underworld with an iron fist. With the help of corrupt politicians and police officers, the Rizzutos built one of the most fearsome and lucrative criminal enterprises this country has ever seen. Their reign was long and bloody. But their fall, was even more gruesome.
Featured in this episode: Peter Edwards (Toronto Star), Pietro Poletti To learn more:</description></item><item><title>COMMONS Needs Your Help | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750110/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 05:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Canada is a big, interesting, and complicated place and COMMONS is committed to bringing you thoughtfully crafted and illuminating stories that will challenge everything you think you know about this country. We make a complex scripted podcast that’s unlike anything else available in this country and cover stories from all across the nation. We want to keep doing this work, but we need your support. This week we’re going to tell you a little bit about the work that goes into making this show and about what’s next for Canadaland.</description></item><item><title>DYNASTIES 3 - The Fords | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750111/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 23:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750111/</guid><description>Podcast Description They call themselves the Canadian Kennedys. And they’re one of the most famous political dynasties to ever exist in this country. But the rise of the Ford family has been marred by violence and self-destruction at almost every turn. The story of the Fords is tragic — for them, for everyone who falls into their orbit, and for the people of Toronto.
Featured in this episode: Jonathan Goldsbie (Canadaland).</description></item><item><title>DYNASTIES 2 - The Irvings | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750112/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 08:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750112/</guid><description>Podcast Description For almost a century, the Irving family has run New Brunswick like a personal fiefdom. They own the newspapers, the industry, and, according to some, even the government. So how does a single family come to so thoroughly dominate an entire province? And what happens when that family starts to fracture and split apart at the seams?
Featured in this episode: Bruce Livesey (Thieves of Bay Street).
To learn more:</description></item><item><title>DYNASTIES 1 - The Stronachs | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750113/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2019 08:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Canada is a country ruled by dynasties — political, commercial and criminal. In the first episode of our new series, we bring you the story of an eccentric, billionaire patriarch; his famous, charismatic daughter; a fire-breathing monument the size of the Statue of Liberty; and the battle over one of Canada’s great business empires. Featured in this episode: Robert Fife (Globe and Mail).
To learn more:
“The $500 Million Family Feud” by Leah McLaren in Toronto Life</description></item><item><title>Our new season: DYNASTIES | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750114/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stories about the rich and powerful families who run Canada.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>CRUDE 10 - The Apocalypse is Now | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750115/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 07:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Canoe-borne bandits strike an underwater town. A new generation of wealthy lobstermen is minted. An island disappears. And hellfire engulfs a highway jammed with broken heroes on a last chance power drive. Just another normal day amidst Canada’s climate catastrophe. Featured in this episode: Catherine Griwkowsky (Alberta Today), Brendan Kennedy (Toronto Star), Keith Stewart (Greenpeace), Markus Harvey.
To learn more:
“There will be floods” by Brendan Kennedy in the Toronto Star</description></item><item><title>CRUDE 9 - Tar Teck: The Final Frontier | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750116/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 06:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teck Resources just got approval to build the largest tar sands operation ever. The Frontier mine would have serious and permanent consequences for the local environment, Indigenous peoples and the global climate. So why haven’t you ever heard about it?
Featured in this episode: Nikki Way (Pembina Institute), Kecia Kerr (Canadian Parks and Wilderness Society), Cleo Reece (Keepers of the Athabasca), Violet Cheecham Clark.
To learn more:
“10 things you need to know about the massive new oilsands mine that just got a green light” by Sharon J.</description></item><item><title>CRUDE 8 - Spies, Lies and Private Eyes | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750117/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 06:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ever get the feeling someone is watching you? If you’ve been to an environmental protest recently, you might be right. Private intelligence firms, the RCMP and even Canada’s spies have all been caught collecting information on everyday Canadians speaking out against the oil industry.
Featured in this episode: Ron Tremblay (Wolostoq Grand Council), Mike De Souza (National Observer), Meghan McDermott (BC Civil Liberties Association)
To learn more:
“Spies in our midst: RCMP and CSIS snoop on green activists” by Bruce Livesey in National Observer</description></item><item><title>Introducing Wag The Doug | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750118/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2019 03:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750118/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the past few weeks, Ontario Premier Doug Ford was loudly booed at the Raptors' victory parade, demoted a bunch of star members of his Cabinet amid sagging poll numbers and lost his Chief of Staff, who got caught up in a nepotism scandal. Are we witnessing the downfall of a government, or is this just another month in Ontario? If you like Wag the Doug, subscribe to hear more!</description></item><item><title>CRUDE 7 - The Billionaire Plot to Destroy Alberta’s Economy is Totally Real! | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750119/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 07:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Has Canada been a casualty of a nefarious campaign by foreign-funded radicals to landlock our country’s energy resources? Is Big Oil the victim of a vast international conspiracy? Naaaah. But there is, as always, another conspiracy afoot. Featured in this episode: Markham Hislop (Energi Media)
Here's what Vivian Krause has said in response to Markham Hislop's piece.
To learn more:
“Debunked: Vivian Krause’s Tar Sands Campaign conspiracy narrative” by Markham Hislop in Energi Media.</description></item><item><title>CRUDE 6 - The Devil in the Deep Blue Sea | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750120/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 06:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750120/</guid><description>Podcast Description An unspeakable tragedy occurs off the coast of Newfoundland. But this isn’t just a story about a nautical disaster. It’s about what happens when a poor province finds immense riches just within reach. And how the promise of oil wealth can twist history around itself.
Featured in this episode: Susan Dodd, Danny O’Brien, Sean Cadigan
ADDITIONAL MUSIC CREDITS: "Seeker" and "Scenery" by Kai Engel, adapted
To learn more:</description></item><item><title>CRUDE 5 - A Town, Annihilated | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750121/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 07:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750121/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Lac-Mégantic rail disaster was a calamity like we’ve never seen before. The families of the victims never got justice. But the conditions that made it possible have barely changed. And the next time could be far worse.
Featured in this episode: Bruce Campbell, Dylan Robertson (Winnipeg Free Press)
To learn more:
The Lac-Mégantic Rail Disaster: Public Betrayal, Justice Denied by Bruce Campbell.
“Alberta Crisis, Winnipeg Danger” by Dylan Robertson in the Winnipeg Free Press</description></item><item><title>CRUDE 4 - Orphan Wells: Citizen Con | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750122/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750122/</guid><description>Podcast Description What happens when the oil wells run dry? Environmental damage, government bailouts and a scheme that some are comparing to the subprime mortgage crisis. And all of this is just the beginning.
Featured in this episode: Sharon J. Riley (The Narwhal), Jeff Lewis (Globe and Mail), Alana Bartol (Orphan Well Adoption Agency), Herman, Shirley and Mark Dorin.
To learn more:
Hustle in the oil patch: Inside a looming financial and environmental crisis by Jeff Lewis, Jeffrey Jones, Chen Wang, Renata D’Aliesio in the Globe and Mail.</description></item><item><title>CRUDE 3 - Let the Bastards Freeze in the Dark | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750123/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 06:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750123/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Alberta oil sands. It’s a cold patch of land (which we once almost nuked into oblivion) that’s become Canada’s economic engine. Governments have fought over it for decades. And now it’s one of the most controversial places on the planet. Will it finally tear our politics apart?
Featured in this episode: Mary Janigan, Chris Turner
To learn more:
Let the Eastern Bastards Freeze in the Dark by Mary Janigan</description></item><item><title>CRUDE 2 - Bombs, Blood &amp; the Battle of Trickle Creek | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750124/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 06:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750124/</guid><description>Podcast Description A family poisoned in their homes. Bombs going off in the night. Shots fired and inside jobs. The story of Wiebo Ludwig is There Will Be Blood come to life. So was he a man of faith facing down the full might of Big Oil? Or a terrorist with blood on his hands?
Featured in this episode: David York (Wiebo’s War), Levi Ludwig
To learn more:
Saboteurs: Wiebo Ludwig’s War Against Big Oil by Andrew Nikiforuk</description></item><item><title>CRUDE 1 - Smell This Town | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750125/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 14:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750125/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you don’t understand oil, you can’t understand Canada. We take you to a place unlike anywhere else in the world, where the booms and busts all began. And find out why just a short distance away, children grow up afraid of the very air they breathe.
Featured in this episode: Pat McGee and Charlie Fairbank (Fairbank Oil Properties), Vanessa Gray.
To learn more:
“Time stands still in oil industry's birthplace” in the Toronto Star by Murray White.</description></item><item><title>Introducing Our New Season: CRUDE | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750126/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 12:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last season Commons covered corruption in Canada. This time around we're talking about Canada's relationship with the oil industry. The good, the bad, the ugly, and the weird. Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>CORRUPTION 10 - The Canadian Company Accused of Using Slaves Today | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750127/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 05:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Canadian companies have committed all kinds of wrongdoing abroad. But this is on a different level. One Vancouver-based company has been accused by the United Nations and Human Rights Watch of using slaves to build a mine with one of the world’s most oppressive governments.
Featured in this episode: Geoffrey York (The Globe and Mail) &amp; Aaron Berhane (Mefti)
To learn more:
“Canadian miner Nevsun Resources has a tangled relationship with one of the world’s most repressive regimes” in The Globe and Mail by Geoffrey York</description></item><item><title>CORRUPTION 9 - Victoria's Secrets | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750128/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 06:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750128/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tens of thousands of dollars in suits, luggage, magazines and mustard. An epic booze heist from the legislature. An undercover legislator exposing corruption. And a wood-splitter that’s transfixed a province.
Just another day in the wild world of B.C. politics.
Featured in this episode: Andrew MacLeod (The Tyee)
To learn more:
“Speaker Report Alleges ‘Flagrant’ Misspending by Two Senior Legislative Officials,” in The Tyee by Andrew MacLeod
“Whistleblower alleges legislature expense issues beyond clerk and sergeant-at-arms,” in Global News by Richard Zussman.</description></item><item><title>CORRUPTION 8 - Hockey's Hall of Shame | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750129/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 10:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750129/</guid><description>Podcast Description Canada is hockey crazy. But at the heart of the sport is a system of unpaid labour that scars some boys for life. And the teams and leagues are doing whatever it takes to make sure things stay exactly the way they are.
Featured in this episode: Scott Wheeler (The Athletic)
To learn more:
“Hockey’s Puppy Mill” in The Walrus by Nicholas Hune-Brown
“How a Dad with NHL Dreams Bankrolled a Hockey Empire” in The Toronto Star by Robert Cribb</description></item><item><title>CORRUPTION 7 - The Only Canadian Imprisoned for Insider Trading | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750130/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jan 2019 14:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750130/</guid><description>Podcast Description One of Canada's most notorious white-collar criminals speaks about his crimes.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>CORRUPTION 6 - Charlottetown's Web | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750131/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Dec 2018 09:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750131/</guid><description>Podcast Description It might be small, but it when it comes to graft, Prince Edward Island plays in the big leagues: a secret off-the-books committee, conflicts of interest run amok, public records mysteriously destroyed, a provincial government doing an end-run on the Criminal Code.
An inside look at PEI’s long, strange attempt to become Canada’s online gambling hub.
Featured in this episode: Robyn Doolittle (The Globe and Mail), Stu Neatby (The Guardian), Paul Maines.</description></item><item><title>CORRUPTION 5 - The King of Cabbagetown | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750132/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 08:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750132/</guid><description>Podcast Description For twenty years, he's controlled public institutions from behind the scenes. He brags about his connections to organized crime. And he's connected to some of the most powerful people in Canada. So who is the King of Cabbagetown? This follows up on the last episode, "Papa Pump and the Small Town Shakedown."
To learn more: "Connected" in The Globe and Mail by Greg McArthur, Karen Howlett and Adrian Morrow.</description></item><item><title>CORRUPTION 4 - Papa Pump and the Small Town Shakedown | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750133/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 04:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750133/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the eleven years that Marolyn Morrison was the mayor of Caledon, Ontario, she faced down deep-pocketed developers, mafia enforcers and corrupt federal officials. When millions of dollars are at stake, things get heated.
To learn more:
"Battleground Caledon" in Toronto Life by Kelly Pullen
"Connected" in The Globe and Mail by Greg McArthur, Karen Howlett and Adrian Morrow
"Corrupt tax auditor gets three years" in The Toronto Star by Marco Chown Oved</description></item><item><title>CORRUPTION 3 - The Trouble with Paradise: How Canadians Built the Offshore World | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750134/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 04:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750134/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Panama Papers revealed to the world just how deeply enmeshed tax havens are in the global economy. And for 100 years, Canadian banks, businessmen and politicians have worked to build that offshore system, alongside crooks, fraudsters and corrupt officials.
To learn more:
Treasure Islands: Uncovering the Damage of Offshore Banking and Tax Havens by Nicholas Shaxson
Canada: A New Tax Haven: How the Country That Shaped Caribbean Tax Havens is Becoming One Itself by Alain Deneault</description></item><item><title>CORRUPTION 2 - How Vancouver Became A Money Laundering Paradise | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750135/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 04:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750135/</guid><description>Podcast Description For years, people could walk into Vancouver-area casinos with tens of thousands of dollars of suspicious cash and walk out with clean money, no questions asked. That money may be fuelling two of the biggest problems the city is facing: the housing crisis and the opiate epidemic. Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>CORRUPTION 1 - The Most Crime-Ridden Neighbourhood In Canada | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750136/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750136/</guid><description>Podcast Description This season, Commons will be focusing on stories at the intersection of money, influence and politics in Canada. In this episode, we take you to what may be Canada’s most criminal neighbourhood — Toronto’s financial district. Along for the ride is investigative journalist Bruce Livesey, author of “The Thieves of Bay Street.”
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 97 - What The Hell Is A Fairness Letter? | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750137/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 06:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mohamed Waleed Taleb is stuck in Turkey. He applied to come to Canada in 2015 and was flagged under section 34 of the Immigration and Refugee Protection Act for his pro-democracy work against the Assad regime. He&amp;rsquo;s responded to the governement&amp;rsquo;s concerns and is now waiting to hear back on a final decision: will he be let into Canada, or will he be deemed &amp;ldquo;inadmissible&amp;rdquo;. We spoke to Waleed about his experience.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 96 - Canada Is Not Racist... According To The Stats | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750138/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 04:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750138/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you look at the stats, Canada has a low incidence of hate crimes, but the numbers that we rely on to tell us if we're racist or not are wrong. In this episode, we speak to journalist and Executive Director, of the Canadian Anti-Hate Network Evan Balgord who explains why that is. Evan represented the research of Barbara Perry Professor and Undergraduate Program Director, of Criminology at the University of Ontario Institute of Technology and Sabreena Ghaffar-Siddiqui PhD Candidate and Researcher at McMaster University.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 95 - What Do Peacekeepers Actually Do? | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750139/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 07:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750139/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Liberal government announced earlier this year that it would send around 200 troops to assist in a UN peacekeeping mission in Mali. But what does &amp;ldquo;peacekeeping&amp;rdquo; look like in today&amp;rsquo;s world and what do peacekeepers actually do? In this episode, we speak to Major-General Denis Thompson (Retired) and Aisha Ahmad, an assistant professor in the Department of Political Science at the University of Toronto, to answer these questions.</description></item><item><title>Ep.94 - Life In Canada Without Clean Water | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750140/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 03:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750140/</guid><description>Podcast Description Canada has 20 per cent of the world's freshwater and yet some Indigenous communities have not had access to clean drinking water for decades. In this episode, we speak to Rachel Arsenault a master’s student at Laurentian University's Indigenous Relations program who works with Decolonizing Water an Indigenous-led community-based water monitoring initiative. We also speak with Samantha Redsky of Shoal Lake 40 First Nation . Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com</description></item><item><title>Ep. 93 - The All-White Jury In Canada | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750141/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 12:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750141/</guid><description>Podcast Description The acquittal of Gerald Stanley in the shooting of Colten Boushie sparked outrage across Canada. The anger was further fuelled by the fact that the jury was all white, in a community that had a significant Indigenous population. After the Gerald Stanley verdict, the government proposed sweeping changes to the legal system in Bill C-75. The legal community has been divided on these proposed changes - some say they are an important first step to make juries more diverse, while other say they will actually make things worse.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 92 - Canadian History X | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750142/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 03:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750142/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a teen, Elisa Hategan joined Canada's most notorious and well-organized white supremacist group, the Heritage Front. She later turned on the group and helped to take them down. What can we learn from the past about how white supremacists operate today? And what do we do about all these Nazis?
Elisa's book about her time in the Heritage Front is called Race Traitor.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 91 - Stories From Solitude | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750143/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 05:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750143/</guid><description>Podcast Description The final episode of our two-parter on solitary confinement in Canada. In this episode, we hear two personal stories about the impacts that solitary confinement can have. Featuring Yusuf Faqiri and Dan Parlow.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep. 90 - Unconstitutional Solitude | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750144/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2018 03:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750144/</guid><description>Podcast Description A two part series in which we explore the conditions and consequences of solitary confinement use in Canada. Featuring Chris Jackel, a correctional officer who works in a maximum security Ontario prison, and lawyer/professor Lisa Kerr.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep. 89 - Finding A Fix: Our Opioid Overdose Crisis | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750145/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 05:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750145/</guid><description>Podcast Description There's a well known narrative about the opioid epidemic: pharmaceutical companies and doctors over-prescribed addictive drugs on patients. But there's an important policy story here too, and we need to talk about it. Featuring longtime opiate user and activist, Garth Mullins, and lawyer, Caitlin Shane.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep. 88 - Our Mis(education): the Erasure of Blackness in Canadian Schools | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750146/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 03:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750146/</guid><description>Podcast Description Robyn Maynard is the author of Policing Black Lives: State Violence in Canada from Slavery to the Present. We chat with Robyn about what she calls our (mis)education: Canada's amnesia to its history of slavery and segregation, and about the ways in which Canadian classrooms are still rife with anti-black racism.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Brief Announcement | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750147/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750147/</guid><description>Podcast Description Back next week with a new episode! In the meantime, check out a new CANADALAND show, Oppo.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep. 87 - Unknown Road: Inside Immigration Detention | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750148/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 04:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750148/</guid><description>Podcast Description Canada's immigration system has a human rights problem. Each year, thousands of people are indefinitely jailed in prisons without any criminal charges. Babou was one of them. This episode features Babou Jobe and Subodh Bharati.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep. 86 - Throwing Shade at 2017: A Political Awards Show | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750149/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 04:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750149/</guid><description>Podcast Description We look back on some notably weird political moments of 2017 and collectively cringe. Featuring guests Tim Fontaine (of Walking Eagle News) and Scott Vrooman (of Centrism Dot Biz).
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 85. - Invisible Victims: The Quest for Police Accountability | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750150/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 07:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750150/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stronger police accountability is an acute need across Canada. In Ontario, recommendations for stronger police oversight are being drafted into legislation. In this episode, we explore the suspicious death of Cheyenne Fox and the ensuing (lack of) investigation. We then speak to a former director of Ontario's Special Investigations Unit, Ian Scott, who takes us inside the organizations responsible for holding police accountable. The final part of our policing miniseries.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 84 - Invisible Victims: How Police Botched the Robert Pickton Case | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750151/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 05:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750151/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;ldquo;If the police don&amp;rsquo;t want you to see a file, you&amp;rsquo;re never gonna know it exists.&amp;quot; We speak with Lorimer Shenher, a former police officer who was in charge of investigating the growing number of disappearing women from Vancouver&amp;rsquo;s downtown Eastside, about how law enforcement overlooked a serial killer. Part one of a two part series on Canada&amp;rsquo;s policing system and police accountability.Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Ep. 83 - No Protest is Genteel: On Antifa | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750152/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 06:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750152/</guid><description>Podcast Description Live from Vancouver: We speak with organizers Garth Mullins and Annie Ohana to unpack what it means to resist fascism in BC. Featuring Hadiya Roderique and guest host Sandy Garossino.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>As If They Were Pets: The Sixties Scoop | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750153/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 04:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750153/</guid><description>Podcast Description Betty Ann Adam is a reporter with the Saskatoon Star Phoenix. She is also a survivor of the "Sixties Scoop". When she was a toddler, the Canadian government pried her from her mother's arms. She was raised by foster parents. A modern version of this is still happening to Indigenous children across Canada. Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>On NAFTA And Niqabs | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750154/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 05:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750154/</guid><description>Podcast Description Quebec's racist bill, unveiled. Plus NAFTA explained by one of its founders, former Mulroney Chief of Staff Hugh Segal. And Vancouver? Commons is headed to your burg!
Support us at patreon.com/CANADALAND and see this year's goals and rewards. Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why We Need Higher Taxes, A Canadian Mt. Rushmore And A Population Of 100 Million | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750155/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 06:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750155/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Liberals put forth a proposal to tax the hell out of small businesses. At least that's how it's being painted by the Opposition.
In reality, the proposed changes would have virtually zero impact on the majority of small business owners, but would focus on self-incorporated doctors. And it wouldn't raise their taxes, per se, but alter how they can claim their family members as employees, and change how the money they park in investments rather than being poured back into their businesses is assessed.</description></item><item><title>BONUS EPISODE -- Jagmeet Singh - The Full Interview | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750156/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 17:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750156/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Episode 79 of Commons we spoke with three of the four NDP leadership candidates: Niki Ashton, Charlie Angus and Jagmeet Singh. These interviews were recorded before Singh's first-ballot victory on Sunday, October 1.
As a bonus to Commons listeners, we present the full interview with now NDP Leader Jagmeet Singh.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ashton, Angus &amp; Singh - Oh My! | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750157/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 09:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750157/</guid><description>Podcast Description Three Commons hosts, three NDP leadership hopefuls, one sweltering studio.
On this episode, just days before the first vote closes in the race, we speak with Niki Ashton, Jagmeet Singh and Charlie Angus about Canada-Indigenous relations, the environment, the economy and the future of the party.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Guy Caron, Guaranteed Income And Climate Refugees | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750158/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 09:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750158/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome back to a brand-new season of Commons!
To kick things off, the Commons team is profiling each of the four candidates vying to replace Thomas Mulcair as leader of the federal NDP. This week, we speak with Guy Caron.
Also, we look at the summer political stories that evolved while we were on hiatus: the Charlottesville tragedy and subsequent events in Canada, the influx of asylum seekers crossing the border and Trudeau's cabinet shuffle which may have just doubled the bureaucracy for Indigenous peoples.</description></item><item><title>The Rise Of The Right | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750159/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2017 12:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750159/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the final episode of the season, the Commons team digs into the rise of the fringe right in Canada.
Journalist Evan Balgord has been covering organizations like the Proud Boys, Soldiers of Odin, and the Three Percenters for the better part of the past year. He joins us to discuss the ongoing street protests and what's driving these groups' discontent.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Ep.76 - Amy Goodman/The Constitutional Clusterf**k | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750160/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 09:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750160/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we're thrilled to welcome legendary broadcast journalist Amy Goodman. Her program, Democracy Now!, was one of the few non-Indigenous media outlets to provide sustained coverage of the Standing Rock camps protesting the building of the Dakota Access Pipeline.
With a pro-pipeline president in the White House and a government in Ottawa that's shown a willingness to green-light our own projects, Goodman weighs in on what we can expect going forward.</description></item><item><title>Ep.75 - Drink Like A Conservative | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750161/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 08:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750161/</guid><description>Podcast Description The dust has settled, and the Conservative Party of Canada has elected Andrew Scheer -- an anti-choice, anti-gay-marriage, anti-refugee, anti-M103 candidate -- as their new leader.
As the election results trickled in, the Commons team were joined by Conservative consultant Ginny Movat and about 50 loyal listeners at Toronto's venerable Monarch Tavern to dissect the various campaigns.
Proceeds from this event were donated to Newcomer Women's Services -- a Toronto-based not-for-profit that supports new immigrants.</description></item><item><title>Ep.74 - Cultural Appropriation Is An Inherently Political Act | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750162/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 09:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750162/</guid><description>Podcast Description Appropriation is the buzzword in the news this week, as a misguided editorial was followed by a white elite up in arms on social media. In the end, two prominent magazine editors were gone from their posts, and the debate about the under-representation of non-white voices in Canadian media got significant traction.
But Commons is a show about politics, so we asked CBC columnist and head of TIFF Cinematheque Jesse Wente how appropriation is represented in the Canadian political sphere.</description></item><item><title>Ep.73 - That's Why We Live In A Democracy | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750163/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 11:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750163/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ontario Premier Kathleen Wynne announced the rollout of a basic income trial. The program is to be introduced in three Ontario communities this summer, including Thunder Bay. This is widely seen as compensation for living in Thunder Bay.
B.C. Premier Christy Clark gives a voter a succinct primer on democracy, while Nova Scotia Premier Stephen McNeil trips on his shoelaces and accidentally drops his writ.
In our feature interview, Ashley speaks with Bloodwatch.</description></item><item><title>Ep.72 - Commons Gets High | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750164/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 07:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750164/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Commons team unpacks the just-released specifics of the Trudeau government's plan to legalize cannabis. And after twenty minutes or so, all they can think about is snacks. Seriously.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep.71 - Being Icky Is The Job | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750165/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2017 07:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750165/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Liberals, according to Conservative MP Scott Reid, are trying to "ram through whatever the fuck they want."
In other, vaguely sexually-themed Conservative news, Brad Trost isn't down with the "the whole gay thing," while k.d. lang asks if Jason Kenney might be secretly fond of it. Kellie Leitch and Senator Lynn Beyak? Just crapping on Muslims and Indigenous peoples again, respectively. Nothing sexy there.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com</description></item><item><title>Ep.70 - You Have No Rights At The Border | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750166/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2017 05:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750166/</guid><description>Podcast Description Having passed a second reading, the controversial bill C-23 stands to give U.S. border guards greater authority to reject, detain, or search Canadians and permanent residents trying to cross the border.
Speaking of the border, a significant chunk of our shared border with the United States comes in the form of four of the five Great Lakes (bonus points if you can name the one entirely contained within one of the two countries).</description></item><item><title>Ep.69 - "I'm Ashamed Of Myself For Being Afraid" | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750167/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 22:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750167/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, the city of Thunder Bay, ON, agreed to implement the recommendations of an inquest that looked into the deaths of seven Indigenous students. This, despite the fact that no one from city council appeared to have attended said inquest.
The case of a Halifax-area cab driver accused of sexually assaulting a heavily intoxicated female passenger was dismissed by a provincial court judge after he claimed that, "</description></item><item><title>Ep.68 - Strong Hearts To The Front | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750168/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2017 09:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750168/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome back to CANADALAND Commons! New hosts Hadiya Roderique, Ryan McMahon, and Ashley Csanady spend their first episode looking into the mostly manufactured controversy behind M103 - a motion to denounce Islamophobia and racism and a push for the Canadian government to set up a committee to look into the rise of discrimination in the country.
Also, refugees from countries on U.S. President Donald Trump's list of banned countries are taking the extraordinary step of trying to cross the border into Manitoba.</description></item><item><title>COMMONS returns! | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750169/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2017 05:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750169/</guid><description>Podcast Description Meet the new hosts of CANADALAND COMMONS: Hadiya Roderique, Ashley Csanady, and Ryan McMahon. New episode available Tuesday February 21 and every two weeks thereafter.
Follow the show on Twitter.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>COMMONS host search | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750170/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 02:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750170/</guid><description>Podcast Description We're looking for new hosts. Please send demos (less than 4 minutes long) to: info@canadalandshow.com
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Message About the Future of COMMONS | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750171/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 01:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750171/</guid><description>Podcast Description Supriya, Vicky and publisher Jesse Brown deliver a message about the future of COMMONS.
Follow @cndlndcmns for developments.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep.67 - A Hodge Podge of Political Hacks: Inside the War Room | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750172/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 02:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750172/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we go behind the scenes in Canadian politics. How do the backroom dealings in Ottawa stack up to the kind of power games we see on shows like House of Cards or the West Wing?
Warren Kinsella brought the American war room model to Jean Chrétien's campaign, making it his mission to drive rival politicians crazy and throw them off their game. Lisa Kinsella has also worked in Liberal war rooms, and is now a "</description></item><item><title>Ep.66 - A Hat Trick of Deceit: First Nations and the LNG Project | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750173/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 02:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750173/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Trudeau government made a lot of commitments in the last election, including improving relations with Indigenous people, fighting climate change and investing in infrastructure. Those commitments are starting to come to a head.
This past week, they approved a massive liquified natural gas (LNG) project on Lelu Island, near Prince Rupert, BC. We check in with Indigenous communities, where support is split on the project.
Grand Chief Stewart Phillip, president of the Union of British Columbia Indian Chiefs, says the project will be destructive to the environment and local economies.</description></item><item><title>Ep.65 - Drunk on Liberal Power / Kellie Leitch on Anti-Canadian Values | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750174/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2016 03:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750174/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conservative leadership candidate Kellie Leitch really wants to talk about her proposal to screen out immigrants over anti-Canadian values, but takes issue with "specific questions" on the matter.
But first, Bloomberg reporter Josh Wingrove drops in for a lookahead to the upcoming year in Parliament. What's gonna happen, who will start the first brawl and what would it take to end Trudeau's popularity?
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Ep.64 - Conservative Leadership Showdown Part 2: Tony Clement &amp; Maxime Bernier | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750175/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 01:53:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750175/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's week two of our Conservative leader-a-thon. Today we bring you our conversations with leadership contenders Tony Clement and Maxime Bernier.
Both men were longtime members of Stephen Harper's cabinet.
Tony Clement says the Conservatives need to communicate better with young people and is now pushing tough-on-terror policies.
Maxime Bernier is often called the Libertarian candidate. In addition to his support for personal freedoms, he wants to de-regulate or privatize a handful of industries.</description></item><item><title>Ep.63 - Conservative Leadership Showdown Part 1: Michael Chong &amp; Brad Trost | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750176/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2016 02:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750176/</guid><description>Podcast Description A bunch of people want to succeed Harper as leader of the Conservative Party. Whoever gets the vote won't just be gunning to be the next Prime Minister; they'll be leading the Opposition, with an aim towards keeping the government in check.
Over the summer, we took some time to figure out who all these people are. We'll share those interviews over the next two weeks.
Today, we hear from Michael Chong and Brad Trost.</description></item><item><title>Ep.62 - When Your Councillor Spams You on Facebook | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750177/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2016 02:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750177/</guid><description>Podcast Description What do you do if you think a city councillor is exploiting his public platform to make money on the side?
Listener Matt Alexander emailed us with this quandary. He points out that Greater Sudbury Councillor Robert Kirwan takes money from local businesses to write promotional posts for a Facebook group he runs. This raises a lot of questions for Matt, but he doesn't know what to do about it.</description></item><item><title>Ep.61 - When CSIS Comes Knocking pt. 2 | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750178/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 02:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750178/</guid><description>Podcast Description Earlier this summer, we spoke to Monia Mazigh about CSIS agents making unannounced visits to Muslims. Now, one of those men joins us.
After studying and teaching English in Egypt, Juned Moid* was visited by CSIS agents, denied entry into the US and had his passport renewal delayed. He doesn't know why.
We also speak to Ken Stone, an activist and political commentator, who launched a complaint against CSIS after two agents showed up at his door, asking him about an op-ed he wrote in the Hamilton Spectator.</description></item><item><title>Ep.60 - MMIW: What Justice Means for a Family Member | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750179/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2016 01:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750179/</guid><description>Podcast Description We check in with Maggie Cywink about the upcoming inquiry into missing and murdered Indigenous women. Maggie’s sister Sonya Cywink was murdered over 20 years ago and the case remains unsolved.
Maggie says the announcement felt like a photo op for the Liberals.
She first spoke to us back in December when the inquiry was announced:
http://www.canadalandshow.com/podcast/families-mmiw-what-can-we-do-tomorrow/
Plus, a TweetBeat in which a Liberal MP tells a vegan to eat a steak.</description></item><item><title>Ep.59 - Canadian Police Are Racist Too | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750180/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 03:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Abdirahman Abdi, a Somali man in Ottawa, is dead after witnesses say he was beaten by cops.
There’s been a lot of attention on police violence against Black people in the U.S. lately. But Akwasi Owusu-Bempah, assistant professor of sociology at the University of Toronto, says Canada’s policing style has a lot of the same problems as the American system when it comes to dealing with racialized and Indigenous populations.</description></item><item><title>Ep.58 - When CSIS Comes Knocking | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750181/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 04:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750181/</guid><description>Podcast Description Muslim men have been telling Monia Mazigh about getting unannounced visits from CSIS agents at home or the workplace. The intelligence agency says the conversations are voluntary, but some people are accusing them of intimidation. Monia is the national coordinator for the International Civil Liberties Monitoring Group. She tells Supriya and Vicky about these visits and discusses Bill C-22, the legislation that the government tabled to create parliamentary oversight of national security agencies, including CSIS.</description></item><item><title>Ep.57 - Buy Gold and Raisin Bran: The Brexit and Canada | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750182/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2016 02:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750182/</guid><description>Podcast Description Supriya and Vicky want to know what the Brexit means for us. Does a vote for the United Kingdom to leave the EU change our lives across the ocean?
Armine Yalnizyan, senior economist for the Canadian Centre for Policy Alternatives, talks about why shifting global markets matter for everyone.
Freelance journalist Steven Zhou gives some social context to the vote.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Ep.56 - Naming a Genocide | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750183/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2016 01:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750183/</guid><description>Podcast Description The government’s declared that ISIS is committing a genocide against the Yazidi people. So what are we doing about it?
Yazidi-Canadian Dalal Abdi talks about her journey to Canada and her family's life back in Iraq and Turkey.
Liberal MP Nathaniel Erskine-Smith talks about voting against the majority of his party to declare a genocide earlier in the week.
Stephanie Carvin, assistant professor at the Norman Paterson School of International Affairs, tells us how using the word "</description></item><item><title>Ep.55 - Cheri DiNovo on How to Fix the NDP | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750184/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 02:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750184/</guid><description>Podcast Description Toronto MPP Cheri DiNovo thinks the NDP needs to return to its roots: unabashedly socialist and anti-capitalist, with an eye towards social justice and the environment. So now she's launched an unofficial leadership campaign, choosing not to pay the $30,000 fee required to enter the race.
DiNovo was the first person within the NDP to speak out against the Party after their collapse during the 2015 election. She talks to Vicky and Supriya about money in politics, the missteps of the NDP and why Veuve Clicquot and high fashion aren't at odds with socialism.</description></item><item><title>Ep.54 - This Is Not Canada: Living as a Migrant Farm Worker | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750185/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 01:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750185/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Are these… 18th century working conditions?” Gabriel Allahdua asks. Gabriel came from St. Lucia to work on a farm as part of the Temporary Foreign Worker program. He describes the long hours, difficult working conditions and his disappointment over speaking to a Parliamentary committee that’s reviewing the TFW program.
Justicia for Migrant Workers put us in touch with Gabriel.
Are Canadian politicians bending gender norms? Jerald Sabin, a research associate at the Carleton Centre for Community Innovation, talks about a study on masculinity in the last election, co-authored by Kyle Kirkup.</description></item><item><title>Ep.53 - Celebrating Defeat: Dispatches from the Conservative Convention | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750186/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2016 02:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750186/</guid><description>Podcast Description We sent the Syrup Trap's Winnie Code to the Conservative Convention in Vancouver. She explains how the convention was a bit like an informercial and gets the official party line on whether or not Justin Trudeau is handsome.
Plus, a discussion about whether the Conservative Party can build credibility when it comes to environmental policy. Featuring Mark Cameron of Canadians for Clean Prosperity and Jason Thistlethwaite, assistant professor at University of Waterloo's environment faculty.</description></item><item><title>Ep.52 - Are Libertarians Conservatives? | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750187/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2016 02:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750187/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matt Bufton is a proud Libertarian who does not want to be lumped in with Conservatives.
With the Conservative leadership race picking up steam, Matt, executive director of the Institute for Liberal Studies, tells us why the Conservatives don’t represent his values… and why he has to look to the past for political role models.
Tannara Yelland tells the story of 21-year old Breanna Kannick, who died in remand in Saskatchewan last September.</description></item><item><title>Ep.51 - How to Make Poor People Disappear (Census Edition) | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750188/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2016 01:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750188/</guid><description>Podcast Description People lost their minds when the long form census came back, after being replaced by the voluntary National Household Survey. But why does it matter?
David Hulchanski, a professor at University of Toronto, tells us how the NHS made Canada look more equal than it was.
Dillon Black from the group Queering613 talks about issues for trans and gender non-binary people in the census.
Plus, why is the government considering giving a billion dollars to a company owned mostly by a single family?</description></item><item><title>Ep.50 - Debating Same-Sex Marriage and Other Ways to Stay Irrelevant | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750189/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 01:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750189/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conservatives may finally decide toembrace gay marriage at a policy convention later this month. Ormaybe not. More than a decade after same-sex marriage was legalisedin Canada, the party still defines it as a union between one manand one woman.
BC’s Premier is under attack forconflict-of-interest, relating to over $300,000 in salary top-upsand a bunch of expensive fundraisers. The Tyee’s legislative bureauchief Andrew MacLeod fills us in on the time she told him the moneywas for a car allowance.</description></item><item><title>Ep.49 - Can a Conservative Be a Feminist? | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750190/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 02:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750190/</guid><description>Podcast Description A Conservative MP’s op-ed aboutthe sexism in Parliament got a lot of praise. But Sarah Beuhler sawit as hypocritical and an attempt to gain favour for a possibleleadership bid. She debates with Supriya and guest co-host JaneLytvenenko whether a Conservative MP can be a feminist.
Mike Duffy’s cleared of all chargesin the Senate expense scandal.
We hear from protestors who wereliving inside the offices of Indigenous and Northern Affairs Canadafor over a week.</description></item><item><title>Ep.48 - Parliament Needs More Women's Bathrooms | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750191/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2016 04:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750191/</guid><description>Podcast Description Guest co-host Vicky Mochama went out to the Hill to interview women about what it’s like to work in a space built for 19th century gentlemen.
In the wake of the NDP convention, the big question is whether Canada can stomach a party that’s a centimetre off centre. A powerful listener calls in with opinions on the Senate. Subscribe to Vicky’s newsletter, NOT SORRY.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.</description></item><item><title>Ep.47 - Should This Old Indian Guy Lead the Conservatives? | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750192/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2016 01:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750192/</guid><description>Podcast Description The fractures in the Conservative Party are showing as people jump into the leadership race.
Desmond wants to know why the Liberals flip flopped on an issue of torture. Supriya wants to get in on that sweet tax free status we've been hearing about in the Panama Papers.
University of Victoria economics professor Lindsay Tedds tells us why, despite the projected $30 billion deficit, "the budget might in fact balance itself.</description></item><item><title>Ep.46 - Tom Mulcair: Hot Prosecutor or Wet Napkin? | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750193/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2016 01:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750193/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jane Lytvynenko, CANADALAND’s news editor, guest co-hosts with Supriya Dwivedi.
As the NDP approaches a leadership review, Jane and Supriya try to figure out who Tom Mulcair even is.
Maclean’s Quebec Bureau Chief Martin Patriquin laughs off the idea that the Quebec government will clean itself up after recent arrests in the provincial corruption scandal.
Jane and Supriya offer free advice on how the Trudeau government can make itself more transparent without having to do the whole public consultation thing.</description></item><item><title>Ep.45 - Police in Canada Get Away With Killing Black People | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750194/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2016 05:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750194/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andrew Loku was shot and killed by police last July. But the public doesn’t know who did it.
When the Special Investigations Unit announced that the officer who killed him would not face charges, it led to a protest organised by Black Lives Matter Toronto that has lasted over a week, day and night, through rain and an ice storm. Protestors have gathered from around the country, demanding for the name of the officer who killed Andrew Loku to be released and for more accountability when police kill or beat black citizens.</description></item><item><title>Ep.44 - Canada's Arms Deals: Beyond Saudi Arabia | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750195/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 01:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750195/</guid><description>Podcast Description Canada’s arms deal with Saudi Arabia has raised a lot of controversy, but they’re not the only ones getting our weapons or weapons parts.
Supriya wants to know who else Canada is selling arms to, what oversight exists to make sure our weapons aren’t being used unethically and what happens if we do see a reason to break an arms contract.
She talks to NDP defence critic Hélène Laverdière, who wants to create a Parliamentary sub-committee to oversee arms sales.</description></item><item><title>Ep.43 - Rogue Senators | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750196/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2016 02:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750196/</guid><description>Podcast Description A group of Senators says partisan activity has "seriously eroded the credibility and reputation” of their workplace. So they’ve formed a non-partisan working group to try to fix it.
Senator Diane Bellemare talks to Desmond and Supra after quitting the Conservative caucus and joining this new group.
Senate scholar Heather Hughson says this is exactly what’s needed to restore faith in the Chamber.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>No Episode This Week | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750197/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750197/</guid><description>Podcast Description No new episode today. We'll be back next week.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep.42 - Live From U of Ottawa: Refugees Welcome, But Bad News About the Job Market... | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750198/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 02:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750198/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andray and Desmond host a live panel asking how cities are preparing refugees to fend for themselves in a year’s time and how they can get on their feet in our terrible job market.
Featuring: Michael Qaqish, an Ottawa city councillor and the city’s refugee liaison; Ula Abu Rashed, a student at the University of Ottawa whose family fled Syria for Germany last fall; Rouba Al-Fattal, a part time professor of Middle East and Arab politics at the University of Ottawa.</description></item><item><title>Ep.41 - Legal Weed is Bad for Poor People | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750199/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2016 02:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750199/</guid><description>Podcast Description Canada has had a marijuana industry for a long time. It just hasn’t always been legal. People in the business have ended up in prison, barred from crossing the border or denied future job prospects.
Now that the Liberals are planning to legalize weed, what will happen to those people?
Andray talks to Liberal MP for Beaches-East York Nathaniel Erskine-Smith and criminal defence lawyer John Struthers. Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.</description></item><item><title>Ep.40 - George Elliott Clarke: A Polyphony of Canadian Blacknesses | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750200/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 04:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750200/</guid><description>Podcast Description George Elliott Clarke has been appointed as Canada’s seventh poet laureate. His wide-ranging conversation with Desmond touches on how working for a trailblazing black MP led him to meeting the Dalai Lama, why politicians should care about poetry and how he thinks Canadians are being ripped off by phone companies. Plus, he nearly sets the studio on fire with a rendition of his poem “Look Homeward, Exile."
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.</description></item><item><title>Ep.39 - Don't Let Harper Happen Here: Wab Kinew on Entering Politics | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750201/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 03:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750201/</guid><description>Podcast Description “I think it would be a real shame if we got rid of Harper at the federal level and then we brought in somebody who wants to take our province in a similar direction,” Wab Kinew tells Andray and Desmond. Kinew is stepping into politics after years in the public eye as a journalist, author, rapper and First Nations community leader.
He talks about what he wants to accomplish in politics that he couldn’t do in his previous roles.</description></item><item><title>Ep.38 - The Government Finally Admitted They Illegally Spy On Us and Nobody Cares | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750202/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2016 01:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750202/</guid><description>Podcast Description Canada's electronic spy agency broke privacy laws by collecting metadata about Canadians, then sharing it with other countries. The issue was exposed in a watchdog report that was released to the public last week. Andray and Supriya speak to Amanda Connolly, national security reporter for iPolitics, about what exactly the Communications Security Establishment did wrong and whether there's any reason to expect it won't happen again. Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.</description></item><item><title>Ep.37 - Michelle Rempel on Heckling | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750203/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2016 03:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750203/</guid><description>Podcast Description Most workplaces discourage yelling and jeering among co-workers. But the government has their own way of doing things.
Desmond and Supriya talk to Calgary - Nose Hill Conservative MP Michelle Rempel about her experiences being heckled. They also get into how social media is changing the political discourse in ways that Rempel herself still hasn't figured out. This follows a recent survey by Samara Canada finding that most MPs think heckling is a problem in the House of Commons, but most of them also do it.</description></item><item><title>Ep.36 - What Is a Post-Harper Conservative? | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750204/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 05:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750204/</guid><description>Podcast Description After the end of Harper's decade-long rule, Conservatives have to figure out what they stand for.
The next leadership race is still a long way away, but people are starting to campaign. Jim Burnett knows conservative leadership races from the inside. He returns to the show to talk about where Conservatives go after Harper. Plus, he answers the burning question: Did you actually like the guy?
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.</description></item><item><title>Ep.35 - White Men Gotta Speak On This | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750205/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2016 03:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750205/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former BC Premier Ujjal Dosanjh recently wrote an editorial called “The Silencing of the White Men of the West." In it, he argues that political correctness stifles powerful white men. Editor-in-chief of The Walrus Jonathan Kay and cultural critic Septembre Anderson give their thoughts on the issue.
Ujjal Dosanjh did not respond to a request to appear on COMMONS.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Ep.34 - A senator on mischief, mutiny and men's rights | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750206/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2016 03:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750206/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a child, Andray was taught to look up to Anne C. Cools, the first black person to join Canada’s Senate. Born in Barbados, she spent her early life as a social worker and pioneer in the field of domestic violence before spending over three decades in the upper house.
Andray’s views change when he hears Desmond’s interview with the senator. Desmond sets out to talk to her about the recent expense probes, the role of the Senate and her activist past.</description></item><item><title>Ep.33 - Canada's Climate Game (of Thrones) | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750207/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2015 03:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750207/</guid><description>Podcast Description Following the Paris agreement, Andray and Desmond speak to climate change expert Jason Thistlethwaite in a conversation touching on the “give a shit factor”, the inevitable death of the suburbs and Game of Thrones.
Plus, they speak to someone who was at the talks and was not happy with what took place. Erica Violet Lee, an Indigenous activist and part of the Canadian Youth Delegation to Paris, felt tokenized and ignored by politicians and the press.</description></item><item><title>Ep.32 - Families of MMIW: "What Can We Do Tomorrow?" | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750208/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2015 03:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750208/</guid><description>Podcast Description "What can we do tomorrow?” Maggie Cywink wants to know. "I don’t have another six months to wait for the government to meet everybody and figure it out.” Mag’s sister Sonya Cywink was found murdered in southern Ontario in 1994. Bernadette Smith’s sister Claudette Osborne-Tyo went missing in Winnipeg. And Lauren Crazybull’s great-aunt Jacqueline Crazybull was killed in a random attack in Calgary.
None of these cases have been solved.</description></item><item><title>Ep.31 - Bringing Refugees To The Rockies | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750209/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2015 06:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750209/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s easy to get lost in the numbers. So we look into what it takes to get a family of three refugees from Syria to the small mountain town of Jasper, Alberta.
And Farah Malik, a refugee from Pakistan, talks about what it was like abandoning her home country.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep.30 - Electoral Reform, or How New Zealand Got a Rastafari MP | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750210/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 02:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750210/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Liberal government has promised to get rid of our current voting system, but they haven’t committed to what those changes will look like. By listener request, Andray and Desmond take a look at what could happen.
They speak to a former political candidate from New Zealand about the reforms his country made. They also speak to conservative strategist Jim Burnett, who thinks Canada doesn't have the will to change the electoral system.</description></item><item><title>Ep.29 - The Beaverton | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750211/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2015 04:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750211/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Beaverton's satire isn't about funny accents or wacky characters. It cuts deep, skewering politicians and other media on issues like the refugee crisis and ISIS. Andray and Desmond speak to The Beaverton's editor-in-chief Luke Gordon Field about using humour as a weapon and what's missing in Canadian political comedy. Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep.28 - Paris: Backlash Against Canadian Muslims? | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750212/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2015 05:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750212/</guid><description>Podcast Description Following the tragedy in Paris, Desmond talks to Imam Syed Soharwardy, founder of the Islamic Supreme Council of Canada, and Amira Elghawaby, communications director of the National Council of Canadian Muslims, about the backlash Muslims face in Canada when attacks are carried out in the name of Islam.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep.27 - How the Cabinet is like Wu-Tang Clan | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750213/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2015 02:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750213/</guid><description>Podcast Description University of New Brunswick's JP Lewis explains how the Cabinet is like Wu-Tang Clan and Buzzfeed Canada's Scaachi Koul proposes a Minister of No Bullsh*t.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep.26 - Losin' Ain't Easy | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750214/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2015 03:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750214/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Conservative Party of Canada has fallen to Opposition status... but what does that mean? Can they actually affect politics or are they just getting ready for their next shot at government? Andray talks about that with Ray Martin, who led Alberta's Official Opposition in the 80s. He also talks to Mark Warner - who was dumped from a Conservative campaign in 2007 - and Tasha Kheiriddin - a conservative Harper skeptic - about what the CPC would have to do to get their full support.</description></item><item><title>Ep.25 - Canada's 1st MP of Somali descent | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750215/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2015 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750215/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andray and Desmond talk to Liberal MP-elect Ahmed Hussen, soon to be Canada's first MP of Somali descent. They discuss the refugee crisis, diversity in Parliament, Bill C-51 and more.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep. 24 - Live on Election Night | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750216/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 06:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750216/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andray Domise, Desmond Cole and Supriya Dwivedi broadcast LIVE to a packed room at the Monarch Tavern in Toronto.
Feat. Jesse Brown in Toronto, Jen Gerson at Harper HQ in Calgary, Drew Brown in Edmonton and Morgan Baskin in Squamish.
#CL42
Warning: there's some profanity in this one.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep. 23 - The Choice for Progressives | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750217/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2015 21:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750217/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tiffany Gooch explains why she's voting Liberal, and Luke Savage tells us why he's voting NDP. Plus, Desmond and Andray debate the value of voting. Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep.22 - A Conservative Makes Their Case | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750218/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2015 02:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750218/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cartoonist and conservative commentator J.J. McCullough tells Andray and Desmond why he's voting Conservative in this election. It gets uncomfortable. Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep.21 - What are women's issues, anyway? | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750219/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2015 03:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750219/</guid><description>Podcast Description Septembre Anderson and Naomi Sayers tell Desmond Cole what they think women's issues are, and what they make of how they're treated in our politics. Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep.20 - Knock Knock | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750220/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2015 02:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750220/</guid><description>Podcast Description Desmond Cole follows a Green Party candidate and his volunteers as they door-knock in the riding of Toronto-Danforth. Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep.19 - Campaign Ads (are for grandmas) | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750221/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2015 04:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750221/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andray Domise and Desmond Cole talk campaign ads with Jen Gerson and Scott Matthews. Featuring a special guest appearance from Andray’s grandma. Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep.18 - A Historic Election | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750222/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2015 03:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750222/</guid><description>Podcast Description We've never seen one like this before. Desmond Cole is back to talk three-way races, minority governments and party cooperation with Paul Fairie (@paulisci) and Mychaylo Prystupa (@Mychaylo). Plus, Andray Domise is reticent to embrace coalitions. Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep.17 - Kids These Days | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750223/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 02:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750223/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andray Domise speaks with former 18-year-old mayoral candidate Morgan Baskin (@MorganBaskinTO) and Generation Squeeze founder Paul Kershaw (@GenSqueeze) about youth in politics.
Don't worry. No one asks you to rock the vote. Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>No New Episode This Week | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750224/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2015 14:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750224/</guid><description>Podcast Description Back next week with a new episode!
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep.16 - Survey Says! | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750225/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2015 04:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750225/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andray Domise and Desmond Cole talk to Kyla Ronellenfitsch from the Gandalf Group and David Coletto, the CEO of Abacus Data to help figure out political polling. When should you pay attention to a poll and why and when should you take the results with a grain of salt. Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep.15 - CANADALAND: COMMONS Guide To Debates | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750226/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2015 02:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750226/</guid><description>Podcast Description Desmond Cole and guest host Supriya Dwivedi present The CANADALAND: COMMONS Guide To Debates. From the zinger to the dodge, Desmond and Supriya break down what you can expect to see in the federal leader's debates this election season. Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep.14: Cash Rules Everything Around Me | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750227/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2015 02:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750227/</guid><description>Podcast Description To kick off the official federal election campaign, Desmond Cole and Andray Domise talk to Harold Jansen and Gerry Nicholls about campaign financing, party fundraising, and why this campaign is set to be the longest in modern Canadian history.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep.13 - Migrant Detention | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750228/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2015 03:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750228/</guid><description>Podcast Description Desmond Cole and Andray Domise talk about the Canadian government's detention of migrants, many of whom have committed no crime, with Renu Mandhane and Syed Hussan. Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep.12 - Debts and Deficits | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750229/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2015 02:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750229/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andray Domise and guest host Supriya Dwivedi talk government debt, recessions and the Balanced Budget Act with Mike Moffatt of the Mowat Centre, and Aaron Wudrick of the Canadian Taxpayers Federation. Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep.11 - Can I Kick It? | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750230/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2015 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750230/</guid><description>Podcast Description Desmond Cole and Andray Domise talk election fraud, Justin Trudeau, and the TRC.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep.10 - Diversity or tokenism? | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750231/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2015 00:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750231/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rachel Décoste joims to talk diversity quotas, tokenism and equity in Canadian politics.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep.9 - The Senate, what it do? | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750232/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2015 01:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750232/</guid><description>Podcast Description Paul Wells and Heather Hughson talk about what the Senate does, and whether or not it's worth hanging on to. Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep.8 - Barbaric cultural practices | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750233/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2015 02:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750233/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andray Domise, guest-host Supriya Dwivedi and Ishmael Daro talk about the Zero Tolerance For Barbaric Cultural Practices Act, the new Quebec secular legislation, and the massacre in Charleston.
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep.7 - Crossing the floor | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750234/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2015 03:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750234/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andray and Desmond speak with former Wildrose leader Danielle Smith about crossing the floor from the official opposition to the governing party. Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep.6 - Residential Schools | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750235/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2015 03:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750235/</guid><description>Podcast Description We haven't even begun to talk about what happened. Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep.5 - Sex work in Canada | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750236/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2015 02:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750236/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kerry Porth, Akio Maroon, Elene Lam join for a panel discussion on Bill C-36 and more.Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep.4 - The PMO, what it is? | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750237/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2015 02:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750237/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is the Prime Minister's Office? How many people work there, who are they, and what do they all do? Just how powerful is the PMO, and is the Prime Minister responsible for what it does?
Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep.3 - Elizabeth May | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750238/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2015 04:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750238/</guid><description>Podcast Description Desmond Cole taks to Green Party leader Elizabeth May about her plans to get arrested, and more. Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep.2 - What happened in Alberta? | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750239/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2015 04:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750239/</guid><description>Podcast Description Desmond and Andray try to understand the NDP's shocking victory. Guests: professor Melanee Thomas and writer Drew Brown. Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep.1 - Who's in charge? | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750240/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2015 10:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750240/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is it the Prime Minister? The Governor General? The Queen? Canada's Head of State may be symbolic, but symbolic of what? Desmond Cole and Andray Domise start with the basics. Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Preview #1. Series launch on May 5th | COMMONS</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5376750241/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2015 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5376750241/</guid><description>Podcast Description Desmond Cole &amp; Andray Domise talk about their ambitions for their new weekly political podcast Support COMMONS: http://commonspodcast.com
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>