<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Passion Struck with John R. Miles on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/passion-struck-with-john-r.-miles/</link><description>Recent content in Passion Struck with John R. Miles on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:01:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/passion-struck-with-john-r.-miles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Art Of Managing Toxic Family Using The Mosquito Principle w/John R. Miles EP 387 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090001/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090001/</guid><description>Podcast Description https://passionstruck.com/passion-struck-book/ - Order a copy of my new book, ”Passion Struck,” today! Picked by the Next Big Idea Club as a must-read for 2024.
Welcome to a special holiday edition of the Passion Struck podcast: ’The Art of Managing Toxic Family: Navigate with the Mosquito Principle.’
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dr. Richard M. Ryan on Exploring the Heart of Human Motivation EP 386 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 08:15:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090002/</guid><description>Podcast Description https://passionstruck.com/passion-struck-book/ - Order a copy of my new book, ”Passion Struck,” today! Picked by the Next Big Idea Club as a must-read for 2024.
In this episode of Passion Struck, John interviews Dr. Richard M. Ryan, one of the world’s top psychologists and co-founder of the self-determination theory. Dr. Ryan shares insights into the core principles of self-determination theory, including the importance of autonomy, competence, and relatedness in our mental health and overall happiness.</description></item><item><title>Hal Elrod on How You Harness ‘The Miracle Morning’ (Bonus Episode) EP 385 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 18:40:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090003/</guid><description>Podcast Description https://passionstruck.com/passion-struck-book/ - Order a copy of my new book, ”Passion Struck,” today! Picked by the Next Big Idea Club as a must-read for 2024.
In this compelling episode of the Passion Struck podcast, host John R. Miles delves into an inspiring discussion with Hal Elrod, best-selling author of ”The Miracle Morning.” This episode is a profound exploration of overcoming adversity and embracing life’s potential.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dr. Lucia Aronica on the Impact of Personalized Nutrition on Epigenetics EP 384 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090004/</guid><description>Podcast Description https://passionstruck.com/passion-struck-book/ - Order a copy of my new book, ”Passion Struck,” today! Picked by the Next Big Idea Club as a must-read for 2024.
In this captivating episode of Passion Struck, host John R. Miles sits down with esteemed guest Dr. Lucia Aronica, a lecturer at Stanford University and expert in epigenetics. They delve into the fascinating world of epigenetics, discussing how our daily choices, including nutrition and lifestyle, can profoundly impact our genes and overall well-being</description></item><item><title>Master Your Mind: 6 Proven Strategies to Overcome Self-Doubt and Fear w/ John R. Miles EP 383 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090005/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090005/</guid><description>Podcast Description https://passionstruck.com/passion-struck-book/ - Order a copy of my new book, ”Passion Struck.’
In this episode of the Passion Struck podcast, host John R. Miles explores the topic of fear and self-doubt and how they can hinder personal growth and success. He shares six powerful strategies to overcome these emotions and unlock one’s true potential. John draws inspiration from the life story of Dwayne ”The Rock” Johnson, highlighting his journey from self-doubt to becoming a Hollywood icon.</description></item><item><title>Gordy Bal on 7 Keys to Unlock Freedom, Purpose, and Abundance EP 382 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090006/</guid><description>Podcast Description https://passionstruck.com/passion-struck-book/ - Order a copy of my new book, ”Passion Struck: Twelve Powerful Principles to Unlock Your Purpose and Ignite Your Most Intentional Life,” today! Picked by the Next Big Idea Club as a must-read for 2024.
In this captivating episode of Passion Struck, host John R. Miles sits down with Gordy Ball, founder of the Conscious Thought Revolution and author of the best-selling book, ”The New Millionaire’s Playbook: 7 Keys to Unlock Freedom, Purpose, and Abundance.</description></item><item><title>Mike Massimino on How to Achieve Your Own Personal Moonshots EP 381 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090007/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090007/</guid><description>Podcast Description https://passionstruck.com/passion-struck-book/ - Order a copy of my new book, ”Passion Struck: Twelve Powerful Principles to Unlock Your Purpose and Ignite Your Most Intentional Life,” today! Picked by the Next Big Idea Club as a must-read for 2024.
In this episode of Passion Struck, host John interviews astronaut Dr. Mike Massimino about his extraordinary journey from a working-class kid with a dream to strapping himself into a NASA space shuttle.</description></item><item><title>How to Live Intentionally With Passion and Perseverance w/John R. Miles EP 380 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090008/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090008/</guid><description>Podcast Description https://passionstruck.com/passion-struck-book/ - Order a copy of my new book, ”Passion Struck: Twelve Powerful Principles to Unlock Your Purpose and Ignite Your Most Intentional Life,” today! Picked by the Next Big Idea Club as a must-read for 2024.
On Passion Struck, I dive deep into the potent combination of passion, perseverance, and intentionality. Join me as we unravel how these dynamic forces can profoundly shape your journey toward success and personal fulfillment.</description></item><item><title>Lee Benson on the Healthy Struggles Children Need to Succeed EP 379 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090009/</guid><description>Podcast Description https://passionstruck.com/passion-struck-book/ - Order a copy of my new book, ”Passion Struck: Twelve Powerful Principles to Unlock Your Purpose and Ignite Your Most Intentional Life,” today! Picked by the Next Big Idea Club as a must-read for 2024.
On Passion Struck, John welcomes Lee Benson, an acclaimed entrepreneur and author who shares his unique perspective on the importance of healthy struggles in children’s development and success. Benson, renowned for his books ”Your Most Important Number” and ”Value Creation Kid,” emphasizes the significance of instilling resilience and a value-creation mindset in children.</description></item><item><title>Dr. Nicole LePera on How to Be the Love You Seek EP 378 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090010/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090010/</guid><description>Podcast Description https://passionstruck.com/passion-struck-book/ - Order a copy of my new book, ”Passion Struck: Twelve Powerful Principles to Unlock Your Purpose and Ignite Your Most Intentional Life,” today! Picked by the Next Big Idea Club as a must-read for 2024.
In this insightful episode of the Passion Struck podcast, host John R. Miles is joined by Dr. Nicole LePera, a #1 New York Times bestselling author and pioneer in holistic psychology. Dr.</description></item><item><title>Matthew Weintrub on the Psychedelic Origin of Religion EP 377 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090011/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090011/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this enlightening episode of the Passion Struck podcast, host John R. Miles welcomes Matthew Weintrub, a multifaceted healer, psychedelic activist, scholar, and entrepreneur. The episode centers around Matthew’s insightful book, ”The Psychedelic Origin of Religion,” which delves into the profound and historical connection between psychedelics and shamanistic practices in various world religions.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Drew Plotkin on Learning to Survive So You Can Thrive EP 376 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s episode of Passion Struck with John R. Miles features an inspiring conversation with Emmy nominee and entrepreneur Drew Plotkin. Drew shares his extraordinary journey as detailed in his book ”Under My Skin,” where he explores the depth of his experiences, from painful past secrets to his ongoing quest for success.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Amy Morin on How You Become a Mentally Strong Couple EP 375 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090013/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090013/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, I interview Amy Morin, a renowned psychotherapist and author. We discuss Amy Morin’s new book, ”13 Things Mentally Strong Couples Don’t Do.” Morin, acclaimed for her groundbreaking work in individual mental strength, now focuses on relationship dynamics.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jerry Colonna on How Your Longing to Belong Influences Your Leadership EP 374 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090014/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090014/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this insightful episode of ”Passion Struck,” host John R. Miles engages with Jerry Colonna, CEO of Reboot and an acclaimed executive coach. They discuss his new book, ”Reunion: Leadership and the Longing to Belong,” which delves into the challenges of leadership in today’s divided world, emphasizing the importance of introspection and vulnerability.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lynn Matrisian on the Frontlines of Pancreatic Cancer – Education, Awareness, and Progress EP 373 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090015/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this heartfelt episode of the Passion Struck podcast, host John R. Miles engages in a deeply personal and timely conversation with Dr. Lynn Matrisian, the Chief Science Officer at the Pancreatic Cancer Action Network (PanCAN), in recognition of Pancreatic Cancer Awareness Day. John shares the story of his sister Carolyn’s brave fight against pancreatic cancer, a battle that mirrors the experiences of many families worldwide.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jim Kwik on Unlocking Your Best Brain and Brightest Future EP 372 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090016/</guid><description>Podcast Description https://passionstruck.com/passion-struck-book/ - Order a copy of my new book, ”Passion Struck: Twelve Powerful Principles to Unlock Your Purpose and Ignite Your Most Intentional Life,” today! Picked by the Next Big Idea Club as a must-read for 2024.
In this episode of the Passion Struck podcast, host John R. Miles welcomes cognitive performance expert Jim Kwik. Jim, renowned for his book ’Limitless,’ delves into his expanded edition, which explores breaking mental barriers and embracing learning, growth, and change.</description></item><item><title>Dr. Kate Bowler on Why There is No Cure for Being Human EP 371 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090017/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join John R. Miles on ”Passion Struck” as he converses with the inspiring Dr. Kate Bowler, a New York Times bestselling author and a beacon of hope in understanding the complexities of the human spirit. In a world that often glosses over the messiness of life with superficial platitudes, Dr. Bowler brings a raw, unfiltered perspective on dealing with life’s harshest realities.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Andrew McAfee on How the Geek Way Builds a Smarter World EP 370 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090018/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dive into the mind of Andrew McAfee, the visionary behind ’The Geek Way,’ as he discusses with John R. Miles the profound impact geek culture has on innovation and societal progress, challenging the status quo with a unique set of cultural norms.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Staff Sergeant Travis Mills on How You Bounce Back and Rise Above Adversity EP 369 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090019/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s Passion Struck podcast, host John R. Miles talks with Travis Mills, a remarkable veteran whose survival story has captured the hearts of the nation. Delve into the teachings of ’BOUNCE BACK,’ where Travis lays out 12 principles that go beyond the battlefield, providing guidance for anyone facing their darkest times and how to conquer them.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Michelle ”MACE” Curran on How to Conquer Your Upside Down Dreams EP 368 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090020/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join us as we dive into the inspirational journey of Michelle ”MACE” Curran, a Combat Veteran, former F-16 fighter pilot, and the author of Upside Down Dreams. From commanding the skies as Thunderbird #5 and #6 to inspiring others to overcome hardships and realize their dreams, Michelle’s story is a testament to the power of perseverance, determination, and grace in achievement.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rusty Shelton on How You Build Your Authority Advantage EP 367 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090021/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090021/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of the Passion Struck podcast, host John R. Miles sits down with Rusty Shelton, Chairman of Zilker Media and author of ”The Authority Advantage,” to discuss the power of personal branding.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Vanessa Bohns on the Psychology Behind Our Daily Choices EP 366 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090022/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090022/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this eye-opening episode of the Passion Struck podcast, host John R. Miles sits down with Dr. Vanessa Bohns, a renowned social psychologist and professor of organizational behavior at Cornell University’s ILR School. Together, they delve into the often-overlooked psychological aspects of choices and the consent behind them, examining how our words, actions, and presence impact others in ways we may not even realize. Vanessa is the author of ”You Have More Influence Than You Think.</description></item><item><title>Jeremy Fall on Creating a Safe Space for Mental Health EP 365 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090023/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Acclaimed entrepreneur Jeremy Fall, author of Falling Upwards, joins me on Passion Struck to discuss the importance of creating safe spaces for mental health conversations. Learn how to break the stigma and address mental health without shame, promoting a healthier, more open dialogue around this vital aspect of our well-being. Want to learn the 12 philosophies that the most successful people use to create a limitless life? Pre-order John R.</description></item><item><title>Thomas Curran on Breaking Free From the Perfection Trap EP 364 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090024/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090024/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Passion Struck, I have the pleasure of hosting Thomas Curran, a distinguished professor at the London School of Economics, as we delve into the intricacies of escaping the clutches of the perfection trap.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kara Collier on How Real-Time Glucose Monitoring Systems Can Transform Your Health EP 363 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090025/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090025/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this captivating episode of Passion Struck, I sit down with Kara Collier, Nutrisense’s esteemed co-founder and VP of Health. Together, we delve into the transformative effects of real-time data and vigilant monitoring on personal health and positive behavioral adaptations. Individuals can unlock a cascade of health benefits by honing in on glucose levels, propelling them toward optimal wellness. This conversation underscores biometrics’ pivotal role and emphasizes the vital feedback loop created by real-time data in our journey to better health.</description></item><item><title>What Is SISU? Harnessing the Finnish Art of Courage For Life w/John R. Miles EP 362 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090026/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Host John R. Miles discusses the concept of Sisu in this episode of Passion Struck. Sisu is a Finnish term that embodies determination, resilience, and courage in the face of adversity. Miles explains that sisu goes beyond survival and can be applied to personal growth, relationships, and success in life. He explores the history and significance of sisu, particularly during World War II when the Finns resisted an invading Soviet army.</description></item><item><title>Simone Stolzoff on the Amazing Art of Finding Work-Life Harmony EP 361 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090027/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 00:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090027/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this inspiring episode of the Passion Struck podcast, we have the pleasure of hosting Simone Stolzoff, a visionary author and advocate for work-life balance and career fulfillment. As the author of &amp;ldquo;The Good Enough Job,&amp;rdquo; Simone challenges conventional notions of work and identity, urging us to redefine our perspectives and pursue a balanced and fulfilling life. Want to learn the 12 philosophies that the most successful people use to create a limitless life?</description></item><item><title>Dr. Gabrielle Lyon on the 3 Keys to Being Forever Strong EP 360 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090028/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090028/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of Passion Struck, host John R. Miles welcomes Dr. Gabrielle Lyon, author of the new book ”Forever Strong.” While many associate muscles merely with physical strength or visual appeal, Dr. Lyon sheds light on the profound significance they hold. Serving as the body’s most substantial endocrine organ, muscles play a pivotal role in dictating our health’s path and the aging process.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Fading into Insignificance: The Impact of Un-Mattering in Our Interconnected Era w/John R. Miles EP 359 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090029/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090029/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of Passion Struck, host John R. Miles explores the profound effects of un-mattering and the importance of valuing every person. He delves into the emotional scars that come from lacking human connection and emphasizes the role of mattering in our social and emotional well-being. Join John as he unlocks the power of intentionality and helps listeners become the best version of themselves.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ivo Brughmans on How to Navigate the Paradoxes of Leadership EP 358 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090030/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090030/</guid><description>Podcast Description On episode 358 of Passion Struck, John R. Miles welcomes Ivo Brughmans, a renowned philosopher, management consultant, and author of ”Paradoxical Leadership.” Brughmans shares his insights on how leaders can navigate opposing approaches and conflicting viewpoints by embracing contradictions and tensions. He provides practical guidance and principles for applying paradoxical thinking in personal and professional contexts, from strategy development to talent management.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Martinus Evans on Why You Need to Set Audacious Goals EP 357 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090031/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090031/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Passion Struck, host John R. Miles interviews Martinus Evans, a man who has dedicated his life to making running a sport for everyone. Martinus’s journey began with a pivotal moment when a doctor’s warning pushed him to take charge of his destiny. Join us as we delve into Martinez’s unwavering commitment to inclusivity and empowerment. Don’t forget to subscribe and leave a five-star review to support the show!</description></item><item><title>Why We All Crave to Matter: Exploring the Power of Mattering w/John R. Miles EP 356 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090032/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090032/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of the Passion Struck podcast, I explore the profound concept of ”mattering.” Mattering refers to the deep human need to feel important and valued by others. It encompasses attention, importance, dependence, and appreciation. The episode dives into the factors that influence mattering, how it differs from other self-concepts, and its significance in various aspects of life.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Katie Horwitch on How You Shift the Narrative of Self-Talk EP 355 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090033/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090033/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of Passion Struck, I interview Katie Horwitch, the founder of WANT, Women Against Negative Talk. We dive into the topic of self-talk and how it can hold us back from reaching our full potential. Katie shares insights from her new book, ”WANT Yourself,” which provides a revolutionary approach to transforming self-talk patterns. Listeners will learn practical steps to shift negative self-talk and embrace self-love.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dr. John Delony on the 6 Choices to Build a Non-anxious Life EP 354 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090034/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you tired of feeling overwhelmed by anxiety and stress? In this episode of Passion Struck, I sit down with Dr. John Delony to discuss six daily choices people have to make to create a non-anxious life. Dr. Delony is the author of the new book ”Building a Non-Anxious Life.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rise Above: 7 Ways to Break Free From the Savior Complex w/John R. Miles EP 353 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090035/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090035/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, I’ll take you on a profound journey of self-discovery, where we’ll navigate the intricate world of the savior complex. Our aim is to gain a deeper understanding of its complexities and, more importantly, to unearth effective methods for breaking free from its grip. Together, we’ll explore seven practical and enlightening strategies that will not only unravel the intricate web of saviorism but also open the doors to healthier relationships, personal growth, and a more profound sense of empathy.</description></item><item><title>Laura Numeroff on Creating a Story of Resilience and Triumph EP 352 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090036/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ever wondered how rejection can fuel resilience, leading to an unexpected journey of success? Celebrated author Laura Numeroff takes us through her captivating trajectory in the world of writing, sharing her unique experiences, from her initial rejection to her eventual triumph, painting a stunning portrait of perseverance. Laura’s story touches not only on her creative process, but also her passion for philanthropy, offering a profound insight into the life-changing power of storytelling.</description></item><item><title>Jacob Morgan on the Vital Power of Leading with Vulnerability (Part 2) EP 351 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090037/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever pondered the elusive keys to unlocking the potential of top leaders, building unwavering trust in their teams, and gracefully navigating the turbulent tides of change? Prepare for an illuminating journey in part 2 of my interview with visionary leadership thought leader and futurist Jacob Morgan, the author of the groundbreaking book, “Leading with Vulnerability: Unlock Your Greatest Superpower to Transform Yourself, Your Team, and Your Organization.</description></item><item><title>Jacob Morgan on the Vital Power of Leading With Vulnerability (Part 1) EP 350 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090038/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090038/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this enlightening two-part episode of Passion Struck, I dive deep into leading with vulnerability and the future of work with Jacob Morgan. In part 1, Jacob and I explore strategies for upskilling and reskilling as the future of work is rapidly evolving, fostering employee well-being, designing flexible workplaces, and navigating the gig economy’s impact on talent acquisition and retention. Jacob is the author of the groundbreaking book, “Leading with Vulnerability: Unlock Your Greatest Superpower to Transform Yourself, Your Team, and Your Organization.</description></item><item><title>8 Practical Steps For How You Thrive Through Tough Times w/John R. Miles EP 349 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090039/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090039/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this compelling episode of the Passion Struck podcast, I dive deep into the art of thriving through challenging times with deliberate action. Life’s hurdles are a certainty, but how we confront them shapes our path forward. Join us as we delve into the remarkable journey of Jason C. Redman, a former U.S. Navy SEAL who not only survived but thrived despite facing severe injuries and adversity.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Arthur Smith on the Art of Intentional Storytelling EP 348 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090040/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090040/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this captivating episode of Passion Struck, I am joined by legendary TV producer Arthur Smith. We discuss his compelling memoir, ”Reach.” Throughout the interview, Arthur invites listeners into the captivating world of nonfiction television and offers a backstage pass to the remarkable story of his life and career. From rubbing shoulders with television icon Dick Clark in Hollywood to collaborating with Dwayne ”The Rock” Johnson on The Titan Games, Arthur’s anecdotes are not just entertaining but also profoundly inspiring.</description></item><item><title>Dr. Neha Sangwan on How You Heal From Spiritual Burnout EP 347 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090041/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you experiencing burnout in your life? Join us in this illuminating episode as Dr. Neha Sangwan takes us on a journey to understand and heal a different kind of burnout—spiritual burnout. Dr. Sangwan is the author of ”Powered by Me: From Burned Out to Fully Charged at Work and in Life.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Maj. Gen. Gregg F. Martin on Breaking the Stigma of Bipolar Disorder EP 346 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090042/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 06:28:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join us in this powerful episode of the Passion Struck podcast, where I sit down with an extraordinary guest, Major General Gregg F. Martin, Ph.D., US Army (Retired). In this candid conversation, Major General Martin shares his inspiring journey, from commanding troops on the battlefield to battling bipolar disorder. Discover how he overcame adversity, shattered stigma, and emerged as a beacon of hope for mental health advocacy. He is the author of ”Bipolar General: My Forever War with Mental Illness.</description></item><item><title>Robin Steinberg on Humanizing Justice Through Compassion EP 345 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090043/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090043/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Passionstruck, John R. Miles interviews Robin Steinberg, the founder and CEO of the Bail Project and author of the book The Courage of Compassion. Steinberg has been a public defender for four decades and challenges the narrative of how she can defend those people by asking a thought-provoking question: What if your entire life was defined by the worst mistake that you’ve ever made?</description></item><item><title>Arthur Brooks on the 4 Ways to Build the Life You Want EP 344 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090044/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090044/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this riveting episode of the Passion Struck podcast, I engage in a profound conversation with Arthur Brooks, a celebrated authority in happiness research and co-author, alongside Oprah Winfrey, of the groundbreaking book, ”Build the Life You Want.” Within this captivating dialogue, Brooks not only unlocks the secrets of happiness but underscores that it is a destination accessible to all.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dr. Amy Edmondson on Why Failure Is the Key to Success EP 343 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090045/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever wondered how embracing failure could become a stepping stone to growth and enlightenment? What if we told you that there’s a paradoxical concept known as ”intelligent failures” that can drive progress and personal development? Today, we journey down this path with Dr. Amy Edmondson, a distinguished professor at Harvard Business School and author of the transformative book ”Right Kind of Wrong.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Eduardo Briceño on Break Free from the Performance Paradox EP 342 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090046/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090046/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Passion Struck, host John R. Miles sits down with Eduardo Briceño, co-founder of Mindset Works and author of &amp;ldquo;The Performance Paradox.&amp;rdquo; Eduardo shares his journey from a successful career in venture capital to discovering the power of a growth mindset and intentional living. They discuss the importance of stepping back and reflecting on our highest goals, the value of embracing the learning zone, and the strategies for continuous improvement.</description></item><item><title>Todd Rogers On How You Communicate Better In The Real World EP 341 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090047/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join us for a masterclass in effective writing with Dr. Todd Rogers, Professor of Public Policy at Harvard Kennedy School. Learn how to engage readers, convey messages clearly, and make a lasting impression. Don’t miss insights from his book, ”Writing for Busy Readers: Communicate More Effectively in the Real World.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>7 Reasons Why Acts of Kindness Are More than Meets the Eye w/John R. Miles EP 340 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090048/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090048/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this thought-provoking episode, I dive into a topic that has the potential to transform lives and the world around us: acts of kindness. Join me as we journey through the science, stories, benefits, and strategies behind the profound influence of kindness on our lives.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dr. Jud Brewer on Breaking Anxiety Shackles and Rewiring Habits EP 339 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090049/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you ready to break free from anxiety’s grip and pave your way to a life of resilience and purpose? Join us in this captivating episode of Passion Struck, where host John R. Miles dives deep into the labyrinth of the human mind alongside the brilliant Dr. Jud Brewer, the author of ”Unwinding Anxiety: New Science Shows How to Break the Cycles of Worry and Fear to Heal Your Mind.</description></item><item><title>Louie Schwartzberg on the Incredible Journey of Gratitude EP 338 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090050/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090050/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of the Passion Struck podcast, John R. Miles sits down with filmmaker and storyteller Louie Schwartzberg to explore the transformative power of gratitude. They dive deep into the significance of finding awe and wonder in ordinary moments and how practicing gratitude can lead to a more fulfilling and purposeful life.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Illusion of Eternal Now: The Problem with Living in the Present w/John R. Miles EP 337 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090051/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090051/</guid><description>Podcast Description The present moment is alluring, promising freedom from worries and regrets. But what if this pursuit of ’now’ blinds us to the consequences of the future? Join me as I peel back the layers of the problem of living in the present, exposing the hidden challenges that can lead to recklessness and neglect of what lies ahead.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dr. Jill Bolte Taylor on How You Embrace Whole Brain Living EP 336 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090052/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you ready to unlock the power of your mind and live a more intentional life? Join me and special guest, author, and neuroanatomist Dr. Jill Bolte Taylor, as we explore the anatomy of choice and the four characters that drive our lives. Dr. Bolte Taylor is the author of Whole Brain Living.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jennifer B. Wallace on the Consequences of Prioritizing Achievements Over Mattering EP 335 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090053/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Discover the shocking truth about the toxic achievement culture and its impact on children’s well-being. Join author Jennifer B. Wallace as she uncovers the devastating consequences of prioritizing achievements over mattering. Jennifer is the author of the new book Never Enough: When Achievement Culture Becomes Toxic-What We Can Do About It.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Harnessing Your Superpowers:10 Ways to Excel as a Multipotentialite w/John R. Miles EP 334 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090054/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090054/</guid><description>Podcast Description What if you could excel in multiple fields, pursue diverse passions, and live a fulfilling life? In this thought-provoking podcast episode, I explore the fascinating concept of being a multipotentialite. Remember the days when you were asked, ”What do you want to be when you grow up?” Join us as we shatter the notion that a single answer defines your future. Meet the modern-day Renaissance souls who pursue an array of passions, crafting lives that are as diverse as they are fulfilling.</description></item><item><title>Jason Harris on How to Boost Your Persuasion Skills EP 333 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090055/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090055/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Passion Struck, discover how to boost your persuasion skills with Jason Harris, CEO of Mekanism and author of The Soulful Art of Persuasion. Uncover the power of storytelling, embracing positivity, the potency of gratitude, authenticity, and giving value in every interaction.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rebecca Rosen on Unveiling Your Divine Purpose EP 332 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090056/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome back, Passion Struck listeners! In this episode, we have a truly extraordinary guest who will take us on a journey to discover our divine purpose and overcome intergenerational patterns. Internationally acclaimed intuitive self-improvement advisor and psychic medium, Rebecca Rosen, shares her insights, wisdom, and practical tools to help you connect with your deepest purpose. Whether you’re searching for clarity, empowerment, or transformation, this episode is a roadmap to discovering your own version of heaven on earth.</description></item><item><title>The Six Key Steps to Bold Risk-Taking for Personal Growth w/ John R. Miles EP 331 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090057/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to another captivating episode of the Passion Struck Podcast, where we delve deep into the world of risk-taking and its pivotal role in achieving personal growth and remarkable success. Join us as we unravel the art of embracing risks, differentiate between strategic risks and poor choices, and uncover how calculated risk-taking can lead to mutually beneficial outcomes. Finally, I’ll explore six steps to effective risk-taking.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Brian Lowery on How You Discover Your Authentic Self EP 330 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090058/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to an intriguing episode of the Passion Struck podcast! Get ready to embark on an extraordinary voyage of self-discovery as we dive into the mysteries of our very being. I’m excited to introduce our guest, Social Psychologist and Stanford Professor Brian Lowery, a recognized expert in social identity and human behavior. Our conversation centers around Lowery’s latest book, Selfless: The Social Creation of “You.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dr. Caroline Leaf on Parenting for a Healthy and Strong Mind EP 329 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090059/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090059/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Passion Struck, I welcome Dr. Caroline Leaf to discuss the keys to parenting for a healthy and strong mind. We discuss Dr. Leaf’s new book How to Help Your Child Clean Up Their Mental Mess: A Guide to Building Resilience and Managing Mental Health.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Master the Art of Asking: 6 Proven Techniques for Getting What You Want w/John R. Miles EP 328 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090060/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ever missed out on something fantastic just because you didn’t ask for it? We’ve all been there! But fear not, in this thrilling episode, join me, as we unlock six proven techniques for how to master the art of asking!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cynthia Thurlow on How To Take Control of Your Health Through Intermittent Fasting EP 327 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090061/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090061/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of the Passion Struck podcast, host John R. Miles sits down with Cynthia Thurlow, a functional nutritionist and nurse practitioner, to dive into the world of intermittent fasting and its impact on overall health and wellness. Cynthia is the bestselling author of Intermittent Fasting Transformation: The 45-Day Program for Women to Lose Stubborn Weight, Improve Hormonal Health, and Slow Aging.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hitendra Wadhwa on How To Pursue Success by Letting Your True Self Shine Through in Everything You Do EP 326 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090062/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Hitendra Wadhwa, a professor at Columbia Business School and founder of the Institute for Personal Leadership, joins host John R. Miles on the Passion Struck podcast to discuss the importance of inner work and personal development in achieving success. Hitendra is the author of the new book Inner Mastery, Outer Impact: How Your Five Core Energies Hold the Key to Success.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Unlocking Your Success: The Habit Stacking Revolution w/John R. Miles EP 325 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090063/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you ready to take your personal growth to the next level? Today’s episode of the Passion Struck podcast with your host, John R. Miles, is about to reveal the secret sauce to leveling up your success through the power of habit stacking!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Andre Sólo on Unlock Your Sensitivity for Personal Growth EP 324 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090064/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090064/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a world that expects toughness, sensitive individuals often face challenges and stigma. But what if sensitivity is actually a gift? Join Andre Sólo on the Passion Struck podcast as he explores the transformative power of embracing sensitivity, leaving you with a question: Can you unlock your true potential by embracing your sensitivity, or will you continue to deny your authentic self?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Amy Finkelstein on a Bold Vision for American Healthcare Reform EP 323 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090065/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090065/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, MIT economist Amy Finkelstein challenges traditional economic thinking and proposes a complete overhaul of the U.S. healthcare system. With a thought-provoking argument for fully free, automatic, universal coverage, Finkelstein leaves us questioning the flaws in patient cost-sharing and the future of American healthcare. Tune in to the Passion Struck podcast for a conversation that will make you rethink everything you thought you knew about healthcare. Amy is the co-author with Larin Einav of the new book: We&amp;rsquo;ve Got You Covered: Rebooting American Health Care.</description></item><item><title>Julie Fleshman on How PanCAN Is Raising the Pancreatic Cancer Survival Rate EP 322 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090066/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090066/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the fight against pancreatic cancer, being your own advocate is crucial. Join host John R. Miles as he interviews Julie Fleshman, CEO of the Pancreatic Cancer Action Network (PanCAN), to uncover the challenges, breakthroughs, and life-saving strategies in treating this deadly disease.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dr. Scott Sherr on How to Improve Brain Function with Methylene Blue and Nootropics EP 321 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090067/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Unleash your limitless potential with a powerful combination of nootropics and methylene blue. Join host John R. Miles and special guest Dr. Scott Sherr as they delve into the world of cognitive enhancement and health optimization medicine. Discover the science behind the groundbreaking nootropics Blue Carnitine, Just Blue, and Trocalm, designed to optimize brain health and unlock your mental clarity. Tune in and explore the path to a sharper mind and boundless potential.</description></item><item><title>Samara Bay on How You Can Change What Power Sounds Like EP 320 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090068/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090068/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of Passion Struck, discover the power of embracing your authentic voice as speech coach Samara Bay challenges traditional notions of power and guides listeners through the journey of reclaiming what power sounds like. Samara is the author of Permission to Speak: How to Change What Power Sounds Like, Starting with You.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How Life Lessons From Sailing Lead To Success and Growth w/ John R. Miles EP 320 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090069/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sail Away to Personal and Professional Growth! Join host John R. Miles as he sets sail on a captivating journey, exploring the profound life lessons from sailing. Prepare to embark on an adventure filled with resilience, teamwork, and the art of embracing the unknown. Discover how the skills acquired on the open sea can transform your everyday life. Don’t miss this inspiring episode of Passion Struck.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dr. Anupam B. Jena on Decoding the Hidden Factors in Healthcare EP 318 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090070/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Anupam B. Jena joins host John R. Miles on the Passion Struck podcast to discuss his research on natural experiments and their impact on healthcare outcomes. Dr. Jena’s studies provide valuable insights into the effects of being a world leader on health, the consequences of playing professional football, and even the influence of birth month on ADHD diagnoses. Dr. Jena is the co-author of the new book, ”Random Acts of Medicine: The Hidden Forces That Sway Doctors, Impact Patients, and Shape Our Health.</description></item><item><title>Scott Jeffrey Miller on the Proven Guide to Great Mentorship EP 317 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090071/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Scott Jeffrey Miller, author of The Ultimate Guide to Great Mentorship, joins host John R. Miles on the Passion Struck podcast to share his valuable insights and advice for mentors and mentees. This episode is a must-listen for aspiring mentors seeking practical guidance and advice. Miller’s book and his expertise can help improve mentorship skills and enhance personal and professional development.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Emotional Mastery: Unleashing the Power of Emotion Regulation Techniques w/John R. Miles EP 316 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090072/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get ready to unlock the secrets of emotional superpowers! In this episode of the Passion Struck podcast, host John R. Miles takes you on a thrilling ride through the captivating realm of emotion regulation techniques. It’s time to level up your emotional well-being, boost your mental health, and become a relationship guru.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Charlotte Fox Weber on How To Unlock the Power of Desire EP 315 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090073/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090073/</guid><description>Podcast Description I am joined by psychotherapist Charlotte Fox Weber, who will guide us in unlocking the power of desire. Get ready to embark on a journey of self-discovery, conquering fears, and creating a future filled with fulfillment. Charlotte is a renowned psychotherapist and the author of the captivating book, ”Tell Me What You Want: A Therapist and Her Clients Explore Our 12 Deepest Desires.” So, let’s dive right in!</description></item><item><title>Christina Maslach on 6 Ways You Overcome Burnout Symptoms EP 314 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090074/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090074/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Passion Struck, I am joined by renowned burnout expert Christina Maslach who takes on the workplace’s darkest secret, exposing the six factors fueling burnout. We discuss how to overcome burnout symptoms and empower employees to reclaim their well-being and productivity. Christina is the author of, ”The Burnout Challenge.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>4 Powerful Trust-Building Exercises for Strong Teams and Relationships w/John R. Miles EP 313 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090075/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trust is the sturdy foundation that underpins our personal and professional relationships. In this episode of Passion Struck, host John R. Miles explores the science and psychology of trust and shares four powerful trust-building exercises that can transform ordinary connections into extraordinary bonds. Through practices like sharing vulnerabilities, active listening, cultivating empathy, and expressing gratitude, listeners will learn how to nurture trust and forge unbreakable alliances.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hilary Billings on the Psychology of Attention, Mastering Short-Form Video, and Personal Brand Building EP 312 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090076/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090076/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of the Passion Struck podcast, John R. Miles interviews Hilary Billings, the CEO and co-founder of Attentioneers and an expert in short-form video content. They explore the psychology of attention, personal brand building, and the power of creating compelling videos that captivate viewers.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dr. Connell Cowan and Dr. David Kipper on Overriding Brain Chemistry and Behavior Patterns EP 311 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090077/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join me on an insightful episode of the Passion Struck podcast as I engage in a captivating conversation with esteemed guests, renowned psychologist Dr. Connell Cowan and internalist Dr. David Kipper. Together, we delve into the illuminating pages of their book, Override: Discover Your Brain Type, Why You Do What You Do, and How to Do it Better. In this thought-provoking discussion, they introduce a groundbreaking theory of personality that unravels the profound impact of neurotransmitters on human behavior.</description></item><item><title>Walking the Unconventional Path: Embracing the Road Less Traveled w/John R. Miles EP310 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090078/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090078/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this thought-provoking episode of the Passion Struck podcast, host John R. Miles takes listeners on an extraordinary journey down ”The Road Less Traveled,” inspired by the iconic words of Robert Frost. Join John as he explores the remarkable life of Malala Yousafzai, the Nobel Peace Prize laureate and education activist, whose unwavering commitment to education and gender equality has reshaped the world’s perception.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kris Carr on How To Find Strength To Face Life’s Challenges EP 309 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090079/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joining me today is Kris Carr, a renowned speaker, wellness activist, and bestselling author whose life took an unforeseen turn when she faced a rare stage four cancer diagnosis at the age of 31. But the unexpected twist of her adoptive father’s battle with pancreatic cancer ignited a profound journey of emotional growth and transformation. Kris’s upcoming book, ”I’m Not a Mourning Person,” releasing on September 19, 2023, beautifully captures her experiences.</description></item><item><title>Joanna Grover on How To Use Choice Points To Alter Your Life EP 308 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090080/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you want to break free from negative thought patterns and live a fulfilling life? Are you tired of feeling stuck and unsure of how to achieve your goals? Well, I have good news for you. Our guest, Joanna Grover, is here to share the solution to help you make better decisions and reach your full potential through Functional Imagery Training. Imagine taking control of your thoughts and actions and finally achieving the life you’ve always dreamed of.</description></item><item><title>Jason Kander on the Journey to Post-traumatic Growth and Community Building EP 307 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090081/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090081/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this thought-provoking episode, Jason Kander, an Army veteran, lawyer, and former politician, joins me. We explore Kander’s personal journey through PTSD and his advocacy for seeking help in dealing with trauma. Gain valuable insights from his memoir, Invisible Storm, as he shares his experiences of reintegrating into civilian life and finding purpose through post-traumatic growth. Join us for an enlightening discussion on PTSD, resilience, and the importance of supporting our veterans.</description></item><item><title>Kristina Mänd-Lakhiani on Finding the Courage to Live Authentically EP 306 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090082/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you want to live a life that’s true to yourself, flaws and all? Are you tired of trying to fit into society’s idea of perfection? If so, I have the solution for you. Join me and special guest Kristina Mänd-Lakhiani as we explore the concept of Becoming Flawesome - embracing imperfection as a key to living an authentic life. Together, we’ll discuss how to let go of the need to be perfect and instead focus on being true to yourself.</description></item><item><title>Dr. Emily Morse on the Keys to Boosting Your Sex IQ EP 305 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090083/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you want to enhance your sexual experiences and increase your self-awareness? Have you been searching for ways to boost your sex IQ and own your pleasure? Look no further, as our guest, Dr. Emily Morse, is here to share the solution. She will provide the keys to Smart Sex so that you can achieve the desired outcome of heightened sexual satisfaction and self-awareness.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Stephanie McNeal on the Raw Truth of Influencer Culture EP 304 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090084/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join us for a fascinating and thought-provoking conversation as Stephanie McNeal, a renowned expert on influencer culture, sits down with John R. Miles. They delve deep into the unfiltered lives of influencers, pulling back the curtain on the glamorous facade and revealing the realities that lie beneath. McNeal is the author of Swipe Up for More!: Inside the Unfiltered Lives of Influencers.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sally Jenkins on How to Master Your Own Agency for Success EP 303 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090085/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 05:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090085/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a captivating episode of the Passion Struck podcast, a renowned sportswriter, Sally Jenkins shares insights from her new book, ”The Right Call.” Through her research and observations, Jenkins unveils the shared characteristics of athletes and successful individuals. Sally’s exploration reveals that greatness is not inherent but a product of continuous improvement. By embracing small steps of progress and rejecting mediocrity, she empowers readers to take charge of their lives and pursue their aspirations.</description></item><item><title>Hal Hershfield on How You Embrace Your Future Self Today EP 302 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090086/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090086/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a world where our future selves are often neglected, UCLA Andersen School of Management professor Hal Hershfield confronts the chasm between the present and the untapped potential of our future. Prepare to challenge the status quo, redefine your relationship with time, and forge a path that leads you closer to the resplendent reality you envision for yourself. The time has come to bridge the gap between who we are and who we strive to be.</description></item><item><title>Gloria Mark on the Power of Attention: Reigniting Focus and Productivity in the Digital Age EP 301 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090087/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 00:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Psychologist Gloria Mark joins me to delve into two decades of groundbreaking research on attention and discover the keys to reclaiming control in a world of endless distractions. Join us on an eye-opening journey as we explore the science behind attention, uncover the reasons for our constant distractions, and unlock the secrets to restoring balance, happiness, and unmatched productivity in our lives.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Scott Simon on How to Harness Courage for a Limitless Life EP 300 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090088/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090088/</guid><description>Podcast Description From panic attacks on a transatlantic flight to embracing the power of courage, Scott Simon’s journey took an unexpected twist that transformed his life. Discover the mantra that pushed him to face his fears and find fulfillment as we explore the inspiring story of a once-fearful child who became a courageous warrior. Scott is the author of Scare Your Soul: 7 Powerful Principles to Harness Fear and Lead Your Most Courageous Life.</description></item><item><title>Seth Godin on How You Create the Song of Significance EP 299 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090089/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Seth Godin, a world-renowned thought leader, experienced a profound moment of realization regarding the need for significance in work culture. Witnessing countless individuals around him stuck in the song of safety, their lives fueled by fear and obedience broke his heart. He knew that there had to be a better way, one that emphasizes respect, dignity, meaning, and autonomy in the workplace. This led him to develop the concept of the Song of Significance, a melody that resonates with those who seek to find meaning in their work and live their lives with purpose.</description></item><item><title>Tinx on How You Use Small Mindset Shifts for Happiness EP 298 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090090/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get ready for an empowering episode of the Passion Struck podcast as Tinx takes center stage, sharing her transformative journey to self-esteem, revealing the profound impact of perspective shifts, and emphasizing the significance of living life with unwavering integrity. Brace yourself for a heartfelt conversation that will ignite your inner fire and fuel your personal growth and ignite your passion for a life of authenticity and fulfillment. Tinx is the author of The Shift: Change Your Perspective, Not Yourself.</description></item><item><title>Rani Puranik on 7 Letters to My Daughters, Love, and Legacy EP 297 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090091/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090091/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of the Passion Struck Podcast, we have a special guest, Rani Puranik, who is a business leader, philanthropist, and author. Rani shares her insights and experiences from her new book, ”7 Letters to My Daughters,” where she explores the idea that individuals can become a new version of themselves, both internally and externally, every seven years.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Peter Singer on the Ethical Fight for Animal Liberation Now EP 296 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090092/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you want to make a tangible impact on reducing speciesism? Look no further than Peter Singer, who shares the solution for achieving a more compassionate world through the power of plant-based diets, ethics, and systemic change. Singer explains how embracing a non-speciesist lifestyle can lead to a more equitable and sustainable future for all beings on this planet. Peter Singer is the author of Animal Liberation Now: The Definitive Classic Renewed.</description></item><item><title>Fuel Your Success With the New Currency of Passion w/John R. Miles EP 295 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090093/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Passion is the new currency, and John R. Miles explores its transformative power in this episode of Passion Struck. From the stories of Maya Angelou to Sarah Blakely, discover how passion can fuel success, innovation, and personal fulfillment. Learn how passion ignites innovation, drives success, and brings unparalleled resilience. Embark on a journey to discover the transformative power of passion and unlock the path to personal growth and lasting happiness.</description></item><item><title>Dr. Scott Lyons on How You Break Free From Drama Addiction EP 294 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090094/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you tired of constantly being caught up in drama? Do you want to break free from the cycle and find true peace and fulfillment in your life? Look no further than the power of self-awareness and empathy. Join Dr. Scott Lyons as he shares his proven strategies for overcoming drama addiction and achieving profound personal growth and transformation through mindfulness and compassion. Dr. Lyons is the author of Addicted to Drama: Healing Dependency on Crisis and Chaos in Yourself and Others.</description></item><item><title>Dr. Marshall Goldsmith on How You Create An Earned Life EP 293 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090095/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090095/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this thought-provoking Passion Struck episode featuring Marshall Goldsmith, a renowned leadership coach, and best-selling author, a fundamental question is posed: Why does a life filled with continuous achievements often leave us with a sense of emptiness? Delving into ancient Buddhist wisdom, the answer becomes clear: true fulfillment and happiness stem not from merely meeting ambitious goals but from actively pursuing meaningful goals. Marshall is the author of The Earned Life: Lose Regret, Choose Fulfillment.</description></item><item><title>Master Self-Awareness by Becoming the Best Version of You w/John R. Miles EP 292 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090096/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Embark on a journey of self-discovery as host John R. Miles guides listeners through the power of introspection and personal growth, exploring the vital components of self-awareness to unlock the mysteries of the inner self.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Olatunde Sobomehin and Sam Seidel on How to Blaze Your Own Path and Make Work That Matters EP 291 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090097/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Seidel and Olatunde Sobomehin’s journey to uncover what makes creative hustlers successful took an unexpected turn when they discovered the vital role of strong values and principles. Their findings, captured in their book, offer a new perspective on achieving creative success. Keep listening to find out why.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cee McDermott on How to Transform Your Wellness Holistically EP 290 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090098/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 05:57:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gone are the days when we were resigned to our genetic fate. Thanks to advances in science, we now know that our health is largely under our control. This episode provides the tools to optimize your well-being based on your DNA and lifestyle habits. With simple and practical information, Cee McDermott, PH.D., explains how you can now regulate the expression of your genes and unlock the key to your wellness destiny.</description></item><item><title>Unlocking the Power of Curiosity: How It Drives Innovation &amp; Success w/ John R. Miles EP 289 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090099/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Unravel the evolutionary and neurological reasons behind our insatiable human curiosity and discover how cultivating this trait can lead to personal growth and success in this fascinating episode of Passion Struck.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dacher Keltner on How You Cultivate Awe and Moral Beauty in Life EP 288 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090100/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090100/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Passion Struck podcast welcomes Dacher Keltner, a professor at UC Berkeley, for a fascinating discussion on cultivating awe and moral beauty. Dacher is the author of the new book, ”Awe: The New Science of Everyday Wonder and How It Can Transform Your Life.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Terri Cole on How to Create Healthy Boundaries &amp; Inner Peace EP 287 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090101/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Terri Cole believed that achieving success as a prominent talent agent would bring her happiness, but she was in for a surprising turn of events. Through her journey of self-exploration, she decided to resign from her job, enroll in graduate school, and embark on a new path in the mental health industry. This decision enabled her to prioritize her own needs and establish healthy boundaries, leading to a more gratifying life.</description></item><item><title>How You Tame the Flames of Shameflammation w/John R. Miles EP 286 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090102/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you struggling with feelings of worthlessness, inadequacy, and shame? Feeling drained and exhausted? You may be a victim of shameflamation. Join me in exploring the physical and emotional effects of shameflamation and how to heal from the trauma that can cause it. But watch out: your journey may leave you with more questions than answers.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Will Guidara on Mastering the Art of Human Connection to Create Unreasonable Hospitality EP 285 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090103/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Little did twelve-year-old Will Guidara know that his life-changing encounter with hospitality at the Four Seasons in New York would lead him on a journey of leadership and connection, inspiring him to create unforgettable experiences for others. Through his unwavering dedication to connecting people and his passion for hospitality, Will has discovered a career that transcends mere service to creating unreasonable hospitality &amp;ndash; but what will be the ultimate outcome of his mission?</description></item><item><title>Dorie Clark on How to Create Success Playing the Long Game EP 284 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090104/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever heard these myths about long-term success? That you have to choose between a job you love and a high-paying career, that playing the long game means giving up short-term rewards, and that there is only one correct path to success. Fortunately, Dorie Clark has the truth to share with career-driven individuals who seek long-term success: How to Create Success Playing the Long Game.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>David Rubenstein on Iconic America, Patriotic Philanthropy and Leadership EP 283 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090105/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 00:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090105/</guid><description>Podcast Description From modest beginnings, David Rubenstein has pursued a unique form of philanthropy - patriotic philanthropy - to preserve ”Iconic America,” America’s iconic symbols and their stories, revealing a twist in history that has the power to foster a greater appreciation for our nation’s past. What can we learn from David’s journey, and what does the future of patriotic philanthropy hold?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dr. Julianne Holt-Lunstad on Navigating Isolation, Loneliness, and Health EP 282 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090106/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Isolation and loneliness are often interchangeable, but is one more important than the other? My guest today, Dr. Julianne Holt-Lunstad, reveals that both are essential to our health and well-being and can increase the risk of premature mortality. But what happens when one is surrounded by others and still feels lonely? Or are isolated but don’t feel lonely? Join us as we explore the complexities between psychological and social well-being and physical well-being.</description></item><item><title>Gretchen Rubin on Rediscover Joy by Intentionally Engaging the Five Senses EP 281 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090107/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090107/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Gretchen Rubin’s eye doctor warned her of the risks of losing her sight, she never expected this unexpected twist in her life&amp;ndash;an awakening that allowed her to experience the world with heightened clarity and joy. Little did she know that this moment of awareness would lead her on a journey to uncover the power of her senses and a newfound connection with the world. We discuss Rubin’s brand-new book Life in Five Senses: How Exploring the Senses Got Me Out of My Head and Into the World.</description></item><item><title>Dr. Gabriella Rosen Kellerman on Thriving in the Future of Work EP 280 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090108/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090108/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Passion Struck, I interview Gabriella Rosen Kellerman, MD, about the future of work and how professionals can successfully adapt to constant change. Kellerman, a seasoned healthcare professional and Chief Innovation Officer at BetterUp, discussed the importance of resilience, creativity, and adaptability in today’s dynamic work environments. Dr. Rosen Kellerman is the co-author with Martin Seligman of Tomorrowmind: Thriving at Work with Resilience, Creativity, and Connection―Now and in an Uncertain Future.</description></item><item><title>Cyrus Khambatta &amp; Robby Barbaro on the Plant-Based Path to Mastering Diabetes EP 279 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090109/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you want to achieve long-term health with diabetes and even reverse it? I am joined on Passion Struck by Cyrus Khambatta and Robby Barbaro, who share the solution - how to conquer diabetes with a plant-based, low-fat diet and regular physical activity - to help you do just that! We discuss their book Mastering Diabetes: The Revolutionary Method to Reverse Insulin Resistance Permanently in Type 1, Type 1.</description></item><item><title>Lori Gottlieb on Embracing Self-Compassion for a Better Life EP 278 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090110/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090110/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Passion Struck, I sit down with Lori Gottlieb, a psychotherapist and NY Times bestselling author of ”Maybe You Should Talk To Someone: A Therapist, HER Therapist, and Our Lives Revealed” to discuss self-compassion’s impact on personal development and relationship building. Gottlieb stresses the importance of examining one’s negative thoughts and beliefs, asserting that self-compassion is essential for showing empathy towards others and fostering personal growth.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Isa Watson on Why Life Beyond Likes Is Finding Authentic Joy EP 277 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090111/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090111/</guid><description>Podcast Description I am joined by Isa Watson, founder and CEO of Squad and an award-winning researcher and scientist who was named one of Inc’s 30 Under 30, as well as a Top 100 Female Entrepreneur of 2020 and one of the 100 MIT Alumni in Tech in 2021. We discuss her debut book ”Life Beyond Likes: Logging Off Your Screen and Into Your Life.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>John A. List on How to Make Good Ideas Great and Great Ideas Scale EP 276 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090112/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090112/</guid><description>Podcast Description I am joined by John A. List, a renowned experimental economist and bestselling author, who is the Kenneth C. Griffin Distinguished Service Professor in Economics at the University of Chicago and the Chief Economist at Walmart. We discuss his new book “The Voltage Effect: How to Make Good Ideas Great and Great Ideas Scale.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dr. Rhonda Patrick on Sauna Benefits to Increase Health Span EP 275 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090113/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090113/</guid><description>Podcast Description I am joined by Dr. Rhonda Patrick, a Doctor of Biomedical Science who is a renowned scientist, researcher, public speaker, and researcher. In this episode, Rhonda Patrick and I discuss the incredible benefits of regular sauna baths and their increase in popularity, as well as the crucial link between vitamins and minerals, stress, and aging.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Gaia Bernstein on How to Fix the Tech Addiction Crisis EP 274 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090114/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 01:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090114/</guid><description>Podcast Description I am joined by Gaia Bernstein, a Doctor of Judicial Science and a Doctor of Jurisprudence, who holds the positions of Technology, Privacy and Policy Professor of Law, Co-Director of the Institute for Privacy Protection, and Co-Director of the Gibbons Institute of Law Science and Technology at Seton Hall University. In this episode, Gaia Bernstein and I discuss her new book titled “Unwired: Gaining Control Over Addictive Technologies.”</description></item><item><title>Susan Magsamen on the How the Arts Transform Your Life EP 273 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090115/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090115/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Passion Struck, I am joined by Susan Magsamen, the founder of the International Arts + Mind Lab and co-founder of NeuroArts BluePrint. Our conversation revolves around her recently published book, “Your Brain on Art: How the Arts Transform Us,” which explores the latest scientific research that highlights the inherent human capacity to create and appreciate art and how it has the potential to bring about transformative changes in our lives.</description></item><item><title>Arthur C. Brooks on Finding Success, Happiness, and Purpose EP 272 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090116/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090116/</guid><description>Podcast Description I am joined by Arthur C. Brooks, an American social scientist who holds the positions of the William Henry Bloomberg Professor of the Practice of Public Leadership at the Harvard Kennedy School and Professor of Management Practice at the Harvard Business School. We discuss his #1 NY Times bestselling book titled ”From Strength to Strength: Finding Success, Happiness and Deep Purpose in the Second Half of Life.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lydia Fenet on Claim Your Confidence and Create Your Best Life EP 271 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090117/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090117/</guid><description>Podcast Description I am joined by Lydia Fenet, the ambassador of Christie’s auction house, an inspiring speaker, and a global media force, to talk about her latest book ”Claim Your Confidence: Unlock Your Superpower and Create the Life You Want.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dr. Will Cole on How to Restore Your Gut-Feelings Connection EP 270 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090118/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090118/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Will Cole, IFMCP, DNM, DC, a functional medicine practitioner, sheds light on the gut-brain connection and the correlation between our physical and emotional health during our conversation about his latest book, ”Gut Feelings: Healing the Shame-Fueled Relationship Between What You Eat and How You Feel.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Uri Gneezy on How to Create Effective Rewards Systems EP 269 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090119/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Uri Gneezy, an economics and strategy professor at the Rady School of Management at UC San Diego, joins me to discuss his new book ”Mixed Signals: How Incentives Really Work.” We explore how we can design reward systems that minimize unintended outcomes and maximize happiness, well-being, wealth, and success.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lisa Honig Buksbaum on How You Heal by Soaring Into Strength EP 268 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090120/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090120/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of Passion Struck, I’m joined by Lisa Honig Buksbaum, Founder and CEO of Soaringwords, to discuss her latest book, ”Soaring into Strength: Love Transcends Pain” and how it can support your path towards healing. As a trailblazing figure in the fields of self-improvement and positive psychology, Lisa’s leadership has inspired millions.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dr. Mike Rucker on How to Change Your Life With the Fun Habit EP 267 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090121/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Organizational psychologist Dr. Mike Rucker joins me on Passion Struck to impart his top tips for integrating fun activities into our daily routines. Drawing on scientific evidence from his book, ”The Fun Habit: How the Pursuit of Joy and Wonder Can Change Your Life,” we’ll explore the advantages of having fun and the kinds of enjoyable habits we can cultivate. Join us now as we explore why fun isn’t solely reserved for children; it’s a crucial element of adult life as well.</description></item><item><title>Charlotte Burgess-Auburn on How to Recruit Yourself to Your Cause EP 266 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090122/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090122/</guid><description>Podcast Description Charlotte Burgess-Auburn, the Director of Community at Stanford University’s world-renowned Hasso Plattner Institute of Design (the d.school), joins me on Passion Struck to discuss her book ”You Need a Manifesto: How to Craft Your Convictions and Put Them to Work.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jay Van Bavel on Why You Are the Architect of Your Identity EP 265 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090123/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090123/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the Passion Struck podcast, I have the pleasure of hosting Jay Van Bavel, the Director of the Social Identity &amp;amp; Morality Lab, Associate Professor of Psychology &amp;amp; Neural Science at New York University, and an affiliate at the Stern School of Business in Management and Organizations. During the episode, we delve into his insights in his book ”The Power of Us,” which explores the potential of shared identities to enhance performance, encourage collaboration, and facilitate social unity.</description></item><item><title>6-Time Cancer Survivor Bill Potts on How to Beat Cancer by Being Your Own Best Advocate EP 264 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090124/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Being diagnosed with cancer can be a daunting and life-altering experience for many individuals. Today, I’m interviewing my friend Bill Potts, who has been battling cancer for the past two decades. In his latest book, ”Up for the Fight,” he shares all the valuable lessons he has learned and highlights the importance of self-advocacy for those fighting cancer.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kim Campbell on How Do You Build the Courage to Lead EP 263 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090125/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, I am joined by Former fighter pilot and retired Air Force Colonel Kim Campbell, and we discuss her new book ”Flying in the Face of Fear: Lessons on Leading with Courage.” Kim provides practical and inspiring insights on leadership and decision-making during our interview.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>5 Boring Ways to Become More Self-Expressive w/ John R. Miles EP 262 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090126/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Many people perceive creativity as an elusive spark of inspiration that cannot be duplicated. However, what if I informed you that there are five boring ways to unleash your inner self-expression? Indeed, the key to creativity does not necessarily require thinking in a novel or unconventional manner. I have compiled a list of five ordinary activities that can aid you in accessing your distinctive expression and allowing it to flourish.</description></item><item><title>Dr. Amy Shah on How You Can Control Your Food Cravings EP 261 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090127/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 01:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get ready for a groundbreaking conversation about the connection between your brain, gut microbiome, and food! On today’s episode of the Passion Struck podcast, Dr. Amy Shah shares her groundbreaking insights on health and wellness. As a double board-certified doctor and nutritional expert, with degrees from Cornell, Harvard, and Columbia University, Dr. Shah is highly qualified to provide valuable information. She is also the author of the new book, ”I’m So Effing Hungry.</description></item><item><title>Steven Kotler on Peak Performance Aging, Flow, and Being Rad EP 260 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090128/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090128/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today on Passion Struck, I welcome the Flow Research Collective’s Executive Director, Steven Kotler. He is one of the top authorities on human performance and a multi-award-winning journalist. Eleven of Steven’s books have achieved bestseller status: The Art of Impossible, The Rise of Superman, Bold, and Abundance. We discuss Gnar Country: Getting Old, Remaining Rad, his most recent publication.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why a Strong Moral Compass Is Vital to Your Future Self w/John R.Miles EP 259 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090129/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090129/</guid><description>Podcast Description I get many questions from the Passion Struck community on the topic of morality. Questions like: How can I prioritize the values and principles that are most important to me and utilize them in my decision-making? What approach do I take when faced with moral dilemmas, and what factors impact my decision-making process? How do I reconcile conflicting moral beliefs or values? To what extent do my cultural, social, and personal experiences influence my moral beliefs and behavior?</description></item><item><title>Dr. Mark Hyman on the Secrets to Living Young Forever EP 258 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090130/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090130/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Passion Struck today, I have the pleasure of interviewing Dr. Mark Hyman, a prominent figure in the world of Functional Medicine with a global reputation as a leader, speaker, educator, and advocate. Dr. Hyman is the founder and director of The UltraWellness Center, as well as the Founder and Senior Advisor for the Cleveland Clinic Center for Functional Medicine. With fourteen New York Times best-selling books under his belt, he joins us to discuss his latest publication, Young Forever.</description></item><item><title>Paralympian Oksana Masters on How the Hard Parts Lead To Triumph EP 257 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090131/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Oksana Masters, the most decorated U.S. Winter Paralympian or Olympian ever, reveals on the Passion Struck Podcast that people often express their admiration for her achievements and assume it was an easy path for her. However, she explains that she faced numerous challenges along the way. She did not qualify for her first Paralympic Games and failed to make the national skiing team. In fact, she was even homeless, living in a car just before the 2014 Winter Games in Sochi, where she won silver and bronze medals for cross-country skiing.</description></item><item><title>Unleash Your Creativity: The Benefits of Creative Expression w/John R. Miles EP 256 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090132/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090132/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you experiencing the urge to express your creativity? Do you seek ways to connect with your inner artist and unleash your creativity? If the answer is yes, then it’s high time to explore creative expression’s mental, physical, and spiritual benefits. Let’s dive deep into understanding how to unleash your creativity and its benefits on Momentum Friday!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Poker Legend Annie Duke on How You Get Good at Quitting EP 255 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090133/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Annie Duke, who gained expertise in quitting from her successful career as a professional poker player on the world stage, advocates for quitting things more frequently. In our interview, she delves into the science of quitting and teaches us how to overcome our obstacles and develop the ability to quit when it’s necessary. We discuss her latest book: Quit: The Power of Knowing When to Walk Away.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Matt Higgins on How to Burn the Boats and Just Figure It Out EP 254 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090134/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090134/</guid><description>Podcast Description I welcome Matt Higgins to Passion Struck, who is co-founder and CEO of private investment firm RSE Ventures and an executive fellow at Harvard Business School, where he co-teaches the course Moving Beyond DTC. A guest shark on ABC’s Shark Tank seasons 10 and 11, he will soon star in a new spinoff, Business Hunters, also executive produced by Mark Burnett. We explore his new book Burn the Boats: Toss Plan B Overboard and Unleash Your Full Potential.</description></item><item><title>Unlock the Benefits of Joining the Exclusive 5 AM Club! w/John R. Miles EP 253 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090135/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are distractions the death of your creativity? Do you seek more persistence and consistency in your day? Do you want to take your life and career to the next level? As a regular listener to the Passion Struck podcast, you may have heard me discuss my morning routine, which involves waking up every day at 5 a.m. The reason for this is to get a head start on the day and gain a competitive advantage in life.</description></item><item><title>Stefan Falk on Why Intrinsic Motivation Is Vital to Success EP 252 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090136/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090136/</guid><description>Podcast Description I welcome Stefan Falk to Passion Struck, who is a senior executive and performance coach working with elite athletes, top executives, special operators in the armed forces, and leaders from all walks of life. We explore his new book Intrinsic Motivation: Learn to Love Your Work and Succeed as Never Before.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jaime Bronstein on How to Manifest the Love of Your Life EP 251 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090137/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you sick and weary of being single? Are you prepared to overcome obstacles, claim power, and let go of your old baggage? If so, our guest today Jaime Bronstein, who Yahoo Finance recognized as ”The Number One Relationship Coach Transforming Lives,” is here to teach you how to manifest the love of your life. Jaime is the author of the new book which launches today, ”MAN*ifesting: A Step-By-Step Guide to Attracting the Love That is Meant For You.</description></item><item><title>Why You Need to Stop Chasing Perfection in Your Life w/John R. Miles EP 250 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090138/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090138/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you constantly fear not doing things correctly? Do you strive for perfection in both your work and personal life? Does your fear of making mistakes and disappointing others drive you to push yourself excessively, making pursuing perfection a part of your daily routine? I understand the pressure you are under to be perfect. I’ve been there too. Let’s dive deep into understanding the need to be perfect and ways to stop chasing perfection in our lives here on Momentum Friday!</description></item><item><title>Captain Sandy Yawn on How to Be the Calm or Be the Storm EP 249 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090139/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today I am joined on the Pasion Struck podcast by Captain Sandy Yawn, the star of the Bravo TV hit series Below Deck Mediterranean. We discuss Captain Sandy’s new book, Be the Calm or Be the Storm: Leadership Lessons from a Woman at the Helm.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rory Vaden on How to Find Your Uniqueness and Exploit It in the Service of Others EP 248 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090140/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090140/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today I am joined on the Pasion Struck podcast by author, award-winning speaker, and personal branding expert Rory Vaden, who reveals the hidden power of finding our uniqueness and exploiting it in the service of others. Rory is the NY Times bestselling author of ”Take the Stairs: 7 Steps to Achieving True Success.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Mind-Blowing Power of the Psychological Immune System w/ John R. Miles EP 247 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090141/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 07:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever been in a challenging circumstance where it seemed like everything was going wrong? It&amp;rsquo;s not just you. Everyone has these moments, but what if we told you that you have a superpower within you that can help you get out of them? The remedy to your issues is the psychological immune system! Let’s dive deep into understanding our amazing mental immune system here on Momentum Friday!</description></item><item><title>Dr. Neeta Bhushan on How You Overcome the Suck and Find Joy in Life EP 246 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090142/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 00:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090142/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode features an interview with Dr. Neeta Bhushan, author of the soon-to-be-released book That Sucked, Now What?: How to Embrace the Joy in Chaos and Find Magic in the Mess. This how-to manual offers grace to the human experience by reassuring listeners that life may throw them a curveball now and then, but they can bounce back and even fly forward.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dr. Ethan Kross on the Hidden Power of Our Inner Voice EP 245 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090143/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 00:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090143/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today I am joined on the Pasion Struck podcast by the award-winning psychologist and author Dr. Ethan Kross, who reveals the hidden power of our inner voice and how we can harness it to live healthier, more satisfying, and more productive lives.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Stop Feeling Stuck: How to Break Free in 3 Easy Steps w/John R. Miles EP 244 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090144/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 00:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090144/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you find yourself feeling stuck? Maybe you feel like you’re not where you want to be in your life. Maybe you’re not living your passion. You may wonder what does it feel like to be stuck? What causes you to be stuck? What are strategies for breaking free from feeling stuck? How does science play into being stuck? I’ll try to find an answer to this and more here on Momentum Friday!</description></item><item><title>John U. Bacon on Leading the Way: How Everyone Can Impact a Great Team EP 243 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090145/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090145/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s Passion Struck episode, I interview John U. Bacon, the New York Times bestselling author of Let Them Lead: Unexpected Lessons in Leadership from America’s Worst High School Hockey Team. John is a highly sought-after expert on shared leadership, and this episode is a must-listen for leaders of any type.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Uri Levine on Fall in Love With the Problem, Not the Solution EP 242 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090146/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090146/</guid><description>Podcast Description I am joined today on Passion Struck by Uri Levine, co-founder of Waze and author of Fall in Love with the Problem, Not the Solution, who shares his advice for aspiring entrepreneurs.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Importance of Struggle for Your Growth w/ John R. Miles EP 241 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090147/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090147/</guid><description>Podcast Description Listeners often ask me about the importance of struggle for their growth, including how can struggling and facing challenges help them to grow and develop as a person? What are some specific ways that struggle can contribute to personal growth? Is it possible to grow and develop without experiencing struggle or adversity? How can they balance the need for struggle and growth with the need for self-care and well-being?</description></item><item><title>Jennifer Edwards and Katie McCleary on How to Bridge the Gap EP 240 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090148/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090148/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we welcome Jennifer Edwards and Katie McCleary, authors of Bridge the Gap: Breakthrough Communication Tools to Transform Work Relationships From Challenging to Collaborative. They urge us to use ”simplexity” and the psychology of human connection to promote effective communication.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Robert Waldinger on What Are the Keys to Living a Good Life EP 239 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090149/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 00:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090149/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s episode, I talk to Harvard Professor Dr. Robert Waldinger about the keys to living a good life. Dr. Waldinger is the current Director of the Harvard Study on Aging and author of the book ”The Good Life: Lessons from the World’s Longest Scientific Study of Happiness.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why We Need Hope Now More Than Ever w/ John R. Miles EP 238 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090150/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090150/</guid><description>Podcast Description Where Do You Find Real Hope in Our Chaotic World? Welcome to Momentum Friday!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bernie Marcus on Why You Have to Go For Your Strengths EP 237 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090151/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090151/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bernie Marcus is the co-founder, former CEO, and Chairman of the Home Depot. He appears on the show to talk about Kick Up Some Dust: Lessons on Thinking Big, Giving Back, and Doing It Yourself, his most recent book.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dr. Benjamin Hardy on the Psychology of Being Your Future Self Now EP 236 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090152/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 00:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090152/</guid><description>Podcast Description Organizational psychologist Benjamin Hardy is the bestselling author of books on self-control, self-limiting thoughts, cooperation, and the pursuit of happiness. He appears on the program to talk about Be Your Future Self Now: The Science of Intentional Transformation, his most recent book.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Finishing Your Year Strong — 7 Steps on How to End the Year w/John R. Miles EP 235 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090153/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090153/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s final Passion Struck episode of 2022, I talk about the significance of finishing your year strong to feel good about your progress, prepare for a prosperous new year, and pinpoint opportunities for development.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>THE POWER OF INTENTIONAL BEHAVIOR CHANGE - The Best Passion Struck Podcast Moments of 2022 EP 234 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090154/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090154/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s episode unites a world-class interdisciplinary team of academic and healthcare experts to advance the science, research, and practice of intentional behavior change, including Katy Milkman, Don Moore, Cassie Holmes, Max Bazerman, Ayelet Fishbach, Jonah Berger, Sara Mednick David Vago, Jordyn Feingold, Scott Barry Kaufman, Kara Fitzgerald, Dominic D’Agostino, Cynthia Li, and Chris Palmer.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>THE POWER OF INTENTIONAL GREATNESS - The Best Passion Struck Podcast Moments of 2022 EP 233 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090155/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090155/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s special year-end episode of the Passion Struck podcast features some of our best moments of 2022, showcasing the power of intentional greatness. You must not undervalue the effort required to change your life. There are habits to break, ideas to reconsider, and abilities to hone as you aim higher, which I explore with our guests in today’s episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How Do You Express the True Spirit of the Holidays? w/John R. Miles EP 232 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090156/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090156/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s special episode, I share how the true spirit of the holidays is all about spreading joy, love, and compassion to those around us. Whether through gift-giving, acts of kindness, or spending time with loved ones, the holiday season is a time to come together and celebrate all that is good in the world.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>James H. Belt on Creating ”All-in Hope” That Can End Poverty EP 231 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090157/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090157/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this powerful Passion Struck episode, author, speaker, and missionary, James H. Belt and I discuss his book Hope Realized: How the Power of Practical and Spiritual Development Can Diminish Poverty and Expose the Lie of Hopelessness which challenges the prevailing wisdom on poverty and offers listeners a new perspective on the global poverty crisis and how each of us can have a role to play.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>John Kim and Vanessa Bennett on How to Find Love That Lasts EP 230 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090158/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090158/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today on Passion Struck, I interview family therapists John Kim and Vanessa Bennett, who reveal the honest truth about why it’s so hard to find love and the keys to creating a lasting relationship. We discuss their new book: It’s Not Me, It’s You: Break the Blame Cycle. Relationship Better.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>7 Ways to Stop Playing the Victim to Your Circumstances w/ John R. Miles EP 229 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090159/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 00:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090159/</guid><description>Podcast Description Too often, we allow our psyche to control our lives. We become prisoners of our own minds and victims of our own circumstances. In this episode, John shares an important message about how we can recognize we are playing the victim, overcome our victim mentality, and live intentionally.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dr. Cynthia Li on Intuitive Healing Using Qigong and Ecosystem Medicine EP 228 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090160/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 00:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090160/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Cynthia Li is a leading expert in ecosystem medicine, Qigong, efficient healing, and intuition, and in this episode, she shares with you the journey to optimal health. Dr. Li takes you on a guided tour of the many facets of optimal health, from food and lifestyle choices to physical and emotional health.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dr. Jonah Berger on How the Great Catalysts Remove the Barriers to Change EP 227 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090161/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090161/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s episode, Dr. Jonah Berger, a bestselling author and University of Pennsylvania Wharton School marketing professor, shares how great catalysts remove the barriers to change. By understanding and tapping into these drivers of change, you can become more effective in your own life, career, and relationships. We discuss his latest book The Catalyst.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why Knowing When to Quit May Be the Best of All Strategies w/ John R. Miles EP 226 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090162/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 00:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090162/</guid><description>Podcast Description .In this episode, I discuss the significance of knowing when to quit vs. when to persevere. Quitting is crucial for your long-term personal development. Knowing when to leave can be the wisest choice you make, whether it’s a career that’s not satisfying you or a relationship that’s not suitable for you. Welcome to Momentum Friday!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dr. Michael Pishvaian on Why Hope Is the Key to Fighting Pancreatic Cancer EP 225 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090163/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 00:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090163/</guid><description>Podcast Description Johns Hopkins gastrointestinal oncologist Dr. Michael Pishvaian joins us with special guest host Carolyn Miles (John’s sister) to examine advances in pancreatic cancer diagnosis and treatment. They discuss why hope is the key in fighting pancreatic cancer, and this interview gives tips on finding it.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dr. Elisa Hallerman on How to Find Meaning through Soul Work EP 224 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090164/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 05:14:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090164/</guid><description>Podcast Description A former attorney and top Hollywood agent, Dr. Elisa Hallerman, pivoted her career to create the first recovery agency devoted to assisting addicts to recover from their addictions. She joins me to discuss her new book, Soulbriety: A Plan to Heal Your Trauma, Overcome Addiction, and Reconnect with Your Soul.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>8 Ways to Control Your Anger So It Doesn’t Control You w/ John R. Miles EP 223 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090165/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 00:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090165/</guid><description>Podcast Description One of the most important things you can master is controlling anger before it controls you. In this Momentum Friday episode of Passion Struck, I will share with you eight simple steps that work for everyone when it comes to controlling your anger.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Marianne Lewis and Wendy Smith on Applying Both/And Thinking to Solve Your Toughest Problems EP 222 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090166/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090166/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today I talk to Wendy K. Smith a professor of management and faculty director at the Women’s Leadership Initiative at the University of Delaware and Marianne W. Lewis the dean of Carl H. Lindner College of Business at the University of Cincinnati about the power of using both/and thinking to solve your biggest problems.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dr. Joshua Greene on Why Effective Altruism Is a Powerful Giving Multiplier EP 221 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090167/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 00:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090167/</guid><description>Podcast Description In honor of Giving Tuesday 2022, today I talk to Joshua Greene, a Professor of Psychology and a member of the Center for Brain Science faculty at Harvard University, about the power of effective altruism and the concept of the giving multiplier, which is the idea that the more people donate to highly effective charities, the more good that can be done.
To learn more and contribute, visit https://givingmultiplier.</description></item><item><title>How to Unlock the Incredible Regenerative Power of Gratitude w/John R. Miles EP 220 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090168/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090168/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s Momentum Friday episode of Passion Struck, I share with you how to unlock the regenerative power of gratitude. By understanding the power of gratitude, we can tap into the strength to heal ourselves and bring about real change in our lives. Listen and learn why the regenerative power of gratitude is the key to a satisfying and meaningful life.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dr. Sherry Walling on How to Engage With Grief and Find Hope After Loss EP 219 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090169/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090169/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today I talk to Dr. Sherry Walling (@sherrywalling), a clinical psychologist, speaker, podcaster, best-selling author, yoga teacher, and mental health advocate. Dr. Walling and I discuss her new book ”Touching Two Worlds” and how to engage with grief and find hope after loss.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Scott Galloway on Why America Is Adrift and How to Fix It EP 218 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090170/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090170/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today I talk to Scott Galloway (@profgalloway), a Professor at the NYU Stern School of Business and a Serial entrepreneur. While the current economic and social crisis in America seems complex, Galloway and I discuss how it can be fixed and examine the country’s future in his new NY Times bestselling book ”Adrift: America in 100 Charts.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>8 Highly Effective Ways to Stay Motivated w/ John R. Miles EP 217 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090171/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 00:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090171/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s Momentum Friday episode of Passion Struck, I share with you 8 highly effective ways to become and stay motivated. These tips will change your life and help you reach your goals. If you’re struggling to find the motivation to pursue your goals, this episode is for you.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dr. Chris Palmer on How Brain Energy Improves Mental Health EP 216 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090172/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090172/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today I talk to Dr. Chris Palmer (@chrispalmermd), a Harvard psychiatrist and neuroscientist researching the link between metabolism and mental health. He is an Assistant Professor of Psychiatry at Harvard Medical School and the Director of the Department of Postgraduate and Continuing Education at McLean Hospital.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Max H. Bazerman on How to Overcome Complicity and Create a More Ethical World EP 215 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090173/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090173/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today I talk to Dr. Max H. Bazerman, the Jesse Isidor Straus Professor of Business Administration at the Harvard Business School. Max and I discuss his new book, ”Complicit,” and explore the root causes of complicity, how it’s enabled and how to stop it.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What Does It Mean to Be a Person of Courage w/ John R. Miles EP 214 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090174/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090174/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s Momentum Friday episode of Passion Struck with John R. Miles, I explore what courage is and what it takes to be a person of courage. I will discuss different examples of courage and how courage is displayed in different situations.
I will explore why courage is one of the most important qualities you can have in life and how it will enable you to face your fears, doubts, and disappointments head-on and continue moving forward.</description></item><item><title>Scott DeLuzio on How to Drive on and Reclaim Your Strength EP 213 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090175/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090175/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today I talk to Scott DeLuzio about the need to drive on and reclaim your strength after experiencing hardship. Scott DeLuzio is an Army veteran who served in the CT Army National Guard as an infantryman between 2005-2011 and was deployed to Afghanistan in 2010. Scott is the author of surviving son and the host of the Drive On podcast.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jeff Struecker on the Importance of Being a Person of Your Word EP 212 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090176/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 00:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090176/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today I talk to Jeff Struecker (@jeffstruecker) about the importance of being a person of your word. Jeff is a pastor, podcaster, author, and featured keynote speaker. He enlisted in the US Army at age 18 and served for almost 23 years before retiring with the rank of Major.
Jeff was inducted into the Ranger Hall of Fame in 2017 and holds many decorations and recognitions for his military service, including the Silver Star from his service during Black Hawk Down.</description></item><item><title>9 Ways to Protect Your Success w/ John R. Miles EP 211 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090177/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 00:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090177/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s Momentum Friday episode of Passion Struck with John R. Miles, I share nine strategies to protect your success from yourself and those around you.
Find out how to stay motivated, deal with setbacks, and prevent people from taking advantage of you. My advice will help you achieve your goals and protect your success from anyone trying to stop you. Tune in to learn what you need to do to maintain success!</description></item><item><title>Juliet Funt on Why It Is Vital to Have a Minute to Think EP 210 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090178/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 00:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090178/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, we talk with Juliet Funt about the importance of having a minute to think and how it can help us achieve our goals and live our lives to the fullest. Tune in to hear her insights and recommendations!
Juliet is the author of A Minute to Think, nominated for the Next Big Idea Club curated by Malcolm Gladwell, Dan Pink, Susan Cain, and Adam Grant. She is an evangelist for freeing the potential of companies by unburdening their talent from busy work.</description></item><item><title>Robin Sharma on Why Changing the World Starts by Changing Ourselves EP 209 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090179/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090179/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today I talk to Robin Sharma (@robinsharma), a multiple-time #1 New York Times bestselling author and one of the world’s premier speakers on Leadership and Personal Mastery, named one of the World’s Top Leadership Gurus. Robin is the author of the new book The Everyday Hero Manifesto: Activate your positivity, Maximize Your Productivity, Serve the World.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Power of Forgiveness and 5 Important Ways to Forgive w/John R. Miles EP 208 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090180/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090180/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s episode, I tackle the power of forgiveness by examining it through the lens of neuroscience and psychology. I then provide 5 powerful ways to forgive. If you’re like most people, the thought of forgiving someone who has hurt you probably seems like the last thing you want to do on earth. This doesn’t make you resentful—it just makes you human.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dr. Marisa G. Franco on How to Nurture True and Deep Connections EP 207 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090181/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090181/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today I talk to Dr. Marisa G. Franco (@drmarisagfranco), a New York Times bestselling author, professor, and psychologist. She communicates the science of connection in digestible ways and is passionate about sharing research with the people it could help the most. Dr. Franco is the author of the NY Times bestseller Platonic: How the Science of Attachment Can Help You Make—and Keep—Friends as an Adult.
Purchase Platonic: https://amzn.to/3zmTZ83 (Amazon Link)</description></item><item><title>Jeremy Utley on Why Mastering Ideaflow Elevates Everything Else You Do EP 206 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090182/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 04:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090182/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeremy Utley is the Director of Executive Education at Stanford’s d.school and an Adjunct Professor at Stanford’s School of Engineering. He is the co-host of the d.school’s widely popular program, “Stanford’s Masters of Creativity.”
Let’s face it. We all strive for grand ideas, but very few truly comprehend how novel ideas are born. Innovation is not a one-time event, nor is it a sprint or a hackathon. It comes from the mastery of ideaflow, a technique that advances everything else you do.</description></item><item><title>5 Ways You Can Break Free From Digital Addiction w/John R. Miles EP 205 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090183/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090183/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s episode, I explore why smartphones are killing conversations and human-to-human connections we need to feel fulfilled. I’ll start by talking about a personal experience I had earlier today. I will then discuss why smartphones are negatively impacting our connections and provide five ways that you can break free from digital addiction.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dr. Nate Zinsser on How Do You Create a Confident Mind EP 204 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090184/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090184/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Nate Zinnser has spent his career training the minds of the U.S. Military Academy cadets as they prepare to lead and perform when the stakes are the highest—on the battlefield.
Dr. Zinsser and I discuss why NFL quarterbacks like Eli Manning can rise to the moment and achieve peak performance. Why, whether your mission involves leading a platoon into combat, returning an opponent’s serve, or delivering a sales pitch to a roomful of skeptical prospects, how you can perform best when you are so sure about your abilities that your flow of fear, doubts, and confusion slows to the barest minimum.</description></item><item><title>Dolly Chugh on How to Create a More Just Future EP 203 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090185/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 00:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090185/</guid><description>Podcast Description NYU Professor Dr. Dolly Chugh joins me on the Passion Struck podcast to discuss her new book, A More Just Future.
Purchase A More Just Future: https://amzn.to/3fZXLNY (Amazon Link)
In our interview, Dolly provides a frank yet endearing compass for ”embracing the paradox” that America was built on the idea that all people are equal. Yet it was founded on slavery. Chugh interweaves lessons on structural racism, the patriot’s dilemma, and settler colonialism.</description></item><item><title>Learning How To Be Vulnerable and 5 Steps to Build It w/John R. Miles EP 202 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090186/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 00:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090186/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s episode, I will tackle vulnerability by sharing the story of my friend who struggled with how to be vulnerable. I will discuss what being vulnerable means, why we avoid it, the benefits of being vulnerable, and five ways I have found you can build it.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Suzanne Gilberg-Lenz on Demystifying Menopause: How to Flourish as You Age EP 201 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090187/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 00:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090187/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Suzanne Gilberg-Lenz joins me on Passion Struck to discuss why she is passionate about demystifying menopause and teaching women how to flourish as they age, optimize their health, the truth about hormones, deal with hot flashes, and so much more. Suzanne Gilberg-Lenz, MD, is deeply connected to her work as an OB-GYN. She is an enthusiastic science nerd with a profound respect for holistic health and life. She earned degrees from the Southern California School of Medicine and California College of Ayurveda and completed a residency at Cedar-Sinai Medical Center in Los Angeles.</description></item><item><title>Laura Vanderkam on How to Make Time for What Matters EP 200 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090188/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090188/</guid><description>Podcast Description Laura Vanderkam joins me to discuss her new book Tranquility by Tuesday, where she lays out 9 steps to manage your productivity and time. Laura explains why we need to build the lives we want now and concrete strategies for getting more done—including having more fun. Laura Vanderkam is the author of several time management and productivity books, including her latest book, which releases today, Tranquility by Tuesday: 9 Ways to Calm the Chaos and Make Time for What Matters.</description></item><item><title>Why Personal Growth Comes on the Other Side of Pain w/John R. Miles EP 199 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090189/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 00:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090189/</guid><description>Podcast Description Often times hardship halts even the best of us in our tracks. It becomes this heavy weight that stops us from becoming our best selves. But in this episode of the Passion Struck podcast, I will explain why experiencing pain in life allows the vast, dormant power within you to awaken and express itself. I will build upon this premise by discussing my own personal journey and how I experienced pain and grew from it.</description></item><item><title>Andreas Widmer on Why Principled Entrepreneurship Creates Enduring Value EP 198 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090190/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 00:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090190/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andreas Widmer joins us on the Passion Struck podcast to discuss principled entrepreneurship and how it creates enduring value for the customer through your own excellence. Thank you InsideTracker (https://insidetracker.com/passionstruck) and Dry Farm Wines (https://www.dryfarmwines.com/passionstruck/) for sponsoring. Principled entrepreneurs unite people to their passion by creating value for their customers through inspired teams. They do this by seeing businesses as being made for people’s benefit and not the other way around.</description></item><item><title>Daniel Pink on Why the Power of Regret Can Transform Your Life EP 197 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090191/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 00:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090191/</guid><description>Podcast Description With millions of copies of his #1 New York Times bestselling big-idea books sold, a renowned TED talk that has been viewed more than thirty-eight million times, lectures around the world, and the acclaim of everyone from Fortune 500 CEOs to Oprah, Daniel H. Pink has changed the way we live by changing how we think. In today’s episode, we explore his new book, The Power of Regret.</description></item><item><title>How to Identify 12 Cognitive Biases and 6 Ways to Stop Them w/ John R. Miles EP 196 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090192/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 00:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090192/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today&amp;rsquo;s Momentum Friday episode of Passion Struck with John R. Miles, I will discuss the 12 major types of cognitive biases that exist, how they affect your thought process, and six ways to stop them so that you can create sounder day-to-day decisions. -► Get the full show notes for all resources from today&amp;rsquo;s episode: https://passionstruck.com/how-to-identify-12-cognitive-biases/ -► Want the transcript: https://johnrmiles.com/cognitive-biases-6-ways-to-minimize-them/ &amp;ndash;► Prefer to watch this episode: https://youtu.</description></item><item><title>Jessie Wisdom on How to Make Every Manager a Great Leader EP 195 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090193/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 00:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090193/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jessie Wisdom joins me on Passion Struck with John R. Miles to discuss her work at Humu to help nudge every manager into becoming a great leader. Based on Jessie&amp;rsquo;s research, she has found the difference between an engaged employee and one ready to walk out the door is their manager. Jessie Wisdom, Ph.D., is co-founder and head of People Science at Humu, a behavioral change platform that nudges people towards better working methods.</description></item><item><title>Max Bazerman and Don Moore on How to Empower Others to Make Better Choices EP 194 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090194/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 00:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090194/</guid><description>Podcast Description Max Bazerman and Don Moore join me on Passion Struck with John R. Miles to discuss their new book, Decision Leadership: Empowering Others to Make Better Choices. Max Bazerman and Don Moore helped birth behavioral economics. This book is a fresh perspective on how decisions are made through the lens of leadership. Max H. Bazerman is the Jesse Isidor Straus Professor of Business Administration at the Harvard Business School.</description></item><item><title>5 Steps to Change Your Perception and Better Your Reality w/John R. Miles EP 193 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090195/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 00:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090195/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you desire a winning mentality that takes your mindset to where it needs to be, you need to change your perception of your reality. So much of our lives are predicated on the lens through which we view life. Our perception impacts how we view, comprehend, analyze, reflect, and interact with the world around us. So many people see everything in life in a negative light. I&amp;rsquo;m really hoping that this podcast is the podcast that inspires you to implement the five steps I laid out in the episode and put them to use to change your perspective, create a winner&amp;rsquo;s mindset, and better your reality.</description></item><item><title>Douglas Rushkoff on Survival of the Richest: Don’t Believe Their Mindset EP 192 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090196/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 00:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090196/</guid><description>Podcast Description Professor and author Douglas Rushkoff (@douglasrushkoff) joins me on Passion Struck with John R. Miles to discuss how human behavior has become controlled by technology, as the &amp;ldquo;Mindset&amp;rdquo; of the obscenely wealthy is pushing us towards a world where they scale money infinitely, resulting in a fractured system with enormous wealth and income inequality. Douglas Rushkoff is a professor of media theory and digital economics at Queens/CUNY. Named one of the world’s ten most influential intellectuals by MIT, he has been exploring, celebrating, and bemoaning tech development since the early 1990s.</description></item><item><title>Rachel Hollis Shares Her Secrets to Becoming Your Best Self EP 191 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090197/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090197/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week&amp;rsquo;s episode of Passion Struck with John R. Miles, author, blogger, podcast host, and motivational speaker Rachel Hollis joins me to discuss her secrets to becoming your best self. Rachel Hollis is a three-time New York Times bestselling author with over 100 Million podcast downloads. She is known for her authenticity and optimism and uses her platform to empower and embolden fellow dreamers. Her energy and real-talk have made her one of the most sought-after motivational speakers in the world.</description></item><item><title>Does the Concept of Free Will Really Exist w/John R. Miles EP 190 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090198/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 00:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090198/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Passion Struck with John R. Miles, I tackle one of the age-old questions debated by scientists, philosophers, theologians, and neuroscientists: does the concept of free will really exist, or is our life predetermined? My aim for this episode is to spark curiosity in you and encourage conversation and deliberation on this topic. -► Get the full show notes for all resources from today&amp;rsquo;s episode: https://passionstruck.</description></item><item><title>Dandapani on How to Harness the Incredible Power of Your Mind EP 189 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090199/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 00:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090199/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dandapani joins me on Passion Struck with John R. Miles to discuss his new book, The Power of Unwavering Focus. We discuss how to harness the power of the mind and focus to overcome worry, anxiety, and fear to unlock a rewarding life. Dandapani is a Hindu priest, entrepreneur, and former monk of 10 years. A highly sought-after international speaker and leading expert on leveraging the human mind and the power of focus to create a life of purpose and joy.</description></item><item><title>Scott Barry Kaufman and Jordyn Feingold on CHOOSE GROWTH: Transcend Trauma, Fear, and Self-Doubt EP 188 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090200/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 00:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090200/</guid><description>Podcast Description Scott Barry Kaufman and Jordyn Feingold join the Passion Struck podcast to discuss their new book Chose Growth: A workbook for Transcending Trauma, Fear, and Self-Doubt. Dr. Scott Barry Kaufman, Ph.D., is a cognitive scientist and humanistic psychologist exploring the depths of human potential. He is a professor at Columbia University and director of the Center for Human Potential. Dr. Kaufman has authored ten books and is the host of The Psychology Podcast.</description></item><item><title>Seth Godin on Why We Need Systems Change to Save the Planet EP 187 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090201/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090201/</guid><description>Podcast Description Seth Godin joins the Passion Struck podcast to discuss The Carbon Almanac and why tackling climate change requires changing the system. One of the things that we need to understand about the climate crisis is that we cannot simply reduce our way out of this problem. We have a systems problem. And the system problem is very simple: carbon extracted from the ground in the form of concrete, combustion, and cows is underpriced.</description></item><item><title>Jason Feifer on Build for Tomorrow by Embracing Change EP 186 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090202/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 00:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090202/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jason Feifer (@heyfeifer) joins us to discuss how you adapt fast and embrace change so that you can build for tomorrow and future-proof your career. Jason Feifer is the editor in chief of Entrepreneur magazine, host of the Build for Tomorrow podcast, and author of Build for Tomorrow: An Action Plan for Embracing Change, Adapting Fast, and Future-Proofing Your Career. -► Purchase Build for Tomorrow: https://amzn.to/3x2kmPm (Amazon Link) -► Get the full show notes: https://passionstruck.</description></item><item><title>Dr. Cassie Holmes on Happier Hour: Being Intentional about What Matters Most EP 185 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090203/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 00:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090203/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever wondered how to make your life rich? In my interview with Dr. Cassie Holmes, we discuss step-by-step how to wisely invest your most treasured resource—time and make the most of it. Cassie Holmes is a professor at UCLA Anderson School of Management. She is the world’s leading authority on time and happiness. In her ground-breaking new book, HAPPIER HOUR: How to Beat Distraction, Expand Your Time, and Focus on What Matters, a Forbes 2022 “Must Read,”—Cassie shares her cutting-edge research guiding readers on how to immediately enrich their lives by better investing the time they have, no matter how “time poor” they feel.</description></item><item><title>Understanding the Value of Time: The Wisdom of the Stoics w John R. Miles EP 184 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090204/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090204/</guid><description>Podcast Description How much is the value of time really worth? Carl Sandburg said, “Time is the coin of your life. It is the only coin you have, and only you can determine how it will be spent.” In this Momentum Friday episode from the Passion Struck podcast, I tackle the value of time. I examine this by studying wisdom from the stoics on the topic and using ten of their mantras for managing time.</description></item><item><title>Dr. Abby Medcalf on Creating a Happy and Fulfilled Relationship EP 183 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090205/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090205/</guid><description>Podcast Description Want to create a happy, connected, and fulfilled relationship? Dr. Abby Medcalf provides straightforward, actionable strategies and tools that you can use today to make your relationships their best (including your relationship with yourself)! Dr. Abby Medcalf is a relationship maven, psychologist, author, and TEDx speaker who has helped thousands of people alter their mindset to create connection, comfort, and enjoyment in their relationships! Abby is the host of the top-rated “Relationships Made Easy” Podcast and author of the #1 Amazon best-selling book, “Be Happily Married, Even if Your Partner Won’t Do a Thing.</description></item><item><title>Dr. Dominic D’Agostino on Ketogenic Diets, Ketosis, and Metabolic Health EP 182 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090206/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 00:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090206/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Dominic (&amp;ldquo;Dom&amp;rdquo;) D&amp;rsquo;Agostino is an expert on a wide range of topics related to ketogenic diets, ketosis, metabolic health, and how to thwart chronic conditions with diet and lifestyle. Dom is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s leading experts on the ketogenic diet, studying its effects under the severe conditions of space and undersea. Additionally, Dr. D&amp;rsquo;Agostino has personally practiced the ketogenic diet for over a decade. In doing so, he brings substantial valuable personal experience along with his human and animal research.</description></item><item><title>Loneliness Is NOT a Joke. Here Are 9 Ways to Deal With It w/John R. Miles EP 181 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090207/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090207/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over the past few months, the growing chronic loneliness epidemic has come up repeatedly in my interviews on the Passion Struck podcast. Given its prevalence, I decided to devote this episode to addressing its significance. Loneliness is a human sentiment that is complicated and unique to every person. Because there isn&amp;rsquo;t a known common cause, the consequences of loneliness and its prevention can vary dramatically. Anne Hathaway did a great job articulating her feelings about loneliness in the following quote, &amp;ldquo;Loneliness is my least favorite thing about life.</description></item><item><title>Rear Admiral Danelle Barrett (Ret.) On Leading with Integrity, Humility, and Humor EP 180 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090208/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 00:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090208/</guid><description>Podcast Description After 30 years in the US Navy, retired Rear Admiral Danelle Barrett has learned a lot about effectively leading at the highest levels. She is insightful in everything that matters most if you want to learn how to lead with integrity, humility, humor, and compassion. Today, Danelle Barrett is a sought-after board director, speaker, and leadership coach. During her time as an Admiral, she served as the director of current operations at US Cyber Command and as the Navy Cyber Security Division Director and deputy chief information officer on the Chief of Naval Operations Staff.</description></item><item><title>Alan Stein Jr. on Peak Performance: How to Create It and Keep It EP 179 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090209/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 00:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090209/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our guest today is ALAN STEIN JR., who is all about what it takes to achieve and sustain PEAK PERFORMANCE. If you want to know what it takes to achieve more MENTAL TOUGHNESS in your life to give you added discipline, success, and responsibility, you will want to take notes and pay close attention. This is the LEVELING-UP episode you&amp;rsquo;ve been waiting for. Alan has been all about PRODUCING CHAMPIONS for over two decades.</description></item><item><title>8 Ways to Stop Making Excuses in Order to Unlock an Intentional Life w/ John R. Miles EP 178 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090210/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 00:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090210/</guid><description>Podcast Description John R. Miles - Eight ways to stop making excuses to unlock an intentional life. Brought to you by Indeed. Receive a $75 credit at: https://www.indeed.com/passionstruck. People often ask me, &amp;lsquo;How does making excuses impact intentional positive change in life?&amp;rsquo; In the words of Benjamin Franklin, “He that is good for making excuses is seldom good for anything else.” As cruel as that sounds, Franklin&amp;rsquo;s words are closer to reality than we think.</description></item><item><title>Ari Wallach on Unlock Your Purpose for Something Greater than Yourself EP 177 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090211/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 00:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090211/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of Passion with John R. Miles, I interview Ari Wallach about the Longpath mindset and how to unlock your purpose for something greater than yourself. | Brought to you by Indeed. Receive a $75 credit at: https://www.indeed.com/passionstruck. Ari Wallach is a futurist and the founder and Executive Director of Longpath Labs, focusing on the thinking and behaviors that will positively impact future generations. As an adjunct associate professor at Columbia University’s School of International and Public Affairs, he lectured on innovation, AI, and the future of public policy.</description></item><item><title>Ayelet Fishbach on Get It Done: Find the Fun Path to a Goal EP 176 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090212/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 00:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090212/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today&amp;rsquo;s episode of the Passion Struck podcast, I sit down with Dr. Ayelet Fishbach to discuss her new book Get It Done as well as how to find the fun path to achieving a goal. | Brought to you by Indeed. Receive a $75 credit at: https://www.indeed.com/passionstruck. Dr. Ayelet Fishbach is a behavioral science and marketing professor at the University of Chicago Booth School of Business. She was president of the Society for the Study of Motivation and continues to publish her insights into motivation research.</description></item><item><title>Rabbi Avremi Zippel on How You Find Purpose in Your Pain EP 175 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090213/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 00:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090213/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rabbi Avremi Zippel shares his story of childhood abuse and how he changed his story to one of hope, strength, and inspiration by finding purpose through his pain. For victims of any form of trauma or abuse, this is a podcast you don&amp;rsquo;t want to miss. | Brought to you by Gusto. Go to (https://www.gusto.com/passionstruck) for three months free. Rabbi Avremi Zippel is the program director at the Chabad Lubavitch of Utah.</description></item><item><title>Dr. Kara Fitzgerald on How to Become a Younger You by Reversing Your Biological Age EP 174 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090214/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 00:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090214/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Passion Struck with John R. Miles, I interview Dr. Kara Fitzgerald about her groundbreaking work in understanding how you can reverse your biological age and become a younger you. | Brought to you by Gusto. Go to (https://www.gusto.com/passionstruck) for three months free. Dr. Kara Fitzgerald, ND, IFMCP, is the first-ever recipient of the Emerging Leadership Award from the Personalized Lifestyle Medicine Institute in recognition of her work on DNA methylation.</description></item><item><title>Dr. Valerie Young on Combating Imposter Syndrome, Perfectionism, and Playing Small EP 173 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090215/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 00:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090215/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Passion Struck with John R. Miles, I interview Dr. Valerie Young about the types and causes of imposter syndrome and how you combat it. | Brought to you by Gusto (https://www.gusto.com/passionstruck) for three months free. Dr. Valerie Young is co-founder of Impostor Syndrome Institute and the leading expert on the subject. In addition to speaking at over 100 universities, she’s spoken at such diverse organizations as Google, Moody’s, Pfizer, NASA, and the National Cancer Institute.</description></item><item><title>5 Ways to Heal From the Shattering Consequences of Abuse w/ John R. Miles EP 172 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090216/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 00:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090216/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over the past several weeks, I have interviewed several guests on the Passion Struck podcast who have experienced the consequences of abuse and neglect. These include my recent interviews with Kara Robinson Chamberlain, who was kidnapped by a serial killer and sexually assaulted. Carrington Smith, who was emotionally abused and neglected for years by her parents and sexually abused while she was in college. I also interviewed Rabbi Avremi Zippel, who was sexually abused for ten years during childhood.</description></item><item><title>Colin O’Brady on How a 12-Hour Walk Can Transform Your Life EP 171 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090217/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 00:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090217/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Passion Struck with John R. Miles, I interview Colin O&amp;rsquo;Brady about his new book The 12-Hour Walk: Invest One Day, Conquer Your Mind, and Unlock Your Best Life. | Brought to you by Masterworks (https://www.masterworks.io/) promo code PASSION. Colin O’Brady is a ten-time world record-breaking explorer, speaker, entrepreneur, and mindset expert. His feats include the world’s first solo, unsupported, and fully human-powered crossing of Antarctica, speed records for the Explorers Grand Slam and the Seven Summits, and the first human-powered ocean row across the Drake Passage.</description></item><item><title>D.J. Vanas on Unleashing Your Warrior Within EP 170 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090218/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090218/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Passion Struck with John R. Miles, I interview D.J. Vanas about his new book, which launches today, The Warrior Within: Own Your Power to Serve, Fight, Protect, and Heal. | Brought to you by Masterworks (https://www.masterworks.io/) promo code PASSION. D.J. Vanas is an internationally-acclaimed speaker for Fortune 500 companies, hundreds of tribal nations, and over 7,000 audiences nationwide. An enrolled member of the Ottawa Tribe of Michigan and a former U.</description></item><item><title>Why We Fail to Take Responsibility for Our Life w/John R. Miles EP 169 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090219/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 00:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090219/</guid><description>Podcast Description People often ask me, &amp;lsquo;Why do we fail to take responsibility for our choices?&amp;rsquo; In the words of Jim Rohn, &amp;ldquo;Either you run the day, or the day runs you.&amp;rdquo; This illustrates how essential it is for us to take charge of our habits or inadvertently allow our choices to dictate our life. When we fail to act, we allow fate to control our lives instead of us owning our destiny.</description></item><item><title>Abi Morgan on the Importance of Hope, Everyday Superheroes, and the Moments of Magic EP 168 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090220/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 00:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090220/</guid><description>Podcast Description Abi Morgan - The importance of hope, the power of everyday superheroes, and the moments of magic throughout daily life. | Brought to you by ZocDoc (https://www.zocdoc.com/passionstruck). Abi Morgan is a playwright, author, and screenwriter. Her plays include Skinned, Sleeping Around, Splendour, Tiny Dynamite, Tender, Fugee, 27, Love Song, and The Mistress Contract. Her television work includes My Fragile Heart, Murder, Sex Traffic, Tsunami – The Aftermath, White Girl, Royal Wedding, Birdsong, The Hour, River, and The Split.</description></item><item><title>Kurt Wilkin On Who’s Your Mike? Addressing the Most Challenging People Decisions Holding You Back EP 167 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090221/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 00:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090221/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kurt Wilkin and I discuss his new book Who&amp;rsquo;s Your Mike?: A No-Bullsh*t Guide to the People You&amp;rsquo;ll Meet on Your Entrepreneurial Journey. | Brought to you by ZocDoc (https://www.zocdoc.com/passionstruck). Kurt Wilkin is an experienced entrepreneur and founder of Hire Better. In his debut book, Who’s Your Mike? Kurt reveals how entrepreneurs can transform their companies by minimizing hiring mistakes, investing in high potentials, and making the difficult decisions to drop dead weight from their team.</description></item><item><title>Why Average Choices Lead to Mediocre Results w/ John R. Miles EP 166 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090222/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 00:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090222/</guid><description>Podcast Description John R. Miles - Why average choices lead to mediocre results. | Brought to you by AppSumo&amp;rsquo;s application marketplace (https://social.appsumo.com/passion), Gusto&amp;rsquo;s all-in-one HR solution https://www.gusto.com/passionstruck, the Policygenius insurance comparison website (https://www.policygenius.com/), and Indeed the platform for hiring (https://www.indeed.com/passionstruck). In last week&amp;rsquo;s episode, I argued that mediocrity achieved as an end result of all our best efforts is not bad. But, it is when we intentionally practice habits that lead to being mediocre.</description></item><item><title>Kara Robinson Chamberlain on Why You Must Be Vigilant about Your Safety EP 165 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090223/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 00:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090223/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kara Robinson Chamberlain - Why you must be vigilant about your safety. | Brought to you by AppSumo&amp;rsquo;s application marketplace (https://social.appsumo.com/passion), Gusto&amp;rsquo;s all-in-one HR solution https://www.gusto.com/passionstruck, the Policygenius insurance comparison website (https://www.policygenius.com/), and Indeed the platform for hiring (https://www.indeed.com/passionstruck). Kara Robinson Chamberlain was 15 years old when she was approached by a man in her friend&amp;rsquo;s front yard in Columbia, South Carolina. At first, the gentleman appeared friendly, but then he drew a gun, shoved it against her neck, and forced Kara into the back of his car into a storage bin.</description></item><item><title>Jean Oelwang on Who and What Will You Love into Being? EP 164 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090224/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 00:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090224/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jean Oelwang and I discuss the power of partnering along with the importance of who and what you will love into being on this episode of Passion Struck with John R. Miles. Brought to you by AppSumo&amp;rsquo;s application marketplace (https://social.appsumo.com/passion), Gusto&amp;rsquo;s all-in-one HR solution (https://www.gusto.com/passionstruck), the Policygenius insurance comparison website (https://www.policygenius.com/), and Indeed the platform for hiring (https://www.indeed.com/passionstruck). Jean Oelwang is the president and founding CEO of Virgin Unite, co-founder of Plus Wonder, and a B Team Leader.</description></item><item><title>How Do You Overcome the Culture of Exceptionalism? w/ John R. Miles EP 163 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090225/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 00:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090225/</guid><description>Podcast Description So many of us struggle with a sense of inadequacy because we are immersed in a culture of exceptionalism. As a result, we will not dare even to consider being average, nor do we know how to accept it with humility. The problem is that this culture of exceptionalism threatens to turn the idea of personal excellence into an anachronism. It is teaching us that it&amp;rsquo;s terrible to be average.</description></item><item><title>Carrington Smith on Why We All Have Moments That Define Us EP 162 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090226/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 00:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090226/</guid><description>Podcast Description Carrington Smith and I discuss why we all have moments that define us on the Passion Struck podcast. Carrington Smith is a single mom, attorney, business owner, and executive search professional. In her debut best-selling memoir, Blooming, Carrington combines wit and wisdom to share her journey through the shit of life to a life bursting with joy, opportunity, and purpose.
Purchase Blooming: https://amzn.to/3P0tGdE (Amazon link) &amp;ndash;► Get the full show notes: https://passionstruck.</description></item><item><title>Dr. Sara Mednick on How to Restore, Recharge and Reinvigorate Your Brain and Body EP 161 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090227/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 00:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090227/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Sara Mednick joins me to discuss why bringing yourself to the downstate allows you to restore, recharge and reinvigorate your brain and body. Professor Sara C. Mednick is a cognitive neuroscientist at the University of California, Irvine, and the author of The Hidden Power of the Downstate which was released in April and Take a Nap! Change Your Life. She is passionate about understanding how the brain works through her research into sleep and the autonomic nervous system.</description></item><item><title>10 Benefits of Meditation for Transforming the Mind and Body w/John R. Miles EP 160 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090228/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 06:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090228/</guid><description>Podcast Description The ancient practice of meditation is as pertinent today as it was two millennia ago when it was discovered. Amid the turmoil of life, we all could use the scientific benefits of meditation which provides a simple yet effective and convenient way to relax your body, calm your mind, and find inner peace amongst the chaos. Meditation allows one to observe the mind and still our thoughts, letting the mind perform at its highest levels.</description></item><item><title>Steven Konkoly On The Lure Of Spy Thrillers, Action, And Intrigue EP 159 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090229/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090229/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nothing passes the time like a good spy thriller and Steven Konkoly is a master at creating books with action, and intrigue, and has an eye for plot intricacies. His books include Deep Sleep, The Jakarta Pandemic, Fractured State, and Hot Zone. Steven Konkoly is the Wall Street Journal, Washington Post, and repeated #1 Amazon bestseller of over twenty thriller novels. Steven graduated from the United States Naval Academy and served the next eight years on active duty, traveling the world as a naval officer assigned to various Navy and Marine Corps units.</description></item><item><title>Vice Admiral Sandy Stosz on How to Become a Leader of Moral Courage EP 158 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090230/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 00:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090230/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vice Admiral Sandy Stosz shares why the world needs leaders with the moral courage to stand strong and steady. Leaders who are capable of uniting people in support of a shared purpose. Leaders who want to make a difference by helping people become their best. Admiral Sandy Stosz served for 40 years in the US Coast Guard, including 12 years at sea. Her career was filled with leadership lessons gleaned while breaking ice and breaking glass as the first woman to command an icebreaker on the Great Lakes and to lead a US armed forces service academy.</description></item><item><title>The Reverse Aging Effect: How to Stay Young and Healthy with John R. Miles EP 157 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090231/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090231/</guid><description>Podcast Description John R. Miles - The Reverse Aging Effect: How to Stay Young and Healthy | Brought to you by AppSumo (https://social.appsumo.com/passion) and Gusto (https://www.gusto.com/passionstruck.) New research indicates that Ponce de Leon&amp;rsquo;s much-hoped-for Fountain of Youth may be closer to reality than we imagined. And, that, my friends, is no science fiction. However, You don&amp;rsquo;t have to imagine or hope for a mythical fountain of youth that holds the secret of reverse aging.</description></item><item><title>Elise Micheals on How to Gain Back the Power of Being a Man EP 156 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090232/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 00:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090232/</guid><description>Podcast Description Elise Micheals - How to gain back the power of being a man. | Brought to you by AppSumo (https://social.appsumo.com/passion) and Gusto (https://www.gusto.com/passionstruck.) Elise Micheals is a trauma-informed Men&amp;rsquo;s Mental Health coach who helps men find purpose and passion again by healing subconscious trauma. Originally a coach for women, she has dedicated her practice specifically to helping men after realizing their lack of support in the mental health space and has been doing it ever since.</description></item><item><title>Katy Milkman on Creating Lasting Behavior Change for Good EP 155 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090233/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090233/</guid><description>Podcast Description Katy Milkman - Creating Lasting Behavior Change for Good. | | Brought to you by AppSumo (https://social.appsumo.com/passion) and Gusto (https://www.gusto.com/passionstruck.) Dr. Katy Milkman is the James G. Dinan Endowed Chair at The Wharton School of the University of Pennsylvania, host of Charles Schwab’s popular behavioral economics podcast Choiceology, and the former president of the International Society for Judgment and Decision Making. She is also the co-founder and co-director of the Behavior Change for Good Initiative, a research center with the mission of advancing the science of lasting behavior change.</description></item><item><title>What Is Unconditional Love and the 8 Ways to Create It w/John R. Miles EP 154 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090234/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 08:03:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090234/</guid><description>Podcast Description John R. Miles - What Is Unconditional Love and the 8 Ways to Create It. | Brought to you by Zocdoc. Go to https://www.zocdoc.com/passionstruck and download the Zocdoc app for FREE. Then start your search for a top-rated doctor today. What is unconditional love? Unconditional love does not mean endless or boundless love. It means, “I choose to love you willingly without limitation.” This means that when we offer love, we supply it without anticipating anything in exchange for it.</description></item><item><title>Erin Diehl on Why Every Day of Our Lives Is an Improv Scene EP 153 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090235/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090235/</guid><description>Podcast Description Erin Diehl - Why every day of our lives is an improv scene. Brought to you by Zocdoc. Go to https://www.zocdoc.com/passionstruck and download the Zocdoc app for FREE. Then start your search for a top-rated doctor today. Erin “Big” Diehl is a Business Improv Edutainer, Failfluencer, and Professional Zoombie. Through a series of unrelated dares, Erin created improve it!, a unique professional development company that pushes others to laugh, learn, play, and grow.</description></item><item><title>David Yaden on Self-Transcendence, Psychedelics, and Behavior Change EP 152 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090236/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090236/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Yaden - Self-Transcendence, Psychedelics, and Behavior Change | Brought to you by Zocdoc. Go to https://www.zocdoc.com/passionstruck and download the Zocdoc app for FREE. Then start your search for a top-rated doctor today. &amp;ndash;►Purchase David&amp;rsquo;s book The Varieties of Spiritual Experiences: 21st Century Research and Perspectives with Oxford University Press: https://amzn.to/3n3BXkN David B. Yaden, Ph.D. obtained his Ph.D. at the University of Pennsylvania and is currently an Assistant Professor at Johns Hopkins University School of Medicine.</description></item><item><title>6 Ways Patience Is an Important Virtue and How You Build It w/John R. Miles EP 151 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090237/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090237/</guid><description>Podcast Description John R. Miles - Six Ways Patience Is an Important Virtue and How to Build It. | Brought to you by Masterworks. Go to https://www.masterworks.io/ and use code passion to start. Today, we live in a fast-paced world where we desire results at the speed of thought. We consume our fast foods, get our groceries and meals delivered to our house, drive our fast cars, and respond to the constant instant messaging, all of which can make us prone to impatience.</description></item><item><title>Jesse Gould on Saving Veterans One Heroic Heart at a Time EP 150 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090238/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090238/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jesse Gould - Saving veterans one heroic heart at a time through the use of psychedelic therapies. Brought to you by Masterworks. Go to https://www.masterworks.io/ and use code passion to start. Jesse Gould is a pioneer in psychedelic therapies. As a former Army Ranger and founder of the Heroic Hearts Project, he has spearheaded the research and acceptance of ayahuasca, ibogaine, ketamine, and psilocybin therapy programs for military veterans.</description></item><item><title>Cathy Heller on How Do You Find Your Life’s Passion EP 149 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090239/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 00:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090239/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cathy Heller - How Do You Find Your Life&amp;rsquo;s Passion. | Brought to you by Masterworks. Go to https://www.masterworks.io/ and use code passion to start. &amp;ndash;►Purchase Cathy&amp;rsquo;s Book: Don&amp;rsquo;t Quit Your Day Job Cathy Heller (@cathy.heller) is a bundle of inspiration and energy. She hosts the popular podcast The Cathy Heller Show, which has over 30 million downloads. She has interviewed everyone from Tony Robbins to Deepak Chopra to Malcolm Gladwell.</description></item><item><title>Why Life Is About The Journey Not The Destination w/John R. Miles EP 148 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090240/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 00:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090240/</guid><description>Podcast Description John R. Miles - Why Life Is About The Journey Not The Destination | Brought to you by BABBEL. Save up to 60 % off your subscription when you go to https://babbel.com/PASSIONSTRUCK. If you discovered this episode of Passion Struck, you are likely on the path of self-discovery and seeking knowledge on how to do it. You are not alone. Often we focus so much on the desired end-state of our goals that we miss the essential part—our journey to achieving your aspirations.</description></item><item><title>Dr. Scott Sherr on His Integrative Approach to Hyperbaric Oxygen Therapy, Nootropics, and Peak Performance EP 147 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090241/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 00:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090241/</guid><description>Podcast Description Scott Sherr - Integrated Medicine, Nootropics, Hyperbaric Oxygen Therapy, and Peak Performance. | Brought to you by BABBEL. Save up to 60 % off your subscription when you go to https://babbel.com/PASSIONSTRUCK. Dr. Scott Sherr is an Internal Medicine Physician Certified in Hyperbaric Oxygen Therapy (HBOT) and Health Optimization Medicine (HOMe). Dr. Scott is the founder of Integrative HBOT and is one of the few providers in the world who uses an integrative approach to HBOT.</description></item><item><title>Michael Slepian on the Secret Life of Secrets: How Do We Trust Others With Our Secrets EP 146 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090242/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 00:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090242/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michael Slepian - The Secret Life of Secrets: How Do We Trust Others With Our Secrets | Brought to you by Babbel - https://babbel.com/passionstruck. Who is Michael Slepian? Michael Slepian Ph.D. is the Sanford C. Bernstein &amp;amp; Co. Associate Professor of Leadership and Ethics at Columbia University. A recipient of the Rising Star Award from the Association for Psychological Science, he is the leading expert on the psychology of secrets.</description></item><item><title>Why Your Micro Choices Determine Your Life w/ John R. Miles EP 145 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090243/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 00:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090243/</guid><description>Podcast Description John R. Miles - why by using the power of micro choices, you can change your life | Brought to you by Masterworks - Go to https://www.masterworks.io/ and use code passion to start your journey. If you found this podcast episode, you are likely searching for how to make changes to how you are living your life. And, you may wonder if it is even possible to change. As I explain on the podcast, yes—creating positive change is always possible if you are intentional about it.</description></item><item><title>Sarah Fay on Pathological: The Dangers of Overidentifying With a Mental Health Diagnosis EP 144 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090244/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090244/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sarah Fay discusses her new book Pathological and how, by researching her six misdiagnoses, she concluded that the Diagnostic and Statistical Manual (DSM) is utterly inaccurate. | Brought to you by Masterworks (https://masterworks.io use code PASSION to start your journey). Sarah Fay (Ph.D., MFA) writes for many publications, including The New York Times, The Atlantic, Time, and The Paris Review. She&amp;rsquo;s the recipient of the Hopwood Award for Literature and grants and fellowships from Yaddo, the Mellon Foundation, and the MacDowell Colony.</description></item><item><title>Tricia Manning on How to Lead With Heart and Leave a Legacy EP 143 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090245/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090245/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tricia Manning - How to lead with heart and leave a legacy. | Brought to you by Masterworks (https://masterworks.io use code passion to start). Tricia Manning (@tricia_whitecapcoaching) is an author, certified coach, and former global business leader having reached the c-suite as only one of two female executives at the table. After facing an unexpected health crisis in 2016, Tricia made the difficult decision to end her 25-year corporate career but wasn&amp;rsquo;t ready to stop helping others.</description></item><item><title>Why You Must Feel to Heal w/ John R. Miles Episode 142 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090246/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 00:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090246/</guid><description>Podcast Description John R. Miles - why you must feel to heal and 6 ways you can do it. | Brought to you by Babbel (https://babbel.com/passionstruck) for up to 60% off. If you found this podcast, you are likely searching for how to heal your emotional pain of some sort. You may wonder how it is even possible. As I explain in the episode, yes—emotional healing is always possible if we make the deliberate choice to tackle our pain.</description></item><item><title>Kegan Gill on Not Just Surviving but Thriving Again in Life EP 141 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090247/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 00:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090247/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kegan Gill on not just surviving but thriving again in life | Brought to you by Babbel (https://babbel.com/passionstruck) for up to 60% off. This is one of the most mind-altering, jaw-dropping, and inspiring episodes I&amp;rsquo;ve ever released, and I really appreciate Kegan for being so vulnerable. Kegan “SMurF” Gill is a former US Navy F/A-18E strike fighter pilot. He endured the fastest survived ejection in the history of naval aviation.</description></item><item><title>Admiral James Stavridis on the Bold Decision to Risk It All EP 140 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090248/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090248/</guid><description>Podcast Description Admiral James Stavridis - The Bold Decision To Risk It All. | Brought to you by Babbel (https://babbel.com/passionstruck Admiral James Stavridis, USN (Ret.) spent more than thirty years in the U. S. Navy, rising to the rank of four-star admiral. He was Supreme Allied Commander at NATO and previously commanded U. S. Southern Command, overseeing military operations through Latin America. He holds a Ph. D. from the Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy at Tufts University, where he recently served five years as dean.</description></item><item><title>Why We Become What We Think About w/ John R. Miles EP 139 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090249/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 00:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090249/</guid><description>Podcast Description John R. Miles - Why we become what we think about and seven ways you can build positive beliefs | Brought to you by Masterworks (https://www.masterworks.io/ code passion) Notable American radio speaker and author Earl Nightingale once said, “We become what we think about.” This truthful statement embodies and emphasizes just how vital our mindsets and beliefs are to creating the lives we live. &amp;ndash; ► Full show notes: https://passionstruck.</description></item><item><title>Chrystal Rose on Why a Life Without Passion Is Like a Life Without Air EP 138 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090250/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 01:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090250/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chrystal Rose on why a life without passion is like a life without air | Brought to you by Masterworks (https://www.masterworks.io/ code passion) Chrystal Rose is a serial entrepreneur, transformative coach for high achievers, and the host of two podcasts, Self Love for Breakfast and Breathwork Bestie. She is dedicated to helping business owners, coaches and corporate rockstars shift from a place of hustle to living their dream life.</description></item><item><title>Jordan Harbinger on Why Building Your Legacy Is Greater Than Currency EP 137 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090251/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090251/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jordan Harbinger on Why Building Your Legacy Is Greater Than Currency | Brought to you by Masterworks (https://www.masterworks.io/ code passion) Jordan Harbinger is a Wall Street lawyer turned podcast interviewer with an approachable style and knack for securing high-profile guests. His podcast, The Jordan Harbinger Show, was selected as part of Apple’s “Best of 2018.” &amp;ndash; ► Full show notes: https://passionstruck.com/jordan-harbinger-on-why-building-your-legacy-is-greater-than-currency/ &amp;ndash; ► Subscribe to My YouTube Channel Here: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Why Your Brain Dictates Your Reality and 5 Ways to Boost It w/ John R. Miles EP 136 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090252/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 03:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090252/</guid><description>Podcast Description John R. Miles - How to build the brain you cherish. | Brought to you by Trade Coffee (https://drinktrade.com/passionstruck) and Babbel (https://babbel.com/passionstruck). In today&amp;rsquo;s episode of the Passion Struck Podcast, I will be providing you with in-depth information on the fascinating organ we call the brain through the amazing story of Phineas Gage. I will educate you on how vital your brain health is to your reality and experience of life.</description></item><item><title>Dr. Michelle Segar on Why We Need to Shift to the Joy Choice EP 135 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090253/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 03:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090253/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Michelle Segar - Why we need to shift to the JOY CHOICE. | Brought to you by Trade Coffee (https://drinktrade.com/passionstruck) and Babbel (https://babbel.com/passionstruck). Dr. Michelle Segar is an award-winning, NIH-funded sustainable behavior change researcher at the University of Michigan and a lifestyle coach. She is the author of the best-selling book No Sweat: How the Simple Science of Motivation Can Bring You a Lifetime of Fitness. For nearly three decades, she has pioneered methods to create sustainable healthy behavior change that is being used to boost patient health, employee well-being, and gym membership retention.</description></item><item><title>Gretchen Rubin on the Key to Happiness Is Knowing Yourself EP 134 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090254/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 06:03:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090254/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gretchen Rubin - The Key to Happiness Is Knowing Yourself | Brought to you by Babbel (https://babbel.com/passionstruck and Trade Coffee (https://drinktrade.com/passionstruck). Gretchen Rubin is an expert on understanding human nature and being able to explain complex emotional topics in easy-to-digest ways. She is the author of the New York Times bestsellers, The Happiness Project, Better Than Before, Outer Order Inner Calm, and Happier at Home. Gretchen has an enormous readership, both in print and online, and her books have sold almost three and a half million copies worldwide, in more than thirty languages.</description></item><item><title>Why Self-Acceptance Is the KEY to Creating Your BEST LIFE with John R. Miles EP 133 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090255/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 04:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090255/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why Self-Acceptance is the Key to Creating Your Best Life. Sam Berns&amp;rsquo;s inspirational story and what we can learn from his courageous life. | Brought to you by Masterworks (https://masterworks.io use code passion to start). Self-acceptance entails ultimately valuing all parts of yourself — both the desirable and undesirable. It means you understand your current reality, come to terms with it, and aspire to live your life as best as possible.</description></item><item><title>Anne O’Neil on Why Life Like Sports Is a Strategy by Design EP 132 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090256/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 05:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090256/</guid><description>Podcast Description Anne O&amp;rsquo;Neil (@heyanneoneil) on our life like sports is a strategy by design. | Brought to you by Masterworks (https://masterworks.io/ - use code passion to start). Anne O’Neil is a former WNBA player for the Sacramento Monarchs and a Division 1 Academic and Athletic All-American at Iowa State University where she played for Bill Fennelly. She broke the Iowa High School State scoring record and was later inducted into the Iowa Girls Basketball Hall of Fame.</description></item><item><title>Nicole Stott on Back to Earth: Combining the Awe and Wonder of Space Exploration with the Healing Power of Art EP 131 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090257/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 03:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090257/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nicole Stott on back to earth: combining the awe and wonder of space exploration with the healing power of art. | Brought to you by Masterworks (https://www.masterworks.io/ code passion). Nicole is an astronaut, aquanaut, artist, mom, and now author of her first book &amp;ldquo;Back to Earth ~ What Life In Space Taught Me About Our Home Planet - And Our Mission To Protect It.&amp;rdquo; She creatively combines the awe and wonder of her spaceflight experience with her artwork to inspire everyone&amp;rsquo;s appreciation of our role as crewmates here on Spaceship Earth.</description></item><item><title>How Do You STOP Living in Fear and Letting It CONTROL You? with John R. Miles EP 130 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090258/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 03:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090258/</guid><description>Podcast Description John R. Miles - How do you stop living in fear and letting it control you. Fears are not just passively forgotten, they must be actively unlearned. Brought to you by Raycon (https://buyraycon.com/passionstruck) and Athletic Greens (https://athleticgreens.com/passionstruck). The Neuroscience Behind Fear We need to realize that fear is just an emotion that is utterly dependent on our thoughts at the end of the day. It does not have to control our lives and can be effectively unlearned.</description></item><item><title>Laurie Singer on You’re Not Crazy: There is Hope for Those Experiencing Anxiety, Obsessions, or Fetishes EP 129 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090259/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 03:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090259/</guid><description>Podcast Description Laurie Singer - You&amp;rsquo;re Not Crazy: There is hope for those experiencing anxiety, obsessions, or fetishes. | Brought to you by Raycon (https://buyraycon.com/passionstruck) and Athletic Greens (https://athleticgreens.com/passionstruck). Laurie Singer is a board-certified licensed marriage and family therapist in applied behavior analysis. Motivated by the tragic death of her son in the late 80s, she devoted her life to the field of mental health. She started her own company to create a team approach for helping individuals resolve behavioral and other mental health issues by applying behavioral and cognitive-behavioral therapy.</description></item><item><title>Liz Fosslien on Big Feelings: How to Be Okay When Things Are Not Okay EP 128 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090260/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 03:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090260/</guid><description>Podcast Description Liz Fosslien - Big Feelings: how to be okay when things are not okay. | Brought to you by Raycon (https://buyraycon.com/passionstruck) and Athletic Greens (https://athleticgreens.com/passionstruck). Liz is an expert on how to make work better and the co-author (Mollie West Duffy) and illustrator of the books Big Feelings and No Hard Feelings. Liz also leads content and communications at Humu, a company that uses behavioral science to make it easy for leaders and their teams to improve.</description></item><item><title>What is Learned Helplessness and Six Ways You Can Unlearn It? with John R. Miles EP 127 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090261/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 03:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090261/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do you go from learned helplessness to learned optimism? Six ways you can unlearn learned helplessness. | Brought to you by Athletic Greens (https://athleticgreens.com/passionstruck) and Trade Coffee Company ((https://drinktrade.com/passionstruck). What Is Learned Helplessness and How Do You Overcome It? In this episode of Passion Struck, I discuss learned helplessness psychology, unravel why we learn helplessness, the consequences of it in our lives, and provide six steps through which you can break free from its hold and become your true self via learned optimism.</description></item><item><title>Kate Gilman Williams on Why Advocacy has No Age Limits and Anyone Can Make a Difference EP 126 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090262/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 03:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090262/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kate Gilman Williams — How kids can save animals, why advocacy has no age limit and anyone can make a difference. | Brought to you by Trade Coffee (https://drinktrade.com/passionstruck). Kate is the Founder of Kids Can Save Animals, Founder of Club 15 – an extension of Project 15 from Microsoft, and Author! She launched Kids Can Save Animals to connect her generation with world-renowned conservation organizations, technologists, policymakers, and global leaders who work to save wildlife and wild spaces.</description></item><item><title>Podcast Hall of Famer Rob Greenlee on the Future of Podcasts and Growth Trends | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090263/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 03:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090263/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rob Greenlee on the current state and the future of podcasting and podcast trends to pay attention to (2022 and beyond). | Brought to you by Trade Coffee (https://drinktrade.com/passionstruck). Today’s guest is Podcast Hall of Famer Robert Greenlee. Rob is the VP of Content and Partnerships at Libsyn (LSYN). He is a current Board Member and Former Chair of The Podcast Academy. He started on radio in 1999 and then podcasting in 2004 with the first nationally syndicated radio show &amp;ldquo;WebTalk World Radio Show&amp;rdquo; to begin podcasting.</description></item><item><title>Nine Simple Ways to Find Your Balance and Get Your Life Back with John R. Miles EP 124 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090264/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 03:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090264/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do you live with a proper work-life balance? In this episode of Passion Struck with John R. miles, I will discuss 9 simple ways to find your balance and get your life back. | Brought to you by Babbel (https://babbel.com/passionstruck). Finding a balanced life helps you improve your overall health. When you have balance, you have time to pay attention to your body&amp;rsquo;s needs. You can prioritize things like diet, exercise, and meditation instead of regretting that you never have time to take care of yourself.</description></item><item><title>Dr. David Vago on Self Transcendence – How to Experience Personal Growth and Awakening Through Meditation and Meta Awareness | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090265/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 03:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090265/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. David Vago on self-transcendence - how to experience personal growth and awakening through meditation and meta-awareness | Brought to you by Babbel (https://babbel.com/passionstruck). David Vago, Ph.D., is on a mission to alleviate suffering and improve well-being through investigating connections between the mind, brain, and body. He is a Research Associate Professor and Director of the Contemplative Neuroscience and Mind-Body Research Laboratory in the Department of Psychology at Vanderbilt University.</description></item><item><title>The Science of Learning: What is it and How does it Work? EP 122 with John R. Miles | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090266/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 03:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090266/</guid><description>Podcast Description We all learn differently and understanding the science of learning helps us all uniquely learn better. And the more we know, the easier it is to learn and understand new things regardless of your profession. | Brought to you by Grammarly (https://grammarly.com/passionstruck) and Raycon (https://buyraycon.com/passionstruck). The science of learning is the ongoing process of information retention over time. Because our memory makes up the very framework through which we make sense of and take action within the present, its importance goes without saying.</description></item><item><title>Susan Cain on: Bittersweet, the Happiness of the Melancholy, and How Sorrow Creates the Union Between Souls EP 121 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090267/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 03:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090267/</guid><description>Podcast Description Susan Cain — Bittersweet, the Happiness of the Melancholy, How Sorrow Creates the Union Between Souls | Brought to you by Grammarly and Raycon. Susan Cain is one of my favorite authors and completely changed the way I viewed myself and my own strengths. Susan is the author of the Quiet Journal, Quiet Power: The Secret Strengths of Introverts, and Quiet: The Power of Introverts in a World That Can’t Stop Talking, which spent eight years on The New York Times bestseller list, and has been translated into 40 languages.</description></item><item><title>How Do You Create Your Own Success? EP 120 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090268/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 03:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090268/</guid><description>Podcast Description All around us, people talk about success all the time and the repercussions of what it is and how it is achieved weigh heavily in society today. These definitions are thrust on us by how others perceive our success and how we define it for ourselves. As I&amp;rsquo;ve discussed in previous episodes, many people define success in materialistic ways such as earning a degree, buying a house, a car, or a yacht.</description></item><item><title>Dr. Jannell MacAulay On: How to Create a Mindset of Winning EP 119 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090269/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 04:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090269/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Jannell MacAulay is a pilot, commander, special operations consultant, international diplomat, TEDx speaker, and professional instructor. She is a combat veteran with 20 years of experience in the US Air Force. Dr. MacAulay was the first leader to introduce mindfulness as a proactive performance strategy within the United States military. About Today&amp;rsquo;s Episode with Dr. Jannell MacAulay I sit down with Jannell to discuss her decision to go to the Air Force Academy.</description></item><item><title>Why is Empathy Vital to Creating a Passion Struck Life? EP 118 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090270/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090270/</guid><description>Podcast Description President Barack Obama said, “The biggest problem we have in our society and the world right now is a lack of empathy. We are in great need of people being able to stand in somebody else’s shoes and see the world through their eyes.” The gap that President Obama alludes to is only growing more expansive as we continually become a society consumed by self-gratitude instead of focusing on ending the suffering of others.</description></item><item><title>Rear Admiral Tim Gallaudet USN (Ret.) On: The Keys to Leading in Turbulent Times EP 117 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090271/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 03:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090271/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Honorable Tim Gallaudet, Ph.D., Rear Admiral, U.S. Navy (Ret), is the CEO of Ocean STL Consulting, LLC. Gallaudet served as the Acting Under Secretary of Commerce for Oceans and Atmosphere/NOAA Administrator and before that Assistant Secretary of Commerce for Oceans and Atmosphere/Deputy NOAA Administrator. Prior to NOAA, Admiral Gallaudet served for 32 years in the U.S. Navy, completing his career as the Oceanographer of the Navy. He was the American Blue Economy Podcast host from 2017 to 2021.</description></item><item><title>What is the Key to Healthy Esteem? EP 116 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090272/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 03:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090272/</guid><description>Podcast Description At some point in our lives, we&amp;rsquo;ve all had times when we felt inadequate and imperfect about ourselves, whether due to a physical flaw or how we perceive ourselves. And the majority of the things we are doing to try to raise our self-esteem are entirely incorrect. However, by recognizing that we always have the freedom and power to choose how situations in life will affect us, we can rise above challenges and build healthy esteem and self-love for ourselves.</description></item><item><title>Kate Eckman On: You Are Powerful Enough EP 115 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090273/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 03:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090273/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kate Eckman is a keynote speaker, author, leadership development, and performance coach. Kate has interviewed some of the world&amp;rsquo;s most prominent newsmakers as a broadcast journalist, from President Barack Obama to Angelina Jolie; serving as the face of multiple global beauty brands as a TV presenter and personality, and working for some of the biggest names in the fashion industry as a professional model. Her book, The Full Spirit Workout, has garnered widespread accolades and is available at all major booksellers.</description></item><item><title>The Science and Traits that Promote Curiosity - John R. Miles EP 114 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090274/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 03:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090274/</guid><description>Podcast Description The majority of the novel discoveries and incredible innovations throughout history, from the printing press to airplanes to landing on the moon, all have something in common: They are the result of curiosity. The instinct to pursue new knowledge and adventures and explore untried possibilities is a fundamental human characteristic vital to our personal development. When our curiosity is activated, we think more profoundly and rationally about decisions and develop more creative solutions.</description></item><item><title>Hannah Ranfranz On: Leading By The Dreams In Your Heart EP 113 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090275/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090275/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hannah Ranfranz is an IFBB professional bikini competitor and Olympian. She coaches lifestyle and competition preparation online and trains clients in person via team infinity. John R Miles sits down with Hannah on the passion-struck podcast to discuss how she lets her heart shine on the biggest stage in the world with the women she has looked up to since the beginning. Her secrets to bringing her personal best, having fun, and making memories that will last her a lifetime with my friends &amp;amp; family!</description></item><item><title>The Key to Enjoying a Rewarding Life is Shared Experiences EP 112 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090276/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 03:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090276/</guid><description>Podcast Description Noel Gallager said, &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t live to work; I work to live.&amp;rdquo; I first heard this expression when I was living in Spain, and a Spanish friend told me that, &amp;ldquo;you Americans live to work, while we Spaniards work to live.&amp;rdquo; As I look back, I should have listened closer to my friend&amp;rsquo;s wise words because they are the keys to living a rewarding life. In this episode, I discuss the story of Kai-Fu Lee and the experiences of Australian author Bronnie Ware.</description></item><item><title>Michael Anthony On: Take Daily Action to Improve Your Life EP 111 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090277/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 03:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090277/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michael Anthony is the author of the best-selling book Think Unbroken and is a coach, mentor, and educator for adult survivors of child abuse. Michaels spends his time helping other survivors get out of &amp;ldquo;The Vortex&amp;rdquo; to become the hero of their own story and take their life back. Michael hosts the Think Unbroken podcast, teaches at Think Unbroken Academy, and is on a mission to create change in the world.</description></item><item><title>Strengthening Your Relationship With Your Best Self - John R. Miles EP 110 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090278/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 03:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090278/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over the years, I have come to a much deeper connection with myself. It is the most important relationship I can have—the one true constant in my life. I have learned that everything that happens in my life for good or bad is based on my reflection with myself and becoming my greatest self. In this episode, I tell a parable to illustrate why your relationship with yourself is the foundation for everything.</description></item><item><title>Katie Chonacas On: Being a Rebel With a Cause EP 109 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090279/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 03:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090279/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, I interview Katie Chonacas, a Greek international actress, filmmaker, voice actor, author, host of the She&amp;rsquo;s All Over the Place podcast, and musician. We discuss her life being a rebel with a cause. You will find during our discussion that Katie has an ethos that surrounds her. Katie talks about becoming an international actor who went from passion to profession and how that experience launched into being a voiceover artist.</description></item><item><title>The Science of Healthy Habits - How to Make Habits Stick EP 108 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090280/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 03:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090280/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, I tell the story of Kieran Behan and, through his account, review the science of creating healthy habits, unhealthy habit elimination, and how the process of neuroplasticity (brain rewiring) facilitates habit formation. I describe the role of the prefrontal cortex, which is grounded in the neuroscience of brain states and our ability to insert conscious effort, intention, and thought into the process. I also discuss neuroplasticity, also known as neural plasticity, or brain plasticity, and the neural networks&amp;rsquo; ability to change through growth and reorganization.</description></item><item><title>Jen Bricker-Bauer On: Everything is Possible EP 107 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090281/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 03:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090281/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jen Bricker-Bauer is an aerialist, motivational speaker, and New York Times, bestselling author. Born without legs, Jen&amp;rsquo;s biological parents left her at the hospital, destined for a life of hardship. However, the hand of God brought her an amazing adoptive family, who taught her that everything is possible. As a child, Jen was obsessed with gymnastics, and her idol was gold medalist Dominique Moceanu. In fact, watching Dominique on TV, helped inspire Jen to start competing herself.</description></item><item><title>How You Use Joy As Your Compass EP 106 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090282/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 03:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090282/</guid><description>Podcast Description Check Out Our Sponsors: NUTRAFOL: Get $15 off your first month at nutrafol.com promo code PASSIONSTRUCK. GRAMMARLY: Get 20% off premium at grammarly.com/PASSIONSTRUCK. I am currently reading The Power of Myth by Joseph Campbell, and one of my favorite quotes from him is, &amp;ldquo;find a place inside where there&amp;rsquo;s joy, and the joy will burn out the pain.&amp;rdquo; Joy is such a powerful compass. It is a gift that actually helps us navigate the complex demands that vie for our attention.</description></item><item><title>Kate Schutt On: The Best Gift You Can Possibly Give EP 105 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090283/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 03:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090283/</guid><description>Podcast Description Check Out Our Sponsors: NUTRAFOL: Get $15 off your first month at nutrafol.com promo code PASSIONSTRUCK. GRAMMARLY: Get 20% off premium at grammarly.com/PASSIONSTRUCK. &amp;ldquo;But you will never know the impact of just deciding to act and using your heart to say, &amp;lsquo;what would really help them right now&amp;rsquo; that I don&amp;rsquo;t even need to ask to do.&amp;rdquo; - Kate Schutt Kate Schutt is an award-winning songwriter, singer, guitarist, and producer.</description></item><item><title>Where You Invest Your Love You Invest Your Life EP 104 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090284/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 03:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090284/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;ldquo;In these bodies, we will live. In these bodies, we will die. And where you invest your love, you invest your life.&amp;rdquo; - Mumford &amp;amp; Sons. This is one of the most potent lyrics the band has ever written, inspiring this podcast episode. I believe this quote is about self-love and finding out about yourself and who you are. When we learn to love ourselves, we also express love to others more powerfully and intentionally.</description></item><item><title>Oluneye Oluwole On: Why You Should Reach For Your Dreams EP 103 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090285/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 03:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090285/</guid><description>Podcast Description Imagine realizing you were in a relationship devaluing you and your gifts?You spiraled down to the lowest depths of your life.You had to take a brutal look at yourself and those things you allowed to happen because you lived life to please others, but not satisfy YOURSELF.And then recovering and rediscovering who YOU are as a result? You started to look at your life as saying yes to opportunities.</description></item><item><title>How Your Environment Influences Who You Become EP 102 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090286/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 03:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090286/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our environment continually influences our lives, our decision-making process, and how we interact with the world around us. In psychology, there is a concept known as &amp;rsquo;the social multiplier effect&amp;rsquo; based on the principle that high levels of one attribute or behavior amongst one&amp;rsquo;s peers can have spillover effects on an individual. In today&amp;rsquo;s episode, John discusses this social multiplier effect and how your environment influences who you become.</description></item><item><title>Claude Silver On: Using Heart Leadership to Create Emotional Optimism EP 101 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090287/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 03:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090287/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, John R. Miles is joined by Claude Silver, Chief Heart Officer of VaynerX, the host of the emotional optimism podcast, and a pioneering world leader in the power of heart leadership. They discuss her role as the Chief Heart Officer and how it differs from a typical chief human resources officer. Miles and Silver explore what it means to have strong-hearted leadership and why misery attracts misery, but, simultaneously, the right kind of company can help heal misery.</description></item><item><title>Why I Created Passion Struck EP 100 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090288/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 03:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090288/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s episode is a special one for a variety of reasons. First, John R. Miles provides a detailed look at how Passion Struck plans to impact the world. Additionally, It is the 100th episode of the Passion Struck podcast and marks a year since Passion Struck (the company behind the podcast) launched. John is asked by many people why he started Passion Struck and made it his life’s mission.</description></item><item><title>Jeffrey C. Walker On: The Criticality of Collaboration in Systems Change EP 99 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090289/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090289/</guid><description>Podcast Description Meeting the sustainability problems facing society will require the kind of authentic collaboration for which there is still no real precedent. It must be co-created by various stakeholders who understand the criticality of collaboration in systems change and want to positively impact the world. Jeffrey (Jeff) C. Walker is on the leading edge of solving the world’s biggest problems using better philanthropy through systems change. His personal mission is to help end global suffering and enhance joy across the world.</description></item><item><title>The 7 Stages of Pain That Lead to Breakthrough Success EP 98 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090290/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 03:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090290/</guid><description>Podcast Description Everyone dreams of success, and most want to have it in the quickest timeframe and by taking the easiest path. But success rarely, if ever, works in that linear fashion. We go through typical stages of pain in hardship to achieve ultimate success, and the rewards from doing so are so much higher when you do. John R Miles explains why you must endure pain to achieve success and the 7 stages we cross in doing so.</description></item><item><title>Adam Posner On: The Secret to Connecting Powerful Relationships EP 97 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090291/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 03:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090291/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adam Posner is the Founder and President at NHP Talent Group and the host of the top career podcast, ThePOZcast- showcasing experts to help you harness your inner tenacity to drive your life and career forward. In today&amp;rsquo;s episode, Adam speaks to John R. Miles about the secret to connecting powerful relationships. The two discuss why Adam left the corporate world to pursue recruiting. We go into the most significant advice that he ever received from Gary Vee when he worked for Gary at Vayner Media.</description></item><item><title>Why Materialism Is Impacting Your Success and Happiness EP 96 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090292/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 03:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090292/</guid><description>Podcast Description It is so easy to fall into the trap of materialism. The attraction is all around us. But it is now believed that by minimizing attachment to material possessions, you naturally allow more room for happiness and abundance to flow into your life, instead of greed, apathy, and ego. John explains how he fell into the materialism trap and why it eventually led to depression, anxiety, apathy, and a failure to live intentionally.</description></item><item><title>Andrew Marr On Living With a Never Quit Mentality While Overcoming the Wounds of War EP 95 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090293/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 03:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090293/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andrew Marr is a retired Green Beret, co-founder of the Warrior Angels Foundation, and author of &amp;ldquo;Tales from the Blast Factory.&amp;rdquo; He is also featured in the new documentary &amp;ldquo;Quiet Explosions.&amp;rdquo; In this Pasion Struck podcast episode, Andrew sits down with John R. Miles to discuss his never-quit mentality overcoming the wounds of war and his traumatic brain injuries. The two veterans discuss: Andrew&amp;rsquo;s 2013 tour of duty in Afghanistan and his underlying medical issues upon returning home.</description></item><item><title>Futurist Chet W. Sisk On: The 10 Predictions For 2022 Impacting the Future of Society EP 94 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090294/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 03:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090294/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chet W. Sisk is a futurist, entrepreneur, author, consultant, speaker, and workshop developer. He talks with John R. Miles about his ten predictions for the future of society in 2022. Have you ever wondered what the future holds for everyone in 2022? Chet uses his skills as a futurist to assess the past to offer insights that predict what’s going to happen in the future. New to this channel and the passion-struck podcast?</description></item><item><title>Jess Faulds On How Stem Cell Transplant Cured Her MS and the Nutrition Science That Promoted Recovery EP 93 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090295/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 03:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090295/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jess Faulds is a certified holistic nutrition consultant diagnosed with Multiple Sclerosis (M.S.) at the age of 15. Through her M.S. journey, she suffered through different disease-modifying drugs and treatments before having a stem cell transplant! She sits down with John R. Miles on The Passion Struck Podcast to discuss how Haematopoietic Stem Cell Transplantation (HSTC) cured her M.S. and the nutrition science that promoted recovery. New to this channel and the passion-struck podcast?</description></item><item><title>Sharon Rolph On How to Find Your Essence in Retirement EP 92 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090296/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 03:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090296/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sharon Rolph is a behavioral scientist who works as a retirement and essence coach. She sits down with John R Miles to discuss how to find your essence in retirement and how to empower everyone to win satisfaction. New to this channel and the passion-struck podcast? Check out our starter packs which are our favorite episodes grouped by topic, to allow you to get a sense of all the podcast has to offer.</description></item><item><title>Cristina Pujol Jensen On How Your Mind Can Free Your Body EP 91 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090297/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 03:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090297/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cristina Pujol Jensen is a Coach, Trainer, Speaker, and Author of Ignite Female Change Makers, Co-Founder of Tú y Tu Mente Coaching, and Hips On Fire Dance specializing in leadership, clarity, and focus. She sits down with John R. Miles to discuss how your mind can free your body and start living intentionally. New to this channel and the passion-struck podcast? Check out our starter packs which are our favorite episodes grouped by topic, to allow you to get a sense of all the podcast has to offer.</description></item><item><title>Christina Sparks On How to Turn a Passion For Giving Into a Business EP 90 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090298/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 04:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090298/</guid><description>Podcast Description Christina Sparks is a Technology Executive turned E-Commerce Fashion CEO and the Founder and CEO of Soulgani Activewear. She sits down with John R Miles to talk about how to turn a passion for giving into a business. For the entire show notes go to https://passionstruck.com/passion-struck-podcast/. New to this channel and the passion-struck podcast? Check out our starter packs which are our favorite episodes grouped by topic, to allow you to get a sense of all the podcast has to offer.</description></item><item><title>Nathalie Plamondon-Thomas On How to Improve Your Inner Self Confidence EP 89 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090299/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 03:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090299/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nathalie Plamondon-Thomas is an internationally acclaimed confidence expert and 8x international #1 bestselling author. She sits down with John R Miles to talk about how to improve your inner self-confidence. For the full show notes go to For the full show notes go to https://passionstruck.com/passion-struck-podcast/ where we have links to Nathalie&amp;rsquo;s books and other unique content.. New to this channel and the passion-struck podcast? Check out our starter packs which are our favorite episodes grouped by topic, to allow you to get a sense of all the podcast has to offer.</description></item><item><title>Stop Hiding the True You EP 88 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090300/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 03:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090300/</guid><description>Podcast Description John R. Miles discusses why it is so vital that you stop hiding the true you. It&amp;rsquo;s an episode that is core to why he started the Passion Struck movement. In the podcast, John will explain why he believes so many today hide behind a mask we wear that hides who we are and the superpower we are meant to bring to the world. Instead of living an intentional life, we live a life in a shroud of pretense.</description></item><item><title>Lily Walford On: How to Create Compatible Love EP 87 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090301/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 03:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090301/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lily Walford is an international dating coach who specializes in using behavioral Psychology, profiling, and body language to help clients meet a compatible partner. She and John R Miles discuss how to create compatible love and how everyone deserves real, honest and genuine love, but not everyone knows how to get it. New to this channel and the passion-struck podcast? Check out our starter packs which are our favorite episodes grouped by topic, to allow you to get a sense of all the podcast has to offer.</description></item><item><title>How Can You Overcome Your Limits? EP 86 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090302/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 03:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090302/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this solo episode, John R. Miles discusses how our limits result from the mindset that we choose to live and act by. Often we develop beliefs that are not real and only exist in our minds. What could you accomplish if you could break free from this mindset and live to your potential? John provides the examples of Michael Jordan and John Bassinger to illustrate those who pushed past their limits and explores this through the lens of Dr.</description></item><item><title>Dr. Rubin Khoddam On: The Importance Of Holistic Mental Healthcare EP 85 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090303/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 03:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090303/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week’s Passion Struck podcast features Rubin Khoddam, Ph.D., a Clinical Psychologist who specializes in the treatment of addiction and trauma and mood disorders, such as anxiety and depression. He and John R. Miles discuss the importance of holistic mental healthcare and examine Cognitive Behavior Therapy, Cognitive Processing Therapy, and Prolonged Exposure for PTSD, as well as Dialectical Behavior Therapy and Acceptance and Commitment Therapy. New to this channel and the passion-struck podcast?</description></item><item><title>What 7 Skills Create High Achievers? EP 84 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090304/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090304/</guid><description>Podcast Description The seven skills that create high achievers: in this episode of the Passion Struck podcast John R Miles provides eye-opening advice on what defines a high achiever, what derails people from becoming high achievers, the seven skills that create high achievers, and the initial four steps you can take to become one. The seven skills include: Action Orienter Visionary Strategiser Cognition Crusader Positivity Embracer Resilience Builder Constant Learner Persistent Adapter New to this channel and the passion-struck podcast?</description></item><item><title>John Lewis On: How to Create Your Virtual Legacy EP 83 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090305/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 03:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090305/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today&amp;rsquo;s episode is with entrepreneur John Lewis, a former division one athlete and founder and CEO of the Virtual Legacy. He and John R. Miles discuss how to create your virtual legacy and maximize your personal brand. New to this channel and the passion-struck podcast? Check out our starter packs which are our favorite episodes grouped by topic, to allow you to get a sense of all the podcast has to offer.</description></item><item><title>How Life‘s Transition Points Impact Your Success EP 82 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090306/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 03:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090306/</guid><description>Podcast Description Life&amp;rsquo;s most important moments are not what you think. It is not the mega-events in our life that create success. Rather, what if everything hinged on infinite small moments; those transition points which occur every day in everything we do. In this Momentum, Friday episode of the Passion Struck podcast, John R. Miles discusses how life&amp;rsquo;s transition points impact your success in more ways than you may realize and how to approach them in your life for maximum impact.</description></item><item><title>Flory Seidel On: How to Create a Happy Life EP 81 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090307/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 03:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090307/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2013, Flory Seidel’s life and career changed in an instant when he was hit on the left side of his body by a large truck and suffered damages to almost every portion of his entire body. He shares with John R. Miles his incredible story of recovery. Subscribe to the Passion Struck podcast: https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-passion-struck-podcast/id1553279283. Like this? Please join me on my new platform for peak performance, life coaching, self-improvement, and personal growth: https://passionstruck.</description></item><item><title>How Do You Overcome Your Deep Insecurity? EP 80 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090308/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 03:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090308/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our deep insecurity reflects how we view ourselves and the impact that the world around us has on our self-perception. By allowing social media and others’ thoughts to dictate how we live, we will only end up with deeper insecurities. The more we are not true to ourselves, the more we open ourselves up to criticism by the world around us. This criticism can cause us to be blinded by the unique gifts we have inside all of us.</description></item><item><title>Amy Malin On: Living Life From a Place of Love EP 79 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090309/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 04:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090309/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amy Malin is a social entrepreneur, human trafficking survivor, philanthropist, and the co-founder of Trueheart, a search engine funding dreams worldwide. She sits down with John R Miles to talk about how she is living life from a place of love. New to the passion-struck podcast? Check out our starter packs which are collections of our favorite episodes grouped by topic, to allow you to get a sense of all the podcast has to offer.</description></item><item><title>6 Ways to Build Resilience EP 78 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090310/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2021 03:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090310/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s episode, John R Miles reveals the most important ways we can develop resilience and learn to use pain for positive growth. Whether you struggle with resilience or not, this podcast will serve you. You&amp;rsquo;ll learn what it means to build resilience and how we can build a stronger legacy on the foundation of struggle. Miles offers practical steps and encouraging insight backed by science on how you can overcome adversity.</description></item><item><title>Gail Swift On: The Power of Taking Action EP 77 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090311/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 03:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090311/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gail Swift is Speaker, Kolbe Consultant, and Certified Life Coach. She sits down to talk to John R. Miles about the power of taking action. When people know how they take action, it&amp;rsquo;s their, ideal sweet spot. It&amp;rsquo;s the nirvana of productivity. New to this channel and the passion-struck podcast? Check out our starter packs which are our favorite episodes grouped by topic, to allow you to get a sense of all the podcast has to offer.</description></item><item><title>The Incredible Power of Being Resilient EP 76 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090312/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 03:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090312/</guid><description>Podcast Description Approximately 60 percent of people in North America report at least one traumatic event in their lifetime. Through this lens, John R Miles discusses why the human capacity for the incredible power of being resilient is quite remarkable. Watch the full episode on YouTube: https://youtu.be/MAUZCNWKXyE. Subscribe to the Passion Struck podcast: https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-passion-struck-podcast/id1553279283. Athletic Greens is a custom formulation of 75 vitamins, minerals, and other whole-food sourced ingredients that make it easier for you to maintain nutrition in just a single scoop.</description></item><item><title>Dr. Jay Lombard On: Brain Science for Better Lives EP 75 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090313/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 03:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090313/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Jay Lombard is an internationally acclaimed neurologist, author, and keynote speaker who creates solutions for brain health and intractable neurological disorders. He sits down with John R Miles to talk about brain science for better lives and his research that are allowing both the prevention and treatment of neurological disorders such as ALS, Parkinson’s disease, and Alzheimer’s. New to the passion-struck podcast? Check out our starter packs which are our favorite episodes grouped by topic, to allow you to get a sense of all the podcast has to offer.</description></item><item><title>The Importance of Play as an Adult EP 74 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090314/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 03:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090314/</guid><description>Podcast Description When we think of playing, we hark back to our childhood days of messing around on the beach, playing tag at recess, or spending hours with dolls or toys. However, we often fail to realize the importance of play as an adult and that is what John unpacks in this episode. Like this? Please subscribe, and join me on my new platform for peak performance, life coaching, and personal growth: https://passionstruck.</description></item><item><title>Shawn Springs On: How to Stay Grounded in Life EP 73 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090315/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 03:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090315/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former NFL pro bowl cornerback Shawn Springs sits down with John R Miles to discuss how to stay grounded in life. We discuss how a traumatic brain injury he suffered while playing for the Washington Redskins, changed his life and created his passion to create better protection for future generations. Like this? Please subscribe, and join me on my new platform for peak performance, life coaching, and personal growth: https://passionstruck.</description></item><item><title>8 Ways To Get Comfortable Doing Uncomfortable Things And Growing Through Them EP 72 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090316/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 04:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090316/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today&amp;rsquo;s episode, John R Miles discusses 8 ways to get comfortable doing uncomfortable things and growing through them. When we get comfortable being uncomfortable, we put ourselves in situations where we force ourselves to address our self-limiting beliefs. You might even actively pursue activities you never thought you would. Huge thanks to Podcorn for sponsoring this episode. Explore sponsorship opportunities and start monetizing your podcast by signing up here: https://podcorn.</description></item><item><title>Cindy Shaw On: The Six Pillars of Brain Health EP 71 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090317/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 03:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090317/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brain Health Coach Cindy Shaw sits down with John R Miles to discuss the six pillars of brain health which include: Physical Exercise, Food &amp;amp; Nutrition, Medical Health, Sleep &amp;amp; Relaxation, Mental Fitness, and Social Interaction. Like this? Please subscribe, and join me on my new platform for peak performance, life coaching, and personal growth: https://passionstruck.com/. About Our Guest Cindy Shaw Thank you for listening to the Passion Struck podcast.</description></item><item><title>Why Hustle Culture Is Toxic (And How to Break Free From It) EP 70 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090318/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 04:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090318/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Momentum Friday episode of the passion struck podcast, John R. Miles discusses a critical topic. It is one he considers to be one of the main culprits leading to over 85% of the world’s workers becoming disengaged and complacent in their jobs. What is that topic, the hustle culture, why it is toxic, and more importantly, what can you do to break out of it? Like this?</description></item><item><title>Nate Dukes On: You Will Never Change Syndrome EP 69 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090319/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 04:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090319/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nate Dukes sits down with John R Miles to discuss you will never change syndrome plaguing society. You Will Never Change. I bet you’ve heard that line before. From friends? Family? Maybe you’ve said it to yourself. Regardless of the source, it hurts to hear. But it hurts even worse when you agree. Like this? Please subscribe, and join me on my new platform for peak performance, life coaching, and personal growth: https://passionstruck.</description></item><item><title>How to Ask For Advice (and Make the Most of It) | Momentum Friday EP 68 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090320/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 04:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090320/</guid><description>Podcast Description One of the questions John R Miles often gets is how to ask for advice (and make the most of it). Asking for advice the right way is one of the most important skills we can master. It’s an asset that sharpens our instincts, exposes us to guidance, and brings us closer to our goals, abilities, and passion. Like this? Please subscribe, and join me on my new platform for peak performance, life coaching, and personal growth: https://passionstruck.</description></item><item><title>Navy SEAL William Branum On Why Transition Points are Vital to Success EP 67 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090321/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 04:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090321/</guid><description>Podcast Description Retired Navy SEAL William Branum sits down with John R Miles to discuss why transition points are vital to success. Transition points are those times in life where complacency can kill your dreams and aspirations because you&amp;rsquo;re not locked on, you&amp;rsquo;re not paying attention. They are those periods that are easy to overlook because they are not significant events. They are those moments of everyday life where you can choose comfort or stay locked in on achieving your dreams.</description></item><item><title>Colonel Bob Adams MD On How to Be Your Own Best Advocate EP 66 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090322/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 04:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090322/</guid><description>Podcast Description Retired Army Colonel and Navy SEAL Bob Adams, M.D. sits down with John R Miles to talk about being your own best advocate in life. He discusses why this is so vital through the viewpoint of over 30 years as a doctor and applying the lessons he learned from BUD/S and his 12 years as a SEAL. Like this? Please subscribe, and join me on my new platform for peak performance, life coaching, and personal growth: https://passionstruck.</description></item><item><title>Mark Divine On How to Live a Life of Excellence EP 65 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090323/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 03:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090323/</guid><description>Podcast Description Navy SEAL Commander Mark Divine sits down with John R Miles to talk about the secrets to living a life of excellence. Becoming passion-struck is all about living a life of excellence. Setting goals, overcoming challenges, getting results, and celebrating victories make living so rich and worthwhile. Like this? Please subscribe to the channel, and join me on my new platform for peak performance, life coaching, and personal growth: https://passionstruck.</description></item><item><title>Astronaut Kayla Barron On Bring Out the Best Version of Yourself EP 64 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090324/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 03:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090324/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kayla Barron is one of the first females in the U.S. Armed Forces to serve on submarines and was selected as part of the NASA Artemis program. Kayla reveals her belief in the work it takes to bring out the best version of yourself in this episode of the Passion Struck podcast with John R. Miles. Like this? Please subscribe, and join me on my new platform for peak performance, life coaching, and personal growth: https://passionstruck.</description></item><item><title>Escaping Afghanistan: How a Navy SEAL Saved a Family of Fourteen w/ Retired Navy SEAL Dan O‘Shea EP 63 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090325/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 12:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090325/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a true story about the operation “Pineapple Express” and helping Afghani allies escape Afghanistan. In this Passion Struck podcast episode, John R Miles interviews retired Navy SEAL Dan O’Shea on how he guided a family of fourteen to safety, successfully evading the Taliban. Dan describes the harrowing details of their 96 hours of terror and what it took to get the family safely to the Kabul airport.</description></item><item><title>Permit Yourself to Dream the Dream w/ Former Astronaut Wendy Lawrence EP 62 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090326/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 03:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090326/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this powerful Episode, John R. Miles interviews former Astronaut Wendy Lawrence on why it is vital to permit yourself to dream the dream and how she followed that advice throughout her own career. What Does Dreaming the Dream Mean? To dream the dream is to live life to its fullest, making the best of every situation and transforming our life into who we aspire to be. It’s the state of becoming passion-struck in the pursuit of your dream with a focus on achieving it regardless of the setbacks or roadblocks that may emerge over time.</description></item><item><title>Jesse Iwuji On Creating an Unstoppable Life EP 61 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090327/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090327/</guid><description>Podcast Description For Naval Officer and NASCAR driver Jesse Iwuji, becoming a race driver was a dream that seemed unreachable. But after deciding to pursue his passion, he told himself he could do it and started to take daily actions that led him closer to a dream that is now a reality. Like this? Please subscribe, and join me on my new platform for peak performance, life coaching, and personal growth: https://passionstruck.</description></item><item><title>Janet and Tony Blackall On Creating a Motorsport Voice for Veterans EP 60 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090328/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 03:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090328/</guid><description>Podcast Description John R Miles interviews the Blackall racing team featuring military veterans Tony and Janet Blackall, who race in the MotoAmerica Supersport division and are a privateer team. When they founded Blackall Racing, they did it to race on the national stage and created a motorsport voice for veterans. Like this? Please subscribe, and join me on my new platform for peak performance, life coaching, and personal growth: https://passionstruck.com/. Who Is Blackall Racing?</description></item><item><title>The Life Changing Power of Saying ”I Can” w/ John R. Miles EP 59 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090329/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090329/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ready for one of the most important life lessons you will ever learn? YOU are the most challenging critic you will ever face. When you realize that you are your biggest obstacle, you can start to take steps to silence your own inner critic and move toward the passion-struck life you&amp;rsquo;ve dreamed of. Like this? Please subscribe, and join me on my new platform for peak performance, life coaching, and personal growth: https://passionstruck.</description></item><item><title>Michelle Royal On How to Create Your Innovative Power EP 58 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090330/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 03:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090330/</guid><description>Podcast Description What innovative power is waiting to be unleashed by you? Michelle Royal discusses how she uses visualization and facilitation to create breakthroughs in state of mind and behavior. She brings visual stories to life, unlocking the hidden collective power of organizations and individuals. Like this? Please subscribe, and join me on my new platform for peak performance, life coaching, and personal growth: https://passionstruck.com/. Creating Your Innovative Power Thank you for Watching the Passion Struck podcast.</description></item><item><title>7 Secrets to Build Mental Strength w/ John R. Miles EP 57 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090331/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 03:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090331/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, John breaks down his 7 secrets to build mental strength. He describes how mental strength is having the capacity to deal with stressors, fears, pressures, obstacles, and life challenges, regardless of the circumstances that you find yourself in. It is understanding that you are so much more powerful than you realize you are. Like this? Please subscribe, and join me on my new platform for peak performance, life coaching, and personal growth: https://passionstruck.</description></item><item><title>Dr. Michael Lewis On The Keys to Traumatic Brain Injury Treatment EP 56 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090332/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 03:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090332/</guid><description>Podcast Description John interviews Dr. Michael Lewis about recovering from traumatic brain injury and how his 30-plus years of military experience, with a special emphasis on TBI, is working towards improving the care and outcomes of people who have experienced psychological or physical trauma the brain. Like this? Please subscribe, and join me on my new platform for peak performance, life coaching, and personal growth: https://passionstruck.com/. Why is Traumatic Brain Injury Treatment so Misunderstood?</description></item><item><title>How Your Mental Health Impacts Your Relationships w/ John R Miles EP 55 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090333/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 03:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090333/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s episode is a solo round with John all about how your mental health impacts your relationships, which is a topic that continues to fascinate him the more he speaks to guests about it on the podcast and the more he sees results show up in his life and for those of you who have shared your experiences with him on social media. Like this? Please subscribe, and join me on my new platform for peak performance, life coaching, and personal growth: https://passionstruck.</description></item><item><title>Amanda Slavin On How to Change Lives by Inspiring Change EP 54 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090334/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090334/</guid><description>Podcast Description Has anyone ever inspired you to change your life in a significant way that made you healthier, happier, or more fulfilled? Inspiration is powerful, but it isn’t easy. In this Passion Struck podcast, Amanda Slavin discusses the life-altering moment that changed her life and how to change lives by inspiring change in others. Like this? Please subscribe, and join me on my new platform for peak performance, life coaching, self-improvement, and personal growth: https://passionstruck.</description></item><item><title>Steve Swift On How to Create a Career of Service EP 53 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090335/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 17:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090335/</guid><description>Podcast Description Captain Steve Swift discusses how to create a career of service to others and how he did so through a 30-year career in the military and now as a running and triathlete coach. Careers helping people come in all shapes and sizes. You can get hands-on in a healthcare or emergency services job, think your way around problems as a social worker or lawyer, or create broader benefits for society in a career such as science or engineering.</description></item><item><title>Philip Anthony Mangan On How to Create Your Best Life EP 52 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090336/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 03:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090336/</guid><description>Podcast Description Philip Anthony Mangan joins John R. Miles to talk about how he overcame his directionless Van Wilder life to become an actor, model, personal trainer, and coach. We discuss how after college, he was living the party lifestyle through his party bus company, how he discovered through a failed relationship the courage to turn his life around and create the best life possible for him. The steps he took on the journey including having to fire his best friend and the opportunity he took moving to New York, and how it altered his life trajectory.</description></item><item><title>Why Humility is Vital to Your Success w/ John R. Miles EP 51 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090337/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 03:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090337/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this powerful Momentum Friday Episode, John R. Miles discusses why humility is vital to your success, and specifically intellectual humility. The definition of intellectual humility, determining if we are practicing humility, what happens when we don&amp;rsquo;t, and techniques to get better at being humble. Thank you for listening to the Passion Struck podcast. Like this? Please subscribe, and join me on my new platform for personal growth and life coaching: https://passionstruck.</description></item><item><title>Dara Kurtz How to Create a Crazy Perfect Life EP 50 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090338/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 07:55:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090338/</guid><description>Podcast Description What would your perfect life look like? Everyone has trials and tribulations in life. How you react to those challenges determines how “perfect” you think your life is. The key to getting what you want out of this life is living with intention. Like this? Please subscribe, and join me on my new platform for personal development: https://passionstruck.com/. Thank you for Watching the Passion Struck podcast. In this powerful interview, John R.</description></item><item><title>Why Your Ego is Holding You Back w/ John R. Miles EP 49 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090339/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 03:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090339/</guid><description>Podcast Description There is such a fine line between confidence and ego. You can have faith in your abilities and be a forceful leader without an ego. In this podcast, John R. Miles discusses what the ego is, how to know if your ego is running your life, why your ego is holding you back, and 5 ways to recognize if you have an ego problem. Like this? Please subscribe, and join me on my new platform for personal development: https://passionstruck.</description></item><item><title>Saskia Lightstar On How To Create Our Best Self EP 48 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090340/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 03:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090340/</guid><description>Podcast Description Saskia Lightstar thought she was living it big when she enjoyed the party girl lifestyle in South Africa. It turns out it was her low point, as she dealt with eating disorders and self-image issues. Then her biggest test came when she learned she had cancer. It was at that point after beating breast cancer she learned the true meaning of how to create our best self. It starts with self-love and kindness.</description></item><item><title>Why You Need To Stop Playing Small w/ John R. Miles EP 47 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090341/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 03:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090341/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this powerful Passion Struck podcast episode, John R. Miles breaks down why we need to stop playing small and instead play big. He goes through what it means to play small vs playing big and 7 skills you can use to play big and live a no regrets life. Why So Many Are Playing Small in Their Life Did you know that Two-thirds of Brits and over seventy percent of Americans feel they are living an unfulfilled life, according to new research?</description></item><item><title>Victoria Humphries On Taking Life to New Heights EP 46 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090342/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 03:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090342/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this powerful episode of the Passion Struck podcast, John R. Miles interviews Victoria Humphries (Riches) about taking life to new heights by being willing to have an anything is possible attitude. By saying &amp;ldquo;I CAN&amp;rdquo; to life&amp;rsquo;s opportunities, she found it to be the key to living her bucket list which she is doing in her 50 at 50 challenge. We discuss that and so much more during our inspirational conversation.</description></item><item><title>Mastering the Art of Tact w/ John R. Miles EP 45 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090343/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 03:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090343/</guid><description>Podcast Description We all have to communicate painful or sensitive information at some point in our careers. And, while it&amp;rsquo;s important, to tell the truth, we need to think about how we do it. Tact allows us to be honest while respecting a person&amp;rsquo;s feelings. Please subscribe, and join me on my new platform for personal development: https://passionstruck.com/. When we communicate tactfully, we can preserve relationships, build credibility, and demonstrate thoughtfulness.</description></item><item><title>How to Implement Your Bucket List w/ Trav Bell ”The Bucket List Guy” EP 44 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090344/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 03:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090344/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you living the life you want to live? Creating your bucket list can be one of the most important things you can do to provide a roadmap for life. Like this? Please subscribe, and join me on my new platform for personal development: https://passionstruck.com/. Thank you for Watching the Passion Struck podcast. In this powerful interview, John R. Miles interviews Trav Bell &amp;ldquo;The Bucket List Guy&amp;rdquo; to discuss how you implement your bucket list and create the life you always wanted.</description></item><item><title>How to Resolve Conflict in 5 Steps w/ John R. Miles EP 43 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090345/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 03:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090345/</guid><description>Podcast Description Just like “death and taxes,” conflict is inevitable! Why? Because no two individuals have the same needs and concerns. That is why it is essential to understand how to resolve conflict in 5 steps. Like this? Please subscribe, and join me on my new platform for personal development: https://passionstruck.com/. In this powerful Momentum Friday Episode, John R. Miles discusses unhealthy vs. healthy conflict resolution and understanding the different conflict management styles.</description></item><item><title>Sydney Wong On The Keys to Becoming a Lean Startup EP 42 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090346/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 03:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090346/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever wondered what the keys to becoming a lean startup are? Entrepreneur Sydney Wong discovered that while on a one-way ticket to San Francisco. From that experience, she decided to launch VenturX in Montreal to help startups achieve funding and overall success. Like this? Please subscribe and join me on my new platform for personal development: https://passionstruck.com/ Thank you for listening to the Passion Struck podcast. Sydney Wong&amp;rsquo;s Journey to Creating VenturX In this powerful Passion Struck Podcast Episode, John R.</description></item><item><title>What is the Secret to Diplomacy w/ John R. Miles EP 41 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090347/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 04:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090347/</guid><description>Podcast Description Earlier in my career, I was lucky to meet and work for Jay Skibinksi who is one of the best leaders I&amp;rsquo;ve ever met. Jay taught me many lessons over the years, but one of the best was understanding the secret to diplomacy. Like this? Please subscribe, and join me on my new platform for personal development: https://passionstruck.com/ Thank you for listening to the Passion Struck podcast. In this powerful Momentum Friday Episode, John R.</description></item><item><title>Steph Lee On Meditation Benefits for People with Chronic Illness EP 40 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090348/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 03:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090348/</guid><description>Podcast Description The biggest thing that holds any of us back is our own minds - specifically, the thoughts our minds think and our willingness to believe them. Imagine the mindset shift for a person with chronic illness and the meditation benefits that they can achieve through mindfulness practice. Like this? Please subscribe, give us a 5-star rating and join me on my new platform for personal development: https://passionstruck.com/. In this episode of the Passion Struck Podcast, John R.</description></item><item><title>Brad Yates On EFT Tapping Into Your True Self EP 39 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090349/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 04:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090349/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is the key to tapping into your true self? Thank you for listening to the Passion Struck podcast. In this powerful Momentum Friday Episode, John R. Miles interviews Brad Yates, who is one of the foremost experts on EFT tapping and the art of using emotional freedom techniques (EFT). We used this discussion to uncover how EFT tapping can help you overcome trauma and post-traumatic stress disorder, as well as helping you overall with your mental health.</description></item><item><title>Abigail Barnes On: Turn Your Time Into Productivity EP 38 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090350/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 03:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090350/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you know how to turn your time into productivity? This search for a more productive life has led to a particular miscategorization about what time management is and how it relates to productivity&amp;ndash; the simple truth is that it is far more than simply having a to-do list and checking this off of it. The most productive people do not concentrate on doing more things. This is actually the opposite of being productive.</description></item><item><title>Charles P. Smith On Why We Need To Stop Veteran Suicide Rates EP 37 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090351/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 03:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090351/</guid><description>Podcast Description According to the 2020 National Veterans Suicide Prevention Annual report, suicide rates continue to increase in the U.S. adult population. There is also a growing correlation between post-traumatic stress disorder and suicide risk. In this episode of the Passion Struck Podcast, John R. Miles interviews Charles P. Smith on the growing suicide rate among veterans, active-duty military members, and the general population. Charles served 10 years as a Marine Corps officer.</description></item><item><title>Nir Bashan On The Secret To Unlocking Your Creativity EP 36 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090352/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 03:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090352/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you know how to unleash the creator mindset? Learn from Nir Bashan, the author who wrote the book on it, the secret to unlocking your creativity and creating the passion-driven life you have always wanted. Thank you for listening to the Passion Struck podcast. In this powerful Episode, John R. Miles interviews Nir Bashan, author of the Creator Mindset. Nir Bashan is a world-renowned creativity expert. He has taught thousands of leaders and individuals across the globe how to harness the power of creativity to improve profitability, increase sales and ultimately create more meaning in their work.</description></item><item><title>Never Believe a Prediction That Doesn’t Ignite You w/ John R. Miles EP 35 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090353/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 03:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090353/</guid><description>Podcast Description One of my favorite TedX Talks featured Sean Stephenson, a former American author, therapist, and celebrated speaker. He inspired this episode on why you should never believe a prediction that doesn&amp;rsquo;t ignite you. Thank you for listening to the Passion Struck podcast. In this powerful Momentum Friday Episode, John R. Miles discusses why predictions in our lives can be so destructive to us living a passion-driven life. New Interviews with the World&amp;rsquo;s GREATEST high achievers will be posted every Tuesday with a Momentum Friday inspirational message!</description></item><item><title>Midori Verity On Identifying Your Zone of Genius EP 34 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090354/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 03:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090354/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you wondered how to build success in your start-up? It starts by creating passion with the entrepreneurial success triangle that helps you identify your zone of genius. Thank you for listening to the Passion Struck podcast. In this powerful interview, Midori Verity and John R. Miles discuss creating passion with the entrepreneurial success triangle. New Interviews with the World&amp;rsquo;s GREATEST high achievers will be posted every Tuesday with a Momentum Friday inspirational message!</description></item><item><title>Letting Go of a Toxic Friend Or A Relationship You Have Outgrown w/ John R. Miles EP 33 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090355/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 03:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090355/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever wondered when it is time to let relationships or friendships go? In doing so, you will learn why you take your power back by letting toxic people go. Learn the keys to letting go of a toxic friend or a relationship you have outgrown. Thank you for listening to the Passion Struck podcast. In this powerful Momentum Friday Episode, John R. Miles discusses why you take your power back by letting toxic people go.</description></item><item><title>Ron Lutz On The Secret to Servant Leadership EP 32 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090356/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 03:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090356/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is the secret to servant leadership skills? In this Passion Struck Podcast episode, John R. Miles interviews Ron Lutz about improving your servant leadership skills. And applying it to your life. New Interviews with the World&amp;rsquo;s GREATEST high achievers will be posted every Tuesday with a Momentum Friday inspirational message! In today&amp;rsquo;s discussion, Ron Lutz and I will discuss some of the mutual experiences we had working together at Lowe&amp;rsquo;s Home Improvement.</description></item><item><title>Stop Applying a Governor to Your Life w/ John R. Miles EP 31 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090357/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 03:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090357/</guid><description>Podcast Description So many today are living short of their potential. I believe it is because of restrictions we place on ourselves, and that is why you need to stop applying a governor to your life. Are you living to your true capability, your purpose in life, your future potential? According to a number of recent studies from Gallup, Gartner, and Bill and Melinda Gates - The majority of us are not.</description></item><item><title>Tricia Dempsey On Why We Need Women At All Levels EP 30 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090358/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 03:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090358/</guid><description>Podcast Description It is becoming increasingly clear that businesses prosper when they have women in leadership roles. That is why we need women at all levels. In this powerful interview, Tricia Dempsey and John R. Miles discuss why we need women at all levels, becoming the CEO of your own life, the secret to overcoming fears, and so much more. In the show, Tricia discusses how she came to a point in her life that she realized she needed change.</description></item><item><title>Applying the Ivy Lee Method to Life w/ John R. Miles EP 29 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090359/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090359/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this powerful Momentum Friday Episode, John R. Miles discusses implementing the daily routine recommended for peak performance through the Ivy Lee Method. New Interviews with the World&amp;rsquo;s GREATEST high achievers will be posted every Tuesday with a Momentum Friday inspirational message! In the early 1900s, the Bill Gates, Jeff Bezos, or Elon Musk of that time was a gentleman named Charles M Schwab. And if you&amp;rsquo;re not familiar with him, he was an American steel magnate as the CEO of Bethlehem Steel.</description></item><item><title>Vice Admiral Walter “Ted” Carter, USN (Ret.) On The Keys to Personal Growth EP 28 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090360/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 03:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090360/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this powerful episode, John R. Miles interviews Vice Admiral Walter &amp;ldquo;Ted&amp;rdquo; Carter Jr., USN (Ret.), the President of the University of Nebraska System. They discuss learning the key to personal growth, how the University of Nebraska responded to the COVID pandemic, and his leadership lessons for aspiring leaders. New Interviews with the World&amp;rsquo;s GREATEST high achievers will be posted every Tuesday with a Momentum Friday inspirational message! Carter discusses his journey to choosing the Naval Academy over attending Brown University and how it shaped the person he is today.</description></item><item><title>I Don’t Have Time Syndrome w/ John R. Miles Episode 27 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090361/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 03:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090361/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, John discusses one of the most common obstacles he confronts with passion seekers - the I don&amp;rsquo;t have time syndrome. I’m sure you’ve run into this person: The person who says, “I don’t have time for that” or “I’m way too busy to spend my time doing that.” In fact, that person may be you currently, and you know exactly how they feel. John discusses how growth seekers often, over and over, allow themselves to subsist in a chronic passion-less lifestyle driven by the choices that take them further from their dreams.</description></item><item><title>Astronaut Chris Cassidy On The Importance in Life of Being Present EP 26 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090362/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 03:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090362/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this powerful episode of the Passion Struck podcast, John R. Miles interviews Navy SEAL and NASA Astronaut Captain Chris Cassidy on the importance in life of being present and his journey from Midshipmen to highly decorated Navy SEAL and Chief Astronaut. New Interviews with the World&amp;rsquo;s GREATEST high achievers will be posted every Tuesday with a Momentum Friday inspirational message! In our discussion, Chris gives a unique perspective on how a single pivotal event changed his life and made him who he is today.</description></item><item><title>Are You Living a Pinball Life w/ John Miles EP 25 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090363/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 03:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090363/</guid><description>Podcast Description You may not think about it, but are you living a pinball life? Like a ball that drifts aimlessly without intentionality and with constant distraction. In this powerful Momentum Friday episode, John explains how so many of us do. we continuously react to what others are throwing our way, instead of being intentional with our passion. John gives a historical example of a famous American who was leading the pinball life and how he went on to not only discover but live his passion.</description></item><item><title>Dave Snowden On Applying Complexity Science to Ignite Your Passion EP 24 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090364/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 04:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090364/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, John R. Miles interviews Welch management consultant and researcher David &amp;ldquo;Dave&amp;rdquo; Snowden on applying complexity science to ignite your passion. They discuss complex adaptive systems theory and other scientific disciplines and their link to individual success. New Interviews with the World&amp;rsquo;s GREATEST high achievers will be posted every Tuesday with a Momentum Friday inspirational message! Dave Snowden discusses his company being acquired by IBM and his seven years with the tech behemoth.</description></item><item><title>5 Ways You Can Apply the Law of Attraction w/ John R. Miles EP 23 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090365/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 04:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090365/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this powerful Momentum Friday Episode, John R. Miles discusses 5 ways you can apply the law of attraction to create success in your life. New Interviews with the World&amp;rsquo;s GREATEST high achievers will be posted every Tuesday with a Momentum Friday inspirational message! Did you know that all molecules, whether they are living or not, vibrate at a specific frequency? Sound, light, physical objects, plants, animals, colors, thoughts, and emotions can carry, transmit, and absorb vibrational energy.</description></item><item><title>Julianna Sweeney On: Finding Your Life’s Mission Through Tragedy EP 22 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090366/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 04:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090366/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today&amp;rsquo;s episode of the Passion Struck podcast, John R. Miles interviews singer/songwriter Julianna Sweeney on finding your life&amp;rsquo;s mission through tragedy. New Interviews with the World&amp;rsquo;s GREATEST high achievers will be posted every Tuesday with a Momentum Friday inspirational message! Julianna and John discuss finding that burning desire in our life that gets us motivated in the morning to get up and conquer the world. You&amp;rsquo;ll hear from her about how she found her passion early in life and how that passion became such a provocative aspect, how not only she carries herself, but how she carries on her mom&amp;rsquo;s legacy through her music.</description></item><item><title>6 Steps To Finding Your Purpose In Life w/ John R. Miles EP 21 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090367/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090367/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s show, John shares his 6 steps to finding your purpose in life and discovering your passion once again. When we start our entrepreneurial journey, we are full of passion and purpose. However, along the way, life happens and our enthusiasm tempers down. From constant learning to defining your core values to surrounding yourself with the right people, we reveal some golden nuggets today. If you are looking to shed your distractions and lead a focused, purpose-driven life, listening to this show will particularly help you out.</description></item><item><title>Katie Higgins Cook On Becoming the First Female Blue Angels Pilot and Reinventing Yourself EP 20 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090368/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 03:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090368/</guid><description>Podcast Description Did you ever wonder who was the first female Blue Angels pilot? In this powerful interview, John R. Miles interviews Major Katie (Higgins) Cook, the first female to join the Blue Angels demonstration team. New Interviews with the World&amp;rsquo;s GREATEST high achievers will be posted every Tuesday with a Momentum Friday inspirational message! Ever wondered what it takes to not only become a Blue Angels pilot but to become the first female in the famed flying squadron?</description></item><item><title>Applying the Power of Choice — Why Our Choices Matter w/ John R. Miles EP 19 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090369/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 03:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090369/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s show is a very personal one about applying the power of choice in your life. Choices occur in our life every day, both unknowingly and knowingly. These can range from simple decisions like purchasing groceries or gas to the heavier ones about friends, influences, and beliefs. One thing is true for everyone: we all have the power of choice. It’s a critical part of our self-development and every one of the choices we make shape our experiences and brings you to where you are in your life.</description></item><item><title>What It Means To be a New Age Digital Leader w/ Sid Tobias EP 18 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090370/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090370/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s show, we interview Director, Digital Standards Office, Technology and Business Transformation, Advanced Education and Skills Training, Sid Tobias who shares with us his distilled wisdom on agile workflow and digital leadership. He mentors new digital teams with the BCDevExchange and teaches digital leadership to executives. Before this, Sid has served for 25 years in the Canadian Armed Forces. We start this show with Sid sharing a life-changing incident that sparked his interest in agile methodology.</description></item><item><title>5 Keys to Creating the Best Morning Routine w/ John R. Miles EP 17 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090371/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090371/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you following a morning routine that turbocharges your mind and body and sets you up for a superhuman performance? On today’s show, John shares the five steps for creating a perfect and impenetrable morning routine. You will learn how to awaken your body, mind, and then prioritize your intentions for the day. Topping off your day with your favorite activities can fill you up with energy, positivity, and fortitude.</description></item><item><title>How Shark Tank Changed Her Life to Overcome Personal Trauma w/ Tereson Dupuy EP 16 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090372/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090372/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ever wondered what sets successful entrepreneurs apart? And how they manage to overcome business and mental health challenges as they go about chasing their big goals? In today’s show, we interview FuzziBunz founder and Shark Tank participant, Tereson Dupuy shares with her distilled wisdom on entrepreneurship, persistence, and mental health. She discusses how Shark Tank changed her life. Growing up in New Orleans, Tereson was always driven and keen to make her own mark.</description></item><item><title>Passion Struck Coaching Process and Passion-Journey Accelerator EP 15 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090373/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090373/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this powerful Momentum Friday Episode, John R. Miles discusses the passion-struck coaching process that he uses to coach personal clients and consult with businesses. New Interviews with the World&amp;rsquo;s GREATEST high achievers will be posted every Tuesday with a Momentum Friday inspirational message! Ever wondered how successful people manage to adapt and reinvent themselves again and again? In today’s show, John walks us through the six-phase passion-struck process, which he has successfully used to help hundreds of clients to date.</description></item><item><title>Sharon Guerin On Unlocking Your Hidden Potential and Taking Control of Your Life EP 14 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090374/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090374/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s show, we interview Chef Sharon Guerin, who shares with us her life story about how she became an executive chef. And how she applied the Personal Agility methodology to unlock her hidden potential and take control of her life. Sharon has been cooking since the age of nine, and she always harbored this secret desire to be a chef and have her own cooking show. But then life happened.</description></item><item><title>Why Doing The Right Thing Is Hard w/John R. Miles EP 13 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090375/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090375/</guid><description>Podcast Description What would you do if you are at the crossroads of your life where you have the option of taking the harder right or, the easier wrong? On today’s show, John shares a deeply personal story where he chose the more difficult, harder path at the risk of jeopardizing his entire career. Additionally, you will learn the Three Things that will help you to make similarly difficult decisions. Back in military school, John found himself in the midst of a high-profile cheating scandal.</description></item><item><title>The Key to Finding Passion in Retirement w/Giles Stewart EP 12 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090376/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090376/</guid><description>Podcast Description You have a fulfilling career and now step into your next chapter. But, What is the key to finding passion in retirement. In this episode, John R. Miles interviews Giles Stewart about his career, it&amp;rsquo;s biggest moments, and how he is leading his best life as he enjoys retirement. Ever wondered how giant companies like Dell and Lowe’s face and overcome some of their biggest challenges? On today’s show, we interview Giles Stewart, a former Fortune 500 Executive who shares with us his wisdom on culture, empowerment, passion, retirement, and how future leaders can bring about positive change.</description></item><item><title>The Importance of a Mentor w/John R. Miles EP 11 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090377/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090377/</guid><description>Podcast Description What if you had a friend, a guide who was always there for you in your most difficult times? In today’s show, our host, John Miles shares how the importance of a mentor and why choosing the right one can make a massive difference to your life and career. Sharing his own experiences, John reveals how mentors have helped him immensely in his military, corporate as well as entrepreneurial career.</description></item><item><title>Overcoming Pancreatic Cancer and Taking Life to New Heights w/Sindy Hooper EP 10 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090378/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090378/</guid><description>Podcast Description The purpose of today&amp;rsquo;s show is to bring awareness to pancreatic cancer survival. In today’s show, John interviews Sindy Hooper about overcoming pancreatic cancer survivor and competing as an Ironman Triathlete. Sindy shares with us her incredible story of grit, hope, and finding success in extreme adversity. Back in 2013, things could not have been better for Sindy. She was leading a happy existence with her physician husband at their countryside home.</description></item><item><title>Stop Being A Visionary Arsonist and Self-Sabotaging Your Dreams w/John R. Miles EP 9 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090379/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 07:37:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090379/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s momentum Friday show, John unpacks the “visionary arsonist” concept. So often in our lives, you aim to reach the stars but often you end up burning down your own dreams and preventing yourself from achieving your main goal. As entrepreneurs, we love to innovate. And, we are constantly enamored by every shiny new object that crosses our path. We hate the status quo. And exploring the new and the unknown gives us an adrenaline rush that we find irresistible.</description></item><item><title>Keeping Your Focus While in Conflict w/Master Chief Tuck Williams EP 8 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090380/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 00:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090380/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s Passion Struck ™ podcast episode, John interviews his long-term friend and navy veteran Master Chief Tuck Williams who shares his wisdom on keeping your focus, conflict resolution, and managing change. Tuck joined the Navy in 1989 and recently retired after 30 years in service. Of these 30 years, Tuck spent 12 at sea. He has served in far-flung places like Spain and Japan and has been decorated with numerous service medals.</description></item><item><title>Applying the Mosquito Principle to Your Life w/John R. Miles EP 7 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090381/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090381/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s show, John explains applying the Mosquito Principle and its impact on maintaining your forward momentum. You will learn how the many “mosquitos” are sucking the motivation and impetus from your life The tiny mosquito is the most dangerous animal in the world and the cause behind diseases like malaria and the Zika virus. Just as these inconspicuous insects can wreck up our health, there are many tiny “mosquitos” in our life (read acquaintances and habits) that rob us of our forward momentum.</description></item><item><title>Applying Personal Agility to Unlock Your Passion w/Maria Matarelli EP 6 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090382/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090382/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wish to learn techniques that can work wonders for your professional life and your personal life? Today&amp;rsquo;s episode will teach you how you can apply personal agility to unlock your passion and creativity. In today’s show, we interview Maria Matarelli, CEO of Formula Ink and co-founder of the Agile Marketing Academy and Personal Agility Institute, where she reveals how her agile management strategies can catapult you miles ahead of the competition both in your business and personal life.</description></item><item><title>What Matthew McConaughey Taught Me About Showing Up w/John R. Miles EP5 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090383/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090383/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is the one thing that Matthew McConoughey taught me which had a profound impact on my life? It’s the importance of showing up. Matthew was a regular at our weekly congregation in Austin. He would show up unfailingly with his entire family, bring along his co-stars, and even mix freely with everyone. This had a huge impact on my son, who was facing a particularly tough time in middle school then.</description></item><item><title>David Dang On The Secret to Building a Magnetic Brand EP 4 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090384/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090384/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s show, we interview Digital Marketing Specialist and Instagram Expert David Dang, who shares his distilled wisdom on the secret to building a magnetic brand. You will learn how he discovered his superpower, which has helped him evolve into one of the most sought-after Instagram experts today. In 2006, when David moved to Canada from Vietnam, he did not speak a single English word. Over the years, he overcame this handicap by listening to audiobooks.</description></item><item><title>Maintaining Forward Momentum When All Odds Are Against You w/ John R. Miles EP 3 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090385/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090385/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ever wondered how you maintain your forward momentum in the face of extreme adversity? How can you keep anxiety and depression at bay even when all odds are stacked against you? In today’s show, John shares his wisdom on confronting your reality, unlocking human potential, and a positive mindset. Nearly 30 years back, John had the good fortune of meeting Admiral James Stockdale in his sophomore year at the Naval Academy.</description></item><item><title>Hugh Campbell On The Key to Becoming a Successful Entrepreneur EP 1 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090387/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090387/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ever wondered how successful business leaders constantly re-invent themselves? And, how they emerge even stronger after every crisis? Today&amp;rsquo;s episode will discuss just that and the key to becoming a successful entrepreneur. In today’s show, we have Hugh Campbell, a five-time serial entrepreneur and founder, AC4S Technologies, who shares his wisdom on growth, innovation, and integrity. You will learn how Hugh went from being a West Point graduate to successfully running a half-a-billion-dollar business.</description></item><item><title>Mac Brazina on Why Your Biggest Competitor is You EP 2 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090386/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090386/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s show, we have a chat with human building coach, Mac Brazina who shares her thoughts on cultivating mental toughness, self-care, and women’s empowerment. When Mac first started Human Builder, she was focusing solely on physical training. However, she soon found her true calling, which was helping her clients cultivate a stellar mindset. Be it the boxing ring, business, or life in general; you will learn that your biggest competition is with yourself.</description></item><item><title>Igniting Your Creativity and Unlocking Your Potential w/John R. Miles EP 0 | Passion Struck with John R. Miles</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9823090388/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 19:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9823090388/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s show is a special one, as John shares his big WHY that pushed him to start this show. John is a former NAVY combat veteran, multi-industry CEO, and human performance expert. He discusses his evolution and lessons for igniting your creativity and unlocking your potential. The Passion Struck podcast is meant to ignite your creativity, and unlock your hidden potential. In this show, business leaders, athletes, and entertainers shall be sharing their life story, their biggest fears, and how they pursued their passions in face of all odds.</description></item></channel></rss>