<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Rest Is Football on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/the-rest-is-football/</link><description>Recent content in The Rest Is Football on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 15:28:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/the-rest-is-football/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The £100m Bargain, City’s Glitch In The Algorithm &amp; The Joy Of Silencing The Fans | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330061/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 15:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can you be a bargain at £100m? Why are Man City struggling defensively at the moment? How does it feel to come up trumps after getting hammered by the opposition fans? Gary, Alan and Micah also reflect on a desperately disappointing game at Anfield and where that leaves both clubs. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Newcastle Pay The Price, The Battle For Ivan Toney &amp; Liverpool To Win the Europa League | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330001/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Should Newcastle have been less gung-ho in their attempt to reach the CL knockouts, which ultimately cost them a place in Europe altogether? Which club would Ivan Toney be best suited for if he was to leave Brentford? Can anyone stop Liverpool winning the Europa League? Gary, Alan and Micah also make their predictions on who will ultimately win this year’s Champions League. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Villa’s January Shopping List, Fighting Over Shirt Numbers &amp; Alan In The Jungle | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who should Aston Villa be looking to sign in January? What happens in the dressing room when another player wants your shirt number? Will Ant &amp;amp; Dec ever be successful in their attempts to tap Alan up to go into the jungle?
Gary, Alan and Micah also discuss what dangers the Premier League could face if 14 or more of the club’s owners are American. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Alarm Bells At Chelsea, The Myth Of Player Fatigue &amp; Front Foot Football | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 14:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is Pochettino the man to fix the problems at Chelsea? Are we focussing too much on the idea that players are fatigued? Why are we seeing sides really having a go at the traditional ‘top teams’ this season?
Gary, Alan and Micah also discuss the results of a poll about the use of VAR, after more than 100,000 fans voted. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description></item><item><title>Managers in a Grump, Villa Show Their Class &amp; Rice or Rodri? | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330004/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why exactly are certain managers being particularly prickly at the moment? How big a statement was Aston Villa’s performance against Man City? Alan and Micah clash over whether they would want Declan Rice or Rodri in their side.
Plus, the boys discuss the troubles at Nottingham Forest and whether Steve Cooper deserves more time in charge. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Danger Of Player Power, Celebrating A Manager's Sacking &amp; Micah’s Short-Lived Music Career | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330005/</guid><description>Podcast Description What’s the best way to deal with player power building in the dressing room? Which of our hosts saw team-mates actively celebrating when they found out their manager had been sacked? And how on earth did Micah Richards end up in a chart-topping music video?
Also, after the sex noises prank during the group stage draw for the Euros, Gary reflects on exactly what was going through his mind when it happened to him live on the BBC last season.</description></item><item><title>Drama At The Etihad, Man Utd’s Attitude Problems &amp; Nutella Sandwiches | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Did Spurs deserve a point against Man City? Is there any way back from the lack of desire some Man Utd players are showing on the pitch? Why on earth were Barcelona players asking for Nutella sandwiches after their matches?
The boys also discuss Liverpool having their own goal of the month competition at Anfield and a crucial win for Burnley. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>Sin-bins, A Tale Of Two Agüeros &amp; The Most Annoying Players | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330007/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Would the introduction of sin-bins be a good thing for football? Why was Sergio Agüero so different on a matchday compared to the rest of the time? Who were the most annoying players that Gary and Micah ever played against?
Alan also tell us what he would have done if he’d been playing for Newcastle in the Mike Ashley era. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description></item><item><title>Introducing... The Rest Is Entertainment | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 00:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330008/</guid><description>Podcast Description In their new podcast TV maestro and hugely successful author Richard Osman, along with The Guardian&amp;rsquo;s razor-sharp columnist Marina Hyde unravel the mysteries and unveil the hidden gems within the vast landscape of entertainment. Blending knowledge, humour, and insight as industry insiders they&amp;rsquo;ll talk television, films, books, music and celebrity gossip as well as offering an enticing peek behind the curtain.
Listen to the full episode now by searching The Rest Is Entertainment wherever you get your podcasts.</description></item><item><title>Micah’s Curse On Alisson, Villa The Real Deal &amp; The Best Ever PL Goal? | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330009/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Did Micah’s pre-match chat with Alisson play a few mind games before his performance against Man City? Will Aston Villa be able to sustain their Top 4 push? Was Alejandro Garnacho’s overhead kick the best goal ever scored in the Premier League? Gary, Alan and Micah also reflect on a big weekend at the bottom of the table. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Remembering the Great Terry Venables | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330010/</guid><description>Podcast Description After the sad news that Terry Venables passed away at the weekend, Gary, Alan and Micah reflect on the incredible person that he was and his tremendous impact on the game of football.
He was Gary’s manager at Barcelona and Tottenham, Alan’s manager with England for Euro 96 and was part of the national set-up as assistant manager for Micah.
We hear stories of his genius footballing brain and the innovations he would try in training, his brilliant man-management skills in handling strong personalties like Paul Gascoigne and how he loved a good sing-song.</description></item><item><title>Mid-Term Reports - All 20 PL Clubs Reviewed | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330011/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who thinks Man City won’t win the league this year? Who has got the best chance of gatecrashing the Top 4? Will Everton survive after their points deduction? Gary, Alan and Micah look back at the predictions they made at the start of the season, to see what they’ve got right and where they’ve been going wrong. They go through all 20 Premier League teams to look at the challenges they face and any surprises we might see between now and the end of the season.</description></item><item><title>A Run in with Roy Keane, England’s Best XI &amp; Battles at the Britannia | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why did Roy Keane threaten to knock Alan out on the pitch? What do Gary, Alan and Micah think is England’s best starting XI? And what was it really like having to go to battle against Tony Pulis’ Stoke City? We also hear the story of when Gazza brought his new Winnebago to training and ended up giving one fan a journey he would never forget. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Everton’s Financial Troubles, The Case For Appeal and What Next For Man City &amp; Chelsea? | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330013/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330013/</guid><description>Podcast Description With Everton having been docked ten points for breaching Premier League financial rules, Gary and Alan are joined by journalist Nick Harris of Sporting Intelligence to discuss the reasoning behind the dramatic decision. Also discussed are the implications for Manchester City, currently facing 115 charges for alleged breaches of the League’s financial rules. Charges Manchester City deny.
Anyone wanting to read the full reasons for the Everton judgement can do so here: https://resources.</description></item><item><title>The Biggest Danger To English Football, Salary Caps &amp; How Much Money Do Football Clubs Lose? | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330014/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330014/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is the biggest threat to the growth, or even survival, of domestic football? Would salary caps help level the playing field? Is it ok for football clubs to continually lose money? Crystal Palace co-owner and chairman Steve Parish joins Gary and Alan on today’s episode to discuss what it’s really like running a professional football club. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Losing The Dressing Room, Bobby Robson’s Dodgy Phone Call &amp; Why The World Cup Should Be Every Two Years | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330015/</guid><description>Podcast Description What actually happens when a senior player turns against the manager? Why did one of Bobby Robson’s phone calls have Gary and the team in fits of laughter? Who thinks the World Cup SHOULD be every two years? Gary, Alan and Micah also discuss which British football team they would each have loved to have played for. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Stamford Bridge Thriller, Liverpool Definite Contenders &amp; Villa Flying High | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Should Man City have sold Cole Palmer to Chelsea? Are Liverpool the biggest threat to Man City retaining their title? Will Aston Villa crash the top four this season? The boys also discuss what will be going through Rasmus Højlund’s mind, as his Premier League goal drought continues after a big money move. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Shevchenko: Nightmare In Istanbul, Getting Married On A Golf Course &amp; Ronaldinho or Kaká? | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330017/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Which specific moment from that Champions League final against Liverpool kept Andriy awake at night for three months? How did he end up getting married on the 14th green of a golf course? And which Brazilian genius did Andriy think was better - Ronaldinho or Kaká? In the second part of our special with the Ukrainian Ballon d’Or winner, Gary also finds out what went wrong during his spell at Chelsea.</description></item><item><title>Mexican Wrestling, FIFA Ratings and Smoking In The Dressing Room | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Has Micah found a new calling in Latin America? How upset do players get with poor FIFA ratings? Who was sneaking off for a cheeky cigarette minutes before kick off? The boys also debate who the second best striker in the Premier League is, after Erling Haaland. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Arteta’s Outburst, Rashford’s Party and Golf With The President | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Was Mikel Arteta right to have a rant about VAR after Arsenal’s defeat? Should Marcus Rashford have been out celebrating his birthday after Manchester United were embarrassed in the derby? How did Gary’s search for Maradona end up with him playing golf with the President? Plus, the boys reflect on a very emotional day for Luis Diaz as he rescues a point for Liverpool and dedicates his goal to his father, who is still missing.</description></item><item><title>Shevchenko: Champions League Celebrations, Ballon d’Or Brilliance &amp; Assisting a Heart Transplant | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330020/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why did the AC Milan players end up celebrating on a golf course at 5am after their Champions League win? What did Andriy think was the key reason why he won the Ballon d’Or? And how exactly did he end up assisting in a heart transplant operation? On today’s episode, Gary Lineker is joined by Ukrainian football legend Andriy Shevchenko. You can buy Andriy’s new book My Life, My Football here: https://backpagepress.</description></item><item><title>Gazza's Air Rifle, Balotelli's Fireworks and the worst thing about being a footballer | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330021/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330021/</guid><description>Podcast Description What happened when Paul Gascoigne brought an air rifle to training? How did Mario Balotelli almost end up repeating his fireworks fiasco? And what’s the least enjoyable thing about being a professional footballer? Gary, Alan and Micah also discuss the best goal they scored during their careers. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>City Rule Manchester, Haaland vs Kane, and Bellingham beats Barcelona | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 01:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Micah hot foots it back from Old Trafford to reflect on a humiliating defeat for United in the Manchester derby. Alan Shearer is forced to choose between Erling Haaland and Harry Kane. And Gary marvels at the match winning performance of Jude Bellingham for Real Madrid in El Classico. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Abuse From Your Own Fans, Fashion Faux Pas &amp; Why Always Meeks? | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330023/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330023/</guid><description>Podcast Description What’s it like when your own fans turn against you? Was Man City’s dress code for their Champions League match the worst we’ve ever seen? And after a wardrobe malfunction of his own on live TV, Micah is left asking ‘Why always Meeks?’. Gary, Alan and Micah also discuss whether Spurs are now a better team without Harry Kane and how the England captain will be feeling watching on from Munich.</description></item><item><title>Getting Catfished for Match Tickets, Konsa for England and the Most Embarrassing Sponsor Mishaps | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who got catfished for a pair of tickets to the Players’ Lounge for the biggest game of the season? Why is Ezri Konsa not getting a look in for the England squad? And who got caught out because they had their own name plastered all over the side of a sponsored car?
Plus, Gary, Alan and Micah discuss who they would start, bench or sack out of Kieran Trippier, Gary Neville and Terry Butcher.</description></item><item><title>The Great Sir Bobby Charlton, Tremendous Trippier and Micah’s Minibar Madness | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gary reveals the impact that Sir Bobby Charlton had on him and his career, as Alan and Micah debate whether he was England’s greatest ever player. Plus, the lads discuss where Kieran Trippier sits on the list of the world’s best full backs and Micah tells us about the time he got a little too excited with the hotel minibar. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description></item><item><title>Altercations With Fans, England’s Best Player Never to Win a Cap and a Nightmare at the Allianz | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330026/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330026/</guid><description>Podcast Description What got Micah hot under the collar at Kidderminster Harriers? Who is the best English player never to get an international call up? And who called for the subs’ bench after a torrid time against Bayern Munich? Plus, Gary tells Alan and Micah how Terry Venables helped him through one of his darkest times after his son George was diagnosed with leukaemia. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>England Beat Italy and Qualify for Euros | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330027/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gary, Alan and Micah discuss a Jude Bellingham masterclass as England come from behind to beat Italy at Wembley. Two goals from Harry Kane, including his 21st penalty for England, plus a rocket from Marcus Rashford give the boys great hope that England could go all the way next summer. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Beckham versus Hoddle, Gazza’s Golf Routine and Why Lampard Blanked Big Meeks | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330028/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Was Glenn Hoddle right to blame David Beckham for England going out of the World Cup? How did Paul Gascoigne entertain Gary and co on his first international call up? And what made Frank Lampard blank Micah Richards at Stamford Bridge? Gary Lineker is joined by Alan Shearer and Micah Richards to talk all things football. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Thierry Henry on Lionel Messi, THAT Pires penalty, and Arteta's Arsenal | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330029/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Which Premier League player is the only one to come close to Lionel Messi? What happened during that infamous Pires-Henry penalty against Man City? Does Arteta have what it takes to go all the way at Arsenal?
For the second of two episodes, Alan, Micah and Gary are joined by Premier League great, Thierry Henry. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Half-time Bollockings, Horror Injuries &amp; Acting Debuts | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330030/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330030/</guid><description>Podcast Description What was the worst a manager let rip in the dressing room? How do serious injuries affect the whole team? And who had to do the most ridiculous TV advert?
Gary, Alan and Micah also compare their favourite shirt swaps and debate who got the best one. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Advantage Arsenal, Last Gasp United, and Spurs for the Title? | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330031/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Micah races back from the Emirates to join Alan and Gary as the boys reflect on a dramatic weekend of football.Have Arsenal taken a psychological advantage over title rivals Manchester City? Has Scott McTominay saved Manchester United from another week of soul searching? And are Raheem Sterling, Nick Pope and James Ward-Prowse all unlucky not to be in Gareth Southgate’s England squad? Spurs title chances, Jude Bellingham’s latest superstar performance for Real Madrid and Olivier Giroud’s remarkable goalkeeping feat also feature.</description></item><item><title>Thierry Henry on Arsene Wenger, Pep Guardiola, and 'Va Va Voom' | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330032/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who does Thierry Henry think was better: Wenger of Guardiola? Why did Arsenal fans shout abuse at him in his early days? Why did he have to hide his fear of failure from Martin Keown and Tony Adams?
On today&amp;rsquo;s episode of The Rest Is Football, the boys are joined by France and Arsenal legend, Thierry Henry. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>England Bonuses, Brazilian Ronaldo and Maradona Mayhem | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330033/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330033/</guid><description>Podcast Description What did each of Gary, Alan and Micah do with their England bonuses and who forced Micah to give his away? How good was the Brazilian Ronaldo? And who stopped Diego Maradona falling off a balcony at the Bombonera? Plus Gary recounts the night he thought his career was over. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Time to Scrap VAR? | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330034/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330034/</guid><description>Podcast Description After another horrendous weekend for VAR, Gary, Alan and Micah wonder if the time has come to scrap football’s video refereeing experiment. And if it does stay, how can it be improved? Plus, what’s it like in a toxic dressing room? And is Ollie Watkins England’s second best striker? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trouble in Naples and the Next Steven Gerrard | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330035/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Micah, Gary and Alan reflect on the shocking treatment of Victor Osimhen by his own club Napoli. Plus, have Liverpool uncovered the next Steven Gerrard? Alan enjoys Newcastle’s victory over Manchester City and the boys recall their experiences playing with the world’s best golfers. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Agents, Ferraris and Top Teams | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330036/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Micah describes the day he knew he was going to make it as a footballer. Gary tells the story of the day he tried to mark Bryan Robson. And Alan explains why he’d play for Manchester City given half a chance. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Battle for North London, Rampant Newcastle and the Gap at the Bottom | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330037/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330037/</guid><description>Podcast Description What did we learn from the North London Derby? Have Newcastle kick started their season? And is the gap between the Premier League and the Championship growing? Gary, Alan and Micah also discuss how the handball law has become so ludicrous. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Who is the greatest Striker of this generation, England Keepers and Manchester City post Pep | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330038/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 12:55:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who is the greatest striker of recent years? As Robert Lewandowski reaches the milestone of 100 goals in European football Gary, Alan and Micah debate the best number nines in the game. After a busy week of European competition the boys look back on all the key action as well as discussing the competition between English goalkeepers to be Gareth Southgate’s number one at next summer’s European Championship. Plus they imagine life at Manchester City when Pep Guardiola eventually decides to move on.</description></item><item><title>Strange Injuries, Selling Salah &amp; Britain’s Next Top Manager | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Micah Richards recalls his bizarre bedroom-based injury, Gary reveals the Match of the Day running order league table, and the boys wonder if Liverpool should cash in on Mo Salah in January. Plus, who are the best managers outside the Premier League and which current players would make top future pundits? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Man United Mess, Players with Terrible Timekeeping and the Joy of Late, Late Goals | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330040/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 14:20:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have Manchester United got a culture problem and if so can Erik ten Hag sort it out? Gary, Micah and Alan examine the problems at a club with so many players under public scrutiny. Alan describes the challenges of enforcing good timekeeping on a difficult dressing room and Micah wonders whether the players are enjoying the longer playing time this season quite as much as the fans are. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Breathtaking Bellingham, How Barca Lost Messi and the Guardiola Effect | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330041/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is Jude Bellingham destined to be one of the world’s greatest? How exactly did Barcelona lose the world’s best footballer? Has anyone had a bigger impact on English football than Pep Guardiola in the last decade?
Spanish football expert Sid Lowe joins Gary to look into what’s going on at Real Madrid and Barcelona and discuss the impact Spain has had on the Premier League and English football as a whole.</description></item><item><title>Excellent England, Doping in Football, and New Owners at Everton? | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330042/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Recorded immediately after England’s victory over Scotland, Gary, Alan and Micah debate the quality of the current England team and enjoy a brilliant performance from Real Madrid’s newest star Jude Bellingham. Plus the boys evaluate the standing of Kyle Walker in the pantheon of England right backs. Also up for discussion are doping in football, the potential take-over at Everton, and the time Micah turned up for England duty with four left boots.</description></item><item><title>England Coaches, Player Loyalty and Gary’s Management Offer | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330043/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Should the next England manager be English? Gary, Alan and Micah discuss Gareth Southgate’s potential successor should he walk away post-Euros. Why are Jordan Henderson and Harry Maguire starting for England while not playing regularly for a top tier team? And which Premier League club offered Gary the manager’s job. Plus the boys look ahead to Scotland v England and reflect on the great rivalry between Lionel Messi and Cristiano Ronaldo.</description></item><item><title>Southgate’s Choices, Brilliant Beckham and Butcher’s Caged Tigers | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330044/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330044/</guid><description>Podcast Description In our international football special Gareth Southgate’s England selection comes under scrutiny from Gary, Alan and Micah. Do England really have the best front six in world football? Plus why does Micah love David Beckham so much? And how did Terry Butcher’s caged tigers help England win away in Yugoslavia? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Balotelli, Bollocks and Barcelona | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330045/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330045/</guid><description>Podcast Description How Mario Balotelli ruined Micah’s first day at his new club. Was Alan really worth £200 million in his pomp? And why did Gary find himself talking bollocks abroad. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Manager Player Fall-outs, Hat-trick Heroes &amp; are Spurs Better Without Kane? | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330046/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Should managers ever publicly criticise players? Has Evan Ferguson got a bit of Erling Haaland about him? And is it possible that Spurs could become a better all-round team without Harry Kane?
Gary also explains how the Match of the Day running order is chosen and why your team isn’t always last on! Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>HERE WE GO! Fabrizio Romano takes us inside the World of Transfers | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330047/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330047/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Deadline Day the transfer specialist Fabrizio Romano explains what goes on behind-the-scenes of this mysterious part of the football world. How exactly does he find out about deals? Why do players contact him directly? And how did Bruno Fernandes change his life? Gary, Alan and Micah also find out which transfer scoop was Fabrizio’s favourite and which team he actually supports. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>How Micah Lost a Million Quid and Alan Found his Trainers | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330048/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Micah Richards describes the goal that lost him a million pounds and names the player who made his life hell at Manchester City. Alan Shearer reveals the truth about his stolen trainers and Gary Lineker describes the utter devastation of losing the World Cup semi-final to West Germany and recounts the sing-song that brought the squad back together. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Battle of St James’ Park, Penalty Misses and the Rise of a Teenage Superstar. | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330049/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 13:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Drama and controversy again in the Premier League as Gary, Alan and Micah debate red cards, red comebacks and penalty misses. Was the Virgil van Dijk challenge a red card? Is this Darwin Nunez’s break out season? The usually faultless Erling Haaland’s penalty miss reminds Alan and Gary of their own spot kick embarrassments. Plus the lads discuss the latest brilliant Barca teenage phenomenon. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Magical Messi and Brilliant Bellingham | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330050/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330050/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a week of stark contrasts, Gary, Alan and Micah discuss the ongoing crisis at Manchester United as the Mason Greenwood situation continues to unravel. They also reflect on the career of the great Lionel Messi after he adds yet another trophy to his collection. Plus Jude Bellingham’s remarkable impact in La Liga, how has his career risen so smoothly? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description></item><item><title>Fernandes’ Moaning, Referees That Gave It Back and Amsterdam Holidays | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330051/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Should the captain be the only player allowed to speak to the referee? What if your captain is the biggest moaner of the lot?
Which referees had the best banter and weren’t afraid to give you stick back? Which two teammates would the lads pick to go to Amsterdam on holiday with?
Gary, Alan and Micah answer these and more of your listener questions. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Trouble at Old Trafford, Brilliant Brighton and Everton Alarm | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330052/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 14:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Manchester United baffled Micah in their first two games of the season, so what’s wrong with ten Hag’s men? And where exactly should Marcus Rashford play? Plus league leaders Brighton won comfortably at Wolves with a Mitoma wonder goal, as Everton sank into early season gloom. We’re also joined by Karen Carney to reflect on the Lionesses performance at the Women’s World Cup and the future of the women’s game in the UK.</description></item><item><title>VAR, Players as Referees and Big Club Bias | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330053/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 14:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Will the fans ever get to hear what’s going on with VAR decisions? Should ex-players be helping referees? And is there really a ‘big club’ bias?
The boys are joined by Howard Webb to discuss all matters referees and VAR. Howard also finally apologises to Alan for his decision that helped relegate Newcastle back in 2009. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>From Gazza to Haaland | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330054/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330054/</guid><description>Podcast Description How did Gary Lineker get Paul Gascoigne into hot water and which current Premier League player reminds Alan Shearer of himself? Gary, Alan and Micah Richards answer listener questions. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Salah’s Tantrum, Caicedo’s Crazy Price and Pitchside Bust-Ups | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330055/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 15:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gary, Micah and Alan reflect on the first weekend of the Premier League season. They ask why strikers go off at the deep end and how a defensive midfielder can really be worth £115m. Plus, after some decent debuts, the boys look back on their own first games at the top level. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Harry Kane: Deal Done! | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330056/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 09:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330056/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this emergency podcast, Gary and Micah get Alan on the phone for his reaction as Kane’s move to Bayern is finally sealed. Will he be able to contain his glee with the Premier League goalscoring record being safe for the foreseeable future? They discuss what it means for Kane’s career and how Spurs move forward without him. They also reflect on Man City’s victory over Burnley and consider another transfer saga: the future of Brighton’s Moises Caicedo.</description></item><item><title>All 20 PL Clubs Predicted! | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330057/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who will be top four? Who’s heading for the drop? Which teams will surprise and which will disappoint? In this special episode, Gary, Alan, and Micah look ahead to the new Premier League Season. They evaluate every one of the twenty Premier League clubs, predicting where they will finish. A Goalhanger Podcasts Production Produced by Harry Lineker Exec Producer: Tony Pastor &amp;amp; Jack Davenport Socials: @RestIsFootball Email: therestisfootball@gmail.com Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Dream Team Mates | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330058/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330058/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the second episode of their new podcast, Gary, Alan and Micah answer your questions. The guys discuss who they would most liked to have played with, who they’ve been starstruck by and which opponents they feared the most. They also look back on England’s victory over Nigeria in the Women’s World Cup and ask whether the Lionesses can go all the way. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>New Season, New Podcast | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330059/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gary Lineker, Alan Shearer and Micah Richards celebrate the start of the season by launching The Rest Is Football. In the first full-length episode, Gary makes a surprising Premier League prediction, Micah worries about where Declan Rice will play at Arsenal and Alan continues to keep his fingers crossed for a Harry Kane move abroad. Plus, with the window still open, the guys tell the inside stories of their big transfers; how close Alan was to joining Manchester United twice and what happened when Micah met a manager in secret… A Goalhanger Podcasts Production Produced by Paul King &amp;amp; Harry Lineker Exec Producer: Tony Pastor &amp;amp; Jack Davenport Socials: @RestIsFootball Email: therestisfootball@gmail.</description></item><item><title>The Rest Is Football: Trailer | The Rest Is Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3134330060/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 00:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3134330060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gary Lineker, Alan Shearer and Micah Richards reveal a new podcast launching on Monday 7th of August ahead of the new football season. In this trailer episode, Gary talks about hiding behind a bush to escape a pre-season fitness test, Micah tells all about a disastrous summer holiday in Ayia Napa and why Alan is putting his chauffeur’s hat on to drive Harry Kane to the airport. Follow now so you don&amp;rsquo;t miss our first full length episode on Monday.</description></item></channel></rss>