<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Try This on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/try-this/</link><description>Recent content in Try This on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 11:55:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/try-this/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What to do if you’re up in the middle of the night | Try This</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1076140001/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 11:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1076140001/</guid><description>Podcast Description In class 3 of our course about how to get better sleep, we dig in on a moment most of us are familiar with – waking up in the middle of the night and not being able to fall back asleep. Sometimes our default setting is to keep thinking our endless thoughts, but, it turns out, what we really need is a distraction. And you want to make sure to find the right kind of distraction – one that requires little to no thinking or mental commitment.</description></item><item><title>Go ahead. Think about the thing that’s keeping you up. | Try This</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1076140002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 11:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1076140002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lying awake at night, ruminating over stuff that bothers you is not fun. But it’s normal! We’ve all done it and it can get in the way of the rest you need. In class 2 of our course on how to sleep better, Cristina walks us through how trying to suppress your difficult feelings from popping up at night might be counterproductive. Sleep expert Lisa Strauss explains a technique for identifying and changing negative thought patterns.</description></item><item><title>Stop trying to fall asleep | Try This</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1076140003/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1076140003/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this first class of our course on how to get better sleep, host Cristina Quinn outlines why trying to get yourself to sleep can sometimes be a barrier to getting rest. But if we shouldn't will ourselves to sleep, what should we do instead? Cristina talks to an expert with a clear plan for how to tackle anxiety at bedtime by taking some tangible steps during the day.</description></item><item><title>Introducing “Try This” | Try This</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1076140004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 17:26:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1076140004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Meet The Washington Post’s Cristina Quinn, who is always game to try something new. She is your guide in “Try This” — a new series of audio courses from The Post that will provide quick, fresh and practical approaches to tackling the kind of hurdles we all face: how to sleep better, get the most out of our relationships, get out of our own way and more. Follow “Try This” now so you catch the first course when it drops Tuesday, Dec.</description></item></channel></rss>