<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/conan-obrien-needs-a-friend/</link><description>Recent content in Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 05:05:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/conan-obrien-needs-a-friend/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Albert Brooks and Rob Reiner | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370440/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370440/</guid><description>Podcast Description Albert Brooks feels confused about being Conan O’Brien’s friend; Rob Reiner feels almost honored to be Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Albert Brooks and Rob Reiner sit down with Conan to discuss their new documentary Albert Brooks: Defending My Life, legendary bits from The Tonight Show lost to time, the fleeting nature of fame and legacy, and much more.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.
Got a question for Conan?</description></item><item><title>Conan Gourley | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370439/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370439/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to Isabel from southern West Virginia about establishing a self-sustaining homestead and how Conan would fill his time if he were forced off the grid.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Adam Driver Live at the Brooklyn Academy of Music | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370438/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370438/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Adam Driver feels thrilled to be Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Adam sits down with Conan Live at the Brooklyn Academy of Music to discuss starting his own fight club, learning how to send a telegraph for Lincoln, and portraying Enzo Ferrari in his new film Ferrari. Plus, Conan, Matt, and Sona answer live audience questions about a new couple’s compatibility, casting the Chill Chums movie, and teaching college courses.</description></item><item><title>People Be Doin’ It | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370437/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370437/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Hannah from Vancouver about working on a yacht, the name of Conan’s boat, and how to handle high maintenance guests.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Robert Smigel (and Triumph the Insult Comic Dog) | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370436/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370436/</guid><description>Podcast Description Triumph the Insult Comic Dog feels very proud to be Marc Maron’s friend.
Robert Smigel sits down with Conan to discuss trying every idea in the early days of Late Night, remembering propmaster Bill Tull, the origin of the Triumph puppet, and writing the new Adam Sandler animated film Leo.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (669) 587-2847.</description></item><item><title>Medicine Is The Best Medicine | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370435/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370435/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Chris from Chico, CA about life as a paramedic and why he refuses to dress up for Halloween.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mike Birbiglia Returns | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370434/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370434/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Mike Birbiglia feels ambitious about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Mike sits down with Conan once again to discuss their casual run-ins with each other, storytelling as cultural tradition, and confronting mortality in his latest special The Old Man and the Pool.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (669) 587-2847.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Married with No Benefits | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370433/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370433/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to Cammy from Buenos Aires about her work as a translator, the rules of dating, and Conan’s potential as a wingman.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Flula Borg Returns | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan O’Brien feels okay about being Flula Borg’s friend.
Flula sits down with Conan once again to discuss his special healthy diet, what confuses him about America, and what kind of family he wants. Plus, Conan answers voicemails from none other than Flula himself.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com. Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (669) 587-2847.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>It’s Wine O’Clock Everywhere | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Yvonne from Hawke&amp;rsquo;s Bay, New Zealand about smelling wine, tasting wine, and then just all be drunk.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Please Don’t Destroy (with Special Guest Paul Rudd) Live at the Brooklyn Academy of Music | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedy trio Please Don’t Destroy feels too young to be Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Ben, John, and Martin sit down with Conan to discuss bringing their act in front of Lorne Michaels, their unique group dynamic, and playing with the evolution of sketch comedy. Plus, Paul Rudd drops by with a special treat for Conan, and the Chums take audience questions about turning into a chair, Halloween costumes, childhood crushes, and more.</description></item><item><title>Old Sharp-Ass | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Brice from Ames, Iowa about haulin’ horses, whether horses get jet lagged, and riding sidesaddle. Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Reggie Watts | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 05:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian and musician Reggie Watts feels quixotic about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Reggie sits down with Conan to discuss his new book Great Falls, MT: Fast Times, Post-Punk Weirdos, and a Tale of Coming Home Again, mashing up music and comedy in his thirties, and childhood heroes Pippi Longstocking and Ferris Bueller. Plus, new numbers debut in the team’s race for Most Popular Sandwich.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Three Days From Retirement | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Bill from Winthrop Harbor, Illinois about his German Shepherd Hondo, working for a funeral home, and retirement life for dogs.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Werner Herzog | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370007/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Werner Herzog feels a little bit weird about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Conan sits down with Werner to talk about traveling great distances by foot, moving a ship over a mountain, and watching Here Comes Honey Boo Boo.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (669) 587-2847.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ambassador Rahm Emanuel | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370008/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ambassador Rahm Emanuel feels a tremendous amount of self-loathing about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Rahm sits down with Conan to discuss prioritizing time with his family, serving as ambassador to Japan, opposing the raw exercise of power on the world stage, and the current situation in Israel and Gaza.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (669) 587-2847.</description></item><item><title>The Gossip Girl of Thames New Zealand | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Amalia from Thames, New Zealand about living in a small town and Conan running said town. Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dave Grohl, Krist Novoselic, and “In Utero” producer Steve Albini | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dave Grohl, Krist Novoselic, and Steve Albini feel good, jazzy and anxiety about being Conan O’Brien’s Friend. Dave Grohl, Krist Novoselic, and producer Steve Albini discuss the making of Nirvana’s “In Utero” on its 30th Anniversary.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com. Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (669) 587-2847.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sgt. Microphone Glassian | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with zookeeper Joy from Columbus, Ohio about penguins, hellbenders, and snot otters.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sir Patrick Stewart | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sir Patrick Stewart feels proud, happy, honored to be Conan O’Brien’s Friend.
Sir Patrick Stewart sits down with Conan to talk about his humble roots, his new book Making It So, and about what it’s like for the two of them to share a passionate kiss. And later, the gang discusses yet another new podcast from Matt Gourley.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>I’ve Needled Many A Perineum | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Sarah from Portland, Oregon about being a new listener, acupuncture, and dubious nether-regions needle placement.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Arnold Schwarzenegger | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Arnold Schwarzenegger feels how the f@#k would he know about being Conan O’Brien’s friend. Conan the Barbarian meets Conan the O’Brien as the two discuss Schwarzenegger&amp;rsquo;s philosophies on exercising, making oneself useful, and feeding little oatmeal cookies to tiny farm animals named Lulu, Whiskey, and Schnelly.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com. Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (669) 587-2847.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Life Of Reilly | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to Reilly from Hokitika, New Zealand about living in a container house, Conan’s anime persona, and the key to a simple life.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ed Sheeran Live from the SiriusXM Garage | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ed Sheeran feels wank about being Conan O&amp;rsquo;Brien&amp;rsquo;s friend.
Live from the SiriusXM Garage, singer-songwriter Ed Sheeran sits down with Conan to talk about emulating his music heroes, the inspiration for his new album Autumn Variations, and unlikely celebrity run-ins. Plus, Conan and his team answer audience questions about their favorite films, childhood aspirations, and more.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.
Got a question for Conan?</description></item><item><title>Craic Mechanic | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Aoife in Connemara about working as a wedding DJ, helping people discover their singing voices, and dealing with the inner critic.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jim Downey | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedy writer Jim Downey feels entirely unapologetic about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Jim sits down with Conan to discuss his favorite sketches from the early days of SNL, acting opposite Daniel Day-Lewis in There Will Be Blood, and fine tuning Weekend Update with Norm Macdonald.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (669) 587-2847.
This episode was recorded on 9/11/2023.</description></item><item><title>Yope | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan speaks to Gualter from Portugal about working as a tailor and what kind of suit he would make for Conan.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Maria Bamford | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actress and comedian Maria Bamford feels excited about being Conan O’Brien’s friend (if he needs her friendship).
Maria sits down with Conan to discuss her new book Sure, I’ll Join Your Cult: A Memoir of Mental Illness and the Quest to Belong Anywhere, the compulsion to consider everything and to share everything, being trained in the Suzuki method of violin, and the roadblocks of getting treatment for an eating disorder.</description></item><item><title>Bike Pervert | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370021/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Rene from the Netherlands about designing custom bicycles, horse riding underwear, and Conan’s favorite biking trails.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cedric the Entertainer | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Cedric the Entertainer feels short, indifferent, sometimes angry about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Cedric sits down with Conan to discuss working as a State Farm claims adjuster, how Steve Harvey helped launch his career, the human message behind The Neighborhood, and his new novel Flipping Boxcars. Plus, Conan and his team provide tips on getting a voicemail through to the show.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Would You Like A Selfie? | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Kayla about their several chance encounters and to see if he can help her expedite her new passport.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Questlove | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Legendary hip-hop musician Questlove feels fine with being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Questlove sits down with Conan to discuss his classical musical training, the improbable genesis of The Roots, how they “pulled a Hendrix” to come out on top, and curating experimental playlists for high-profile friends.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.
This episode was recorded on 6/20/23.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Summer S’mores with Conan and the Chill Chums Season 3 Episode 6 | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370025/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370025/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the Summer S&amp;rsquo;mores finale, Conan expresses his deep and profound shame at his own indulgence around the campfire.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Liam Neeson | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370026/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Liam Neeson feels like he wants to sing, but also a bit nervous about being friends with Conan O’Brien.
Liam sits down with Conan to discuss his real-life set of particular skills, working at the Guinness plant, and his personal litmus test when reading a script for the first time. Later, David Hopping gives a first-hand report from the Taylor Swift concert.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Summer S’mores with Conan and the Chill Chums Season 3 Episode 5 | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370027/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370027/</guid><description>Podcast Description The wheels begin to fall off as Conan and the Chill Chums eat their own pizza faces and roast dessert bananas.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Steve Martin and Martin Short | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370028/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Martin Short feels duped about being Conan O’Brien’s friend. Steve Martin feels sad about being Conan O’Brien’s only friend.
Martin and Steve sit down to talk with Conan about his cameo appearance in their live show, season 3 of Only Murders in the Building, the origin of their working partnership, and run-ins with Elvis and Frank Sinatra.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.
This episode was recorded on 5/17/2023.</description></item><item><title>Summer S’mores with Conan and the Chill Chums Season 3 Episode 4 | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370029/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan and the Chill Chums take a moment to appreciate a pizza art gallery featuring their likenesses.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>John Mulaney Returns Again | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370030/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370030/</guid><description>Podcast Description John Mulaney feels [redacted] about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
John and Conan sit down to discuss the mystery of how art gets financed, seeking attention as kids, and early morning wiffle ball games with his son. Plus, Conan finally delivers on his long-awaited gift for Matt Gourley’s birthday.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.
This episode was recorded on 8/7/2023.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Summer S’mores with Conan and the Chill Chums Season 3 Episode 3 | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370031/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan and the Chill Chums get a hands on lesson in pizza crafting from their Solo Stove representatives.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Matthew Rhys Returns | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370032/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Matthew Rhys feels equal parts confused and terrified about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Matthew sits down with Conan once more to discuss competing for the role of James Bond, riding vintage motorcycles on Perry Mason, purchasing and restoring a 1939 Wheeler Playmate antique wooden boat, and more. Plus, Conan recalls the time Andy Richter stepped up to help out with a dental procedure.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Remembering Paul Reubens | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370033/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan shares memories of the great Paul Reubens before revisiting their interview on the podcast.
Original episode release date: March 9, 2020
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Summer S’mores with Conan and the Chill Chums Season 3 Episode 2 | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370034/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan and the Chill Chums take in breathtaking views, enjoy a seasonal beverage, and rate each other’s fashion choices on another Summer S’mores special.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Roy Wood Jr. | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370035/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Roy Wood Jr. feels thankful about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Roy sits down with Conan to discuss tailoring an effective set for the White House Correspondents’ Dinner, honing crowd work during sports practice, and the changing landscape of informational media. Plus, the competitive energy heightens as Conan, Matt, and Sona compare the relative popularity of their eponymous sandwiches.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.</description></item><item><title>Summer S’mores with Conan and the Chill Chums Season 3 Episode 1 | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370036/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan and the Chill Chums plan out the rest of their summer by deciding their hypothetical last meals on a Summer S’mores special.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>David Byrne | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370037/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Talking Heads frontman David Byrne feels carefree and buoyant about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
David sits down with Conan to discuss his Scottish heritage, the inspiration for the iconic oversized suit, and telling the story of Filipino First Lady Imelda Marcos in his new Broadway musical Here Lies Love. Plus, Matt Gourley shares his training regimen as he prepares to return to the soccer pitch.
This episode was recorded on 5/11/23.</description></item><item><title>Off To The Ice Follies | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370038/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to boxing instructor Terri from Atlanta about fight promotion and working as an undercover police officer before running through a practice drug sting.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Billy Corgan And The Songs That Inspired Him | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan sits down with Billy Corgan of The Smashing Pumpkins for a conversation about navigating the changing music industry over a 35 year career and the songs that inspired him.
Follow along with the full list of songs here:
Wish You Were Here (Pink Floyd) Fade to Black (Metallica) Love Will Tear Us Apart (Joy Division)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Patton Oswalt Returns | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370040/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian and actor Patton Oswalt feels radiant about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Patton sits down with Conan once more to discuss the impending takeover of AI, why spectacle doesn’t equal interesting, and his debut comic series Minor Threats. Later, Conan gets grilled over his excuses for why his birthday gift for Matt Gourley never arrived.
Find the Slipnutz sketch here: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fj-VQTiO0Sw
This episode was recorded on 5/31/23.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Weird Around The Eyes | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370041/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Greg in Kildare about playing the bassoon in a symphony orchestra.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jake Tapper Returns | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370042/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Anchor Jake Tapper feels ironic about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Jake returns for another conversation with Conan about the colorful characters of 1977 explored in his new book All The Demons Are Here, why people follow demagogues, and handling constant exposure to the news each and every day. Later, Conan has a hypothetical conversation sharing his likes with his father.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Paddywhackery | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370043/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to Dave from Galway about life as a working musician and how Conan might manage to win over his wife.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Harrison Ford | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370044/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Harrison Ford feels confused about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Harrison sits down with Conan to discuss nearly changing his name in the early days of his career, smashing the Lego Millennium Falcon on one of his many Conan appearances, and the upcoming release of Indiana Jones and the Dial of Destiny. Plus, Sona asks Conan for tips in preparing her speech as the 2023 Mt SAC Alumnus of the Year.</description></item><item><title>What's The Craic? | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370045/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to Henry from County Donegal about working as a local tour guide and tips for being taken seriously in everyday life.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sir Paul McCartney | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370046/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sir Paul McCartney feels wildly elated about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Paul and Conan sit down for a live conversation about the incredible photographs chronicling The Beatles’ first transatlantic trip featured in Paul’s new book 1964: Eyes of the Storm.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tomato Soup Chin | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370047/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Sebastian from Buenos Aires about painting for rock stars, being good looking men, and what would give Conan away in Argentina.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kelly Clarkson | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370048/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Singer Kelly Clarkson feels honored and super cheesy about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Kelly sits down with Conan to talk about all the odd jobs she worked prior to her singing career, the uncertain early days of American Idol, getting personal with her 10th studio album Chemistry, and collaborating with Steve Martin. Plus, Conan takes audience questions about his new Max series Conan O’Brien Must Go, the whereabouts of Jordan Schlansky, the future of the Chill Chums, and more.</description></item><item><title>Eric Andre Returns | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370049/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Eric Andre feels moist about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Eric sits down with Conan to discuss the upcoming sixth season of The Eric Andre Show, pranks that have gone awry, and why you just can’t be ripped as a comedian. Later, Conan primes his team for a notable upcoming potential guest.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Ice Machine | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370050/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan speaks with Gaew from Buriram about his family racing enterprise, working for a factory team, and stepping out of his brother’s shadow.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Claire Danes | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370051/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actress Claire Danes feels decidedly giddy about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Claire sits down with Conan to discuss how an early interest in mimicry sparked a prolific lifelong career in the industry, throwing costume parties in her bachelorette pad, and the most emotionally striking scene from Fleishman Is In Trouble. Later, Matt Gourley opens the floodgates of rhyming reviews as the team Reviews the Reviewers.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Yo Soy Messi | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370052/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to Matias from Buenos Aires about his long-running news radio show entering its 11th season.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Lost Hans and Franz Movie Episode 4 | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370053/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370053/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the thrilling finale of The Lost Hans and Franz Movie, Hans, Franz, and Arnold discover the true face behind the evil girlyman plot. Plus, remembering other SNL inspired movie scripts that never made the cut.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sharon Horgan | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370054/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor, writer, and director Sharon Horgan feels exhausted about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Sharon sits down with Conan to discuss winning a BAFTA for Bad Sisters, grade school confessional galas, starting from scratch, and her process for writing believable characters. Later, Conan cautions his team against the perils of having specialty dishes named after them.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>41 Insults | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370055/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Whitney from Thailand about working in HR for the UN and specific tips for Conan should he ever attempt to rock climb.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Lost Hans and Franz Movie Episode 3 | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370056/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hans and Franz must race to solve the girlynappings before it’s too late in the third part of The Lost Hans and Franz Movie. Plus, Conan and the cast discuss how they planned to snag the long list of guest stars intended for the film.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sebastian Maniscalco | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370057/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian and actor Sebastian Maniscalco feels honored about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Sebastian sits down with Conan to talk about the terror of reading to children, the hardest venues in which to perform comedy, and casting Robert De Niro as his dad in his new film About My Father. Plus, Conan shares the story of getting gerbil’d in public for the first time.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>He’s Just Quite Ill | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370058/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to Eugenia in Córdoba, Argentina about learning English from television and living a loner’s lifestyle in a mountain town.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Lost Hans and Franz Movie Episode 2 | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370059/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370059/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the second installment of the Lost Hans and Franz Movie, Hans and Franz continue their quest with the help of their famous cousin Arnold Schwarzenegger. Plus, Conan, Dana, Kevin and Robert share true memories of personal Arnold encounters.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bill Hader Returns | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370060/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor, writer, and director Bill Hader feels tired about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Bill returns to chat with Conan once more about his favorite bits to do at parties, the timelessness of quality storytelling, and writing Barry backwards from its narrative conclusion. Later, Conan celebrates Matt Gourley’s birthday by exposing shocking details from his own lurid past.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Amiable Assassin | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370061/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Youssef from Egypt about voice acting, living outside the city, and being Christian in a predominantly Muslim country.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Lost Hans and Franz Movie Episode 1 | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370062/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan is joined by Dana Carvey, Kevin Nealon, and Robert Smigel along with the Team Coco staff to perform selections from the unproduced screenplay for Hans and Franz: The Girlyman Dilemma, more than 30 years after its original conception. Hear them now and believe them later - this script is going to PUMP YOU UP!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Javier Bardem | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370063/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Javier Bardem feels scared about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Javier sits down with Conan to talk about reinventing the Bond villain, playing with the threat of violence in No Country For Old Men, learning English from AC/DC, and portraying King Triton in the live action adaptation of The Little Mermaid. Plus, Conan’s team voices collective upset at being pod-blocked from great guests.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>The Rolls Royce Of Vikings | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370064/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan speaks with fish farmer Kai from Norway about the fun games he plays while out at sea, living in a town of 50 people, and how Conan would fare on the open ocean.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Steven Wright | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370065/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian and author Steven Wright feels anxious about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Steven sits down with Conan to talk about honing his trademark deadpan humor, debuting on Johnny Carson, and pouring everything he thinks about being alive into his new novel Harold. Plus, Conan tries to make Matt Gourley jealous with an in-person visit to an iconic James Bond filming location.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Fun Facts About Colombia | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370066/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to David from Colombia about working in a dangerous profession, death metal, and fun facts about his home country.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Charlie Day | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370067/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor, writer, and producer Charlie Day feels euphoric about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Charlie sits down with Conan to chat about his Rhode Island upbringing, committing himself to absurdity on It’s Always Sunny in Philadelphia, and satirizing Hollywood in his new film Fool’s Paradise. Later, Conan reassures a listener with fears about the threat Conan poses to his marriage.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.</description></item><item><title>Spatchcocking | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370068/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Florencia in Argentina about guided yoga and the local specialty cuisine.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lars Ulrich | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370069/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Metallica drummer Lars Ulrich feels psyched about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Lars sits down with Conan to discuss Metallica’s 11th studio album 72 Seasons, playing every continent on Earth (including Antarctica), and the synchronicity of drumming and tennis. Plus, Conan takes the recent baseball rules change as an opportunity to issue his own improvements on America’s favorite pastime.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ink-A-Dink | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370070/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Kassem from Beirut about workplace romances, boxing, and his worst fear.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Julia Louis-Dreyfus Returns | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370071/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Julia Louis-Dreyfus feels not much about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Julia sits down with Conan once more to discuss the inspiration for her podcast Wiser Than Me, discovering her comedic talents in a grade school play, and the importance of constantly trying new things. Later, Conan confronts his impending milestone 60th birthday.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Singapore Sona | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370072/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to Dee in Singapore about working as a hair stylist, dating, and Conan’s long lost leather jacket.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Al Franken Returns | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370073/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Al Franken feels privileged about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Al sits down with Conan once more to discuss why you can’t be funny in Washington, getting his parents cut from SNL, and The Only Former U.S. Senator Currently On Tour Tour. Later, Conan attempts to extract an apology from Sona.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Let Him Do His Bits | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370074/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Tara in Bangkok about working as a university lecturer and how Conan helped her find love.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Zach Braff | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370075/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor and filmmaker Zach Braff feels so honored about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Zach sits down with Conan to discuss his complicated Jewish upbringing, meeting his real-life best friend Donald Faison on Scrubs, and his new film A Good Person. Later, Matt and Sona recap running afoul of the law while recording an episode of Mallwalkin’.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is It A Party In Here? | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370076/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan speaks with Jarle from Bergen, Norway about his musical duo and the wide range of regional dialects in Norway.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Billie Eilish and FINNEAS | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370077/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Billie Eilish and FINNEAS feel really excited and dubious, respectively, about being Conan O’Brien’s friends.
Billie and FINNEAS sit down with Conan to discuss skyrocketing to worldwide fame at an early age, growing up seeing themselves all over the internet, favorite instruments, and their documentary Billie Eilish: The World’s a Little Blurry. Later, Adam Sachs stops by to drop some info about Gourley’s new high-concept podcast.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lost In Translation | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370078/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to Waleson from São Paulo about working as a translator and Conan’s favorite controversial historical figure.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chris Martin | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370079/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Musician Chris Martin feels really great about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Chris sits down with Conan to discuss the voices that encouraged him, the improbable story of finding drummer Will Champion, using SubPacs to make Coldplay concerts more accessible, and more. Plus, Conan responds to a curious listener’s voicemail about his “sock game.”
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Swipeout | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370080/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Avril in Dublin about working in reality tv, the typical Irish dating app experience, and how Conan would market himself for online dating.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Neil Young And The Songs That Inspired Him | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370081/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Neil Young sits down for a special conversation with Conan about the songs that inspired him.
Follow along with the full list of songs here: Four Strong Winds (Ian &amp;amp; Sylvia) The Wayward Wind (Gogi Grant) Baby, What You Want Me to Do (Jimmy Reed) Ballad of a Teenage Queen (Johnny Cash) Bob-A-Lena (Ronnie Self)
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Michelle Zauner | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370082/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Musician and author Michelle Zauner feels elated about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Michelle sits down with Conan to talk about her book Crying in H Mart, the impact her relationship with her mother had on her career and the success of her band Japanese Breakfast, drawing inspiration from video game music, and more. Later, Conan reviews fan-submitted drag name suggestions.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>DJ Jazzy Josh | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370083/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to Josh in Cape Town, South Africa about working on impact games and his history as an auctioneer.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Norah Jones | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370084/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Singer-songwriter Norah Jones feels ecstatic about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Norah sits down with Conan to discuss her podcast Norah Jones Is Playing Along, collaborating with Ray Charles and Willie Nelson, serendipitous run-ins, and more. Plus, Conan responds to a voicemail with a state senator’s official invitation to the USS Sequoia.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We DO Talk About Bruno | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370085/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks with Bruno in Madrid about working as an airline pilot and tips for giving alarming news from the cockpit.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Elizabeth Banks | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370086/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actress Elizabeth Banks feels cautiously optimistic about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Elizabeth sits down with Conan to chat about standing up to her childhood bullies, communion, and mixing horror and comedy in her new film Cocaine Bear. Plus, a Neil Diamond song takes Conan on a trip down a memory lane of misheard lyrics.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hear Ye, Hear Ye! | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370087/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan speaks to Jack from Abingdon about working for Yellow Submarine Charity, playing in a ukulele ensemble, and the best and worst places Conan has ever slept in.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jason Segel | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370088/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Jason Segel feels very happy about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Jason sits down with Conan to chat about the real-life inspiration behind Forgetting Sarah Marshall, joke texts from Anthony Hopkins, and his new tv series Shrinking. Later, Conan and his team get administered a professional hearing test.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Conapotamia | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370089/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Moataz in Alexandria, Egypt about meeting his wife playing a video game and their subsequent virtual wedding ceremony.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jane Fonda | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370090/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actress and activist Jane Fonda feels so, really deeply happy and excited to be sitting opposite Conan for a conversation.
Jane sits down with Conan to discuss all the ways in which the world has changed around us since she was growing up, connecting with her father Henry Fonda and how his films influenced her activism, touring Appalachia with Dolly Parton, and more. Plus - Conan issues a very positive State of the Podcast address.</description></item><item><title>Keepin' It In The Family | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370091/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Ellen from Tullamore, Ireland about going to law school while working in a whiskey distillery and how Conan takes his dram.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sarah Silverman Returns | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370092/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian and actress Sarah Silverman feels ambivalent about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Sarah sits down with Conan once more to share her most irrational fear (and most embarrassing childhood memory), stories of family know-it-alls, and the thrills that come along with age-related hearing loss.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Name Name | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370093/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to Anna in Bangkok about how to get her mom to stop yelling across the house, the most popular names in Thailand, and what it would be like to bring Conan to a ping pong show.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Vir Das | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370094/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Vir Das feels unique about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Vir sits down with Conan to discuss faking appendicitis as a child, the first laugh he ever got on stage, the controversy over his “Two Indias” monologue, and his new special Vir Das: Landing. Later, Sona and David Hopping recount their adventures visiting every single Friends filming location.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Underground Museum Coffee | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370095/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Simon from Slovenia about his favorite specialty coffee shop and its unusual location.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Timothy Olyphant Returns | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370096/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Timothy Olyphant feels splendiferous about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Timothy and Conan sit down once more to discuss their unique friendship, being shot at in New Orleans while filming Justified: City Primeval, and a possible new talk show featuring the two of them.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>C.S.I. Kansas City | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370097/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to Allan in Missouri about working as a crime scene investigator, surprising scenes she’s investigated, and which of Conan’s team would make the most skilled investigator.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ramy Youssef | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370098/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor, writer, and comedian Ramy Youssef feels the inevitability of God coming into our lives about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Ramy sits down with Conan to discuss sharing personal history with castmates on his Hulu comedy series Ramy, the universal concept of “refinancing” with God, and filming in the West Bank. Plus, a bacteria sharing Conan’s name inspires debate over Conan and his team’s relative celebrity status.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Red Ass-fault | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370099/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Carles about working as a video game designer and what drag persona Conan would create for himself.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bryan Cranston Returns | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370100/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Bryan Cranston feels stimulated about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Bryan sits down with Conan once more to dive into the details of his wild first sexual encounter in Salzburg, transitioning from physical comedy in Malcolm in the Middle to the high-stakes drama of Breaking Bad, how kindness and hard work are the key to a satisfying career, and the upcoming season two of Your Honor. Plus, Conan regretfully comes to terms with how Joop!</description></item><item><title>Klingons and Cowboys | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370101/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan speaks with Jill from Vulcan, Alberta about growing wetland plants in a commercial greenhouse, fainting goats, and what Conan would name a wetland species of his own discovering.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Penn Badgley | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370102/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Penn Badgley feels the dull echo of imposter syndrome about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Penn sits down with Conan to discuss his journey to Hollywood as a child actor, the value of educating yourself, and THAT scene from his Netflix series YOU. Conan shares his love of Gossip Girl and pitches an alternate version as a sketch. Stick around for the end, where Conan and the team try on Tracy Morgan&amp;rsquo;s favorite cologne.</description></item><item><title>Undercover Rabbi | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370103/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to David from New Rochelle, NY about being a congregational rabbi and what a clergy team meeting with Conan and the chums would look like.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ed Helms | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370104/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor and comedian Ed Helms feels humbled about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Ed sits down with Conan to chat about the real-life Andy Bernard, learning the banjo, and exploring history’s greatest screwups with his podcast SNAFU. Plus, Conan and his team read a review of the podcast written by an AI.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ashley Flowers from Crime Junkie | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370105/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370105/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this special episode of Conan O’Brien IS a Fan, Conan sits down with Ashley Flowers of the podcast Crime Junkie to discuss what got her into true crime, why LA is the place to be for the genre, and her novel All Good People Here.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Michelle Obama Returns Again | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370106/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former First Lady Michelle Obama feels less cautious about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Michelle returns to sit down with Conan once more to discuss her new book The Light We Carry, developing tools to deal with anxiety, the importance of working with one’s hands, and preparing for the empty nest.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Welcome to the Jungle | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370107/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Jackie from Ontario about working at the Toronto Humane Society, studying baboons, and tricks to get your cat to love you.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Randall Park | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370108/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Randall Park feels neither here nor there about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Randall sits down with Conan to discuss coming out as an actor to his parents, honing his comedic talents in workplace training videos, and his new show Blockbuster. Plus, Conan helps his team come up with age-appropriate toy ideas for their kids.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Thing | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370109/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to Alexandra about being a janitor in Antarctica, traveling the world, and which Disney Princess Conan identifies with the most.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lizzy Caplan | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370110/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actress Lizzy Caplan feels confused about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Lizzy sits down with Conan to talk about being well-positioned geographically, her new show Fleishman Is in Trouble, and the abandonment issues that come along with a career in acting. Later, Conan takes engineer Eduardo to task about distractions in the workplace.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Party In My Mouth | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370111/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Visa from Finland about coffee, the sauna, and playing in a metal band.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Stephen Colbert Live at the Beacon Theater | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370112/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stephen Colbert feels put upon about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Stephen sits down with Conan live at the Beacon Theater to discuss dalliances in Italy, playing the egomaniac, and visiting an airbase in northern Greenland. Plus, Conan answers audience questions about being a lumberjack, his favorite sounds, what he’d put in his museum, and more.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Need, By Conan O'Brien | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370113/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Edom from Ethiopia about crafting scented candles and perfumes and what Conan would choose as his signature scent.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tracy Morgan Live at the Beacon Theater | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370114/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tracy Morgan feels like a man about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Tracy sits down with Conan live at the Beacon Theater to discuss getting back into dating, his famous relatives, and gentrification. Plus, Conan answers audience questions about winning the lottery, the law, his favorite tv show, misfit toys, and more!
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>The Stranger | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370115/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to Jenna from Dallas about working as a middle school principal and which classroom management strategy Conan should use with his team.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kumail Nanjiani Returns | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370116/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kumail Nanjiani feels skeptical about being Conan O’Brien’s best friend.
Kumail sits down with Conan once again to discuss being an awkward kid, discovering his identity as an adult, and his upcoming miniseries Welcome to Chippendales. Later, Conan revels in his own bravery after getting not one, but two shots at a doctor’s visit.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821. For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Goulash on the Beach | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370117/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to Veronika from Eger, Hungary about beach food, getting engaged, and writing a wedding speech.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bill Burr Live from the SiriusXM Garage | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370118/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370118/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Bill Burr joins Conan live from the SiriusXM Garage to discuss his new film Old Dads, shingles, and laughing at what you can’t change. Plus, Conan takes audience questions about what he misses most about Boston, being a comic in another era, and more.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821. For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nick Kroll Returns | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370119/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian and actor Nick Kroll feels strongly about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Nick sits down with Conan once again to discuss his new special Little Big Boy, becoming a dad, and working with Mel Brooks on History of the World, Part 2. Plus, Conan recounts his run-in with a delivery drone. Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821. For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Inaction Figure | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370120/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370120/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with toymaker Ben from northwest Arkansas about the toys he despises, which ones he’s most proud of, and Conan’s favorite toy of all time.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>JB Smoove Live from the SiriusXM Garage | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370121/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370121/</guid><description>Podcast Description JB Smoove feels frustrated about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
JB joins Conan live from the SiriusXM Garage to discuss fashion, how to pull people in, and ways that Conan could be more charismatic. Plus, assistant David Hopping joins the crew to help field questions about the seven-year itch, what other genre of podcast they would host, and more.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Colin Hanks | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370122/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370122/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Colin Hanks feels…excited (?) about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Colin sits down with Conan to discuss composing a good Twitter bio, creating a documentary about the great John Candy, and going dark with his role in the series A Friend of the Family. Plus, Dana Carvey returns to talk about his sci-fi comedy podcast The Weird Place.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Amir From Iran | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370123/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370123/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan is joined by Amir from Tehran to hear firsthand about the situation in Iran, what it’s like to live through revolution, and what we can do to help.
Find a transcript of this episode here: https://teamcoco.com/amir-from-iran
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kevin Nealon Returns | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370124/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor and comedian Kevin Nealon feels obligated about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Kevin sits down with Conan once again to discuss his new book I Exaggerate: My Brushes with Fame, the upcoming season of Hiking with Kevin, living in the moment, and who he thinks is the funniest of all time.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Kee-ra Attack! | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370125/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to falconer Roxanne from San Diego about her birds&amp;rsquo; unique responsibilities and what work Conan could do to join her avian crew.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jon Bernthal | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370126/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Jon Bernthal feels extraordinarily lucky about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Jon sits down with Conan to discuss his unique introduction to acting, the importance of discipline and well-roundedness, and speaking with life-without-parole inmates on his podcast Real Ones. Later, Conan recalls just a few of his greatest fighting victories. Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821. For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Zero Degrees Kelvin | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370127/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks with Kelvin from the Canadian Far North about his Dene ancestry and which of Conan, Matt, and Sona would survive the longest alone in the wild.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rivers Cuomo | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370128/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370128/</guid><description>Podcast Description Weezer frontman Rivers Cuomo feels excited about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Rivers sits down with Conan to talk about his love of Beethoven, going from worldwide tours to enrolling in Harvard, enduring painful corrective leg surgery, and Weezer’s latest project SZNZ. Plus, Conan and his team celebrate their collective advancements in age.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Recessive Elegance | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370129/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370129/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Molly from Collingwood, Ontario about working as a model, being paid to plant trees, and whether they might be related.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mila Kunis Returns | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370130/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370130/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actress Mila Kunis feels irrelevant about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Mila returns to chat with Conan about talking her kids through the tough stuff, sustainable farming, passing down her Ukrainian heritage, and her new film Luckiest Girl Alive. Plus, Conan takes note of his increasingly frequent run-ins with listeners of the pod.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Aguerotic Flux | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370131/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks with historian Joris in the Netherlands about the Black Death, Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles, and what historical disease Conan would personally design.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Billy Eichner Returns | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370132/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370132/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor and comedian Billy Eichner feels over the moon about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Billy sits down with Conan once again to discuss making an authentic gay romcom with Bros, taking control of his own career amidst a changing culture, and what he owes to the iconic Joan Rivers. Later, Conan wallows in distress over his wife’s healthy grocery selection.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>The Naked Therapist | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370133/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Violet in Kalamazoo, MI about working as a stripper, what Conan’s stage name would be, and what song he would dance to.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jack McBrayer | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370134/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor and comedian Jack McBrayer feels honored about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Jack sits down with Conan to discuss working in a factory, landing the role of Kenneth on 30 Rock, and being invited to a big celebrity wedding (in India). Plus, Conan and his team finally get to the bottom of the mysterious maybe-fake caller from last week’s segment.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Brazilian Butt Lift | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370135/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to plastic surgeon Ahmed to find out what procedures he recommends to spruce up Conan&amp;rsquo;s aging physique and to perform a little surgery role-play.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Leslie Jones | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370136/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370136/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Leslie Jones could give a sh*t if she was Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Leslie sits down with Conan to discuss her new podcast The Fckry, writing stand-up to fit her style, the lost art of accountability, and who at SNL she was secretly in love with. Later, Conan and his crew play sleuth to validate a dubious listener voicemail.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Bedside Conan | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370137/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan speaks with ICU nurse Effie from Durham, North Carolina to find out how she and her fellow nurses keep themselves entertained and how Conan might be of service in a hospital setting.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>James Burrows | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370138/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370138/</guid><description>Podcast Description Legendary sitcom director James Burrows feels sanguine about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
James sits down with Conan to talk about his new book Directed by James Burrows, casting for Cheers and Frasier, which of his shows he still thinks is the funniest, and the evolution of the Norm-ism. Plus, Conan tries to get to know his own feet a bit better.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>The Juili Juanka of Juárez | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370139/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Kevin in Juárez, Mexico about working in a candy factory and the one bit of American history Conan thinks every first-time visitor should know.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Luke Wilson | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370140/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370140/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Luke Wilson feels that, on the advice of his counsel, it’s best that he agree to be clear about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Luke sits down with Conan to chat about interacting with the pioneers of his craft, mastering his put-upon film persona, taking inspiration from MAD Magazine, and more. Later, Gourley mourns how the tragic power of the podcast has ruined a small part of his life.</description></item><item><title>The Worst Cow Thief | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370141/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks with Benji from Kampala about the challenges of organizing a traditional Ugandan wedding.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nicole Byer Returns | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370142/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370142/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Nicole Byer feels giddy about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Nicole returns to chat with Conan about being loved by kids, the wisdom of John Cena, and being horny for love. Later, Conan and his team attempt to hold it together while Sona is away on her book tour.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.</description></item><item><title>The Motorcycle Diaries | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370143/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370143/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Jake in Tbilisi, Georgia about his adventures riding his motorcycle around the world.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Aubrey Plaza | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370144/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370144/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actress, comedian, and producer Aubrey Plaza feels totally fine about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Aubrey sits down with Conan to discuss playing basketball in disguise, getting cast in her breakout role as April Ludgate on Parks and Recreation, and her new movie Emily the Criminal. Later, Sona’s assistant David Hopping tells the tale of how he came to work under Conan.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>The ‘Couve | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370145/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370145/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan speaks with Connor from Vancouver about directing animated features and the hardships of height.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jeff Ross | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370146/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370146/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Jeff Ross feels tan about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Jeff sits down with Conan to talk about learning from the great Don Rickles, his reaction to “the slap,” great moments in roast comedy history, and memories of some of the great comics lost in recent years. Later, Conan and his crew reveal the surprising and controversial way they made national news headlines.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Conan Sits Down with his Significant Other | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370147/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370147/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan sits down with his significant other, Liza Powel O’Brien, in this very special bonus episode from her own podcast, Significant Others. Listen as Liza and Conan chat about all things Abe and Mary Lincoln.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>912, What's Your Emergency? | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370148/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370148/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to Taylor from Salt Lake City about working as a 911 operator and to walk through an emergency simulation.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>B.J. Novak | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370149/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370149/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor, writer, and comedian B.J. Novak feels excited, but cautious about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
B.J. sits down with Conan to talk about hailing from rival towns, the personal impact of Bob Saget, working on Punk’D, and B.J.’s new film Vengeance. Plus, Conan’s wife Liza stops by to share stories from her new podcast “Significant Others.”
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>21st Century Bangable | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370150/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370150/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to salon owner Kristi to get recommendations for his style and to get the scoop on the weirdest conversations she’s had with someone in the chair.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nikki Glaser Returns | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370151/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370151/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Nikki Glaser feels chill about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Nikki sits down with Conan once more to discuss moving back in with her parents, handling criticism, hosting Fboy Island, and pushing the boundaries with her latest special Good Clean Filth.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Space Porn | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370152/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370152/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks with NASA engineer Smythe about the craziest things he’s smuggled into space and how Conan’s team would fare in the final frontier.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Steven Yeun | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370153/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370153/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Steven Yeun feels ecstatic about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Steven sits down with Conan to talk about landing the role of Glenn in The Walking Dead, emigrating from South Korea at an early age, and the beauty of submitting to life as a parent. Plus, Conan reviews Sona’s new book The World’s Worst Assistant.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Summer S’mores with Conan and the Chill Chums Season 2 Episode 6 | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370154/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370154/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan, Sona and Matt plan out their next grand outing on the final Summer S’mores special of the season
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dana Carvey Returns | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370155/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370155/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dana Carvey feels stupefied about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Dana sits down with Conan once again to discuss winding up on a Neil Young bootleg album, stretching out an impression, developing his new Team Coco podcast The Weird Place with his sons, and more.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Summer S’mores with Conan and the Chill Chums Season 2 Episode 5 | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370156/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370156/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan and the Chill Chums conduct a review of the s’more as a concept before attempting to make and eat their own.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Taylor Tomlinson | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370157/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370157/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Taylor Tomlinson feels braggadocious about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Taylor sits down with Conan to discuss the benefits of starting out at a young age, the joke that got her kicked out of church gigs, the horrors of performing on a cruise ship, and more. Plus, part two of the rejected Bond theme quiz!
Get tickets for Taylor’s upcoming tour here.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Summer S’mores with Conan and the Chill Chums Season 2 Episode 4 | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370158/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370158/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan and the Chill Chums tell jokes around the fire and fiercely debate which of them is the coolest on another Summer S’mores special.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Conan O'Brien &amp; Jeff Ross Look Back | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370159/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370159/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan O’Brien and longtime executive producer Jeff Ross join writers Mike Sweeney and Jessie Gaskell to discuss Conan and Jeff&amp;rsquo;s first meeting, the start of Late Night, Tom Hanks’ message to Conan, and the fate of Conan’s Ford Taurus.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jack White | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370160/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370160/</guid><description>Podcast Description Musician Jack White feels magnanimous about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Jack sits down with Conan to talk about his new album Entering Heaven Alive, running his own upholstery shop, what it means to pander, melding art and business, and pre-show rituals. Plus, Conan goes head to head with his team with a rejected Bond theme quiz.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Summer S'mores with Conan and the Chill Chums Season 2 Episode 3 | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370161/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370161/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan shares his most traumatic backyard memories with the Chill Chums on another Summer S’mores special.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>David Sedaris Returns | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370162/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370162/</guid><description>Podcast Description Writer David Sedaris feels fantastic about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
David and Conan sit down together once more to discuss David’s new book Happy-Go-Lucky, the importance of dressing up, being alone in Alaska, and family dysfunction. Later, Conan considers the possibility of performing in hospital delivery rooms as he and his team Review the Reviewers.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Summer S'mores with Conan and the Chill Chums Season 2 Episode 2 | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370163/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370163/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan and the Chill Chums enjoy the beautiful outdoors as Conan panics over whether his photo made it into the local newsletter.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Vanessa Bayer | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370164/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370164/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actress and comedian Vanessa Bayer feels honestly thrilled about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Vanessa sits down with Conan to discuss the perks of her childhood illness, performing improv on a cruise ship, originating iconic sketches like the Bar Mitzvah Boy and Totino’s on SNL, and her new home shopping comedy I Love That For You. Later, Sona gives Conan a lesson in basic Armenian.
Got a question for Conan?</description></item><item><title>Summer S'mores with Conan and the Chill Chums Season 2 Episode 1 | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370165/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370165/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan and the Chill Chums create a soothing outdoor summer soundscape with the return of the Summer S’mores special.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jeff Goldblum Returns | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370166/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370166/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeff Goldblum feels utterly drenched and purged about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Jeff and Conan sit down once again to discuss Jeff’s mysterious dreams, jazz musicianship, the movie theater experiences that blew them away, and reprising the role of Dr. Ian Malcolm in the upcoming Jurassic World: Dominion.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Safari So Goody | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370167/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370167/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with safari guide Alex about his most intense experiences in the field and what animal Conan most identifies with.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Professor Brian Cox | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370168/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370168/</guid><description>Podcast Description Professor and physicist Brian Cox has no idea how to feel about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Professor Brian Cox sits down with Conan to discuss feeling insignificant at the size of the universe, doing sketch comedy with Stephen Hawking, starting out as a rock musician, and his new show Horizons: A 21st Century Space Odyssey. Later, Conan and his team desperately try to get themselves in sync.
Got a question for Conan?</description></item><item><title>Cat Shaming | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370169/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370169/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to Lynnea about haunted hotels, massive cats, and what kind of ghost Conan plans on being.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tig Notaro Returns | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370170/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370170/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tig Notaro feels gay about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Tig sits down with Conan once again to discuss which of her kids she thinks is going into comedy, favorite jokes and pranks, and her inability to identify celebrities. Plus, Conan and his team issue an inaugural broadcast from their brand new podcast space.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Shawshank O’Brien | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370171/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370171/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks with Walt in North Carolina about what it’s like to work on death row and how Conan would fare as a prison warden.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Live With Bill Hader At The Wiltern Theater | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370172/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370172/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bill Hader joins Conan live at the Wiltern Theater to talk about the first time he met Arnold Schwarzenegger, bits that never die, and coping with anxiety. Plus, Conan and his team take audience questions about how Conan would break into the industry today, moments that make them glad to be alive, and more.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Elle Fanning | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370173/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370173/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actress Elle Fanning feels honored about being Conan O’Brien’s pretty good friend.
Elle and Conan sit down to discuss taking liberties with history on The Great, famous relatives, and her new drama miniseries The Girl from Plainville. Plus, Conan recounts his pre-late night success with his boy band during the State of the Podcast.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>The Stressed Pelvis | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370174/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370174/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to Lindsay from Halifax about her work with sensory deprivation chambers and Conan’s personal meditation practice.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Paul F. Tompkins | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370175/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370175/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Paul F. Tompkins feels cautiously optimistic about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Paul sits down with Conan to discuss getting started in one of the hardest cities for stand-up comedy, the origin behind his trademark gentleman’s wear, and his live variety show Varietopia. Later, Conan muses at the list of books purchased on his stolen Kindle.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>The Body Man | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370176/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370176/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Tyler from Mississippi Mills about being a bus driver, feeling unsafe on the job, and what disses Conan would sling at his younger self.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>John Mulaney Returns | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370177/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370177/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian John Mulaney feels irregardless about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
John sits down with Conan once again to discuss what goes into crafting an SNL monologue, putting all of himself into his new special From Scratch, and seeing the world through the eyes of his son.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Melissa and the Cherry Wood Hand | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370178/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370178/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Melissa from Detroit about risking life and limb building picture frames and what to do with the scrap wood left over.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Molly Shannon | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370179/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370179/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actress Molly Shannon feels proud to be Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Molly sits down with Conan to talk about being a child stowaway, the reckless physicality of Mary Katherine Gallagher, and her new memoir Hello, Molly! Later, Matt Gourley shares comments from a lustful thread on the Conan subreddit.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Emotional Health of My Don Johnson | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370180/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to Chris from Wilmette, IL about working as a North Pole expedition guide and whether Conan could handle life in the Arctic.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Stephen Merchant | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370181/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370181/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian, writer, and director Stephen Merchant feels overqualified about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Stephen sits down with Conan to discuss his outrageous height, finding the right showrunner for the American version of The Office, getting to work alongside legends like David Bowie and Christopher Walken, and his newest series The Outlaws. Later, Conan wonders how to capitalize on his natural appeal to kids when he and his team Review the Reviewers.</description></item><item><title>Gonzo's Nose | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370182/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370182/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan speaks with Emma about her work making leather bondage harnesses and the wonderful world of custom sex gear.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nick Offerman Returns | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370183/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370183/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick Offerman feels earnestly grateful about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Nick sits down with Conan once more to discuss processing feelings of intense jealousy, pitching his new book Where the Deer and the Antelope Play on its own merits, why creating things is critical to overall health, and his new column on Substack, Donkey Thoughts. Later, the gang reunites in person for the first time in years.
Got a question for Conan?</description></item><item><title>The High Priestess | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370184/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370184/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan consults with tarot reader Patti to receive his very own personalized fortune.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Aimee Mann | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370185/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370185/</guid><description>Podcast Description Singer-songwriter Aimee Mann feels apprehensive about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Aimee sits down with Conan to discuss her tumultuous childhood, early days on the scene with her band The Young Snakes, and the importance of being able to say what you think and feel. Plus, Team Coco’s own gossip expert Solomon Georgio shares some hot historical goss dating all the way back to 1892.
Check out The Juice with Solomon Georgio here.</description></item><item><title>Rest In Pee Wee | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370186/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370186/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan speaks with Maureen from Michigan about working as a taxidermist and how and where she would pose a taxidermied Conan.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Paul Rudd Returns | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370187/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370187/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Paul Rudd feels heart-warmed about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Paul sits down with Conan once again to talk about their love of European food, measuring their junk, Paul’s upcoming projects, and getting knee-deep in the shit. Later, Matt Gourley shares a song about his relative who was attacked by a chicken.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Social Morays | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370188/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370188/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to Rebecca in Seattle about working as a professional organizer and how Conan disposes of his unwanted belongings.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tracy Morgan | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370189/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370189/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Tracy Morgan feels bloated to be Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Tracy sits down with Conan to talk about the roots of his iconic comedic sensibilities, his favorite character bits on SNL, starring in The Last O.G., and his emotional recovery from his 2014 truck accident. Plus, Sona confesses to a truly despicable sushi-related crime.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Lux et Veritas | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370190/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370190/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Lux in London about rock climbing with a visual impairment and the dumbest, most physically dangerous thing Conan has ever done.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>David Cross | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370191/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370191/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor and comedian David Cross feels envious about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
David sits down with Conan to discuss his incredible career in comedy, being attacked by his audience, passing down cherished comedic influences through generations, and his new special I’m From the Future. Later, Sona looks back ruefully on her most recent temper tantrum.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>The Mafia Puppy Doctor | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370192/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370192/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to Jonathan about being a small animal veterinarian and what kind of animal Conan would turn into if he had the chance.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Julie Bowen | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370193/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370193/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actress Julie Bowen feels cautiously optimistic about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Julie sits down with Conan to talk about tuning in to the show while cycling, the human reproductive system, finding the right sleep aids, and her new podcast Quitters. Later, Conan looks back on his appearance in the latest iteration of SNL&amp;rsquo;s Five-Timers Club.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Livin’ The Dean | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370194/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370194/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Dean in Florida about being a professional sand sculptor and what moment in history Conan would change to benefit himself (and only himself).
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mike Schur | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370195/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370195/</guid><description>Podcast Description Producer and writer Mike Schur feels fine about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Mike and Conan sit down to talk about Mike’s new book How To Be Perfect: The Correct Answer to Every Moral Question, the culture of consequence, and striving to be better at apologizing and forgiving. Later, Conan recounts his experience assisting an unlucky fan with their marriage proposal.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Phil The D!@k Whittler | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370196/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370196/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks with designer Phil from Minneapolis about designing fake products for a fake grocery store.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Oops, All Ads! | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370197/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370197/</guid><description>Podcast Description While Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend has fans all over the world, one very important part of the show is only available to US listeners–the ads! From Magoosh to Mizzen &amp;amp; Main, Conan has been known to go a little off the rails with his ad reads, so as a treat for our international and American fans alike, Team Coco presents a very special episode of the weirdest and wildest ad reads to date.</description></item><item><title>Slash | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370198/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370198/</guid><description>Podcast Description Legendary guitarist Slash feels pretty damn good about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Slash sits down with Conan to discuss loving bikes before loving guitars, acquiring his iconic top hat, and working with Myles Kennedy and The Conspirators on their newest album 4. Plus, Conan and his team react to a listener’s colonoscopy prank.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>An Eye for an Eye | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370199/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370199/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan speaks with Sara from Westerly, Rhode Island about the worst eye ailment she’s ever seen in her work as an optometrist.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Marshawn Lynch | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370200/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370200/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former NFL star Marshawn Lynch feels blessed to be Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Marshawn sits down with Conan for a special live Super Bowl episode to talk about playing off of Will Arnett in Murderville, recovering from the physical intensity of the game, and launching his own agency with Beast Mode Marketing. Plus, Conan and Sona answer audience questions about Conan’s newest project and more.
Got a question for Conan?</description></item><item><title>The Need for Weed | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370201/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370201/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to Matthew in Las Vegas about what it’s like to manage the world’s largest cannabis dispensary and which terrible superpower Conan would saddle himself with.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Judy Greer | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370202/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370202/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actress Judy Greer feels very privileged to be Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Judy sits down with Conan to discuss being late bloomers, onscreen intimacy with George Clooney, Judy&amp;rsquo;s new scripted podcast ‘Self Center’, and trying to eat more candy. Plus, Conan bemoans the struggle of shopping for compression socks.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tanks for the Memories | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370203/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370203/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan speaks with Forrest in Maine about his work designing commercial tanks and what sort of tank Conan would drive (if he was allowed).
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Justice Sonia Sotomayor | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370204/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 14:16:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370204/</guid><description>Podcast Description Justice Sonia Sotomayor feels intimidated about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Justice Sotomayor sits down with Conan to discuss the foundations of Supreme Court collegiality, her new book Just Help! How to Build a Better World, reacting to the news of Justice Breyer’s retirement, and teaching kids the importance of working together.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821. For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Moses Storm | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370205/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370205/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Moses Storm feels psychotic about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Moses sits down with Conan to talk about his new comedy special Trash White, being raised by grifters, performing for an audience of cars during the lockdown, and more. Later, Engineer Sam delivers Christmas presents to the team.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>An American In Scotland | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370206/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370206/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan speaks with Mimi in South Queensferry, Scotland about the town’s history of witch hunts and her work in conservation geography.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Patton Oswalt &amp; Meredith Salenger | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370207/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370207/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Patton Oswalt feels 100% not embarrassed about being Conan O’Brien’s friend. Actress Meredith Salenger feels so blessed about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Patton and Meredith sit down with Conan to talk about how they met, odd encounters with Orson Welles, their podcast Did You Get My Text?, and hunting for impossible snacks. Later, Conan helps Sona and Matt prepare for their children&amp;rsquo;s eventual betrothal to one another.</description></item><item><title>Dating Your Family In Iceland | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370208/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370208/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks with Bjarki from Reykjavik about life in Iceland and how it could be improved by Conan’s despotic rule.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bowen Yang | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370209/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370209/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Bowen Yang feels dissociative about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Bowen sits down with Conan to discuss SNL-induced dread, putting together the iconic Iceberg skit, touchy interview subjects, and why it’s impossible to write a sketch in advance. Later, Matt Gourley struggles to announce the new season of Sona’s web series Sona Fixes Your Life.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>The Fiddler And The Ski Mall | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370210/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370210/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan speaks with Jesse at the World Expo in Dubai about playing rock violin and which musical act Conan would play lead guitar for if given the opportunity.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Zach Galifianakis Returns | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370211/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370211/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Zach Galifianakis feels…sincere about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Zach sits down with Conan once again to discuss comedy bits to do in a restaurant, cultivating a certain kind of rudeness, and little-known historical facts. Later, Matt Gourley seeks Conan’s guidance on raising a red-headed child.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Skull Soup | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370212/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370212/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Phil in Fall River, MA about working in the Lizzie Borden house and how Conan would solve the murder once and for all.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chris Redd | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370213/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370213/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Chris Redd feels lucky as a motherf*cker to be Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Chris sits down with Conan to talk about escaping his hometown, how rap trained him for stand-up comedy, getting iced out by Kanye, and never forgetting what it&amp;rsquo;s like to struggle. Plus, Conan and his team respond to a listener voicemail about Conan’s Miracle Voice.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>C.U.T.I.E. | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370214/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370214/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan speaks with roboticist Abhijeet about improving people’s lives with robots and his robot companion C.U.T.I.E.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kieran Culkin | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370215/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370215/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Kieran Culkin feels like goal-achieved to be Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Kieran sits down with Conan to discuss fulfilling a dream of hosting SNL, playing extravagant wealth as Roman Roy on Succession, and picking roles based on location. Plus, Conan takes a moment to exercise his New York grit.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.</description></item><item><title>A Lesson In Provinces | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370216/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370216/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks with criminal defense lawyer Anny about how he would do on the stand and which historical crime he would go back and commit properly.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jim Gaffigan Returns | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370217/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370217/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Jim Gaffigan feels ecstatic about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Jim returns to the show to sit down once again with Conan to discuss very American opinions, Conan’s worst guest ever, holiday traditions, and his new special Jim Gaffigan: Comedy Monster. Later, Conan comes to grips with his terrible taste in Christmas decorations.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Turner Classic Wine Club | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370218/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370218/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan speaks with dental hygienist Chrissy from Baltimore about listening to the podcast while she runs and silent movie-themed wine.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Quentin Tarantino | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370219/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370219/</guid><description>Podcast Description Screenwriter and director Quentin Tarantino feels trepidatious about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Quentin sits down with Conan to discuss drawing influences from iconic 1970s television, going deeper into the story of Rick Dalton with the novelization of Once Upon a Time in Hollywood, his favorite Burt Reynolds story, and much more.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Will Forte | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370220/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370220/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor and writer Will Forte feels honored about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Will sits down with Conan to discuss getting married and becoming a father, overcoming “writer’s brain” during his time on SNL, reviving MacGruber with the new Peacock series, and teaming up with Val Kilmer to get on The Amazing Race. Later, Conan gives his cool-guy persona another honest attempt.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>The Professional Patient | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370221/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370221/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to Katie from Virginia about her work as a standardized patient and to test his reaction to receiving bad medical news.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lea DeLaria | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370222/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370222/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian, musician, and actress Lea DeLaria is gagging to be Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Lea sits down with Conan to talk about bursting onto the standup scene in the early 80s, coming out at an early age and the importance of finding one’s space, her upcoming film Potato Dreams of America, and working to preserve the last lesbian bars in the country with The Lesbian Bar Project. Later, Conan gets feedback from his team about his brand new headshot.</description></item><item><title>Kidditch Camp | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370223/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370223/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan speaks with architect Erik from Milwaukee about designing summer camps and the torture chambers that Conan and his team would design for one another.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ellie Kemper | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370224/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370224/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actress Ellie Kemper feels thrilled about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Ellie sits down with Conan to talk about mining sincerity for comedy while starring in The Office and Unbreakable Kimmy Schmidt, Conan’s rowdy relationship with her husband Michael, and her upcoming film Home Sweet Home Alone. Later, Conan responds to a listener voicemail asking which animal he would give birth to.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Trapped and Neutered | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370225/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370225/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Emily from Kentucky about studying clinical psychology and working with a trap-neuter-release nonprofit for cats.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>John Lithgow | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370226/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370226/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor John Lithgow is already Conan O’Brien’s friend.
John sits down with Conan to discuss his favorite sketches from collaborating together during SNL, the inconveniences of being tall, and select excerpts from his new book A Confederacy of Dumptys: Portraits of American Scoundrels in Verse. Later, Conan welcomes back Matt Gourley during his State of the Podcast address.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Thinking About Stew | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370227/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370227/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to Brittany from Buffalo, NY about working as a skydiving instructor and whether Conan would be able to keep it together on a dive.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Howie Mandel | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370228/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370228/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian and actor Howie Mandel feels fantastic about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Howie sits down with Conan to talk about why one must own a bidet, his very first onstage experience, and his podcast Howie Mandel Does Stuff. Plus, an exclusive bonus edition of Big Dick History, live from the Wiltern Theatre!
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Pharmacies and Fast Food in Cairo | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370229/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370229/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan speaks with Nariman from Cairo about tanning, Egyptian fast food, and dealing with post-pandemic anxiety.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Live with Will Arnett at the Wiltern Theatre | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370230/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 15:06:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370230/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Will Arnett feels absolutely ecstatic about being Conan O&amp;rsquo;Brien&amp;rsquo;s friend.
Live from the Wiltern Theatre, Conan is joined by Will Arnett to talk about having the best voice in show business, portraying GOB on Arrested Development, and what made Norm Macdonald the gold standard in comedy. Plus, Conan takes live voicemails about his celebrity emergency contact, working through a breakup, and more.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Rachel Dratch | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370231/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370231/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actress, comedian, and writer Rachel Dratch feels overly excited about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Rachel sits down with Conan to discuss the Debbie Downers that live inside us all, embarrassing odd jobs, and spoofing the Hallmark Christmas genre with Rachel’s new film A Clüsterfünke Christmas. Later, Conan responds to a listener voicemail asking what musical instrument he would like to be.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Karaoke Tribal Law | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370232/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370232/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan speaks with Marcus from Kamloops, British Columbia about his work as a land assessor and Conan’s mysterious improv technique.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Elvis Costello | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370233/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370233/</guid><description>Podcast Description Singer-songwriter Elvis Costello feels splendiferous about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Elvis sits down with Conan to talk about his new Audible original How to Play the Guitar and Y, the worst chord in existence, finding the right guitar, and why making mistakes is just as important as learning out of a book. Later, Conan considers a wide array of possible Conan-themed product lines as he and his team Review the Reviewers.</description></item><item><title>Mike Sweeney and Jessie Gaskell | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370234/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370234/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mike Sweeney and Jessie Gaskell join Conan to discuss the upcoming third season of Inside Conan: An Important Hollywood Podcast while they share favorite bits from the early days of Late Night and test Conan’s memories of sketches long gone by.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Daniel Sloss | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370235/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370235/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian, actor, and writer Daniel Sloss feels privileged about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Conan sits down with Daniel to chat about the importance of swearing, why being alone isn’t as bad as we’re taught to think, and his new book Everyone You Hate Is Going to Die. Later, Conan lays down the law with his team over their terrible misbehavior.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>A Belgian In France | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370236/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370236/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Manu from Nassigny, France about renovating a small-town Airbnb in the country&amp;rsquo;s geographical center.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Simon Rich | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370237/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370237/</guid><description>Podcast Description Writer and humorist Simon Rich feels extremely grateful about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Conan sits down with Simon to discuss writing affable villains, choosing colleges courses for their comedic premises, and the inspiration behind the hilarious stories in Simon’s latest book New Teeth. Plus, Sona seeks advice for a child-rearing quandary as she makes a welcome return to the team.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Hometown Dermatologist | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370238/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370238/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to dermatologist Tim from his very own hometown of Brookline, MA about getting a full body exam and whether Conan would be tasty if consumed.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jake Gyllenhaal | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370239/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370239/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Jake Gyllenhaal feels so many things about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Jake sits down with Conan to talk about kindness in entertainment, shooting his new film The Guilty on a contained set, and why performance is so integral in maintaining mental health. Plus, Conan and Sona offer words of encouragement to Matt Gourley as he prepares for impending parenthood.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>The Looming Comedian | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370240/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370240/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to obituary writer Kitty to better understand how he’ll be remembered after he’s dead.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Anderson Cooper | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370241/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370241/</guid><description>Podcast Description Journalist and news anchor Anderson Cooper feels kind of thrilled that he can be considered Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Anderson sits down with Conan to discuss the time they were boondoggled in South France, his thoughts on the modern news anchor, becoming a father, and researching his new book Vanderbilt: The Rise and Fall of an American Dynasty. Later, Conan responds to a listener&amp;rsquo;s voicemail about his resemblance to a certain Harry Potter character.</description></item><item><title>The Dungeonmaster | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370242/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370242/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to Turner from Austin, TX about the work that goes into being a quality D&amp;amp;D Dungeon Master and whether or not he could take Stephen Colbert in a LARP fight.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tiffany Haddish | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370243/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370243/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actress and comedian Tiffany Haddish feels amazing about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Tiffany sits down with Conan to chat about the life-saving power to make others laugh, why success is the best revenge, and phone sex hotline coaching. Plus, Engineer Sam debuts a new gadget to help keep Conan on track during the show.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821. For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Roller Girl | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370244/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370244/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to Rose from Tennessee about the roller derby scene and her professional life as an exterminator. Plus, Conan shares which historical figure he’d like to be murdered by.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Melissa McCarthy | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370245/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370245/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor, comedian, and producer Melissa McCarthy feels just delightful about being Conan O’Brien’s best friend.
Melissa sits down with Conan to chat about getting her start in stand-up and at The Groundlings, catapulting to stardom with Bridesmaids, and producing the Netflix documentary Bob Ross: Happy Accidents, Betrayal &amp;amp; Greed. Later, Conan receives a visual update from tattoo artist Kristina. Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>New Team Coco Podcast! | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370246/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370246/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Conan podcast universe just got a little bigger with Parks and Recollection, the definitive Parks and Recreation recap podcast hosted by Rob Lowe and Alan Yang—and your pal Conan is here to share a little tid-bit!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Conan Talks About Norm Macdonald | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370247/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 23:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370247/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan, Andy Richter, and longtime show producer Frank Smiley sit down to pay tribute to and discuss the legacy of Norm Macdonald - from his first stand-up appearance on Late Night with Conan O&amp;rsquo;Brien in 1993 to Norm&amp;rsquo;s infamous Moth joke and the story behind it. Conan wants to try and answer the question: who was this completely original genius and how was he so insanely funny?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A.T.O.S | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370248/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370248/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to author Megan about the rules of writing children’s books. Then, he speaks with Christian from San Diego about the best lock-picking tools available.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Alan Yang | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370249/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370249/</guid><description>Podcast Description Writer/director/producer Alan Yang feels like he’s weirdly fulfilling a childhood dream-thing about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Alan sits down with Conan to discuss writing for the full span of Parks and Recreation, growing up the son of Taiwanese immigrants, and unexpectedly introducing certain catchphrases into the popular lexicon. Later, Conan peers into the inner mechanisms of TikTok fame as achieved by his assistant David Hopping.
Check out Alan&amp;rsquo;s new podcast Parks and Recollection here.</description></item><item><title>Whip It Well | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370250/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370250/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks with opera singer Kyle to learn techniques for improving his singing (and speaking) voice.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kristen Schaal | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370251/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370251/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor and comedian Kristen Schaal feels relieved about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Kristen sits down with Conan to talk about growing up on a rural farm, what happens after we die and go to heaven, and managing self-expectations. Plus, Conan inquires with his team about the fine art of TikTok-ery.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>A Cobb Salad For The Lady | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370252/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370252/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks with Mary Anna from North Carolina about his absolute worst dating experience.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Joel McHale | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370253/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370253/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor and comedian Joel McHale feels a little anxious, but good about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Joel sits down with Conan to talk about his affinity for the blade, reflecting back on Community, danger stories of climbing Mt. Rainier, and joining the superhero world in the DC series Stargirl. Later, Conan and his team debate the science behind The Human Centipede.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Coroner O'Brien | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370254/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370254/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks with pathologist Yaman from Texas about how to perform an autopsy.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hannah Einbinder | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370255/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370255/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Hannah Einbinder feels confused about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Hannah sits down with Conan to discuss skin care secrets, launching her comedy career while managing ADHD, her role on the HBO Max series Hacks, and more. Plus, Conan gets a surprise visit from Sona to hear about her journey as a new parent.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Therizinosaurus O'Brien | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370256/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370256/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to Jimmy from Orlando about paleontological history and Conan’s personal favorite dinosaur.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Michael Keaton | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370257/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370257/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Michael Keaton feels so happy about being here and being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Michael sits down with Conan to talk about childhood acting games, portraying the original big-screen Batman, and looking back on his storied career with a different perspective. Plus, Matt Gourley makes a surprise announcement that catches Conan totally off-guard.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Pen Pals | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370258/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370258/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rory Scovel and Daniel Van Kirk join Conan to talk about their podcast Pen Pals and to answer a listener question on how to fall asleep fast.
Listen to Pen Pals here.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Cecily Strong | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370259/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370259/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actress and comedian Cecily Strong feels honored about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Cecily sits down with Conan to discuss the poignant themes that drive her memoir This Will All Be Over Soon, being plucked from iO Theater to perform as a main player on SNL, and the cast members that never fail to crack her up. Later, Conan receives genuine praise from his team as he offers a State of the Podcast address.</description></item><item><title>Down To The Cockaroo | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370260/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370260/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to tattoo artist Kristina about what kind of tattoo Conan ought to get and the incredible tattoo belonging to her husband.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Flula Borg | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370261/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370261/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor, comedian, and musician Flula Borg feels mmmmmh…oooooooh about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Flula sits down with Conan to talk about his fanny pack collection, developing an action-hero persona for his upcoming film The Suicide Squad, and his wildest dreams for the future. Later, Flula joins Conan and his team for a trip to the zoo on another Sound Effects Theater.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Haunted Hoochie | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370262/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370262/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to Nancy from Chicago about her work as a haunted house reviewer, and gets assigned his very own haunted house role.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>John Wilson | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370263/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370263/</guid><description>Podcast Description Filmmaker John Wilson feels very fortunate about being Conan O’Brien’s friend…?
John sits down with Conan to talk about the oddest discoveries made producing his show How To with John Wilson, the authenticity of old home videos, and indulging in propaganda-machine reality TV. Plus, Conan trains David Hopping to do the things Sona does, and should do.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Uncle Chutney and the Bubble Bunch | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370264/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370264/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to university graduate Lewis about bad dreams and how to introduce parents to comedy. Then, he chats with William from Anchorage about reluctant outdoorsmanship and whether Conan would be difficult to hunt.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Daniel Radcliffe | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370265/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370265/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Daniel Radcliffe feels cautiously optimistic about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Daniel sits down with Conan to talk about his comedy anthology series Miracle Workers, which role he’d play in the next Fast and Furious, and co-hosting the podcast Cunning Stunts with former Harry Potter stuntman David Holmes. Later, Conan and his team welcome David Hopping to fill in for Sona.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Maker's On The Rocks | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370266/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370266/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan chats with Michael from Reno about being a ‘spirits educator’ and which fictional bar he’d go to (and who he would bring along).
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Weird Al" Yankovic | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370267/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370267/</guid><description>Podcast Description Musical comedy legend &amp;ldquo;Weird Al&amp;rdquo; Yankovic feels figuratively tickled pink to be Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Weird Al sits down with Conan to talk about the Yankovic that inspired him to pick up the accordion, practicing comedy without punches, and forging his own trademark career in parody songwriting. Later, Conan and his team prepare for the imminent arrival of Sona’s twins.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Quoll-nan O’Brien | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370268/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370268/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to Brenna from Louisville, Colorado about herpetology and what kind of species Conan would want to be named after him.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sean Penn | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370269/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370269/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Sean Penn feels relieved to be Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Sean sits down with Conan to discuss finding a balance between art and advocacy, the modern preoccupation with optics over empathy, and working with CORE to make positive change in the world. Later, Sona and Matt Gourley bring a Conan-centric dating app exchange to life. See Sean Penn in his new film Flag Day, releasing August 20th.
Got a question for Conan?</description></item><item><title>Pre Bottled Urine | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370270/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370270/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks with copywriter Chloe about his happiest memory from the last year. Then he chats with Elizabeth about the new words he’s invented and his preferred pick-up lines.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bill Burr Returns | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370271/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370271/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Bill Burr feels honored to be Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Bill sits down with Conan to talk about the art of roasting, steering into shortcomings with character acting, his fandom for CHiPs and other 70s tv, and dog advice. Plus, Conan gives an update on his beach house situation as he and his team Review the Reviewers.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Dr. FUPA | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370272/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370272/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks with pharmacist Kathy from Illinois about amusement park mishaps and what kind of drug Conan would be.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Desus &amp; Mero | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370273/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370273/</guid><description>Podcast Description Desus Nice feels like a diversity hire about being Conan O’Brien’s friend; The Kid Mero feels semi-aroused about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Conan sits down with the hosts of Bodega Boys and Desus &amp;amp; Mero to talk about their new book God-Level Knowledge Darts: Life Lessons from the Bronx, the benefits of sporting their merch, and their beef with Jaleel White. Later, Conan and Sona go head to head with a Big Dick History quiz.</description></item><item><title>Conezone | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370274/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370274/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to Mohammad from Dublin about Conan’s go-to pump-up song if he were a DJ working a crowd. Then, he speaks with Leah from Michigan about what to do if trapped in a zoo.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kathryn Hahn | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370275/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370275/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actress Kathryn Hahn feels like she’d be lying about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Kathryn sits down with Conan to talk about hamming it up in grade school theater, bringing iconic eras of TV back to life with Wandavision, and her earliest role as a child actor on Hickory Hideout. Later, Conan ponders how he may have ruined his own name as he and his team Review the Reviewers.</description></item><item><title>Energeeza | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370276/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370276/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to Jenna from Boulder about his favorite conspiracy theories. Then, he describes his dream history museum exhibit while chatting with energy lawyer Jenny.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>John Krasinski | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370277/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370277/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor/director John Krasinski feels effervescent about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
John sits down with Conan to talk about going from an intern at Late Night to a megastar as Jim on The Office, favorite bits out of Boston, and the parallels between his new film A Quiet Place Part II and the tumultuous year of pandemic. Plus, Conan puts his vocal skills to the test with a wartime edition of Sound Effects Theater.</description></item><item><title>Sasha And The Massive Tea Cup | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370278/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370278/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks with Sasha from Kiev about new and exciting video game ideas, Sasha’s 7-month Dungeons &amp;amp; Dragons campaign, and the weirdest jobs he and his team have ever worked at.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>President Barack Obama | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370279/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370279/</guid><description>Podcast Description President Barack Obama feels ambivalent about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
The 44th President of the United States sits down with Conan to discuss making the decision to enter public service, his lifelong love of writing and latest book A Promised Land, why it’s not as hard as it looks to be funny as the president, and persevering with optimism in the 21st century.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Don’t Sit Down on Wet Grass | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370280/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370280/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan hears a diary excerpt from Katelyn at CalTech and shares some of his superstitions. Then he talks with Farhan at NYU about pursuing a career photographing comedy.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tracee Ellis Ross | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370281/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370281/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actress, producer, and entrepreneur Tracee Ellis Ross feels really strange, excited, a little squirrelly about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Tracee sits down with Conan to talk about getting the wiggles out, the characters that have developed out of her love of fashion, exploring questions of identity and race with Black-ish, and more. Plus, producer Matt Gourley shares the origin of his H. R. Giger obsession.
Got a question for Conan?</description></item><item><title>Beef Stock Bouillon Broth | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370282/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370282/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks with caller Andrew about the importance of colorizing your home and the pleasures of a good soak. Then he speaks with Chelby in Brooklyn about vision boards and being more confident on stage.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jake Tapper | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370283/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370283/</guid><description>Podcast Description Journalist and author Jake Tapper feels cromulent about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Jake sits down with Conan to talk about hanging out with the Eisenhower sisters, journalistic credibility (in superhero films), and exploring dark Hollywood in his new novel The Devil May Dance. Plus, Conan and his team consider the question of unseasonable horniness in response to a listener’s voicemail.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Avery Blaze | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370284/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370284/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks with Pauline from Sacramento to get professional style tips and to offer advice he’d give to help a friend out of a breakup slump.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Seth Rogen | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370285/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370285/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor, comedian, and writer Seth Rogen feels fantastic about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Seth sits down with Conan to talk about getting started in comedy writing jokes for a mohel, close encounter with Nic Cage and George Lucas, and incredible pornographic discoveries. Later, Conan enlists his team in an attempt to showcase his vocal sound effects.
Check out Seth&amp;rsquo;s new book Yearbook here.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Fruit, There It Is | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370286/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370286/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan discusses which cereal mascot he could take in a fight while speaking with Maggie from New Hampshire. Then he’s introduced to a very cute bunny and the idea of transforming a house into a cafe while talking to Keri from Pennsylvania.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Eric Andre | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370287/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370287/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Eric Andre is Conan O’Brien’s friend, and he feels titillated by that.
Eric sits down with Conan to talk about showcasing unity and an uplifting spirit with his new film Bad Trip, how street pranks can bring out the best of humanity, and the ways in which performing comedy can mess with one’s head. Later, Conan gives us live updates on his reaction to his second vaccine shot.</description></item><item><title>Fiki’s Gambit | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370288/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370288/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks to Andrew from Ohio about dairy farming and opening a Conan-themed amusement park. Next, he learns a bit about chess and cursed mugs while speaking with student Fiki.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>JB Smoove Returns | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370289/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370289/</guid><description>Podcast Description JB Smoove feels optimistic about being Conan O’Brien’s friend, and Miles Grose feels awkward about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
JB and Miles join Conan to talk about their new podcast May I Elaborate? Daily Wisdom from JB Smoove, using “profounity,” and aphorisms to help Conan appreciate his unique packaging. Plus, Conan and his crew check out fan-made art and a theme song for his conceptual Whirligig film.
Listen to May I Elaborate here.</description></item><item><title>The Student Has Become The Master | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370290/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370290/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan talks with Merin from Mexico City about the best places to go sightseeing. Then he gives advice on a pastor’s sock puppet problem while speaking with Ricky from El Paso.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Abbi Jacobson | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370291/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370291/</guid><description>Podcast Description Writer, comedian, and actress Abbi Jacobson feels scrumptious about being Conan O&amp;rsquo;Brien&amp;rsquo;s friend.
Abbi sits down with Conan to talk about hitting the mainstream with the webseries-turned-sitcom Broad City, exchanging letters with Tom Hanks, and highlights from her experiences working on her latest movie The Mitchells vs. the Machines and the upcoming reboot of A League of Their Own. Plus, Conan and his team consider the health impact of binge-listening to the podcast on another edition of Reviewing the Reviewers.</description></item><item><title>Fanhausen | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370292/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370292/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the very first Conan O’Brien Needs a Fan, Conan talks with minor league pro wrestler Donovan about his Conan-inspired wrestling persona. Then, Conan speaks on intrusive mothers and always being himself during a call with Leigh-Anne from Toronto.
Wanna get a chance to talk to Conan? Submit here: TeamCoco.com/CallConan
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bob Odenkirk | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370293/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370293/</guid><description>Podcast Description Writer and actor Bob Odenkirk feels confused about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Bob sits down with Conan to talk about making a (literal) mess together during their days at SNL, Bob’s favorite absurd characters to play over the years, and a storied career spanning sketch writing to portraying the iconic Saul Goodman to starring as an action hero in his new film Nobody. Later, Conan debuts his very own action-star character.</description></item><item><title>Adam McKay | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370294/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370294/</guid><description>Podcast Description Writer/director/producer Adam McKay feels old-fashioned-twelve-year-old-about-to-have-a-sleepover excited about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Adam sits down with Conan to talk about birthdays in Worcester, MA, famous pranks from the early days of UCB, the challenge of adapting The Big Short to film, and exploring the untold narratives around basketball players who lost their lives with his new podcast Death at the Wing. Later, Conan demands his assistant Sona explain her reasons for not owning a microwave.</description></item><item><title>Seth Meyers | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370295/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370295/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian and television host Seth Meyers feels anxious and excited about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Seth sits down with Conan to talk about coming on to SNL as a cast member first and a writer second, parsing praise from the enigmatic Lorne Michaels, and lessons learned at the Late Night desk. Later, Conan takes it up a notch in his quest for the perfect pen.
Got a question for Conan?</description></item><item><title>Kate Hudson | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370296/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370296/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actress and entrepreneur Kate Hudson feels insecure about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Kate sits down with Conan to talk about the key to being a good salesperson, rediscovering the music of the 90s through her kids, and family lessons learned from iconic parents Goldie Hawn and Kurt Russell. Plus, Conan shares an urgent news update with his team.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Shaquille O'Neal | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370297/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370297/</guid><description>Podcast Description Basketball legend Shaquille O’Neal feels enigmatic about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Shaq sits down with Conan to talk about his uniquely philosophical outlook, being yelled at by Charles Barkley’s mother, how he decides which brands to rep, and remembering Kobe. Later, Conan reprimands his assistant Sona over a mistaken order of pens.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Angela Kinsey and Jenna Fischer | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370298/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370298/</guid><description>Podcast Description Angela Kinsey and Jenna Fischer feel zippy and super-duper excited, respectively, about being Conan O’Brien’s friends.
Angela and Jenna sit down with Conan to talk about revisiting The Office with their hit podcast Office Ladies, why it’s important to treat interns fairly, and how their onscreen proximity led to a lifelong friendship. Plus, Conan hears a voicemail from his fantasy lover.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Jane Lynch | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370299/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370299/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actress Jane Lynch feels chosen and honored about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Jane sits down with Conan to talk about throwing a track suit on seething rage with her character Sue Sylvester on Glee, making film history with Christopher Guest, and going to where the love is. Plus, Conan asks for a favor involving a lost cell phone and a potential murder.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Kenan Thompson | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370300/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370300/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor and comedian Kenan Thompson feels great about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Kenan and Conan sit down to talk about the importance of manners, a shared love of biking, and Kenan’s new self-titled television series. Plus, Conan considers his own personal clothing brand.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dave Grohl | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370301/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370301/</guid><description>Podcast Description Musician Dave Grohl feels somewhat conflicted about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Dave sits down with Conan to talk about the merits of fried chicken and champagne, jamming with Paul McCartney, the pre-show ritual, and Foo Fighters’ new studio album Medicine at Midnight. Plus, Sona shares a big announcement with the team.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>David Spade | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370302/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370302/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor and comedian David Spade feels sort of excited about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
David sits down with Conan to talk about learning the ropes while working at Saturday Night Live, texting with Norm Macdonald, and memories of his father. Plus, Conan and Sona go head-to-head with a Big Dick History pop quiz.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Bryan Cranston | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370303/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370303/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Bryan Cranston feels very lucky about being happily paid to be Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Bryan sits down with Conan to talk about brushes with Charles Manson, establishing contact with Vince Gilligan on The X-Files, and portraying characters with complex moralities from Breaking Bad to his new show Your Honor. Later, Conan responds to a listener voicemail regarding his strangest purchases.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Mike Birbiglia | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370304/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370304/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Mike Birbiglia feels terrified about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Mike sits down with Conan to talk about taking advantage of his many ailments, not being the class clown, and giving back to the community with Tip Your Waitstaff. Plus, Conan provides another taste of his spinoff podcast focusing on well-endowed historical figures.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Anthony Anderson | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370305/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370305/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor and game show host Anthony Anderson feels bloated, hungover, and constipated about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Anthony sits down with Conan to discuss working in showbusiness with his mother, throwing his son a Bro Mitzvah, and playing dominoes with Michael Jordan. Later, Conan pitches a potential history podcast on the Russian Revolution.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Introducing Why Won’t You Date Me? With Nicole Byer | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370306/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370306/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s time to get sexy! The hilarious comedian Nicole Byer joins Conan to introduce her sex &amp;amp; relationship podcast ‘Why Won’t You Date Me?’ to the Team Coco network! Each week Nicole sits down with a comedian, actor, or ex-fling to interview their dating life while she figures out her own. With great guests like Jameela Jamil, Paul F. Tompkins, Whitney Cummings, and yes, Conan too! Literally nothing is off-limits, as Nicole unpacks first date horror stories, dating during COVID, sexcapades gone wrong, and more!</description></item><item><title>Fred Armisen | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370307/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370307/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian and actor Fred Armisen feels productive about being Conan O’Brien’s friend. Fred sits down with Conan to talk about approaching life from a drummer’s mentality, being a tech wiz, and hating the beach. Later, Conan responds to an issue with show merchandise as he and his team Review the Reviewers.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Ron Reagan | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370308/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 01:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370308/</guid><description>Podcast Description Political commentator Ron Reagan joins Conan to discuss the insurrection at the US Capitol building on January 6th.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>JB Smoove | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370309/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370309/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor, comedian, and writer JB Smoove feels as though Conan is taking advantage of him and pressuring people into being his friend.
JB sits down with Conan to talk about his favorite pitches that never made it to air, learning to read people by selling fire extinguishers, making strong choices on Curb Your Enthusiasm, and life lessons on fashion. Plus, Conan checks in with his team for another State of the Podcast address.</description></item><item><title>Matthew Rhys | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370310/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370310/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Matthew Rhys feels blank about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Matthew sits down with Conan to talk about living out his boyhood fantasies on Perry Mason, passing down his Welsh heritage to his son, and the one thing he’d wish for besides world peace. Later, Conan and his team get to know the next Golden Ticket winner in a fated meeting.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Amy Sedaris | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370311/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370311/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actress and comedian Amy Sedaris feels bullied into being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Amy sits down with Conan to talk about unfriendly wig shops, the fun of playing mean, and her comedy series At Home with Amy Sedaris. Plus, Conan and his team meet their first Golden Ticket winner.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kaley Cuoco | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370312/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370312/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actress Kaley Cuoco feels giddy about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Kaley sits down with Conan to talk about working with John Ritter, going full blast as the voice of Harley Quinn, horse caretaking tips, and her new mini-series The Flight Attendant. Plus, Conan laments the caloric scarcity of his new meal plan.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>John Cleese | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370313/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370313/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor and comedian John Cleese feels it is morally imperative to be Conan O’Brien’s friend.
John sits down with Conan to talk about his new book Creativity: A Short and Cheerful Guide, writing essays on the subject of time, and favorite philosophical definitions of humor. Plus, Conan finds kinship in a photograph of a mailbox that bears his likeness.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Kristin Chenoweth | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370314/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370314/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actress Kristin Chenoweth feels petite about…peeing?
Kristin sits down with Conan to talk about their kindred need for an audience, life-changing advice from Carol Burnett, and Kristin’s Food Network show Candy Land. Plus, Conan considers his impact on the English language as he and his team Review the Reviewers. Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.</description></item><item><title>Kevin Hart | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370315/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370315/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor and comedian Kevin Hart feels extremely blessed about being Conan O’Brien&amp;rsquo;s friend.
Kevin sits down with Conan to talk about the importance of taking care of the body, molding an environment for future success stories, and walking in fear at the highest levels of achievement. Later, Conan doubles down on one of his most hilarious jokes.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>John Leguizamo | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370316/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370316/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor, comedian, and playwright John Leguizamo feels great about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
John and Conan sit down to talk about attempting to master every performative craft, how sharing a room with a sibling makes one a better communicator, and digging into untold history with John’s one-man show Latin History for Morons and his new film Critical Thinking. Later, Conan ponders his frightening visage as he and his team Review the Reviewers.</description></item><item><title>Sam Richardson | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370317/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370317/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor and comedian Sam Richardson feels honored and obligated to be Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Sam sits down with Conan to talk about traveling to Ghana together for Conan Without Borders, his childhood obsession with Ghostbusters, and performing on cruise ships and in the hit HBO series Veep. Plus, Conan discovers a brand new effect he’s having on today’s youth.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Jim Parsons | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370318/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370318/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Jim Parsons feels okay about people saying that he’s Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Jim sits down with Conan to talk about recovering from COVID-19, working with dangerous animals on set, and starring in The Boys in the Band. Later, Conan makes a desperate plea to one of his sponsors.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.</description></item><item><title>Welcome to the Con-gregation! | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370319/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370319/</guid><description>Podcast Description Team Coco now bows at the altar of scams. That’s right—the Scam Goddess podcast has joined the Team Coco network! Scam Goddess is a show dedicated to fraud and all those who practice it. Each week host Laci Mosley digs into the scammiest scammers in history with guests like Paul Scheer, Jameela Jamil, and yes, even Conan! Get a taste of what Scam Goddess is all about with this clip featuring the hilarious Nicole Byer talking about career conman Jeremy Wilson.</description></item><item><title>Bruce Springsteen | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370320/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370320/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rock icon Bruce Springsteen feels ecstatic about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Bruce sits down with Conan to talk about his new album and documentary Letter to You, the death cult of rock ’n roll, the best go-to cover song, and his favorite American rock bands. Plus, Conan responds to a voicemail praising him for his allyship.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Rashida Jones | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370321/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370321/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actress and producer Rashida Jones feels fine about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Rashida sits down with Conan to talk about the importance of diversifying your skills, creating a documentary about her father Quincy Jones, and working with Bill Murray on her new film On the Rocks. Later, Conan responds to a voicemail about a man with no name.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hillary Clinton Returns | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370322/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370322/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former Secretary of State Hillary Clinton feels enthusiastic about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Hillary sits down with Conan to talk about launching her new podcast You and Me Both, overcoming the double standard for women in the public eye, and the need for an American moral reckoning. Plus, Conan gives the world a much-needed update on his iconic hair.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Willie Nelson | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370323/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370323/</guid><description>Podcast Description Music legend Willie Nelson feels great about being Conan’s friend.
Willie sits down with Conan to talk about his new book Me and Sister Bobbie: True Tales of the Family Band, favorite guitars and musical influences, and losing money in hog-raising. Plus, Conan shares fond memories of antagonizing his own mother.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Colin Quinn | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370324/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370324/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Colin Quinn feels euphoric about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Colin sits down with Conan to talk about his tenure on Weekend Update, why simple transgression isn’t comedy, and the best quotes out of his new book Overstated: A Coast-to-Coast Roast of the 50 States.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Michelle Obama Returns | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370325/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370325/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former First Lady Michelle Obama feels very, very hopeful about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Michelle sits down with Conan to discuss her new show The Michelle Obama Podcast, the importance of humility in politics, and changing the voting culture with WhenWeAllVote.org.
Check out Conan&amp;rsquo;s conversation with Michelle on her podcast here: https://open.spotify.com/episode/2n57zGznX7ZXlkGC0I521o
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rory Scovel | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370326/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370326/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Rory Scovel feels grateful about being Conan O’Brien’s best friend.
Rory sits down with Conan to talk about selling the most bizarre bits onstage, fights in the audience, and his new podcast Dads. Later, Conan recalls his search for family roots in Dungarvan, Ireland.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Keith Urban | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370327/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370327/</guid><description>Podcast Description Singer, songwriter, and record producer Keith Urban feels incredibly confused about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Keith sits down with Conan to talk about playing a surprise drive-in concert for healthcare workers, quitting school to pursue his music career, and releasing his new album &amp;lsquo;The Speed of Now Part 1.&amp;rsquo; Later, Conan envisions the mascot of the Conan O’Brien Elementary School.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Sean Hayes | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370328/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370328/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor and producer Sean Hayes feels indifferent about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Sean sits down with Conan to talk about choosing acting over becoming a concert pianist, dangerous childhood games, and his podcast SmartLess with Jason Bateman and Will Arnett. Plus, Conan decides what kind of uncle he wants to be on another Review the Reviewers.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Deon Cole | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370329/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370329/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian, writer and actor Deon Cole feels wonderful every time he’s with Conan O’Brien.
Deon sits down with Conan to discuss the authentic mini-bar experience, being a comedian before anything else, and learning to DJ during the pandemic. Later, things get heated between Conan and his team as they share controversial opinions on a summertime treat during a Review the Reviewers.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Introducing Dads: The Podcast with Rory Scovel | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370330/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370330/</guid><description>Podcast Description You may know the hilarious comedian Rory Scovel from his many appearances on CONAN, or maybe you even saw him live on tour with Conan &amp;amp; Friends. If you’ve ever wondered what he’d sound like as the host of his very own Team Coco podcast, wonder no more! Rory has a brand new show called “Dads: The Podcast.” Each week he and co-host Ruthie Wyatt are joined by their hilarious celebrity friends to unpack the mysteries of fatherhood, parenting, and the weirdos who raised us.</description></item><item><title>Jameela Jamil | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370331/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370331/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actress Jameela Jamil feels better about her hair for being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Jameela sits down with Conan to talk about the roots of British self-deprecation, injecting humor into sex, and encouraging body positivity with the ‘I Weigh’ Instagram movement. Later, Conan shares his excitement over his newest piece of headwear.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Michael Che | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370332/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370332/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Michael Che feels honored to be Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Michael sits down with Conan to talk about his first stand-up experience, jumping into the deep end at Saturday Night Live, and why jokes about politics and race will always hold up. Plus, Conan tries his hand at reading some erotic fiction.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Maya Rudolph | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370333/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370333/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actress and comedian Maya Rudolph feels pretty terrific about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Maya sits down with Conan to talk about making Emmy history by competing against herself in a single category, meeting (and hugging) Prince, her inspiration for voicing Connie the Hormone Monstress on Big Mouth, and more. Plus, Conan learns about his surprising impact on the human population as he and his team respond to a listener voicemail.</description></item><item><title>Jim Carrey | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370334/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370334/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Jim Carrey feels warm all over about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Jim sits down with Conan to talk about the prophecies in his new book ‘Memoirs and Misinformation,’ deliberately getting into a fight with the audience, and balancing the introvert with the extrovert throughout his legendary career. Later, Conan faces the pressure as he gives another State of the Podcast address.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>W. Kamau Bell | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370335/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370335/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian and writer W. Kamau Bell feels cautiously optimistic, but still not great about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Kamau sits down with Conan to talk about meeting Anthony Bourdain, doing bits with his kids, and tolerating discomfort. Later, Conan’s assistant Sona recounts losing her wallet.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Summer S'mores with Conan and the Chill Chums 6 | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370336/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370336/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the final Summer S’mores special, Conan and the Chill Chums discuss who Conan should expect to see at his own funeral.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Summer S'mores with Conan and the Chill Chums 5 | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370337/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370337/</guid><description>Podcast Description On another Summer S’mores special, Conan and the Chill Chums discuss the perfect murder.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Summer S’mores with Conan and the Chill Chums 4 | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370338/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370338/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan gives the Chill Chums some friendly criticisms during another Summer S’mores special.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tom Hanks | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370339/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370339/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Tom Hanks feels grand about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Tom sits down with Conan to talk about recovering from COVID-19 in Australia, writing the screenplay for his new WWII-era film Greyhound, and the first thing he ever saw on YouTube.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Summer S’mores with Conan and the Chill Chums 3 | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370340/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370340/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan and his team contemplate an alternate presidential history on another Summer S’mores special.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Introducing Literally! with Rob Lowe | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370341/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370341/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rob Lowe takes over Conan O&amp;rsquo;Brien Needs A Friend to share a clip from his new podcast, Literally! with Rob Lowe. Check out the first episode with special guest Chris Pratt now on Apple Podcasts: apple.co/literally
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Summer S’mores with Conan and the Chill Chums 2 | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370342/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370342/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan’s team tries to induce chill-ness by any means necessary on another special Summer S’mores episode.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Summer S’mores with Conan and the Chill Chums 1 | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370343/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370343/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the first installment of a special Summer S’mores series, Conan and his team loosen up by sharing memories of summers past.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Amy Schumer | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370344/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370344/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Amy Schumer feels fully indifferent about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Amy and Conan sit down to talk about comedians getting buff, cult leaders, debuting Amy Schumer Learns to Cook, and whether a baby can have “it”. Plus, Conan and his team celebrate the culmination of their second season with some parting thoughts.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Rob Lowe | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370345/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370345/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Rob Lowe feels optimistic about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Rob and Conan sit down to talk about advice from Cary Grant and Paul Newman, what’s in store with Rob’s new podcast Literally! With Rob Lowe, and which Supreme Court justice Rob considers a friend. Plus, Conan reviews submitted pieces of risqué fan art.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Russell Brand | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370346/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370346/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Russell Brand feels nervous about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Russell and Conan sit down to talk about the appearance of the sacred within the ordinary, making pain lucrative, and the constant of late-night talk shows in America. Later, Conan answers a listener question about which member of his team he would fire.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>J. J. Abrams | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370347/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370347/</guid><description>Podcast Description Filmmaker J.J. Abrams feels exceedingly lucky about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
J.J. sits down with Conan to discuss finding the confidence to take the reins on iconic franchises like Star Trek and Star Wars, how to cut together a good trailer, and getting his first gig writing the music for the 1982 horror film Nightbeast. Later, Conan considers his approach to ad reads as he and his team Review the Reviewers.</description></item><item><title>Mike Myers | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370348/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370348/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Mike Myers feels prehensile about being Conan O’Brien’s friend
Mike sits down with Conan to talk about treating the audience as the boss, sharing his iconic comedic filmography with his kids, and the “cinema bleak” of Canada. Later, Conan gets frantic with a one-off segment titled “Maybe I’m As Big a Nerd As Gourley”.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Ted Danson | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370349/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370349/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Ted Danson feels oddly comforted about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Ted and Conan sit down to talk about false humility, being recognized (while wearing a mask), and pandemic farts. Plus, Conan shares a touching clip from the set-up of the remote recording.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nick Kroll | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370350/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370350/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick and Conan sit down to talk about how being a late bloomer informed the making of Big Mouth, collaborating with longtime partner John Mulaney on Oh, Hello: the P’dcast, and finding positives within a long stretch of quarantine. Later, Conan and his team answer listener questions about homeopathic remedies and more.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Ricky Gervais | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370351/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370351/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian, actor, writer, producer Ricky Gervais feels strangely underwhelmed about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Ricky sits down with Conan to discuss getting a laugh out of the worst of humanity, the upcoming season of his Netflix show After Life, and finding out his heroes are just regular people. Plus, Conan shares what he’s learned about tech in the days of quarantine.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Kevin Nealon | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370352/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370352/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian and actor Kevin Nealon feels confused that he’s considered Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Kevin and Conan sit down to talk about working on the Hans &amp;amp; Franz musical, perfecting the interview on his YouTube show Hiking with Kevin, and planning a road trip. Plus, Conan gives out much-needed advice on dating and getting along with family during quarantine.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>D'Arcy Carden | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370353/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370353/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actress D’Arcy Carden feels hopeful about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
D’Arcy and Conan sit down to talk about bringing Janet to life on The Good Place, meeting her comedic heroes, babysitting for Bill Hader, and being rewarded for working hard and not asking too much. Later, Conan takes a look at an old college photo with his team.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Steve Coogan | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370354/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370354/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian and actor Steve Coogan feels quietly optimistic about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Steve sits down with Conan to talk about channeling comic persona Alan Partridge, Steve’s newest film Greed, portraying Stan Laurel in Stan &amp;amp; Ollie, and not minding when someone doesn’t think he’s funny. Plus, Conan and his team look back on Conan’s technological achievements with a special montage.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Whitney Cummings | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370355/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370355/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian and actress Whitney Cummings feels stressed out about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Whitney and Conan sit down to talk about being a serious child, impetigo and epigenetics, and the stresses of planning a wedding. Later, Conan hears about his assistant Sona’s medical procedure.
Check out Whitney’s latest comedy special Can I Touch It? on Netflix here.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Will Arnett | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370356/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370356/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Will Arnett feels pretty put out about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Will and Conan sit down to talk about being known as a voice-over artist, the best bits of Brian McCann, and finding his crowd with Arrested Development. Plus, Conan and Sona take another swing at a Podcast Quiz.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>A Very Special Self-Quarantine Episode featuring Andy Daly | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370357/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370357/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian and actor Andy Daly joins Conan and crew for a bonus quarantine episode of Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend. Coming to you from Matt’s allegedly safe and socially-distanced home, Conan discusses the current state of things, enjoys a visit from two questionable characters — Dalton Wilcox and August Lindt, and speaks to Team Coco assistant David Hopping about life without access to Disneyland.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Paul Reubens | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370358/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370358/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor, producer, and writer Paul Reubens feels fantastic about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Paul and Conan sit down to talk about wanting to join the circus, the letter Paul wrote to Walt Disney, remembering Phil Hartman, and anxiety over getting recognized. Later, Conan and Sona go head to head with a podcast statistics quiz.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Ali Wong | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370359/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370359/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Ali Wong feels very new about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Ali and Conan sit down to talk about her father’s love of pajama pants, why travel is the hardest part of stand-up, the mysterious metrics of Netflix, and maintaining her strong sense of Asian-American identity. Plus, Conan talks to his assistant Sona about getting caught breaking the rules at Disneyland.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Jim Gaffigan | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370360/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370360/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Jim Gaffigan feels like Nikki Glaser felt about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Jim and Conan sit down to talk about showbiz friendships, the power of bragging, drinking options, and presidential endorsements. Later, Conan recalls an overreaction to a home emergency.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Judd Apatow | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370361/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370361/</guid><description>Podcast Description Writer/director/producer Judd Apatow does not feel hopeful about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Judd sits down with Conan to talk about using silence in their work, lifting up comedy stars like Seth Rogen and Pete Davidson, fashion tips from Jon Lovitz, reminiscing about eating, and comic rhythm. Plus, Conan and Sona dish on producer Matt Gourley in his absence.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Keegan-Michael Key | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370362/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370362/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Keegan-Michael Key feels overwhelmed about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Keegan and Conan sit down to chat about growing up a 60s guy (in the 80s), favorite niche impressions, performing sketch alongside President Obama, and discovering entertainment as a career path. Later, Conan responds to a listener voicemail about socks.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sarah Silverman | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370363/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370363/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Sarah Silverman feels grateful about being Conan O’Brien’s friend. Sarah and Conan sit down to chat about first times, getting aggressively dumb and silly, lessons from Garry Shandling, and the fear of speaking up. Plus, a listener voicemail forces Conan to contemplate a sandwich that bears his name.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jesse Eisenberg | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370364/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370364/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor, author, and playwright Jesse Eisenberg feels desperate to be Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Jesse and Conan sit down to discuss the better ways of humbling oneself, being driven by anthropological curiosity, avoiding online negativity, and the odd homogeneity of Los Angeles. Later, Conan attempts to inspire a pregnant listener as he and his team Review the Reviewers.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Eugene Levy and Catherine O'Hara | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370365/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370365/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actors, writers and comedians Eugene Levy and Catherine O’Hara feel absolutely delighted, flattered, and honored to be considered Conan O’Brien’s friends.
Eugene and Catherine sit down with Conan to talk about taking chances in the pre-internet era with SCTV, transforming into the characters they play on Schitt’s Creek, the formula that makes a successful comedy show stick, and legendary tales from the Second City stage. Later, Conan takes it up with the Cheesecake Factory menu.</description></item><item><title>Nikki Glaser | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370366/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370366/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Nikki Glaser feels overwhelmed about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Nikki and Conan sit down to discuss modern perspectives on the vagina, the emotional toll of performing a roast, how discovering stand-up comedy helped Nikki manage an eating disorder, and going down in flames with her worst-ever jokes told at a wedding. Plus, Conan responds to the idea of his name on a rump-cheek as he and his staff Review the Reviewers.</description></item><item><title>Charles Barkley | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370367/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370367/</guid><description>Podcast Description Basketball legend Charles Barkley feels great about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Charles and Conan sit down to chat about the extreme competition of going pro, getting booed offstage at a Katy Perry concert for dissing the Timberwolves, his friendship with Shaq, and advocating for education. Later, Conan issues a warning to his staff about spoiling certain tv shows.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Al Franken | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370368/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370368/</guid><description>Podcast Description Author, comedian, and former senator Al Franken is already a f***ing friend of Conan O’Brien’s.
Al and Conan sit down to talk about favorite SNL sketches that never made it to air, doing ‘The Brain Tumor Comedian’ with Tom Davis, shutting down George Harrison’s drunken piano playing, and the jokes that failed to land with guests of The Al Franken Podcast. Plus, Conan follows up on the resurfacing of his correspondence with iconic writer E.</description></item><item><title>Malcolm Gladwell | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370369/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370369/</guid><description>Podcast Description Author and journalist Malcolm Gladwell feels pressured into being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Malcolm and Conan sit down to talk about Malcolm’s new book Talking to Strangers: What We Should Know about the People We Don&amp;rsquo;t Know, conversations about gardening, tabloid inventions, tales from the IRA, and Conan’s own special cult of personality. Plus, Conan and his assistant Sona engage in a struggle for power.
Got a question for Conan?</description></item><item><title>Introducing Smartr- Episode 1: Puel with Tim Heidecker | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370370/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370370/</guid><description>Podcast Description Smartr is a new scripted Podcast from Team Coco that follows tech genius, Noa Lukas, as he profiles the monopolies of tomorrow and gives them advice on how to grow without being hindered by the dinosaur concepts of regulations, public opinion, and basic morality. In the first episode of Smartr, Noa Lukas visits Puel, whose pool-match algorithm finds the perfect pool filled with swimmers like you based on your demographic profile.</description></item><item><title>John Mulaney | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370371/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370371/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian John Mulaney feels falsely modest about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
John and Conan sit down to talk about growing up in a family trapped in the 1950s, the power of dressing well, fulfilling a lifelong dream of a career in comedy, and the rewarding experience of creating his new Netflix show John Mulaney &amp;amp; The Sack Lunch Bunch. Later, Conan and his team share their formative cinematic experiences.</description></item><item><title>Jack Black | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370372/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370372/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor/musican Jack Black feels shitty about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Jack and Conan sit down to talk about the 1999 pilot Heat Vision and Jack, laying down hot tracks with Jack White, bringing the energy to max performing with Tenacious D, the greatest mobile golf game, and the later films of Ruth Gordon. Plus, Conan issues another State of the Podcast address.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Hillary and Chelsea Clinton | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370373/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370373/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former First Lady and Secretary of State Hillary Clinton and daughter Chelsea Clinton feel great (but a little apprehensive) about being Conan O’Brien’s friends.
Hillary and Chelsea sit down with Conan to discuss the stories that inspired them to co-write The Book of Gutsy Women, Chelsea’s teenage years in the White House, unusual Halloween costumes, the incredible pace of technology, and why we should never quit betting on optimism.</description></item><item><title>Eric Idle | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370374/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370374/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedy icon Eric Idle feels moderately aroused about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Eric and Conan sit down to talk about his autobiography Always Look on the Bright Side of Life, playing ukulele with George Harrison, Monty Python’s genesis at Cambridge, finding a fan in Elvis Presley, the Fab Four’s response to parody group The Rutles, and looking back on fifty years of Python. Plus, Conan makes an effort to help his assistant Sona manage her side hustles.</description></item><item><title>Ellen DeGeneres | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370375/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370375/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian, television host, writer and producer Ellen DeGeneres feels honored to be Conan o Brien’s friend.
Ellen and Conan sit down to talk about wearing gold jackets in the 80s, Ellen’s return to stand-up after 15 years with her special Relatable, the pressures of maintaining a talk show persona, and the importance of not taking things so seriously. Plus, Conan contemplates his own name while dropping others in response to a listener’s email.</description></item><item><title>Paul Rudd | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370376/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370376/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Paul Rudd feels excited about Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Paul and Conan sit down to talk about Paul’s long-running “Mac and Me” gag on Conan, the urge to go out of bounds, showbiz muscle memory, and learning how to bartend. Later, Conan and his team respond to a listener voicemail about being scared.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Neil Young | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370377/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370377/</guid><description>Podcast Description Music legend Neil Young feels good about being Conan’s friend.
Neil and Conan sit down to talk about Neil’s 1957 Eldorado Biarritz, why he won’t allow his songs in commercials, the importance of preserving musical sound quality, recording his new album Colorado with Crazy Horse at 9,200 ft elevation, and what Neil loves about his Gretsch White Falcon guitar. Plus, Conan and his staff conduct a Gerber taste test.</description></item><item><title>Zach Galifianakis | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370378/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370378/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor and comedian Zach Galifianakis feels cautious about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Zach and Conan sit down to talk about the showbiz cult of ego, mining comedy from miscommunication, phone calls from the president, hunting for clay, and being inspired by a professional whistler. Later, Sona and Matt Gourley surprise Conan with a Halloween treat.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>John Oliver | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370379/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370379/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian and host of Last Week Tonight John Oliver feels cautiously optimistic about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
John and Conan sit down to chat about being nominated for an OBE, the silliest ways they’ve spent their show budgets, why the U.S. got the best of British comedy, performing with the Cambridge Footlights, and why John can never watch The Great British Baking Show. Plus, Conan gets a lesson in printer etiquette from his staff.</description></item><item><title>Tina Fey | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370380/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370380/</guid><description>Podcast Description Writer, comedian, and actress Tina Fey feels good about being Conan O’Brien’s friend; it tracks.
Tina and Conan sit down to discuss SNL-induced OCD, bringing Mean Girls to Broadway, husband Jeff Richmond’s mysterious recurring Conan role, getting over the “chipple,” and improvising like a writer. Plus, Conan responds to a voicemail about which president he’d like to eat.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>David Letterman | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370381/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370381/</guid><description>Podcast Description Legendary television host David Letterman has endless admiration for Conan O’Brien.
David joins Conan to kick off season two with a conversation about David’s unmatchable career in late night, interactions with Johnny Carson and Bob Hope, what they see for their kids in the future, and why the best people in showbiz are always the hardest working. Plus, Conan gives an update on the horse David gifted to him, and Conan’s assistant Sona and producer Matt Gourley join in for another round of Review the Reviewers.</description></item><item><title>Bob Newhart (Re-Release) | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370382/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370382/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stand-up comedian and actor Bob Newhart feels anxious about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Bob sits down with Conan to share stories about meeting Don Rickles for the first time, sitting in for Johnny Carson on The Tonight Show, leaping from accounting to showbusiness, beautiful moments from The Bob Newhart Show, the danger of cynicism in comedy, and Chicago values. Plus, Conan responds to a listener voicemail about an award that was named after him.</description></item><item><title>Michelle Obama (Re-Release) | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370383/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370383/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former First Lady Michelle Obama feels cautiously optimistic about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Michelle and Conan sit down to talk about Michelle’s memoir Becoming, childhood inspirations, embarrassing her kids, spending time alone with Chipotle, putting the right people in office, and the loss of anonymity. Original airdate: March 17, 2019.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Jeff Goldblum (Re-Release) | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370384/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370384/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Jeff Goldblum feels…truthful about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Jeff and Conan sit down to chat about mini-orgasms, spousal criticism, pinky rings, raising comic children, and speaking in jazz. Plus, producer Matt Gourley reveals the results of the latest blind drawing contest, and Conan responds to a voicemail regarding proper elocution. Original air date: Feb. 24, 2019.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Deep Dive with Dana Carvey 6 | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370385/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370385/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dana’s reclusive side takes hold. Dennis Miller eats sushi. Bernie Sanders works as a crosswalk guard. Paul McCartney gets bronchitis. Dana’s landlord tries to take his money. Jimmy Carter has a nervous breakdown.
This episode is sponsored by Buffy Comforters (www.buffy.co code: CONAN), Betterhelp (www.betterhelp.com/conan code: CONAN), Vital Farms (www.vitalfarms.com/coupon), Mizzen+Main (www.comfortable.af code: CONAN), and HotelTonight (www.hoteltonight.com).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Deep Dive with Dana Carvey 5 | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370386/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370386/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan and Dana revisit Hitler, Elvis and the Kennedys in the bunker. Tracing the evolution of the rock star. Jimmy Stewart gets lucky.
This episode is sponsored by Betterhelp (www.betterhelp.com/conan code: CONAN), Atoms (www.atoms.com/CONAN), KiwiCo (www.kiwico.com/CONAN), and MyBookie (www.mybookie.ag code: conan).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Deep Dive with Dana Carvey 4 | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370387/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370387/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan and Dana deal with being hyped up. Impressions of a late 19th century science symposium, Conan’s talent manager, and Jeff Bridges celebrating life. Plus: John Wayne’s fury at fear and agnostic hymns.
This episode is sponsored by Betterhelp (www.betterhelp.com/conan code: CONAN), Vital Farms (vitalfarms.com/coupon), Mizzen+Main (www.comfortable.af code: CONAN), and HotelTonight (www.hoteltonight.com).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Deep Dive with Dana Carvey 3 | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370388/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370388/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dana gets into a competitive fashion. Robert Shaw (from Jaws) discusses the Mueller Report. Tony Montana at Thanksgiving Dinner. Plus, Bradley Cooper &amp;amp; Lady Gaga at the Oscars, Norm MacDonald, and Mike Tyson.
This episode is sponsored by Amazon Launchpad (amazon.com/shoplaunchpad), Betterhelp (www.betterhelp.com/conan code: CONAN), NHTSA, KiwiCo (www.kiwico.com/CONAN), and Stamps.com (www.stamps.com code: CONAN).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Deep Dive with Dana Carvey 2 | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370389/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370389/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dana reveals his more aggressive characters plus Jon Lovitz’s secret catchphrase. Also: Trump sings a song and Obama makes a pitch to Netflix.
This episode is sponsored by Vital Farms (www.vitalfarms.com/coupon), Mizzen+Main (www.comfortable.af code: CONAN), Atoms Shoes (www.atoms.com/CONAN), HotelTonight (www.hoteltonight.com), and WGU (www.wgu.edu/CONAN).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Deep Dive with Dana Carvey 1 | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370390/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370390/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the first episode of Deep Dive with Dana Carvey, Dana and Conan talk about the Beatles, the key to impersonating British actors, and Predator Island. Plus, Paul McCartney catches up with John Lennon in the afterlife.
This episode is sponsored by HotelTonight (www.hoteltonight.com), Lights Out With David Spade, and Clif Bar (www.clifbar.com/CONAN).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Introducing The Three Questions with Andy Richter | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370391/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370391/</guid><description>Podcast Description Out now on Earwolf, Host Andy Richter asks the same three questions to each guest: Where do you come from? Where are you going? What have you learned? This will not be a one-sided process, as Andy won’t shy away from getting personal himself. Check it out now in Apple Podcasts: apple.co/threequestions
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trailer: Deep Dive with Dana Carvey | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370392/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370392/</guid><description>Podcast Description On each episode of this six-part miniseries, Dana Carvey and Conan O’Brien will deepen their friendship and fall into comedy madness along the way. Premieres August 5th.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Julia Louis-Dreyfus | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370393/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370393/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actress and comedy icon Julia Louis-Dreyfus feels a tad hopeful (but not really) about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
On the season finale, Julia and Conan sit down to talk about when it’s okay for their kids to hear them swearing, the melding of Veep and reality, how frustration can be good for you, learning via failure at SNL and much more. Plus, Conan responds to a listener looking for work as he and his team Review the Reviewers.</description></item><item><title>Kumail Nanjiani | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370394/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370394/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian, actor, and writer Kumail Nanjiani feels apologetic about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Kumail sits down with Conan to discuss his recent absence on the television program, coming from a hardworking family, having incredible balance, hating Ferris Bueller, and the best way to reward oneself. Plus, Conan responds to a listener voicemail about being a godfather.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Andy Richter | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370395/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370395/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Andy Richter feels just fine about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Andy sits down with Conan to talk about their 26 years of friendship, how funny and gross the human body can be, using the early internet to pull pranks at work, the advances of plastic surgery over the years, and his new podcast &amp;lsquo;The Three Questions with Andy Richter&amp;rsquo; - the first episode is available now on Stitcher, Apple, Spotify, or wherever you listen to fine podcasts.</description></item><item><title>Mila Kunis | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370396/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370396/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actress Mila Kunis feels indifferent about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Mila sits down with Conan to talk about not being wasteful, running moneymaking schemes (while working on That ‘70s Show), addressing her stardom with her kids, and the importance of having a job at a young age. Plus, Conan gives producer Matt Gourley’s mother Welford a call.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Billy Eichner | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370397/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370397/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Billy Eichner feels mixed about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Billy sits down with Conan to talk about his dream guests for ‘Billy on the Street,’ creating his own world in the industry, writing the first major gay rom-com, and voicing Timon in the remake of The Lion King. Plus, Conan and producer Matt Gourley resolve a scheduling dispute.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Lin-Manuel Miranda | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370398/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370398/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor, composer, playwright, and producer Lin-Manuel Miranda feels great about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Lin-Manuel and Conan sit down this week to chat about the perks of youth theatre, rhyming as a superpower, the magic of Queen &amp;amp; David Bowie’s “Under Pressure,” and handling the immeasurable success of &amp;lsquo;Hamilton.&amp;rsquo; Plus, Conan comes clean about a grand cover-up involving his producer Matt Gourley.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Martin Short | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370399/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370399/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian and actor Martin Short feels ashamed about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Martin and Conan sit down to chat about the best time to be 30, the production of Godspell that started it all, how Martin’s Irish heritage shaped his comedy, doing Bette Davis in front of Bette Davis, and which character Martin would like to be buried as. Plus, Conan and his team deconstruct the family dynamic of the show.</description></item><item><title>Hannah Gadsby | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370400/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370400/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Hannah Gadsby feels confused about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Hannah and Conan sit down to talk about her new show &amp;lsquo;Douglas,&amp;rsquo; the pitfalls of self-deprecation, breaking the comedy code with ‘Nanette,’ reacting to her mother in the audience, and needing to not care. Plus, sparks fly between Conan and producer Matt Gourley as they once again Review the Reviewers.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Bob Newhart | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370401/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370401/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stand-up comedian and actor Bob Newhart feels anxious about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Bob sits down with Conan to share stories about meeting Don Rickles for the first time, sitting in for Johnny Carson on The Tonight Show, leaping from accounting to showbusiness, beautiful moments from The Bob Newhart Show, the danger of cynicism in comedy, and Chicago values. Plus, Conan responds to a listener voicemail about an award that was named after him.</description></item><item><title>Howard Stern | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370402/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370402/</guid><description>Podcast Description Radio personality Howard Stern feels badly about not being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Howard and Conan sit down to talk about Howard’s new book ‘Howard Stern Comes Again,’ the punk rock element of radio, the stigma of psychotherapy, and the most painful parts of publicity. Plus, Conan recalls his childhood pets as he and his team respond to a positive review of the show.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Bill Hader | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370403/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370403/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor and comedian Bill Hader feels great about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Bill and Conan sit down to chat about their fondness for antiquated terms, the importance of relaxation, crime show narrators, and competing with YouTube. Plus, Conan issues a State of the Podcast address.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
This episode is sponsored by The Great Courses Plus (www.thegreatcoursesplus.com/CONAN), Bombas (www.bombas.com/CONAN), Robinhood (www.</description></item><item><title>Jimmy Kimmel | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370404/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370404/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fellow late-night TV host Jimmy Kimmel feels sexually excited about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Jimmy joins Conan to talk about the competitive late-night landscape, Jimmy’s love of feeding people, Conan’s many hobbies, intermittent fasting, and the best ways to keep guests talking. Plus, Conan responds to a listener voicemail inviting him over for a game of bridge. Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
This episode is sponsored by State Farm (www.</description></item><item><title>Robert Caro | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370405/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370405/</guid><description>Podcast Description Author Robert Caro is cautiously optimistic about being Conan O Brien’s friend.
Robert and Conan discuss his biographical works on Robert Moses and Lyndon Johnson, getting into the shoes of his subjects, his new book “Working,” searching for the man who helped steal a Senate election, and the parallels we can draw to today’s events. Plus, Conan responds to a listener voicemail about the size of his skull. Got a question for Conan?</description></item><item><title>Tig Notaro | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370406/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370406/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Tig Notaro feels glad about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Tig and Conan sit down this week to discuss the hilarity of crashing and burning onstage, vacationing with rock stars, wearing a nightcap, playing Vegas, and drawing Civil War portraits. Later, executive producer Adam Sachs weighs in on the dos and don’ts of casual schmoozing with guests.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Patton Oswalt | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370407/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370407/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian and actor Patton Oswalt feels anxious about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Patton and Conan sit down to talk about remembering comedy misfires, SNL’s best hosts from the sports world, getting screwed over by decency, the importance of spellcheck, and recapturing the magic of breakfast cereal. Plus, Conan gets to the bottom of a sweatpants mystery during a game of True or False with Sona Movsesian.
Got a question for Conan?</description></item><item><title>Nicole Byer | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370408/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370408/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian and actress Nicole Byer feels excited about being Conan O’Brien’s friend!
Nicole and Conan sit down to chat about loving the people they torment, marriages of convenience, Ayahuasca side effects, Conan’s dateability, and making your own tattoos with Microsoft Word. Later, Conan recaps a texting miscommunication during a game of True or False with Sona Movsesian.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Ben Stiller | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370409/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370409/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor, writer, and director Ben Stiller feels excited to be Conan O&amp;rsquo;Brien&amp;rsquo;s friend, but he isn’t holding his breath.
Ben and Conan sit down this week to chat about growing up in show business, getting the finger from strangers, returning to Saturday Night Live, how Ben came into his latest project Escape at Dannemora, and being able to make yourself laugh. Plus, producer Matt Gourley shows off a piece of true presidential memorabilia.</description></item><item><title>Ray Romano | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370410/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370410/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor and comedian Ray Romano feels good about being Conan O’Brien’s friend (with an exception).
Ray and Conan sit down to chat about last-minute gifts for Adam Levine, being a good Samaritan, Ray’s first time doing stand-up, legendary horrible gigs, and the joy of winning over a room full of strangers. Plus, Conan responds to a voicemail from a listener regarding his advertisers.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Michelle Obama | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370411/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370411/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former First Lady Michelle Obama feels cautiously optimistic about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Michelle and Conan sit down to talk about Michelle’s memoir Becoming, childhood inspirations, embarrassing her kids, spending time alone with Chipotle, putting the right people in office, and the loss of anonymity.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.
This episode is sponsored by FX - What We Do in the Shadows, SoFi (www.</description></item><item><title>Thomas Middleditch and Ben Schwartz | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370412/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370412/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actors, comedians, and improvisers Thomas Middleditch and Ben Schwartz feel both sizzlin’ and curious about being Conan O’Brien’s friends.
Thomas and Ben sit down with Conan this week to talk about their two-man improvised show (plus Conan’s own improv history), playing off mistakes in the moment, performing at Carnegie Hall, and cross-theatrical integration. Later, Conan responds to a listener voicemail regarding celebrity codenames.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>16.5 Jessie Gaskell and Mike Sweeney | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370413/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370413/</guid><description>Podcast Description Writers Jessie Gaskell and Mike Sweeney feel hungry and starving, respectively, about being Conan O’Brien’s friends.
Jessie and Mike sit down with Conan to talk about their new show ’Inside Conan: An Important Hollywood Podcast,’ moving to the second floor, office snacks, and Gene Simmons.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.
This episode is sponsored by Simple Contacts (www.</description></item><item><title>Lisa Kudrow | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370414/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370414/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actress Lisa Kudrow feels tired about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Lisa and Conan sit down to chat about their first meeting at an improv class, not taking criticism personally, the backlash to Friends, how Lisa predicted Conan’s career, and being rescued from their dreams.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.
This episode is sponsored by Mercari (www.</description></item><item><title>BONUS: Introducing Inside Conan | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370415/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370415/</guid><description>Podcast Description Out now on Earwolf, Conan writers Mike Sweeney and Jessie Gaskell take you behind the pompadour with exclusive and extended versions of their favorite interviews and stand-up from the week in late night, as well as the stories behind them. Check it out now in Apple Podcasts: apple.co/insideconan.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Jeff Goldblum | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370416/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370416/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Jeff Goldblum feels&amp;hellip;truthful about being Conan O&amp;rsquo;Brien&amp;rsquo;s friend.
Jeff and Conan sit down to chat about mini-orgasms, spousal criticism, pinky rings, raising comic children, and speaking in jazz. Plus, producer Matt Gourley reveals the results of the latest blind drawing contest, and Conan responds to a voicemail regarding proper elocution.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Timothy Olyphant | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370417/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370417/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Timothy Olyphant feels “eh” about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Timothy and Conan sit down this week to chat about their favorite hobbit names, playing a mean mofo on-screen, buying a gingerbread house, and fantasies of quitting Twitter. Plus, Conan’s wax figure controversy heats up with an official response from the Dreamland Wax Museum.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Stephen Colbert | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370418/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370418/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian, writer, and television host Stephen Colbert feels cool about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Stephen and Conan sit down this week to chat about bonding like brothers, growing a sustainable farm, silliness as a religion, the healing power of connecting with an audience, and hiding from their producers. Plus, Conan gives a history lesson as he and his staff pick a new subject for another drawing contest. Got a question for Conan?</description></item><item><title>David Sedaris | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370419/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370419/</guid><description>Podcast Description Writer and humorist David Sedaris feels apprehensive about being Conan O’Brien’s friend. David sits down with Conan this week to talk about the perks of having a colonoscopy, backhanded compliments, being honest about your family, and how to dispose of old tumors. Plus, Conan and his assistant Sona respond to a listener voicemail regarding a wax museum conspiracy.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Dana Carvey | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370420/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370420/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian and actor Dana Carvey feels masculine about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Dana sits down with Conan this week to talk about the key to a nailing perfect impression, how The Church Lady got her euphemisms, and memories of George H. W. Bush. Plus, Dana shares a few of his latest favorite characters, and Conan gets taken to task for losing his belongings by his assistant Sona on a reverse “True or False.</description></item><item><title>Ron Funches | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370421/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370421/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Ron Funches feels grateful and excited to be Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Ron and Conan sit down this week to talk about idolizing Dwayne Johnson, losing weight, having a deceptive voice, and the best place to get their toes done. Plus, Conan and Sona reveal the results of the Christmas puppy drawing contest.
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Adam Sandler | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370422/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370422/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian and actor Adam Sandler feels stunned to be Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Adam and Conan sit down this week to talk about their early shared SNL experiences, getting mad at the audience, letting their kids be their conscience, remembering Chris Farley, and their comedy inspirations. Plus, Conan addresses a fruit-related incident with his assistant during the segment “True or False with Sona Movsesian.”
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Marc Maron | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370423/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370423/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian, actor, and podcaster Marc Maron feels nervous about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Marc and Conan sit down this week to chat about beginner podcast tips, difficult interviewees, health scares, and why they don’t hang out. Plus, Conan receives feedback on his showmanship from his assistant Sona during a new segment called Ways In Which Conan Is Like Freddie Mercury. Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Pete Holmes | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370424/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370424/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Pete Holmes feels frustrated but honored to be Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Pete and Conan sit down this week to chat about their shared Boston lineage, pulling out the dad energy, finding silliness in the world around them, and Pete’s new special ‘Dirty Clean’. Plus, Conan checks in with his producer Matt Gourley to get an update on the State of the Podcast. Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Wanda Sykes | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370425/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2018 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370425/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Wanda Sykes feels trapped into being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Wanda and Conan sit down this week to talk about their mutual love of murder television, bowling with the railings down, and planning a vacation together. Plus, Conan gives a staff performance review. Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.
This episode is sponsored by Palm (www.</description></item><item><title>Nick Offerman and Megan Mullally | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370426/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370426/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actors and comedic couple Nick Offerman and Megan Mullally feel ambivalent, yet hopeful about being Conan O’Brien’s friends.
Nick and Megan join Conan this week to discuss lovemaking in the woods, unusual fashion choices, cute sociopaths, revenge fantasies, and Nick’s Survivor goals. Plus, Conan contemplates his own mortality as he and his assistant Sona check out the latest reviews of the show. Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.</description></item><item><title>Dax Shepard | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370427/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370427/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor Dax Shepard feels very optimistic about being Conan O’Brien’s friend. Dax and Conan sit down to talk about manhood, being made fun of, tycoons, shyness in comedy, and making plans to hang out. Plus, Conan finds out where his assistant Sona disappeared to while they were on tour during a game of “True or False.”
Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.</description></item><item><title>Bill Burr | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370428/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370428/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Bill Burr feels great about being Conan’s friend.
Bill joins Conan to chat about feeling jealous of his kids, his latest life-changing breakthrough, the end of the Burt Reynolds era, and more.
Plus, Conan answers questions from fans about messing with his staff, sports, and Pokémon. Got a question for Conan? Call our voicemail: (323) 451-2821.
For Conan videos, tour dates and more visit TeamCoco.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Kristen Bell | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370429/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370429/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actress Kristen Bell feels supercharged about being Conan O’Brien’s friend! Kristen joins Conan to chat about imparting kindness to their kids, Kristen’s complex relationship with her husband’s recliner, driving motorcycles, and Conan’s goals for a potential double date.
Plus, Conan gets to know his assistant Sona a bit better with the segment “True or False.”
For Conan videos, tour dates, and more visit TeamCoco.com.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Will Ferrell | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370430/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370430/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian and actor Will Ferrell feels awkward about being Conan O’Brien’s friend.
Will joins Conan along with trusty assistant Sona Movsesian and producer Matt Gourley to reflect on his unmatched commitment to comedy, sharing humble roots with Conan at The Groundlings, feeling good about bad reviews, and remembering the comedy bit Will performed on Late Night that got them both in trouble with Lorne Michaels.
Plus, Conan answers questions from fans about hair, Star Wars, and staff favorites.</description></item><item><title>Are you ready to make friends? | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370431/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370431/</guid><description>Podcast Description Coming November 19th…
The first episode of Conan O’Brien’s new podcast is less than two weeks away. Conan really needs a friend. But does he need a podcast? Turns out he does. If only to find that friend. So Conan&amp;rsquo;s bringing his favorite celebrity guests by the studio for some lively conversations. Look out for episodes with Will Ferrell, Nick Offerman and Megan Mullally, Wanda Sykes, Marc Maron, Bill Burr, Kristen Bell, Dax Shepherd, and more!</description></item><item><title>Introducing Conan’s new podcast | Conan O’Brien Needs A Friend</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1826370432/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1826370432/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conan O’Brien really needs a friend. But does he need a podcast? Turns out he does. If only to find that friend. Conan&amp;rsquo;s bringing his favorite celebrity guests by the studio for some friendly conversations. In the meantime, he is joined by his dependable assistant Sona Movsesian, in an attempt to figure out why a venerable TV legend like himself might want to start a podcast in the first place.</description></item></channel></rss>