<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Say More with Dr? Sheila on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/say-more-with-dr-sheila/</link><description>Recent content in Say More with Dr? Sheila on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 08:01:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/say-more-with-dr-sheila/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Chris Chatman | Say More with Dr? Sheila</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9906850001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9906850001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr? Sheila counsels the canceled podcast host Chris Chatman on how to reach a female audience. Starring Amy Poehler and Ike Barinholtz.
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Musical Episode | Say More with Dr? Sheila</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9906850002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9906850002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Marilee just wants her husband, Ed, to stop being such a passive partner. Thankfully, Dr? Sheila knows just how to get this couple singing the same tune. Starring Amy Poehler, Fred Armisen, and Maya Rudolph.
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Analysis Paralysis | Say More with Dr? Sheila</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9906850003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9906850003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr? Sheila is so exhausted by her counseling session with therapist couple Paulette and Janie, she needs an emergency session with her own therapist, who then needs a session with her therapist, who then needs one with hers. Starring Amy Poehler, Janine Brito, Rachel Dratch, Tina Fey, and Paula Pell.
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>Red Herrings | Say More with Dr? Sheila</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9906850004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9906850004/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Bonnie makes an appointment with Dr? Sheila, she thinks she and her husband Frank are there to discuss his gambling addiction. As Dr? Sheila asks them to “Say More” she gathers up all the clues to make her final accusation of what is truly killing this marriage. Starring Amy Poehler, John Lutz, and Lennon Parham.
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy</description></item><item><title>Keeping Score | Say More with Dr? Sheila</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9906850005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9906850005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Competitive couple Claire and Ben keep track of who does what in the relationship to an unhealthy degree. Dr? Sheila explains that this level of keeping score will never work. They need to go further and one of them needs to be named the winner of the marriage. Starring Amy Poehler, Kate Berlant, and John Early.
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy</description></item><item><title>Ghosting | Say More with Dr? Sheila</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9906850006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9906850006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Deliah is worried that Judy is too codependent. Judy is worried, Delilah is going to ghost her. Dr? Sheila turns to the Harry Potter movies for her therapy inspiration. Starring Amy Poehler, Ilana Glazer, and Abbi Jacobson.
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Only One Queen | Say More with Dr? Sheila</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9906850007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9906850007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michelle desperately needs a break from her needy mother-in-law. But her husband, Donald, doesn’t know how to tell his mom to back off. Dr? Sheila decides to take a radical approach. Starring Amy Poehler, Peter Grosz, Jean Villepique, and Stephnie Weir.
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Open Relationship | Say More with Dr? Sheila</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9906850008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9906850008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Steve wants to explore an ethical non-monogamy poly lifestyle, otherwise known as an “open marriage.” Julia is just too tired to care. Dr? Sheila counsels the pair on how to set sexual boundaries with some unexpected results. Starring Amy Poehler, June Diane Raphael, and Paul Scheer. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bickering | Say More with Dr? Sheila</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9906850009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 07:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9906850009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jamison isn’t sure why they are going to couples therapy, while Pam thinks it’s because they argue about everything. Jamison disagrees. Dr? Sheila helps them find some much needed common ground. Starring Amy Poehler, Jessica St. Clair, and Jason Mantzoukas. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Suspected Infidelity | Say More with Dr? Sheila</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9906850010/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9906850010/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Beth wants advice about her husband Ryan’s suspected infidelity, Dr? Sheila turns to the words of O.J. Simpson and the “If I Did It” method to help the couple navigate their issues. Starring Amy Poehler, Chris Parnell, and Ana Gasteyer. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Introducing Say More with Dr? Sheila | Say More with Dr? Sheila</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9906850011/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 22:27:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9906850011/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the world of feelings, there are winners and losers, and somebody has to be the judge. World-renowned, self-proclaimed couples therapist Dr? Sheila invites you to sit in on her private sessions with clients. (For legal reasons, Dr? must be said in the form of a question.) Each week, a new couple…and a new puzzle to crack. You’ll get to hear, and benefit from, many of her famous techniques as she counsels patients on overcoming disagreements, dealing with an overstepping mother-in-law, navigating open relationships, and much more.</description></item></channel></rss>