<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Heavyweight on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/heavyweight/</link><description>Recent content in Heavyweight on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 09:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/heavyweight/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Heavyweight Short: Loch | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390092/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Loch swears his kindergarten teacher used to steal his cheese. But no one believes him. Credits This episode was produced by Phoebe Flanigan, Mohini Madgavkar, and Kalila Holt, along with Jonathan Goldstein. The supervising producer is Stevie Lane. Editorial guidance from Emily Condon. Special thanks to Pierce Singgih, Wendy Zukerman, and extra special thanks to Loch’s mom, Dawn. The show was mixed by Bobby Lord. Music by Christine Fellows, John K Samson, Blue Dot Sessions, Sean Jacobi, Matthew Hollingsworth, Jaybird Blonde, and Bobby Lord.</description></item><item><title>Heavyweight Short: Yasser | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390091/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390091/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Yasser was a boy, he saw a cartoon that changed his life. He’s been searching for it ever since. The only problem is… it’s vanished.
Credits This episode was hosted and produced by supervising producer Stevie Lane, along with Jonathan Goldstein, Mohini Madgavkar, and Phoebe Flanigan. The senior producer is Kalila Holt. Editorial guidance from Emily Condon. Special thanks to Pia Gadkari, Bobby Lord, Dr. Mohamed Ghazala, and Tom Scharpling over at The Best Show.</description></item><item><title>Introducing: Death, Sex &amp; Money | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390090/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Heavyweight will be back next week with a brand new episode. But today, we’re excited to introduce you to Death, Sex &amp;amp; Money — a show hosted by Anna Sale about the topics that we tend to shy away from in polite conversation. The story we have for you is about a New York City mover named Adonis Williams. Over the past 20 years, Adonis has moved thousands of people in and out of the city.</description></item><item><title>#57 The Budget Motel | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390088/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390088/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1993, Nick was shot in an Idaho motel room. One stranger came to his aid. Nick wants to find him.
CREDITS Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was produced by senior producer Kalila Holt, along with Phoebe Flanigan. The supervising producer is Stevie Lane. Production assistance by Mohini Madgavkar. Editorial guidance from Emily Condon. Special thanks to Annie Minoff, Laura Morris, Lauren Silverman, and Jackie Cohen.</description></item><item><title>#56 44 Photos | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390086/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390086/</guid><description>Podcast Description One morning, Amy opened her mailbox and found a package with 44 photos inside—photos of complete strangers. Now Amy wonders: Who are they? And why were the photos sent to her?
Credits This episode was hosted and produced by supervising producer Stevie Lane, along with Jonathan Goldstein, Phoebe Flanigan, and Mohini Madgavkar. The senior producer is Kalila Holt. Editorial guidance from Emily Condon. Special thanks to Alex Blumberg, Mimi O’Donnell, Lauren Silverman, Maureen Taylor, Estelle Ivory, and all the incredibly patient people over at the USPS.</description></item><item><title>#55 Toby | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390001/</guid><description>Podcast Description After his father’s death, Toby found a box of cassette tapes in his dad’s house. These private recordings tell the story of how his parents’ relationship fell apart—a story that Toby never knew, and might not want to know.
CREDITS Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was produced by senior producer Kalila Holt, along with Phoebe Flanigan. The supervising producer is Stevie Lane. Production assistance by Mohini Madgavkar.</description></item><item><title>Introducing: The Retrievals | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Heavyweight will be back with a new episode next week. In the meantime, we’re excited to introduce you to a show we love from our friends at Serial and The New York Times. The Retrievals follows a group of women who went to the Yale Fertility Center for a procedure called an egg retrieval. For months, patient after patient complained that they were experiencing excruciating pain during the procedure.</description></item><item><title>#54 Victor and Maite | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Victor can’t stop painting portraits of his ex-wife, decades after their divorce.
You can find Victor&amp;rsquo;s work at victorrodrigueznyc.com, or on his Instagram at instagram.com/victorrodrigueznyc CREDITS Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was produced by supervising producer Stevie Lane, along with Phoebe Flanigan. The senior producer is Kalila Holt. Production assistance by Mohini Madgavkar. Editorial guidance from Emily Condon. Special thanks to Lauren Silverman, Neil Drumming, Mimi O’Donnell, Anya Schultz, Jackie Cohen, and Jessica Bashir—the director of Heroin, a short documentary about Victor and Maite.</description></item><item><title>#53 Leif | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390004/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Valentine’s Day in junior high, Leif was supposed to ask Kalila out. But he never did. Seventeen years later, Kalila wants to know why.
Credits This episode was hosted and produced by senior producer Kalila Holt, along with Jonathan Goldstein and Phoebe Flanigan. The supervising producer is Stevie Lane. Production assistance from Mohini Madgavkar. Editorial guidance from Emily Condon. Special thanks to Max Green, Flora Lichtman, and Connor Sampson.</description></item><item><title>#52 Lenny | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lenny was Jonathan&amp;rsquo;s childhood best friend, but they drifted apart as they grew into adulthood. Now, Lenny is dying and needs a friend. So Jonathan makes the call.
Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was produced by supervising producer Stevie Lane, along with Phoebe Flanigan. The senior producer is Kalila Holt. Production assistance by Mohini Madgavkar. Editorial guidance from Emily Condon. Special thanks to Lauren Silverman, Neil Drumming, and Jackie Cohen.</description></item><item><title>Trailer: Heavyweight Season 8 | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Here’s a taste of what’s in store. Season 8 begins October 5th. Listen on Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#51 The Elliotts | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390007/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1525, the Archbishop of Glasgow placed a curse on the Elliott family. Now, 500 years later, one very unlucky branch of the Elliotts wants it lifted.
Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was produced by supervising producer Stevie Lane, and Mohini Madgavkar. The senior producer is Kalila Holt. Special thanks to Emily Condon, Alex Blumberg, Valentina Powers, Max Green, Damiano Marchetti, and Jackie Cohen.</description></item><item><title>#50 Nick | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is Nick hearing his dead brother’s voice in a song by a Grammy-nominated musician?
Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was produced by senior producer Kalila Holt, along with Mohini Madgavkar. The supervising producer is Stevie Lane. &amp;ldquo;We Are the Paradox&amp;rdquo; is by The Brilliant. Written and produced by James Moss/Jake Wherry at The Herbgarden. Guitars/Bass/Keys/Programming by Jake Wherry. Vocals/Programming/Keys by James Moss. Special thanks to to to Chris’s parents, Steve and Stephanie, as well as to Emily Condon, Steve Marsh, Liz Fulton, Max Green, Ellen Frankman, Nathalie Russell, Alex Blumberg, and Jackie Cohen The show was mixed by Bobby Lord.</description></item><item><title>Heavyweight Short: Jesse &amp; Tori | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390009/</guid><description>Podcast Description For Jesse, Tori has always been the one that got away.
Credits
This Heavyweight short was hosted and produced by Stevie Lane, along with Mohini Madgavkar and Jonathan Goldstein. The senior producer is Kalila Holt. Production help from Damiano Marchetti. Special thanks to Special thanks to Emily Condon, Alex Blumberg, and Sanya Dosani. The show was mixed by Bobby Lord. Music by Christine Fellows, John K Samson, Ben Alleman, Aaron Paul Low, Michael Charles Smith, and Bobby Lord.</description></item><item><title>#49 Another Roadside Attraction | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390010/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390010/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Stephanie was in high school, a bookstore seemingly dropped out of the sky into her small Texas town. Then, just as quickly, it was gone.
Credits If you or someone you know is thinking about suicide, dial the US National Suicide Prevention Lifeline at 988. Those outside the US can find your local helpline at befrienders.org. Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was produced by senior producer Kalila Holt, along with Mohini Madgavkar.</description></item><item><title>#48 Ben | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ben was just a kid when Sihan arrived from Korea. He lived with Ben’s family for several years. And then one day, just as suddenly as he’d arrived, Sihan was gone. Ben has been trying to find him ever since.
Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was produced by Mohini Madgavkar. The Supervising Producer is Stevie Lane. The Senior Producer is Kalila Holt. Production help from Damiano Marchetti.</description></item><item><title>#47 Frederick J. Brown | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Maia found a painting in the garbage and took it home. But as it turned out, it wasn’t just any painting.
Credits This episode was hosted and produced by senior producer Kalila Holt, along with Jonathan Goldstein. The supervising producer is Stevie Lane. Production help from Damiano Marchetti. Special thanks to Sam Reisman, Emily Condon, Alex Blumberg, Lydia Polgreen, Marcy Flynn, Karl McCool, Caitlin Kenney, and Kayla Lattimore. The show was mixed by Bobby Lord.</description></item><item><title>Heavyweight Short: Cody | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390013/</guid><description>Podcast Description One day in high school, Cody received a hug that melted his heart. Sixteen years later and he still can’t stop thinking about it.
Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was produced by senior producer Kalila Holt, and Mohini Madgavkar. The supervising producer is Stevie Lane. Production help from Damiano Marchetti. Special thanks to Special thanks to Emily Condon, Aaron Randle, and Hannah Chinn.</description></item><item><title>#46 Dan | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390014/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390014/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Dan’s first date with his wife Nancy, a stranger took their photograph. Nineteen years later, Dan wants the photo back. But to get it, he&amp;rsquo;ll have to face the last person he wants to.
Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was produced by supervising producer Stevie Lane, and Mohini Madgavkar. The senior producer is Kalila Holt. Production help from Damiano Marchetti. Special thanks to Emily Condon, Alex Blumberg, Caitlin Kenney, Phoebe Flanigan, and Jackie Cohen.</description></item><item><title>#45 Sgt. John Kapphahn | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390015/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Melanie was a kid, she recorded Billy Ray Cyrus’s 1993 TV Special over something irreplaceable: the sole copy of an interview her father did on Walter Cronkite after being injured in Vietnam. Thirty years later, she wants to make things right.
Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was produced by senior producer Kalila Holt, along with Mohini Madgavkar. The supervising producer is Stevie Lane.</description></item><item><title>#44 Sara | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 18:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sara received a letter from a woman with the exact same name as her. In it, the woman claimed to be her childhood best friend. The only problem? Sara doesn’t remember this person. At all.
Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was produced by supervising producer Stevie Lane, and Mohini Madgavkar. The senior producer is Kalila Holt. Production help from Damiano Marchetti. Special thanks to Emily Condon, Alex Blumberg, Mimi O’Donnell, Sanya Dosani, Rosie Guerin, and Jackie Cohen.</description></item><item><title>#43 Maura | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390017/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Maura was 17, her favorite cousin died in a car crash. Maura’s been too afraid to drive ever since. But now, a decade later, she wants to face her fear.
Credits This episode of Heavyweight was hosted and produced by Kalila Holt, Mohini Madgavkar, Stevie Lane, and Jonathan Goldstein. Special thanks to Emily Condon, Augie Goldstein, Alex Blumberg, Bethel Habte, Anna Foley, Lynn Levy, Paul Bowman, Zac Schmidt, and Jackie Cohen.</description></item><item><title>#42 Mark | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390018/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390018/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Mark was in college, his dream was to be a famous painter. It’s a dream he missed out on by only an inch. This is the story of that inch.
Credits This episode of Heavyweight was hosted and produced by Stevie Lane, along with Mohini Madgavkar and Jonathan Goldstein. The senior producer is Kalila Holt. Special thanks to Emily Condon, Alex Blumberg, Phoebe Flanigan, Reyhan Harmanci, Andrea B Scott, and Bobby Lord.</description></item><item><title>#41 Barbara Wilson | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 09:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390019/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the second and final part of episode #40 Barbara Shutt. So if you’ve not yet heard it, go back and listen to that first.
Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was produced by Stevie Lane, along with Mohini Madgavkar. The senior producer is Kalila Holt. Special thanks to Emily Condon, Alex Blumberg, Phia Bennin, Justin McGoldrick, JT Townsend, the Cincinnati History Museum, the Berea College Archives, and Jackie Cohen.</description></item><item><title>#40 Barbara Shutt | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390020/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390020/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1968, Jonathan’s mother-in-law Becky spent one of the best summers of her life with a woman named Barbara. But then they never spoke again. Now, over fifty years later, Becky learns something about Barbara that makes her question whether she ever really knew her at all.
Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was produced by Stevie Lane, along with Mohini Madgavkar. The senior producer is Kalila Holt.</description></item><item><title>#39 Stephen | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390021/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390021/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the second and final part of last week’s episode. So if you’ve not yet heard the episode “Justine,” go back and listen to that first.
Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was produced by senior producer Kalila Holt, along with Stevie Lane and Mohini Madgavkar. Special thanks to Emily Condon, Jorge Just, Alex Blumberg, Sharon Mashihi, Connie Walker, Isabelle Larreur, and Jackie Cohen.</description></item><item><title>#38 Justine | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Growing up, Justine’s father always told her unbelievable stories about his life: that he was a big winner on Jeopardy; an outlaw who robbed banks armed only with flowers. But now, as an adult, Justine has started to question—are her father’s stories so unbelievable because none of them are true? In the process of fact-checking her dad’s life, something surprising emerges that neither Justine nor Jonathan ever saw coming.</description></item><item><title>#37 John | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Before he became a best-selling author, John Green was going to dedicate his life to God. Until he crossed paths with Nick. Twenty years later, John sets off to find Nick and revisit the day that changed the course of both their lives.
Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was produced by senior producer Kalila Holt, along with Stevie Lane and Mohini Madgavkar. Special thanks to Emily Condon, Reverend Patricia Shelden, Alex Blumberg, Caitlin Kenney, Gabby Bulgarelli, and Jackie Cohen.</description></item><item><title>#36 Brandon | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390024/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Throughout high school, Brandon was a misfit. Then one day, out of the blue, one of the school’s prettiest, most popular girls asked him to prom. Fifteen years later, Brandon wants to know: why him?
Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was produced by Stevie Lane, and Mohini Madgavkar. The senior producer is Kalila Holt. Special thanks to Emily Condon, Alex Blumberg, Sharon Mashihi, Mimi O’Donnell, Jessica Yung, and Jackie Cohen.</description></item><item><title>Heavyweight Short: A Canadian Tale | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390025/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adam swears he met Fidel Castro in Montreal 25 years ago. But ever since, no one’s believed him. Fortunately for Adam, the one person—one Canadian—who can prove his story is Jonathan Goldstein. Heavyweight returns with a full new season on September 30th.
Credits This episode was produced by Stevie Lane, Kalila Holt, and Jonathan Goldstein. It was mixed by Catherine Anderson, with music by Trabants, Blue Dot Sessions, and Bobby Lord.</description></item><item><title>Heavyweight Short: The Sharing Place | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390026/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Heavyweight often features grownups grappling with childhood trauma. But in today’s Heavyweight Short, Jonathan visits a place where children grapple with trauma in the present. At The Sharing Place, kids talk about things most adults can’t even face. A warning: This episode deals with sensitive topics like suicide and death.
Credits This story originally ran on This American Life in 2015, and was produced by Sean Cole. It was mixed for Heavyweight by Emma Munger, with music by Christine Fellows, Blue Dot Sessions, Bobby Lord, and Poddington Bear.</description></item><item><title>Heavyweight Short: Hallie | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390027/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390027/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Hallie was 17, she spent a few minutes with a stranger who changed her life. A decade later, Hallie sets out to find her.
Credits This Heavyweight short was hosted and produced by Kalila Holt, along with Stevie Lane, Mohini Madgavkar, and Jonathan Goldstein. Special thanks to Sam Reisman, Cheri Mantz and Dr. Lynd. The show was mixed by Catherine Anderson. Music by Christine Fellows, John K Samson, Blue Dot Sessions, and Bobby Lord.</description></item><item><title>Check In: Holiday Special | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390028/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy holidays! In our last check in of 2020, Stevie confronts her grandfather with a question she’s been afraid to ask for over twenty years, and Kalila solves the mystery of an enigmatic gravestone.
Mixed by Bobby Lord. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Check In: Curtis Sittenfeld | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390029/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jonathan speaks with Curtis Sittenfeld about her novel Rodham, which deals with many of the themes we explore on Heavyweight: things like returning to the past to change it, and the question of what our lives might have been like if we’d made one decision differently. Rodham is a novel about what Hillary Clinton’s life and political career might have looked like if she had never married Bill Clinton.</description></item><item><title>Check In: Do You Like Music? | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390030/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jonathan, Stevie, and Kalila are back, to talk about Thanksgiving and music.
Music and mix by Bobby Lord. Additional music by Sean, Ryan, Kevin, and Brian Jacobi.
Find our playlist, &amp;ldquo;Goldstein&amp;rsquo;s Party Faves to Get the Party Going,&amp;rdquo; here Find Madeline Forman&amp;rsquo;s music here Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#35 Rachel and Jon | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390031/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rachel and Jon are siblings who were separated as young children. Jonathan helps them confront the woman responsible&amp;hellip; fifty years later. Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was produced by Kalila Holt, along with Stevie Lane. Special thanks to Emily Condon, Alex Blumberg, PJ Vogt, Mohini Madgavkar, Nabeel Chollampat, and Jackie Cohen. The show was mixed by Bobby Lord. Music by Christine Fellows, John K Samson, Blue Dot Sessions, and Bobby Lord.</description></item><item><title>#34 Annie | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390032/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Every time Annie’s family comes to town, they exclude her from their plans. Annie needs to know why.
Credits This episode of Heavyweight was hosted and produced by Kalila Holt, along with Stevie Lane and Jonathan Goldstein. Special thanks to Emily Condon, Alex Blumberg, Mathilde Urfalino, Mia Bloomfield, Emma Munger, Zac Schmidt, Sam Reisman, and Jackie Cohen. The show was mixed by Bobby Lord. Music by Christine Fellows, John K Samson, Bobby Lord, Hew Time, Blue Dot Sessions, and Shanghai Restoration Project.</description></item><item><title>#33 Bobby | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390033/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390033/</guid><description>Podcast Description How the worst McDonald’s commercial ever made came to be. And how Bobby got mixed up in it.
Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was produced by Stevie Lane, along with Kalila Holt. Special thanks to Emily Condon, Alex Blumberg, Chris Neary, Nazanin Rafsanjani, Phoebe Flanigan, Nabeel Chollampat, Jake Anderson, Billy Klein, Nicholas Papaleo, and Jackie Cohen. The show was mixed by Bobby Lord.</description></item><item><title>#32 Vivian | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390034/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390034/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1995, Vivian’s uncle Helio died of AIDS. Now, 25 years later, Vivian’s on a search to find the man who cared for him until his death.
Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was produced by Stevie Lane. The senior producer is Kalila Holt. Special thanks to Emily Condon, Alex Blumberg, Caitlin Kenney, Mimi O’Donnell, Lydia Polgreen, Reyhan Harmanci, Nabeel Chollampat, and Jackie Cohen.</description></item><item><title>Why Is Mason Reese Crying? | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390035/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mason Reese was the biggest child star of the early 1970&amp;rsquo;s. Recently, he posted a YouTube video of himself crying. Jonathan sets out to discover why. This is a story Jonathan made for Reply All in 2015. The new season of Heavyweight starts next week. Credits This episode was produced by Jonathan Goldstein, along with Chris Neary, Tim Howard, Sruthi Pinnamaneni, PJ Vogt, and Alex Goldman. Editing by Alex Blumberg.</description></item><item><title>Heavyweight Check In 8 | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390036/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390036/</guid><description>Podcast Description As we turn our attention back to producing classic Heavyweight episodes, we leave you with one last check in. SPOILER ALERT: This check in contains a special treat. Special thanks to Matthew Boll and Doug Barron. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Heavyweight Check In 7 | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390037/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 16:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390037/</guid><description>Podcast Description During these times of uncertainty and sadness, we bring you two stories of two women seeking the comfort of childhood. Amber and Eva are in search of their first grade teachers.
Mix by Bobby Lord. Music by Christine Fellows, John K Samson , Bobby Lord, and Blue Dot Sessions.
Further Reading: https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2020/06/becoming-a-parent-in-the-age-of-black-lives-matter/612448/
https://www.esquire.com/news-politics/a23960/james-baldwin-cool-it/
https://www.mpd150.com/report/overview/
https://www.newyorker.com/news/dispatch/george-floyd-houstons-protests-and-the-privilege-of-the-benefit-of-the-doubt
https://newrepublic.com/article/157949/fascism-america-trump-anti-police-george-floyd-protests
https://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2014/06/the-case-for-reparations/361631/
And you can find Amber’s memoir about leaving the Jehovah’s Witnesses here: https://bookshop.</description></item><item><title>Heavyweight Check In 6 | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390038/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 01:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Milestones and cramped houses.
Mix by Bobby Lord. Music by Christine Fellows, Bobby Lord, and Blue Dot Sessions. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Heavyweight Check In 5 | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390039/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 15:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jonathan surprises Stevie and Kalila with some special friends from seasons past who, wouldn’t you know it, are still in need of his help.
Mix by Bobby Lord. Music by Bobby Lord, Christine Fellows, Blue Dot Sessions, and Connie Shi (https://www.iamconnieshi.com/).
We put together a Heavyweight playlist… fan and staff favorites. If you’re looking to introduce friends to the show, it’s a good place to start: heavyweight.show/playlist.
You can find Connie&amp;rsquo;s song here: https://open.</description></item><item><title>Heavyweight Check In 4 | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390040/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stuck in new homes and old.
Mix by Bobby Lord. Music by Christine Fellows and Bobby Lord.
Also, we put together a Heavyweight playlist… fan and staff favorites. If you’re looking to introduce friends to the show, it’s a good place to start: heavyweight.show/playlist. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Heavyweight Check In 3 | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390041/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390041/</guid><description>Podcast Description A lot of people have been feeling lonely lately. So, they&amp;rsquo;ve been reaching out.
Music by Christine Fellows and Bobby Lord. And Simon. Mix by Bobby Lord. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Heavyweight Check In 2 | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390042/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 20:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jonathan, Stevie, and Kalila check in, to talk about what’s been going on in their lives, and in your lives, too.
Mix by Emma Munger. Music by Christine Fellows, Blue Dot Sessions, and Bobby Lord. Special thanks to Paul Swensen. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Heavyweight Checks In | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390043/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 16:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Things are feeling strange and uncertain right now. So we on the Heavyweight team decided to record our day and share it with you.
Mix and music by Bobby Lord. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#31 Marie-Claude | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390044/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jonathan’s oldest friend, Marie-Claude, had a problem in high school. At 50, she thought it was behind her. But the problem’s recently returned with a vengeance. Lucky for Marie-Claude, her old pal Jonathan’s here to help in the Heavyweight season 4 finale.
Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was produced by Stevie Lane, along with Kalila Holt and BA Parker. Editing by Jorge Just.</description></item><item><title>#30 The Marshes | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390045/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390045/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a drunken slip of the tongue, Steve Marsh and his siblings discover a secret their mother has been keeping for almost 40 years. Now, Steve wants to help his mom take action. Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was produced by Kalila Holt, along with BA Parker and Stevie Lane. Editing by Jorge Just. Special thanks to Emily Condon, Lulu Miller, Hans Buetow, Damiano Marchetti, Alex Blumberg, and Jackie Cohen.</description></item><item><title>#29 Elyse | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390046/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390046/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Elyse was 21, her father, Billy, disappeared without explanation. When Elyse finally learned of his whereabouts, she was shocked by the new life he was living. Now, for the first time in five years, Billy and Elyse sit down to talk. Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was produced by BA Parker, Kalila Holt, and Stevie Lane. Editing by Jorge Just. Special thanks to Emily Condon, Kaitlin Roberts, Alex Goldman, Caitlin Kenney, Alex Blumberg, and Jackie Cohen.</description></item><item><title>#28 Dr. Muller | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390047/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390047/</guid><description>Podcast Description In his twenties, Jonathan began seeing an inscrutable, mysterious therapist. After 6 years without progress, she told him it wasn’t working out because of him. 25 years later, Jonathan wants to know if it was really his fault. Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was produced by Stevie Lane, BA Parker, and Kalila Holt. Editing by Jorge Just. Special thanks to Emily Condon, Tim Howard, Annika Witzel, Sir Richard Evans, Dr.</description></item><item><title>#27 Scott | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390048/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eight years ago, when Scott was addicted to heroin, he crossed a line he thought he would never cross. And he’s been trying to uncross it since.
Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was produced by Stevie Lane, along with Kalila Holt and BA Parker. Editing by Jorge Just. Special thanks to Emily Condon, Alex Blumberg, Nathan Foster, Jacob Eppler, and Jackie Cohen. The show was mixed by Bobby Lord.</description></item><item><title>Without Fail, WITH Jonathan Goldstein | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390049/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Heavyweight will be back with a brand new episode next week. In the meantime, we bring you a special episode of Without Fail, co-hosted by Jonathan. He and Alex Blumberg interview comedian Nick Kroll. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#26 Beverley and Van | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390050/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ashley’s grandmother, Beverley, had a hard life and an unhappy marriage. But she spoke frequently of a man named Van. Ashley believes Van was the great unfulfilled love of her grandmother’s life. And now, she wants to know: did Van feel the same way? Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was produced by Kalila Holt, along with Stevie Lane and BA Parker. Editing by Jorge Just.</description></item><item><title>#25 Becky and Jo | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390051/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Becky and Jo were raised by a procession of eccentric babysitters, 16 in total. But their favorite was Leticia. The girls adored her… right up until the day she mysteriously vanished. Twenty years later, Becky and Jo want to know what happened. Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was produced by Kalila Holt, along with Stevie Lane and BA Parker. Editing by Jorge Just.</description></item><item><title>#24 Jimmy and Mark | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390052/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390052/</guid><description>Podcast Description When he was only 10 years old, Jonathan Marshall was sent on a 240 mile bicycle trip. 3 days. Across 2 states. With no adult supervision. 45 years later, Jonathan can’t stop thinking about the trip. Or the little boys he made it with. Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was produced by Stevie Lane, along with BA Parker, and Kalila Holt. Editing by Jorge Just.</description></item><item><title>The Heavy Wait Diaries: Chapter 8 | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390053/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Heavyweight Season 4 begins September 26th. Until then, we bring you The Heavy Wait Diaries. Each Thursday, a new chapter will be presented to ease the burden of your wait. In Chapter 8—the final chapter—Jonathan takes a co-reporting trip. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Heavy Wait Diaries: Chapter 7 | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390054/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Heavyweight Season 4 begins September 26th. Until then, we bring you The Heavy Wait Diaries. Each Thursday, a new chapter will be presented to ease the burden of your wait. In Chapter 7, the most challenging interview of Jonathan’s life. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Heavy Wait Diaries: Chapter 6 | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390055/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Heavyweight Season 4 begins September 26th. Until then, we bring you The Heavy Wait Diaries. Each Thursday, a new chapter will be presented to ease the burden of your wait. In Chapter 6, Jonathan gets a new co-host. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Heavy Wait Diaries: Chapter 5 | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390056/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 15:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Heavyweight Season 4 begins September 26th. Until then, we bring you The Heavy Wait Diaries. Each Thursday, a new chapter will be presented to ease the burden of your wait. In Chapter 5, the Heavyweight union rep threatens Jonathan’s dominion. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Heavy Wait Diaries: Chapter 4 | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390057/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Heavyweight Season 4 begins September 26th. Until then, we bring you The Heavy Wait Diaries. Each Thursday, a new chapter will be presented to ease the burden of your wait. In Chapter 4, Jonathan spends the weekend in a terrible funk. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Heavy Wait Diaries: Chapter 3 | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390058/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Heavyweight Season 4 begins September 26th. Until then, we bring you The Heavy Wait Diaries. Each Thursday, a new chapter will be presented to ease the burden of your wait. In Chapter 3, Jonathan goes to a strategy meeting. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Heavy Wait Diaries: Chapter 2 | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390059/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Heavyweight Season 4 begins September 26th. Until then, we bring you The Heavy Wait Diaries. Each Thursday, a new chapter will be presented to ease the burden of your wait. In Chapter 2, Jonathan tells a ridonculous lie. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Heavy Wait Diaries: Chapter 1 | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390060/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Heavyweight Season 4 begins September 26th. Until then, we bring you The Heavy Wait Diaries. Each Thursday, a new chapter will be presented to ease the burden of your wait. In Chapter 1, Alex wants to see Jonathan in the studio. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#23 Alex | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390061/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 08:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390061/</guid><description>Podcast Description 16 years ago, Gimlet Media CEO and founder Alex Blumberg made a promise that he didn’t keep. And it’s been eating at him ever since. In this season finale, Jonathan sets out to clean up his boss’s mess. Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was also produced by Peter Bresnan, Kalila Holt, and Stevie Lane. Editing by Jorge Just, with additional editing by Alex Blumberg.</description></item><item><title>#22 Marchel | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390062/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 08:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Russian Ark is a cinematic masterpiece. Dozens of sets, thousands of actors, years of planning. It’s a perfectly executed work of art. Almost. In this episode, Jonathan sets off to find the one guy who ruined it for everyone. Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was also produced by Stevie Lane, Peter Bresnan, and Kalila Holt. Editing by Jorge Just, with additional editing by Alex Blumberg.</description></item><item><title>#21 Rachael | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390063/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ten years ago, Rachael had a baby. She never told the father. All these years later, she thinks it’s about time she did. Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was also produced by Kalila Holt, Peter Bresnan, and Stevie Lane. Editing by Jorge Just, with additional editing by Alex Blumberg. Special thanks to Emily Condon, Katelyn Bogucki, Andrew Goldberg, Rachel Ward, and Jackie Cohen.</description></item><item><title>#20 Soraya | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390064/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390064/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Soraya was in college, her favorite professor hired her to help research a book she was writing. But when she fell into a deep depression and dropped out of school, she abandoned both the book and the professor who’d shown her so much kindness. Now, with Jonathan’s help, Soraya wants to make things right—with a grand gesture. Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was also produced by Peter Bresnan, Kalila Holt, and Stevie Lane.</description></item><item><title>#19 Joey | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390065/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joey recently had a very bad day, all due to awkward misunderstandings. So now, he&amp;rsquo;s enlisted the help of Jonathan &amp;ldquo;Debonair&amp;rdquo; Goldstein and Jonathan’s friend Gregor to redo the day and set things right. Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was also produced by Kalila Holt, Peter Bresnan, and Stevie Lane. Editing by Jorge Just, with additional editing by Alex Blumberg. Special thanks to Emily Condon, Flora Lichtman, PJ Vogt, Saidu Tejan-Thomas, Grace Hawkins, and Jackie Cohen.</description></item><item><title>Zoe, PJ, and Chanel | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390066/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Heavyweight performed a sold-out live show in Brooklyn, NY, last June. Jonathan is joined by This American Life’s Zoe Chace and Reply All’s PJ Vogt to talk about Heavyweight stories that never made it onto the air… until now. Plus: human beatboxing, Gimlet Media CEO Alex Blumberg’s vape pen collection… and Jackie Cohen. Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was also produced by Stevie Lane, Peter Bresnan, and Kalila Holt.</description></item><item><title>#18 Sven | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390067/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sven was on a jury that sentenced a man named Paul Storey to death. He&amp;rsquo;s regretted it ever since. Then, eight years later, Sven gets an email from Paul’s mother. The original article that Maurice Chammah reported with Sven about his experience on the jury: https://www.themarshallproject.org/2016/03/10/my-regrets-as-a-juror-who-sent-a-man-to-death-row Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was also produced by Stevie Lane, Peter Bresnan, and Kalila Holt. Editing by Jorge Just, with additional editing by Alex Blumberg.</description></item><item><title>#17 Skye | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390068/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390068/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Skye was in middle school, her best friends showed up at her home one night and wrote “f*ck you” on her garage door. After that, they never spoke again. Now Skye has a son entering middle school, and he can’t believe his mom never asked her friends why they did it. So, thirty years later, Skye and her son set off to find out. Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein.</description></item><item><title>#16 Rob | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390069/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rob remembers breaking his arm as a kid. But the rest of his family says it never happened. Did he break his arm? The answer will determine Rob’s sanity. Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was also produced by Kalila Holt, Peter Bresnan, and Stevie Lane. Editing by Jorge Just, with additional editing by Alex Blumberg. Special thanks to Emily Condon, Phia Bennin, BA Parker, Matthew Nelson, Sandra Corddry, Maximum Fun, and Jackie Cohen.</description></item><item><title>#15 Dina | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390070/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 18:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390070/</guid><description>Podcast Description During a visit back home, Jonathan’s mother inadvertently admits something that forces him to question his past. In this season finale, Jonathan turns the mic around on himself for one of the more personal episodes of the series. Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was also produced by Kalila Holt. The senior producer is Kaitlin Roberts. Editing by Jorge Just, Alex Blumberg, and Wendy Dorr.</description></item><item><title>#14 Isabel | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390071/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 18:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390071/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1999, an old suitcase was found abandoned on a Brooklyn street corner. The suitcase contained 5 years worth of love letters between a young man and young woman. In this episode, Jonathan tries to track them down. Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was also produced by Kalila Holt. The senior producer is Kaitlin Roberts. Editing by Jorge Just and Alex Blumberg. Special thanks to Emily Condon, Meg Driscoll, Kelly Coonan, Nicole Wong, Jonathan Zenti, Alvin Melathe, Anne Silk from the Museum of Fine Arts in Boston, and Jackie Cohen.</description></item><item><title>#13 Kenny | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390072/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 20:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ken Carter was a Canadian daredevil who dreamt of performing the biggest stunt the world had ever seen. He wanted to jump a rocket car one mile over a river. For 5 years he prepared, only to have his dream hijacked at the very last moment by the very last person he ever expected. Thanks to the National Film Board of Canada for their use of audio from The Devil At Your Heels.</description></item><item><title>#12 Jesse | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390073/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 18:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Four years ago, Jesse was hit by a car and nearly died. Now he wants to find the driver. And thank him. Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was also produced by Kalila Holt. The senior producer is Kaitlin Roberts. Editing by Jorge Just, Alex Blumberg, and Wendy Dorr. Special thanks to Emily Condon, Saidu Tejan-Thomas, and Jackie Cohen. The show was mixed by Kate Bilinski.</description></item><item><title>#11 Christina | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390074/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 17:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390074/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Christina was in 11th grade, her foster mother made her quit playing basketball. After that, she felt like her life never got back on course. And so, she’s always wanted to ask her foster mother: why’d you make me quit? Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was also produced by Kalila Holt. The senior producer is Kaitlin Roberts. Editing by Jorge Just, Alex Blumberg, and Wendy Dorr.</description></item><item><title>#10 Rose | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390075/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 16:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over a decade ago, Rose was kicked out of her college sorority. “You know what you did,” was the only explanation she was ever given. All these years later, Rose still wants to know what it is she did. Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was also produced by Kalila Holt. The senior producer is Kaitlin Roberts. Editing by Jorge Just, Alex Blumberg, and Wendy Dorr.</description></item><item><title>#9 Milt | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390076/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 17:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last season’s episode, &amp;ldquo;Gregor,&amp;rdquo; led to an unfortunate event that Jonathan could’ve never predicted. In this pre-season episode, he tries to set things right. Heavyweight’s second season begins October 26th. Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was also produced by Kalila Holt. The senior producer is Kaitlin Roberts. Editing by Alex Blumberg and Jorge Just. Special thanks to Emily Condon, Stevie Lane, Wendy Dorr, Kate Parkinson-Morgan, and Jackie Cohen.</description></item><item><title>#8 Jeremy | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390077/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2016 18:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390077/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Jonathan was 16, he went to synagogue every morning. He even thought that one day he might become a rabbi. Things didn’t exactly work out that way, but he’s always wondered what if they had. In this episode, he finds out. Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was also produced by Chris Neary and Kalila Holt. The senior producer is Wendy Dorr. Editing by Alex Blumberg, Paul Tough, and Jorge Just.</description></item><item><title>#7 Julia | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390078/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 21:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390078/</guid><description>Podcast Description In grade 8, Julia was bullied so badly by a group of girls that she changed schools without telling anyone. Soon after, the girls from her old school showed up at her house and rang her doorbell. She didn’t answer it. For the past 20 years, Julia’s been wondering what those girls wanted. Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was also produced by Chris Neary and Kalila Holt.</description></item><item><title>#6 James | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390079/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2016 19:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390079/</guid><description>Podcast Description James’s father’s dying wish was for his ashes to be disposed of on the 18th hole of a fancy private golf course. That was 16 years ago. In this episode, James, Jonathan, and their friend Howard attempt a golf heist to get into the club and set things right. Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was also produced by Chris Neary and Kalila Holt.</description></item><item><title>#5 Galit | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390080/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 19:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Galit was Jonathan’s first girlfriend. When she dumped him, he cried a lot and then locked away his emotional vulnerability in a safe for the next several decades. In this episode, Galit sends Jonathan a Facebook message asking if he’d like to meet up. Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was also produced by Chris Neary and Kalila Holt. Our senior producer is Wendy Dorr.</description></item><item><title>#4 Tony | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390081/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 19:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Years ago, Tony messed up his relationship with each of his three godchildren owing to three difficult chapters in his life. Now, childless and single in his late 40’s, and fearing he may never have kids of his own, Tony wants to win them back. Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was also produced by Chris Neary and Kalila Holt. Our senior producer is Wendy Dorr.</description></item><item><title>#3 Tara | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390082/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 17:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jonathan watched a short experimental video in college in which a little girl sat in silence while her parent sobbed. Now, Jonathan wants to know if that girl is okay. You can find Maxi Cohen&amp;rsquo;s website here: http://www.maxicohenstudio.com/ Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was also produced by Chris Neary and Kalila Holt. Our senior producer is Wendy Dorr. Editing by Alex Blumberg and Jorge Just.</description></item><item><title>#2 Gregor | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390083/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2016 04:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390083/</guid><description>Podcast Description 20 years ago, Gregor lent some CDs to a musician friend. The CDs helped make him a famous rockstar. Now, Gregor would like some recognition. But mostly, he wants his CDs back. Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein, along with Wendy Dorr, Chris Neary, and Kalila Holt. Editing by Alex Blumberg &amp;amp; Peter Clowney. Special thanks to Emily Condon, Jackie Cohen, Paul Tough, Stevie Lane, Michelle Harris, Dimitri Erlich, Sean Cole and Jorge Just.</description></item><item><title>#1 Buzz | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390084/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 22:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Buzz and Sheldon are brothers in their eighties who have been estranged for decades. Buzz visits Sheldon to see if there’s still a relationship left to salvage. Credits Heavyweight is hosted and produced by Jonathan Goldstein. This episode was also produced by Wendy Dorr, Chris Neary, and Kalila Holt. Editing by Alex Blumberg and Peter Clowney. Special thanks to Caitlin Kenney, Starlee Kine, and Rachel Ward. The show was mixed by Haley Shaw.</description></item><item><title>Welcome to Heavyweight | Heavyweight</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8862390085/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2016 13:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8862390085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Maybe you’ve laid awake imagining how it could have been, how it might yet be, but the moment to act was never right. Well, the moment is here and the podcast making it happen is Heavyweight. Join Jonathan Goldstein for road trips, thorny reunions, and difficult conversations as he backpedals his way into the past like a therapist with a time machine. From Gimlet Media. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item></channel></rss>