<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Curve on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/the-curve/</link><description>Recent content in The Curve on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 22:02:32 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/the-curve/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>TCW48: Hot tips, hot chips and hot guys in Morocco. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030141/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 22:02:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today – coming to you all the way from sunny NZ and the back of Muhammed’s car – we’re wrapping up the year that’s been for some of our favourite international stock markets. We look at who’s crushed it and who’s had a shocker, and what it’s meant for IPOs and investors. We’ve got big news from Boots, an out-of-this-world announcement from McDonalds, and some smokin’ hot tips for choosing sectors to invest (and find employment) in.</description></item><item><title>RTC93: Microsoft – good investment or amazing deep fake? | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 20:36:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030001/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s episode, Vic goes head-to-head with Alison George, our very clever and succinct friend at Australian Ethical. If you’ve listened to this podcast before, you’ll no doubt be aware of Vic’s undying love for Microsoft in all its nerdy-tech glory … so naturally, we’ve put her on the ‘against’ side of today’s ethical investment debate. From the risks of facial recognition to carbon neutral data centres, increased productivity to who’s responsible for the recycling, we dive deep into the highs and lows of investing in this multi-(multi)-billion-dollar company.</description></item><item><title>RTC92: What we’ve learnt in 2023. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 23:16:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030002/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, we’re rolling out a slightly different format. With 2023 nearly behind us, we’re wrapping up the year that’s been and all the lessons it has given us. From learning to live with significantly less to taking your own advice, from the importance of a healthy emergency fund to the heartbreaking realities of the ADHD tax – we’re here to reflect and share (and we’re actually quite vulnerable).</description></item><item><title>TCW47: Big shorts, big bounce-backs and big red flags. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030003/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ahhh, December. The trees are up, the carols are cranking, and things are looking rather bright and merry in the world of finance – unless, of course, you’re Michael Burry (the man behind The Big Short – it has Ryan Gosling in it, you’ve probably seen it). Today, we’re talking big risks, big bets and the danger of betting on failure. On a more positive note, the S&amp;amp;P500 is up, Uber’s finally in the big-dog club, Facebook is flying, Zuckerberg’s selling, TikTok is absolutely massive and Vic’s hit travel gold (for only 35 measly little Euros).</description></item><item><title>RTC91: Shortland Street and Elon Musk: Getting ethical with Beth Allen. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 03:27:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Child actor, teenage homeowner, Shortland Street star and mum-of-three … it’s safe to say that Beth Allen (Google her face immediately, you know her) has lived a pretty exciting life. Today, we have the privilege of sitting down with Beth to talk about her own financial journey, and the importance of keeping her finances aligned with her ethics. From industry pay disparities to the cost of being a woman on screen, investing her kids’ pocket money to Elon Musk’s big plans for Mars, Beth’s here to tell it like it is.</description></item><item><title>TCW46: Black Friday, Kim K and the return of Robin Hood. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030005/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 20:14:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030005/</guid><description>Podcast Description A big week for The Curve! Soph went to the movies (and ordered nachos – questionable), Vic discovered Temu and we won a podcast award! Morale could not be higher, and neither could the latest Black Friday stats. We look at the sky-high spending, massive profits and a few scary red flags. We’re also talking the joy of black cabs, the (third) return of Robin Hood, Soph’s saucy Christmas costume and this summer’s hottest fashion trend – the IPO.</description></item><item><title>RTC90: The cost of transitioning with Allegra Bambi Haines. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030006/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 19:43:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030006/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re always excited to chat to our guests, but this week Soph has quite possibly lost her mind in anticipation. To celebrate the recent Transgender Awareness Week, we’re talking to the hilarious, honest and totally inspiring Allegra Bambi Haines. Born and raised in South Wales, in an idyllic (and very sheltered) community, Allegra’s journey from uncertain child to proud trans-woman has not been an easy one. From her traumatic ‘lightbulb moment’ at 21 to being struck off the NHS waiting list, from estrogen on toast to funding the renovation that never ends – Allegra takes us, graciously and wittily, through the real cost of transitioning.</description></item><item><title>TCW45: AI’s booming, fashion’s getting faster and crypto’s doing it dirty. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030007/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 21:44:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030007/</guid><description>Podcast Description AI scandals, dirty crypto and weeping at Singapore Airport … safe to say, it’s been a wild old week for all involved. While Vic finally touched down on safe ground (yes, the weeping was hers) the same can’t be said for the big dogs behind ChatGPT, who are currently dealing with a veeery shaky landing. We talk about riding the AI wave, the inevitability of greed following success, and the beauty of investing in an ETF.</description></item><item><title>RTC89: The cost of infertility with Brett Russo. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030008/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 20:10:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030008/</guid><description>Podcast Description For so many, fertility doesn’t come easy. In fact, it can come at a huge, overwhelming and often unattainable cost. In today’s episode, we’re talking to Brett Russo, author of ‘The Underwear in my Shoe’ – a powerful, funny and unflinchingly honest account of her journey through IVF – about her own experience with infertility. Born and raised in New Jersey, Brett and her husband endured five rounds of IVF to have their two gorgeous sons.</description></item><item><title>TCW44: Never trust a man called Dirk. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030009/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 21:49:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030009/</guid><description>Podcast Description We all know Vic loves a party … so to celebrate her birthday week, Soph’s bringing the party to this episode! We’re talking messages of love, a few dirty secrets and one very sexy bunch of flowers. And because this is a finance podcast, we’ve also found time to cover WeWork’s ongoing bankruptcy saga (and why it may actually make them more powerful), the widening gap between men and women, why Amazon’s getting into bed with Snapchat, and the scandalous rise of ‘shrink-flation’ (we’re looking at you, Dirk).</description></item><item><title>RTC88: The cost of having kids (and a life) with Chancè Hindirlane. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030010/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 20:27:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030010/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you’re looking for amazing energy, absolute honesty and a big old mindset-shift – then have we got the episode for you. Today’s guest, Chancè Hindirlane, is a trailblazer, a boss and a genuine breath of fresh air. Originally from Congo, Chancè and her 11 siblings were raised by their mother – and a village of support people. After moving to America and having her first child, she quickly realised that not only was finding her own village incredibly tough – it also came at a huge financial cost.</description></item><item><title>TCW43: Love, money and stopping to smell the Gherkin. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030011/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 20:11:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030011/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a founder steps down, usually so does the share price. And this week, Whitney Wolfe Herd – founder and CEO of Bumble, and the world’s youngest self-made female billionaire – is calling it quits. We talk about plummeting share prices, the cost of love and the benefits of having a founder in the driver’s seat. We’re also looking at some Shein IPO rumours, Buffy the Finance Slayer’s savings account (Vic's attempt at a Warren Buffet joke), Uber’s latest offering (hot air balloon, anyone?</description></item><item><title>RTC87: Apples for apples: Our big, curvy ethical debate. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030012/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 23:19:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Here at The Curve, we love ourselves a good debate – and today’s guest, Lily from Pathfinder, is an incredible (and very succinct) contender. We’re partnering with Pathfinder on a brand-new ethical miniseries – and to kick things off, we’re going right to the core of one of the juiciest names in the business. Apple. With Lily fighting in Apple’s corner, and Vic doing her best to pick it apart, we go deep into Apple’s operations to find out how many problems the world’s largest tech-giant is solving … and causing.</description></item><item><title>TCW42: Canada Goose is flapping, there’s interest in Pinterest and WeWork might be WeGone. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030013/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 21:57:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030013/</guid><description>Podcast Description The S&amp;amp;P500’s had a big bad month, but it’s not all doom and gloom! We look at the realities of over performing and why all that goes up must, at some point, come down. And when it comes to going down, we couldn’t go past WeWork’s recent bankruptcy saga and the tough choice investors will face between getting the hell out or keeping the faith. We look at the surprising success of Pinterest, the public perils of IPOs, and dive under the coyote-fur hood of Canada Goose … and Vic gives herself a new nickname.</description></item><item><title>RTC86: Figuring out what your rich life is with Laurie Wang. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030014/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 22:42:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Let us introduce you to Laurie Wang - inspiring, humble and incredibly talented. Laurie grew up in a first generation Chinese immigrant family in the US. Her parents wanted her to follow a traditional career path, so she found herself completing a finance degree, although she knew it wasn't what she really wanted to do. Fast forward a decade, and Laurie has truly 'found her flow' in a completely different industry.</description></item><item><title>TCW41: Meta’s getting sued, Hong Kong’s lost its mojo and Microsoft’s doing it for the ladies. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030015/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 21:40:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030015/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a bid to make finance more fun, we decided to dress up for Halloween … and instantly regretted it. Bear with us as Vic reads her notes through wonky eyeholes. It’s reporting season (again!) so we’re bringing you a few tricks and treats to pop into your little finance buckets. We’re talking Snapchat’s highs and lows, Meta’s latest (and potentially very expensive) controversy and Hong Kong’s not-very-sexy problem – as well as the impact the Israel-Palestine war is having on advertising revenue, and Microsoft’s epic commitment to looking after women going through menopause.</description></item><item><title>RTC85: How Vic made $800,000 in 6 years! | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 18:20:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030016/</guid><description>Podcast Description In todays episode Vic opens up about one of the best investments she's ever made drum roll please... in property! Six years ago Vic was deported from the US and no she wasn't smuggling anything up her 🍑 for those wondering. It was a simple visa error, but one that meant she ended up back in NZ unexpectedly. Nearing 30, with nowhere to live and no job, she decided to buy a house.</description></item><item><title>RTC84: Property Powerhouse: Nicole Bremner's wild ride with 108 property investments. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 21:05:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030017/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today's episode, we're chatting with Nicole Bremner, the financial wizard juggling a share in 18 properties. Fun fact: Ross from Friends once tried to buy one of her houses! From global banking, to investing in a dynamic mix of startups, stocks, and property, Nicole's journey is a rollercoaster of financial adventures. With a history of once owning shares in a whopping 108 properties, she dishes out valuable investment insights, like the golden rule: "</description></item><item><title>RTC83: The Psychology of Money: Earn by day, sleep like a baby by night. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030018/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 20:09:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vic’s decided to build herself a library (complete with old-timey ladders, naturally) and the first book on the shelf is without a doubt going to be ‘The Psychology of Money’, by Morgan Housel. We’re here to run you through this incredible book’s key takeaways – to help you gain control of your time, prioritise saving, lean into kindness and ultimately sleep much, much better at night … while making lots of money along the way.</description></item><item><title>TCW40: Birks are down, women are out of pocket, and Soph might be in for more baggage. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030019/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 23:28:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Since entering the stock market with their IPO, Birkenstock have gone from smokin’ hot to a little bit not – but why the fall from grace? Meanwhile, global tech company Klaviyo is sitting pretty after their own IPO – so why the different outcomes? We look at a couple of key questions to help you come to terms with the whos, whats and whys in the world of IPOs.</description></item><item><title>RTC82: The Millionaire’s Wife: Freedom, feminism and $80 lattes. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030020/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 16:05:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ok everyone, this one’s a bit different. In today’s episode, we’re talking to viral TikTok sensation, Linda Andrade – aka ‘The Millionaire’s Wife’ (the inspiration for our personal weekly spending chat from a few weeks back). Famous for being beyond-bougie with her husband’s money, Linda proudly broadcasts her excessive spending, and her followers can’t get enough. Chanel bags, first-class travel, coffee sprinkled with literal gold – all on her husband’s dime.</description></item><item><title>RTC81: Hot Property! Myths, mortgages and margaritas. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030021/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 09:21:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today at Curve HQ we’ve got property myths, ping pong bats and mortgage-wizard Laura from Lighthouse Financial … that’s right, it’s our first (and maybe last) game of TRUTH or SPOOF, The Property Edition. Can you buy your first home with a 5% deposit? Does an election impact property prices? Do the banks judge you for your spending habits? Will Michael Hallwright stake his house on Sophie paying her mortgage?</description></item><item><title>TCW39: Why we’re breaking from tradition to take a little look at politics. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 23:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030022/</guid><description>Podcast Description While we usually avoid the murky old waters of politics, with the New Zealand election happening this week we thought it was a good time to talk parties, policies and personal impact. We look at promises vs action, the highs and lows of tax, and how your vote can have a huge impact on the economy, the stock market and the world. Who’s pledging to remove GST from fruit and veg?</description></item><item><title>RTC80: Let’s get ethical: Putting your money where your morals are. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 21:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030023/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s World Investor Week! To celebrate we’re partnering with the FMA (the investing-police) to share a really important (and interesting, we promise) episode about ethical investing. While some people are in this game for the big bucks alone, others want to channel their money into companies they believe in. Or, at the very least, companies that aren’t actively damaging our planet or the people on it. It’s a complex topic, full of personal preferences and endless balancing acts, but we’ve come up with a way to keep things simple and streamlined (spoiler: it’s a cute little pyramid).</description></item><item><title>TCW38: Costco’s pumping, Nike’s jumping, and Tay-Tay’s raining gold on the NFL. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 01:41:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030024/</guid><description>Podcast Description While September has been a bit of a (predicted) shocker, it’s not all bad news out there. Despite the ongoing struggles of the cozzie-livs, a few big names are doing ok for themselves. Things are going strong for Costco and its recession-proof stock, Nike’s recent reporting led to a big sporty jump in their shares, and everything Taylor Swift touches is still turning to gold. We also talk about the lasting effects of reputational damage and why Soph will never eat a McCain’s pizza again, and dangle the old carrot for our exciting new project.</description></item><item><title>RTC79: Manifesting the life you've always wanted with Roxie Nafousi | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030025/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 20:44:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030025/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you don't know her already, let us introduce you to Roxie Nafousi. She was described by The Times as 'the face of manifesting' and wow wow wow - what an absolute inspiration. She is a self-development coach, two time best-selling author and an ambassador for the Mental Health Foundation - but it's fair to say things haven't always been peachy. Roxie battled with addiction in her 20's and then fell pregnant to someone she barely knew.</description></item><item><title>TCW37: Good news! Inflation’s coming down, Disneyland’s still cool, and it’s a big month for hot guys in sandals. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030026/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 23:50:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030026/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, we’re saying goodbye to doom and gloom by bringing you a few juicy titbits to brighten up your Monday. First of all – Birkenstocks. Everyone’s favourite sandal is going public! After keeping things private for 250 years, this German institution is ready to IPO and the world is pretty excited. Whether you’re into a classic slide, an oiled leather sandal or a sock-and-clog combo, this is one IPO to watch.</description></item><item><title>RTC78: The cost of being a woman: the endometriosis edition. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030027/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 21:40:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030027/</guid><description>Podcast Description TRIGGER WARNING: hysterectomy. Today’s episode is an exploration on the financial cost of being a woman, thanks to Eve Wellness. For 1/9 women, Endometriosis costs not only a huge amount financially, but also physically, mentally and emotionally. Bree Tomalson from the ZM drive show, and Erin Alysha Barnett from Love Island were kind enough to open up to us about the reality of living with this condition. In this ep we hear about blood clots on a desert island and what it’s like to suddenly have no uterus (and also what it might mean to have more than one uterus in a relationship!</description></item><item><title>TCW36: Cranking side-hustles, a hairy week for Airbnb and another big win for AI. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030028/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 23:38:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonjour! This week, Vic’s getting bougie in St Tropez, Soph’s having serious croissant withdrawals and it seems the global IPO drought may finally be lifting. We look at Arm (an AI powerhouse similar to our old mate Nvidia) and their sky-high first day on the stock exchange, the importance of staying cautious when it comes to the IPO hype, and the striking similarities between being a new IPO and a Bridgeton debutante.</description></item><item><title>RTC77: Why we’re no longer talking about retirement. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030029/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 08:12:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030029/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you’re anything like us, when you hear the word ‘retirement’, your mind goes straight to the rest home: long lonely days, wiry greys, and endless games of bingo. But the reality is, retirement can actually be a massively exciting time (if you’re prepped and ready for it, which you will be after this episode). Alongside giving retirement the hot new look it deserves, we discuss how much you may need (and how to get there), balancing experiencing today with saving for tomorrow, the mind-blowing beauty of compound interest, and the joys of an adult star-chart.</description></item><item><title>TCW35: Sour apples for China, sexy dividends for OnlyFans and the lucrative rise of female fever. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030030/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 23:40:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030030/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the ongoing US vs China big-dog showdown, China has banned the use iPhones for all government officials, leaving Apple shareholders (and everyone else in the world) spooked. But it’s not all bad news – for the rest of this episode, we’re feeling positive, empowered and all kinds of sexy. We’re talking the rise of OnlyFans and its insane dividend payouts, three bad-ass women transforming the US economy with their art, and the joys of finding ‘really nice upholstery’ in the South of France.</description></item><item><title>RTC76: Limes and tequila: Vic + Soph’s weekly spending revealed | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030031/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 08:03:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030031/</guid><description>Podcast Description The self-proclaimed 'Millionaires Wife', AKA Linda Andrade is a TikTok sensation known for her outrageous spending habits. She posted a video recently talking about having spent $16,540USD in a day on Chanel bags, gold lattes, detox massages and a personal chauffeur... Obviously Vic and I weren't going to top Lindas spending, but we thought it could be a fun (and scary) to pick a random week and look at each others statements.</description></item><item><title>TCW34: The Danish pharma-giant taking the world by storm, and how literal storms are adding to inflation. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030032/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 06:31:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030032/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s episode, we’re dealing with a bit of doom and gloom – but don’t worry, Vic still has some great jokes to rehash! We’re talking rainy days for the S&amp;amp;amp;P500, the rising cost of natural disasters, and the Danish pharma-giant taking the EU stock market by storm with their brand-new weight loss drugs. Hot on the heels of the EU’s biggest company, Novo Nordisk’s investors are all smiles … but what could it mean for society?</description></item><item><title>RTC75: Shit … do we need wills? | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030033/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 08:29:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Strap in, people. In today’s episode we’re going slightly rogue and vaguely uncomfortable. We’re talking money (obviously), scandal (yes please) and everyone’s favourite upbeat podcast topic: death. That’s right, it’s will time. We talk to the queen of wills and estate planning, Belinda Heunis, about how to create a will, why they’re so important (spoiler: they’re really, really important), why young people need to get on board, what happens if you die without one, and why you should always tell someone where your will is kept.</description></item><item><title>TCW33: Is there a run on the stock market or are Gen Z just not buying shoes? | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030034/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 01:37:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bad news comes in threes for Soph this week and then she finds out how her Netflix shares would be looking if she hadn’t sold them back in June…✨devastating✨. Some interesting stock reports could be confirming signs of a recession, so Vic gives us some tips on how to recession-proof your portfolio through diversification (hint: what are you still shopping for despite the 💸Cozzie Livs💸?)
For more from The Curve:</description></item><item><title>RTC74: My Grandma left behind a million dollar portfolio | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030035/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030035/</guid><description>Podcast Description In todays episode we talk about intergenerational wealth, and how you can leave it behind. Soph's very clever Grandmother started investing 50 years ago, at a time when women weren't even allowed to work in finance. She was part of an investing club with some of her other girlfriends (um - amazing), and invested regularly. What started out as $12,000NZD, grew to over $1,000,000... We can learn so much from her portfolio and the way she invested.</description></item><item><title>TCW32: How much do the FIFA Women's World Cup winners earn? | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030036/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 00:49:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030036/</guid><description>Podcast Description How much do you think the Spanish team got paid for winning the FIFA Women’s World Cup? We hit the streets of East London this weekend to ask a few people this question, and honestly the answers were not that surprising! Also this week, a very scary prediction about the stock market has been made by someone who, well, has guessed right before 😬So what should we do to protect our investments?</description></item><item><title>RTC73: Plastic Fantastic: How Visa, Mastercard &amp; Amex are doing on the stock market. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030037/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 20:33:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you swiped your Visa, Mastercard or American Express today? Well, so have BILLIONS of other people. These companies are so familiar to us that we can forget that they profit from our everyday purchases, and we can invest in them on the stock market too! In this episode, Vic &amp;amp; Soph discuss how buying stocks in companies we already know about can reduce the complexity of investing. And Vic, (being a little too familiar with one of these credit card companies 💸), gives us the market low down on the three biggest names in the payments industry.</description></item><item><title>TCW31 - Disney’s getting greedy, China’s deflating and everyone’s living with their parents. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030038/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 23:23:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030038/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s trip around the globe, we look at French takeover offers, the home-life of Brits in their 30s and why we all need China to stay inflated. Plus, WeWork is WeCrashing (again) and Disney’s on the up – but at what cost? We talk Hollywood strikes, how we can spot rising share prices, and unrelated to investing, but Soph met a hot, flirty stranger (who does his most powerful thinking on the dance floor, apparently).</description></item><item><title>RTC72: The Power of the Prenup (and the cost of being Kevin Costner) | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 06:36:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030039/</guid><description>Podcast Description In case you haven’t seen the news lately, Yellowstone star Kevin Costner has found himself in some seriously hot water – all thanks to a little piece of paper from 18 long years ago. His prenup. In today’s episode, we do a deep dive into the world of prenups with New York’s finest: the brilliantly bad-ass lawyer to the stars, Stephanie Lehman. We discuss the value of ‘women’s work’, the importance of looking ahead, and how to make that prenup conversation a little bit sexier (spoiler alert: it involves wine, dinner and a whole lot of nudity).</description></item><item><title>TCW30: 115 million reasons to think about renting your house out on Airbnb and HOT GOSS on why Vic doesn’t invest in airlines. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030040/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:10:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030040/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you’ve ever thought about renting your house out on Airbnb, now would be a good time because more than 300,000 years worth of nights were booked out in the June quarter alone! We’ve also got more financial reports this week and some (finally) good news from the New Zealand property market. Vic shares the goss on why she doesn’t invest in airlines (and it’s not because she just lost her bag on the way home from Greece).</description></item><item><title>RTC71: London Life Lessons: money, men and makeshift music. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030041/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 02:52:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to Season 5 of Raising The Curve! We can't wait to share all of the incredible guests *from all over the world* with you, but first, the girls thought it was about time they shared their London Lessons. It's been eight weeks of earning NZ dollars, while spending British pounds and lets just say they are both seriously reconsidering their caffeine addictions, online shopping and party habits. For more from The Curve:</description></item><item><title>TCW29: Reporting season, baby! Highs, lows and Google hash browns. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030042/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 00:09:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030042/</guid><description>Podcast Description ‘Tis (still) the season for reporting – and Vic’s (still) absolutely pumped. We cover big dogs on the rise, the inevitable decline of Snapchat, and why more is still more when it comes to diversification. Plus, it’s good news for Vic’s all-time favourite stock, the world is (probably) going to be ok, and Soph shares her high-risk behaviour in public toilets. It’s all here.
For more from The Curve:</description></item><item><title>TCW28: Grab the popcorn, big stock market moves! | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030043/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 20:43:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030043/</guid><description>Podcast Description You'd think Christmas, New Years Eve or maybe even her birthday would be Vic's favourite time of the year...nope! Our favourite finance geek LOVES when financial reporting season rolls around. This is when all the worlds biggest public companies disclose their financial results. Netflix and Tesla were some and there was even news this week about Kimmy K's business Skims!
For more from The Curve:
Instagram
Website
TikTok</description></item><item><title>TCW27: Why Vic is popping the champagne (and Soph isn't drinking it)! The fastest growing app ever, and China the outlier. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030044/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 23:59:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030044/</guid><description>Podcast Description FINALLY some good news with interest rates for home owners. Vic also shares some stats on the fastest growing app ever, what's happening in China that we aren't seeing anywhere else in the world and why are men paid more in sports than women! For more from The Curve:
Instagram
Website
TikTok
Newsletter
Partners Life (a life and health insurance company) is the proud sponsor of The Curve Weekly.</description></item><item><title>TCW26: Mark Zuckerberg had a baby and Elon Musk did NOT send flowers | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030045/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 07:32:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030045/</guid><description>Podcast Description We know you would have heard by now, but there's a new scroll-worthy social media app in town. If you don’t already know about Mark Zuckerberg’s new baby, Threads, it’s okay - everyone else is still just excitedly figuring it out (except Elon Musk, he’s just PISSED). All things Threads vs Twitter, Apple vs Microsoft and more are in this week’s ep - plus interest rates and stock market updates of course!</description></item><item><title>RTC70: Embracing your broken pieces and buying expensive shoes with Sarah Lindsay | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030046/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 22:25:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030046/</guid><description>Podcast Description After moving across the world to New Zealand with her partner Josh, British born Sarah Lindsay didn’t set out to own a yoga studio, she set out to find her community. When they heard about an empty space in a London-esque brick building in Auckland, Sarah and Josh put all their savings into starting SALA, a multidisciplinary movement studio. But this episode isn’t all about founding a prolific business, it’s about having deep self awareness, creating space for inner healing, and overcoming barriers that most of us could never imagine.</description></item><item><title>TCW25: Tom Hanks inspired our new investing strategy! | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030047/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 23:11:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030047/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Curve weekly there is a LOT going on. Vic gives us a mid-year stock market update, explains why Bitcoin is up 90%, talks about the latest CEO feud and tells us about a booming investing opportunity that any of us could have spotted (especially those on TikTok!). For more from The Curve:
Instagram
Website
TikTok
Newsletter
Partners Life (a life and health insurance company) is the proud sponsor of The Curve Weekly.</description></item><item><title>RTC69: Changing your money mindset with the friend that paid for Soph’s bus ticket. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030048/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 07:53:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get yourself a non-judgemental friend like Ella Gordon Latty. She was the person Soph messaged when she couldn’t pay for her bus ticket recently. We invited Ella onto the pod to ask how she really felt when she got Soph’s text. This is a beautifully honest chat amongst three friends - two of which are walking financial disasters. We hope this ep makes you feel a little better about some of your own financial low points, because lets be honest, we've all had them!</description></item><item><title>TCW24: We know when we'll reach gender equality! Spoiler: it's 131 years. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030049/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 02:04:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stats that have come out about gender inequality, and how long it's going to take to disappear completely. News flash - it's f*cking ages. We talk about why the UK's inflation is taking longer than other parts of the world to chill out, and Mastercard has launched a pretty epic campaign - this ones especially of interest to those who lose their cards all the time!
For more from The Curve:</description></item><item><title>RTC68: The $100,000 reason you need to sort your retirement fund TODAY. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030050/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 07:20:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Margaritas on the beach in Mexico? Spending time with your Grandchildren? No matter how you picture your ideal retirement, your KiwiSaver is going to help you get there. In this episode Soph finally gets her head out of the sand and learns the tangible, financial benefits of getting her KiwiSaver sorted so that her future self will thank her (and be able to afford the Margaritas). We can’t stress enough how vital this conversation is, so get ready to take some action after listening to this chat!</description></item><item><title>TCW23: Don't panic, but we are officially in a recession | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030051/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 07:35:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030051/</guid><description>Podcast Description For anyone freaking out that NZ is officially in a recession, and other countries around the world are close, firstly - take a deep breath. In this ep Vic explains exactly what's going on, so you can (hopefully), not panic too much. The media likes to play up their stories, and NZ officially being in a recession is no exception. Once you understand what's going on a little better, it might calm your nerves.</description></item><item><title>RTC67: Low-maintenance investing and how the $100 challenge could make you RICH in 40 years with Bryce &amp; Alec from Equity Mates | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030052/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 21:29:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Let’s hear it for the boys! Our first male guests on the pod - Bryce and Alec from Equity Mates AKA one of Australia's top podcasts! In this episode we hear from our new investing BFF’s about how they automate and track their spending and investments, why index funds are an investing no-brainer and how the $100 challenge can make you RICH in 40 years. This one has all the tips, so take some notes.</description></item><item><title>TCW22: Why the crypto market is like a naughty teenager and Australia’s surprise interest rate announcement | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030053/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 23:12:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Coming to you live from our Italian rooftop! In this week’s The Curve Weekly we discuss some pretty big teething issues happening across the Crypto market and Australia’s surprise interest rate announcement. Vic explains to a very confused Soph how interest rates affect inflation and thus how inflation affects the value of a nation’s currency, plus a savings tip for your next holiday. I bet you didn’t think an Aperol Spritz paired so well with finance news, but let us tell you - they do.</description></item><item><title>RTC66: Cash baggies and other millennial money saving tips with Sharyn Casey | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030054/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 21:22:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030054/</guid><description>Podcast Description When we tell you it features tequila shots and cameo’s from Sophie’s latest mystery man, you might mistake this episode for a Thursday night out at the clubz. It's not - we promise. And the third voice you recognise? That’s Sharyn Casey, co-host of The Edge radio show for the last seventeen years. We chat to her about job loyalty, getting someone external to handle salary negotiations, and how to teach your 5 year old to save up for his own petrol money for the family trip.</description></item><item><title>TCW22: Why and how is AI impacting money, biz + the markets! | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030055/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 22:18:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030055/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week's Curve Weekly Vic and Soph are on the other side of the world! Coming to you live (well not really live), from the UK! So this week the stock market has massively over performed... but why? Vic explains the TWO main reasons. Hint: AI is expected to be worth 1.3 TRILLION dollars by 2032... that's an annual growth rate of 40% per year! For more from The Curve:</description></item><item><title>RTC65: Vic spills the ☕ on the size of her mortgage and what's going on in the property market | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030056/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 00:52:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you noticed crickets with all the (lack of) property market chat lately? Well, it's because house prices are going one way right now - down! For those on the property ladder, it's been a tough 12 months! For those who aren't, well, we explain why it hasn't been thaaaat sh*t for you. In this ep Vic explains what's been going on the property market, so we can all understand what's going on a little better - homeowner or not!</description></item><item><title>TCW21: A mid-year check in on what's hot and what's not in the money, business + finance world | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030057/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 04:19:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030057/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week's Curve Weekly, we look at how the stock market has performed this year to date. Luxury brands have taken a dive, there was a really important announcement about interest rates, and more great news for women in the workplace. Unrelated to the world of money, biz + finance - we've started a brand new segment at the end of each episode. Feedback welcomed - should it stay or should it go?</description></item><item><title>RTC64: How a money diary can change your life with Frances Cook | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030058/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 05:21:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030058/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode we talk to fellow podcaster Frances Cook from Cooking the Books! She talks about how difficult it can be to save money in the current climate, but how a money diary can change your spending habits to help you cut back on areas that don't bring you much joy. Spoiler - she also tells us about a once in a lifetime investing opportunity that you can take advantage of right now!</description></item><item><title>TCW20: US debt through the roof, Burberry stock and big NZ budget changes! | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030059/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 05:48:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030059/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week's Curve Weekly, we zoom around the world in 15 minutes! There's been huge news in the UK, the US and NZ - all of which has seriously impacted our portfolios. If you noticed a huge drop in the value of your shares over the weekend, you'll know exactly why after this ep. Also quite NZ centric, but epic news for those wanting to take time out of work to have kids in Aotearoa.</description></item><item><title>RTC63: A guide to adulting - Getting your Plan B sorted before it’s too late | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030060/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 05:52:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you like Soph and have selective hearing every time someone mentions the word insurance? Traditionally insurance is just like all other areas of finance where there are too many acronyms to understand what's going on, but that's where Philly and Rochelle come in. Do you know what life, income, mortgage, trauma and health insurance are and why they’re important? Neither did we until we talked to them! They’re the most lovely, independent insurance advisors and they explained everything we needed to know.</description></item><item><title>TCW19: SUPER incredible news has come out of the UK for women in the workplace | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030061/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 06:57:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030061/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week's Curve Weekly we are coming to you live from the bush in Raglan (Vic's nature getaway), and mountains in Arrowtown (Soph's nature getaway). There were so many things that happened this week, first off - lots of people are cancelling their subscriptions (Disney+ and Peloton both took a hit). We also had some SUPER incredible news come out of the UK for women in the workplace.</description></item><item><title>RTC62: Jess Quinn talks about the price of losing her leg (literally) | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030062/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 05:59:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030062/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode we were lucky enough to speak to the ever inspirational Jess Quinn. At the age of 9 she battled cancer and ever since has been a pillar of strength, hope and example of self love and acceptance. In this episode she shares how open she is with her now husband (Todd) with money, why she decided not to sign a prenup and the price her prosthetic leg has (and continues) to cost her.</description></item><item><title>TCW18: Adidas is making a comeback after ditching Kanye West! | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030063/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 07:31:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030063/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week's Curve Weekly we talk about the Adidas stock which has gone up 30% after ditching Kanye West and his Yeezy line, and Vic explains why Apple's 90 BILLION dollar share buy back is such a big deal. If you've been listening to The Curve podcasts for a while, you'll know there are always some raaaaandom lols scattered throughout and this episode is no exception. For more from The Curve:</description></item><item><title>RTC61: How to invest during a recession with Izzy Truman | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030064/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 05:35:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030064/</guid><description>Podcast Description With all the uncertainty in the economy you might be considering how to balance your spicy investments vs conservative ones. Or maybe you're wondering what your portfolio should look like as you get closer to your savings goal or retirement. In this episode we answer burning questions from fellow podcaster Izzy Truman (a Curve Classroom student) and discuss the challenges of podcasting with your best mate (don't worry Vic &amp;amp; Soph don't need couples therapy just yet).</description></item><item><title>TCW17: Is AI taking over the world, the NASDAQ comeback and a new IPO! | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030065/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 04:35:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030065/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this weeks Curve Weekly it looks like a lot of acronyms, but basically we had a BIG (and good) week for the NASDAQ (the New York Stock Exchange) which has lots of big tech companies listed, we talk about AI and how you can get access to it, as well as what Vic thinks is going to be the biggest IPO (company to go public so you can buy shares) for 2023!</description></item><item><title>RTC60: How to negotiate a pay rise with Meggie Palmer | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030066/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 05:49:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Does the thought of approaching your boss for a pay rise make you want to run for the hills? Turns out you're not alone - almost a third of The Curve Community have NEVER asked for a pay rise, and of those who have - only half of them were successful. In this episode we talk to the queen of negotiating, Meggie from PepTalkHer. She's on a mission to help women build their confidence and skills to get a pay rise!</description></item><item><title>TCW16: Taylor Swift and Ryan Reynolds are surprisingly clever with their money! | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030067/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 04:33:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030067/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on The Curve weekly there were lots of famous people making headlines. We talk about Taylor Swift + Ryan Reynolds genius investing decisions, the Tesla and Netflix stocks (both of which have recently fallen off a cliff and are climbing their way back up), as well as some good news about inflation! For more from The Curve:
Instagram
Website
TikTok
Newsletter
Disclaimer: Raising The Curve has been prepared solely for informational and educational purposes.</description></item><item><title>RTC59: Pfizer - a very stiff competitor 😏 | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030068/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 06:01:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030068/</guid><description>Podcast Description You better believe there are a fair few penis jokes in this episode, and that's because we looked at the Pfizer stock! The company who first invented viagra. We talk about the FIVE things to look for before investing, and whether or not we think Pfizer will thrust our portfolios upwards. LOL ok sorry, we're done now.
For more from The Curve:
Instagram
Website
TikTok
Newsletter
We'd like to say a warm and delicious thank you to Nespresso for sponsoring this podcast!</description></item><item><title>TCW15: LVMH is killing it, the UK economy is battling away, and France have raised their retirement age! | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030069/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 03:56:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030069/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Curve Weekly Vic updates us on what the markets are doing around the world, some scary news about the UK + US economies, and what France raising their retirement age means! Also pre warning, this episode ends in quite possibly the worst joke we've ever told. For more from The Curve:
Instagram
Website
TikTok
Newsletter
We'd like to say a huge thank you to Audi for sponsoring this podcast!</description></item><item><title>RTC58: Amy Fraser on balancing family and career when life doesn't go according to plan | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030070/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 06:35:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030070/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you haven’t yet met the powerhouse that is Amy Fraser, then you’re welcome in advance. Amy is the founder of OKREAL, a coach, mentor and mum of two. In this inspiring chat, she generously opens up about her own life experiences to give some practical insight on how to cope when life doesn’t go to plan. We discuss what finances in a relationship can look like when kids are involved, and talk about the return on investment from children when we view them as the assets that they are.</description></item><item><title>TCW14: An expensive Easter, Apple's secret and Aesop is now public! | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030071/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 01:20:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030071/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week's Curve Weekly Vic explains why you might have noticed Easter was extra expensive this year, a big update with one of the world's biggest companies, and Aesop [a crowd favourite] is finally public - AKA you can now buy shares!
For more from The Curve:
Instagram
Website
TikTok
Newsletter
We'd like to say a huge thank you to Audi for sponsoring this podcast! Progress has always been part of Audi's DNA, and as a brand they're leading the way in electric mobility with their fully electric Audi e-tron range (one of which Vic and I have been lucky enough to drive over summer)!</description></item><item><title>RTC57: Everything you need to know about prenups | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030072/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 04:26:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pre-nup? Or Pre-yup? You might be wondering whether or not you need a prenup. Or maybe you're wondering how the hell to bring up such an awkward conversation without hurting anyone's feelings. In this episode we chat to a lawyer well versed in this space, Lauren Aspin about all things Contracting Out Agreement (AKA a prenup). We answer a bunch of your questions, along with some finer details you might need to consider in order to protect your pretty pennies in the future!</description></item><item><title>TCW13: All the bits and bobs of the stock market (including chats on miracle pimple patches!) | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030073/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 08:48:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030073/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this weeks Curve Weekly we managed to keep it to 10 mins! That was always the plan for this pod, short and snappy - but somehow we always struggle to shut up. Sophie talks about her recent experience with pimple patches (always bringing the informative chat), and Vic [actually] educates on some useful stuff that's happened in the stock market this week.
For more from The Curve:</description></item><item><title>TCW12: Crypto is back in vogue and there's a battle of the sneaker giants | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030074/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 02:23:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last year cryptocurrency fell off a cliff, and in this Curve Weekly Vic explains why it seems to be climbing back up again. The Adidas and Nike stocks battling away, with Adidas about to report it's first loss in 30 years... is a recession looming? We hope not, but things aren't looking great! CONTENT WARNING: in this episode, there are an alarming amount of Mum jokes for two women without kids.</description></item><item><title>TCW11: The economy might be up shit creek but it's not all bad... | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030075/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 05:42:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030075/</guid><description>Podcast Description You may have been wondering how far up shit creek we are in terms of the overall global economy... especially after the two major bank meltdowns last week. In this weeks Curve Weekly Vic admits that although we are up shit creek, we can get our metaphorical rain jackets on, and sensibly wait for the storm to pass. For more from The Curve:
Instagram
Website
TikTok
Newsletter
We'd like to say a huge thank you to Audi for sponsoring this podcast!</description></item><item><title>TCW10: A BIG week for the banks. Is your money safe? | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030076/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 05:24:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over the weekend a big bank in the US (SVB - Silicon Valley Bank) fell over, which hasn't happened since the Great Financial Crisis. Questions have been swirling about what this means for the global economy... and rightfully so, people have been panicking. However, it's not as scary when you understand the context. In this (slightly longer) ep of The Curve Weekly, Vic explains what's been going on in layman's terms so you can understand wtf is going on.</description></item><item><title>RTC56: Why does the gender pay gap exist and how can we change it? | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030077/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:15:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030077/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this International Women's Day Special, we were lucky enough to speak to the CEO of Spark Jolie Hodson. Wild fact - Spark is the only company in the NZX50 (the NZ stock exchange) that has a female CEO and Chairwomen. When Vic was looking through their financials, she noticed them transparently call out their gender pay gap and how much it has improved over the past few years.</description></item><item><title>TCW9: Why the oil price is skyrocketing and who pays for what when it comes to weddings! | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030078/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 05:24:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Many things were discussed in this episode, including a fair amount of wedding chat as both Vic and Soph attended one this weekend. Who should pay for the bridal party's extras (dress, suits, nails, makeup etc)? Plz feel free to weigh in about this on our socials! Vic also explained why the cost of oil is skyrocketing (again), and why companies like BP, Exxon Mobil etc are raking in record profit-highs (again).</description></item><item><title>RTC55: An inspiring and incredibly important conversation with the Māori Millionaire | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030079/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 06:33:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030079/</guid><description>Podcast Description An inspiring and incredibly important conversation with Te Kahukura AKA The Māori Millionaire. At just 8 years old she read the iconic investing book 'Richer Dad Poorer Dad', and at 19 she has $45,170 worth of assets! She is incredibly clued up with growing her own wealth and is on a mission to empower others to do the same. In this podcast we talk about the flow on effects that colonisation has had on the Māori population, and the importance of understanding why that wealth imbalance is so prevalent here in Aotearoa.</description></item><item><title>TCW8: The worst week in markets and how investing has nothing to do with maths.... | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030080/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 02:48:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Soph loved this episode - she learnt (and laughed) lots. Vic talks about the future of retailing + how investing has nothing to do with maths (she always has to use a calculator). She explains why the market had its worst week this year, and how you shouldn’t stress if you miss out on shares when a company goes to market for the first time (and does really well) - Beyond Meat is a good example of why.</description></item><item><title>RTC54: How to save for BIG TICKET items | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030081/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 05:47:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030081/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode we talk about Soph's big money goal of wanting to buy a new car. It's been something she's wanted for years, but felt too embarrassed to admit it. She also had NO idea how to get there, so when Audi got in touch and said that they were keen to help, we both screamed like excited 6 year olds. If you want to save for something big, but it feels outlandishly out of reach then this episode is a must listen.</description></item><item><title>TCW7: Another inflation update and what some of the BEST investors are investing in | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030082/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 01:53:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030082/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Curve Weekly we get a quick market and inflation update and talk about a recent [and quite weird] investment decision that Warren Buffet. Being one of the worlds best investors, a lot of other brilliant investors look to his portfolio for ideas so it'll be interesting how this one plays out! Are you ready to take the leap and learn more about investing? You can secure your seat in the course here!</description></item><item><title>RTC53: JJ Feeney on money, mental health + sharing finances with her ex-husband | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030083/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 02:57:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030083/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of our Mindful Miniseries we were lucky enough to speak to JJ Feeney, the queen of radio. She talks candidly about her relationship with money, mental health and why she still shares finances with her ex-husband Dom Harvey. For more from The Curve:
Instagram
Website
TikTok
Newsletter
We would like to say a huge thank you to the wonderful sponsor of this miniseries - BraveFace. We have created a resource to help you improve both your finances and your mental health which you can download here.</description></item><item><title>RTC52: Forget Love Languages, let's talk Money Languages! | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030084/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 02:18:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030084/</guid><description>Podcast Description We've all heard about love languages but have you heard about money languages? In this bonus podcast ep we talk to BraveFace's resident psychologist Dr Victoria Thompson about what they are and how they affect our relationships. With money being one of the main things couples argue over, we thought they were worth bringing to your attention, especially since it's V Day! If you want to find out what your money language is then try our quiz here!</description></item><item><title>TCW6: A company at the top and bottom of The Curve | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030085/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 01:24:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030085/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Curve Weekly we talk about the the Disney stock! Vic explains why it's at the top of The Curve, as well as why Lyft (Ubers competitor) is at the bottom. Today we were feeling extra perky because the doors are finally open to The Curve Classroom! Secure your seat in the course here!
For more from The Curve:
Instagram
Website
TikTok
Newsletter
We'd also like to say a huge thank you to Audi for sponsoring this podcast!</description></item><item><title>RTC51: Building resilience with your money when times are tough with Kayla Gordine | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030086/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 03:41:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030086/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the second episode of our Mindful Miniseries we interview the amazing Kayla Gordine about her journey with wealth (and health). She is an absolute ray of sunshine - entrepreneur, LesMills instructor and singer/songwriter. We talk about how her upbringing impacted her relationship with money, her personal struggles with mental health + how she combats it, as well as her her money goals and how she channels an abundance mindset.</description></item><item><title>TCW5: The best way to grow your $$ and why the NASDAQ is soaring! | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030087/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 01:51:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030087/</guid><description>Podcast Description We hope you've had a relaxing Waitangi weekend. In this Curve Weekly we talk about the NASDAQ (one of the main US indexes) which is doing really well, and why dollar-cost-averaging (essentially auto investing), is one of the BEST things you could be doing to grow your wealth. Side note: The Curve Classroom starts in three weeks! To join the waitlist click here!
For more from The Curve:</description></item><item><title>RTC50: Why are our finances + mental health so intertwined? | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030088/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030088/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the first episode in our new mindful miniseries, where we interview four amazing women and talk about all things mental health + wealth. In this first interview, we chat to Dr Victoria Thompson, the resident Clinical Psychologist at @braveface about how our childhood can impact our relationship with our finances in later life. The four money scripts (think love languages but the finance edition) and all sorts of different tools that can help improve both our mental health and our finances.</description></item><item><title>TCW4: Who might be the next Google and a (depressing) inflation update | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030089/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 04:03:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030089/</guid><description>Podcast Description It may be a public holiday in NZ but AS IF we would take a day off The Curve Weekly! In this weeks episode we talk about ChatGPT which is apparently going to be the new Google (wild), two stocks that are at the top of the Curve and worth paying attention to and an inflation update!
For more from The Curve:
Instagram
Website
TikTok
Newsletter
We'd like to say a huge thank you to Audi for sponsoring this podcast!</description></item><item><title>TCW3: Travel getting cheaper (yay!), Google cutting staff and Netflix making a comeback | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030090/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 04:29:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pre-warning: we were both QUITE sleep deprived when recording this ep. In hindsight recording every Monday morning may not have been the cleverest planning from us LOL however in this ep we talk about why we can expect to see plane airfares starting to drop soon (phew), what's happening at Google + why are they cutting 6% of their staff and what's happening with Netflix (it looks like it's making a comeback)!</description></item><item><title>TCW2: Apple, Tesla and Disney move the stock market higher &amp; recession ow more? | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030091/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 04:17:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030091/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this ep it was another good week in the stock market which we love to see. Big news with Apple, Tesla, Disney and crypto that you'll want to know about, and finally some good news about the potential of a recession. For more from The Curve:
Instagram
Website
TikTok
Newsletter
We'd like to say a huge thank you to Audi for sponsoring this podcast! Progress has always been part of Audi's DNA, and as a brand they're leading the way in electric mobility with their fully electric Audi e-tron range (one of which Vic and I have been lucky enough to drive over summer).</description></item><item><title>TCW1: Welcome to our new podcast, The Curve Weekly! | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030092/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 07:11:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030092/</guid><description>Podcast Description We're so excited to bring you this new Curve podcast! With weekly 10-minute episodes, we're going to give you all the money, business + the stock market tea. In this ep we break down what's happening in the stock market, talk about stocks at the top (and bottom) of The Curve, as well as explain why new data suggests we might be seeing the backside of Inflation (finally). For more from The Curve:</description></item><item><title>RTC48: A deep dive into the Meta stock + why it's fallen 60% | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030093/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 01:35:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Facebook (Meta’s) share price fell 60% in 2022! But what does that mean if you own shares? We obviously can’t tell you what to do with your portfolio, but in this episode Vic explains the reasons why the share price dropped so much, and what she thinks about the future of this company. For more from The Curve:
Instagram
Website
TikTok
Newsletter
Disclaimer: Raising The Curve has been prepared solely for informational and educational purposes.</description></item><item><title>RTC47: Why you shouldn't panic if your portfolio isn't doing well | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030094/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 18:59:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030094/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's really important to remember in times of uncertainty not panic sell or buy. If you're seeing a lot of your investments go down, remember blips happen, it doesn't necessarily mean you need to re-arrange your whole portfolio! For more from The Curve:
Instagram
Website
TikTok
Newsletter
Disclaimer: Raising The Curve has been prepared solely for informational and educational purposes. Any information provided and serviced described in this website are intended to be of general nature and provide general information only.</description></item><item><title>RTC46: Why tech companies share prices are SO unpredictable | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030095/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 11:02:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030095/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you've invested in any of the big tech companies like Meta, Amazon or Alphabet (Google), you'll have noticed a huge drop in their share prices recently. Why? It's all due to US reporting season. Vic explains which companies are booming at the moment, and which are suffering (warning - you might not like what you hear)!
For more from The Curve:
Instagram
Website
TikTok
Newsletter
Disclaimer: Raising The Curve has been prepared solely for informational and educational purposes.</description></item><item><title>RTC45: How auto-investing will change your life | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030096/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Auto investing, also known as dollar cost averaging is a tactic that Vic, and many famous investors swear by. A good way to think about DCA is essentially auto investing - just like how you set up an automatic payment for rent each week. It's figuring out how much you can put aside (in advance), and making sure that the money goes into your investments - opposed to spending it on food or clothes!</description></item><item><title>RTC44: What are stock splits + are they red or green flags for investors? | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030097/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 16:59:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030097/</guid><description>Podcast Description You might've seen news headlines along the lines of 'Amazon announces stock split', or 'Apple announces stock split' - and although it might sound confusing it's actually really simple. In this episode, Vic explains what they are, how they work and if they're considered red or green flags for investors. **If you want to get straight to the finance + investing chat, skip to 4:50**
For more from The Curve:</description></item><item><title>RTC43: How to avoid paying $1300 a year of pink tax! | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030098/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 20:21:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030098/</guid><description>Podcast Description You might have heard pink tax being thrown around in conversation - but what actually is it? How does it work? And how can we avoid paying it because hint: it's not actually real tax and you can avoid it! For more from The Curve:
Instagram
Website
TikTok
Newsletter
Raising The Curve has been prepared solely for informational and educational purposes. Any information provided and serviced described in this website are intended to be of general nature and provide general information only.</description></item><item><title>RTC42: The two main investing strategies explained | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030099/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 18:21:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030099/</guid><description>Podcast Description We've had maaany requests for this episode, so here it finally is - an entire episode dedicated to index funds! Index funds can be a great little feature in the old portfolio - especially for those who are new to investing. In this episode, Vic also explains the difference between active (managed funds) and passive funds (ETF or Index Funds). She talks about these two investing strategies and which one she uses.</description></item><item><title>RTC41: A 101 on interest rates and how they effect the economy | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030100/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 20:26:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030100/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, we cross to our very own UK correspondent (Sophie) to give an on-the-ground account of what is happening in the UK. At the moment they are trying to cool inflation by increasing interest rates. In this ep Vic uses the UK's current situation as a lesson in Economics as a whole and how interest rates affect the economy. For more from The Curve:
Instagram
Website</description></item><item><title>RTC40: One of the greatest returning dividend companies of all time (aka a dividend queen) | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030101/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 18:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Did you know there are only 38 companies in the history of the stock market that have paid a dividend for over 50 years? Traditionally referred to as 'Dividend Kings' (note: as of now we have re-coined the term 'Dividend Queens' for obvious reasons) are very stable, reliable companies. Dividend stocks are companies often held my investors with a shorter time to keep their money invested, but they can also be a great way to diversify if your portfolio has some more risky holdings.</description></item><item><title>RTC38: Investing trends for those with a long time horizon (10+ years) | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030102/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030102/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode we talk about long term investing trends. These are trends that play out over a long period of time - think 10, 20, 30+ years. This is a really incredibly insightful episode, and relevant (especially) if you have a long time that you can keep your money invested for. We speak to Steph Perrin, who is a Global Equities Analyst at Milford Asset Management. She talks about the trends that she thinks we should be paying attention to, and looking for opportunities in.</description></item><item><title>RTC39: Short-term investing trends: what are they and how to spot them | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030103/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 14:03:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Picking successful stocks can feel overwhelming, but a great place to start is by looking at current and future trends. In the investing world, these can be grouped into two main buckets: short and long terms trends. In this episode we were lucky enough to talk to Steph Batchelor who is a Global Equities Analyst at Milford Asset Management. She explains the importance of understanding short term trends, and how as investors we can use them to help us pick successful stocks.</description></item><item><title>RTC37: A deep dive into the fifth biggest retailer in the world: CostCo | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030104/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to Season 3 of Raising The Curve! We are so stoked to be back. For this first episode, we've decided to bring back a crowd favourite - a stock story. This is where we analyse a stock in detail and in todays episode we look at CostCo which is the fifth largest retailer in the world. We discuss their unique business strategy, it's billions of dollars on the balance sheet, returns to date and its future growth projections.</description></item><item><title>RTC36: What's the best way to share finances when in a relationship | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030105/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 14:54:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you understand how the law works when I comes to being in a de facto relationship + splitting your assets if you separate? A lot of us don't! In this ep we talk to Lauren Asprin, a proud member of The Curve Community and is passionate about educating when it comes to relationship rights. She has been working in this area of the law for over a decade so is well versed in what you need to know before you make a decision about keeping your assets separate, or combined.</description></item><item><title>RTC35: How to invest smarter not harder | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030106/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030106/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is part two of our conversation with Buffy Ellen - in this episode she gives us a peek into her personal investing portfolio. She talks about a few holdings (complains she has invested in) that she’s really excited about, and that have seen great returns so far. She explains why she invested in shares (rather than a house), and where her personal KiwiSaver funds are.
For more from The Curve:</description></item><item><title>RTC34: A conversation with a million dollar investor | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030107/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 04:41:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030107/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode we speak to Buffy Ellen, who worked in investing banking for a loooong time. She shares her insights on personal finances and in particular, her mentality towards saving and investing. It’s an incredibly empowering episode, that will remind you that women can be boss babe investors. For more from The Curve:
Instagram
Website
TikTok
Newsletter
This conversation has been proudly brought to life by our friends at Pathfinder (KiwiSaver &amp;amp; Managed funds), who have been investing ethically since before it was cool.</description></item><item><title>RTC33: The best way to put your money where your mouth is | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030108/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 17:56:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030108/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the third episode of our green mini-series we speak to the lovely Olive from Mindful Money, which is a charity working on improving investing transparency in NZ. She shares some SHOCKING stats about how much money is being sent offshore and invested in the likes of weapons, fossil fuels and animal cruelty. ALARM BELLS PEOPLE! This conversation massively reinforces the importance of understanding what and how your money is being invested - we hope you enjoy it!</description></item><item><title>RTC32: How to avoid investing in companies that test on animals | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030109/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 07:33:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030109/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the second episode of our green mini-series, we talk to the incredible Tara Jackson. Tara is the director of a NZ charity called NZAVS, who are trying to end animal testing in Aotearoa. You might be thinking - how does this relate to investing? There are still a LOT of companies still testing on animals, so this episode will help you understand how you can avoid companies that are still implementing these practices.</description></item><item><title>RTC31: Financial success and fashion (without fu*king up the planet)! | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030110/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 20:56:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030110/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are SO excited to bring you a Raising The Curve mini-series, about ALL things ethical investing. Both Vic and I are super passionate about investing in a way that grows your wealth, while also impacting the world in a positive way. In this episode we speak to Ethically Kate, an ambassador for sustainable fashion and living. She's an absolute wealth of knowledge, so combined with Vic's investing knowledge, it was a real winning combo.</description></item><item><title>RTC30: Global conflicts: how they impact our economy &amp; our investments. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030111/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 23:17:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030111/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode we deep dive into the devastating Russia-Ukraine conflict through an investing and economics lens. We discuss how events like this effect our investments, as well as the overall economy. We talk about the volatility created by unforeseen 'black swan' events, what mindsets we should try to adopt in these uncertain times.
For more from The Curve:
Instagram
Website
TikTok
Newsletter
Disclaimer: Raising The Curve has been prepared solely for informational and educational purposes.</description></item><item><title>RTC29: Why you should care about low interest rates | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030112/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Despite everything going on globally right now, there's something else happening that's been impacting your investments. Can we have a drum roll for... interest rates! We were in a low interest environment for a while, but with things changing, it's important to understand how interest rates can effect your investments. Even small increases in interest rates can have a huuuge impact on the stock market. It might sound boring, but we do our best to keep it fun, and it's an important piece of the puzzle when it comes to understanding the overall economic environment.</description></item><item><title>RTC28: The inside scoop about cryptocurrencies from the queen of crypto. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030113/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030113/</guid><description>Podcast Description One for those who are crypto curious! In this episode we have our first ever in-studio guest - Janine Grainger, the CEO and Co-Founder of Easy Crypto! We talk about what moves the different coins and currencies, how to spot upcoming trends, top tips for budding crypto investors and what we can expect for the future of crypto!
For more from The Curve:
Instagram
Website
TikTok
Newsletter
Disclaimer: Raising The Curve has been prepared solely for informational and educational purposes.</description></item><item><title>RTC27: This stock has delivered nearly 300% for the past 5 years | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030114/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030114/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode we analyse the LVMH (Louis Vuitton Moet Hennessy) stock which has consistently delivered a 30% return per year for the past 5 years - that's a pretty solid return! We explore why it's been such an incredible investment to date, discuss how the company works, and what the secret sauce is that sets it apart from other companies!
For more from The Curve:
Instagram
Website</description></item><item><title>RTC26: Four questions to ask before investing in a managed fund | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030115/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you best to use the DIY platforms? Or give your money to a fund manager? The answer is totally up to you - some people even like to do a mixture of both! If you decide you'd like to give your money to a fund manager, this episode is a great listen before you decide on which one is right for you. Vic shares her four top questions to ask - and since she's a fund manager herself, you know this ep is worth a listen!</description></item><item><title>RTC25: How to invest in environmentally friendly companies | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030116/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030116/</guid><description>Podcast Description The way we spend our money can be so powerful! You vote with your wallet every time you buy something, and the same goes with investing. In this episode we talk about 'conscious investing' which basically means - investing in companies that align with your values. You can grow your portfolio, while also being mindful of the planet - something we're both super passionate about. For more from The Curve:</description></item><item><title>RTC24: NFT's - the new kid on the block(chain) | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030117/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Another investing acronym explained! In this episode, we talk about the new kid on the block(chian) - see what we did there? NFT's or non-fungible tokens have very quickly become the new buzz word of the crypto world. But what are they? And how do we trade them? We talk about their uses, how they work, and why all of a sudden they have become so popular!
For more from The Curve:</description></item><item><title>RTC22: An introduction to cryptocurrency: part two. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030118/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030118/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, we dig into 'blockchain' and discuss it's vital role in the world of cryptocurrencies. It might seem a bit mind boggling at first, but the more we break it down, the easier it is to understand. Will crypto become a part of our daily life just like the internet and Facebook? How do you buy and sell it? And where can you use it? Find out in this episode!</description></item><item><title>RTC21: Is cryptocurrency something you should be investing in? | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030119/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030119/</guid><description>Podcast Description We've had so many requests for an episode on cryptocurrency so here it finally is! In this episode we delve into the weird, wild and wonderful world of cryptocurrency. Did you know there are over 10,000 different types of crypto? WILD. We talk about where and why it started, how it's used in the world today, as well as the pros + cons of this very risky asset. Some people will love it and some people will hate it - hopefully this ep you'll know if it's for you or not!</description></item><item><title>RTC20: How to spot investments that go up by 100% | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030120/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030120/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode we talk about what the finance and investing world refer to as '100-baggers’. They are the stocks that quite literally change your life - the rainbow fish of investments. One great example is AfterPay. If you had invested in it at the right time, you would have earned some seriously good returns. '100-baggers' are the kinds of investments that professional investors spend their entire careers looking for, and hopefully after this episode, you'll be able to spot them too.</description></item><item><title>RTC23: We're taking a break this week. Enjoy your holidays! | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030121/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Raising the Curve is taking a week off this week with the Christmas break, we'll be back on January 5th with tips on how to spot life changing investments, or as they're known in the game... 'The Hundred Bagger".
For more from The Curve:
Instagram
Website
TikTok
Newsletter
Disclaimer: Raising The Curve has been prepared solely for informational and educational purposes. Any information provided and serviced described in this website are intended to be of general nature and provide general information only.</description></item><item><title>RTC19: Is the Netflix stock actually a good investment? | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030122/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030122/</guid><description>Podcast Description At the time of this podcast being recorded, Netflix is worth US$300bn? That is a LOOOT of money. It has over 200 million subscribers, and a share price that has risen nearly 400% over five years - but does that mean it makes a good investment? In this episode Vic explains the stocks strengths and weaknesses so you can decide if it's a company you want to have in your portfolio.</description></item><item><title>RTC18: How to invest if you have short-term money goals | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030123/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030123/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Vic explains what on earth 'capital preservation' is. Spoiler: it's basically just a fancy way of referring to an investing strategy that does it's best to make sure you don't lose money if it's needed soon. This kind of strategy would work if you wanted to invest but also need to use that money in the not-so-distant future. It’s a low-risk approach so if you’re saving for something in the mid-to-short term, like a new car or a wedding.</description></item><item><title>RTC17: How to master the stock markets like Buffett: a beginners guide. | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030124/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Before you start trading in stocks, it’s super important to understand the difference between stock markets, stock exchanges and indexes. Did you know there are different exchanges all over the world? In New Zealand we have the NZX, in Australia they have the ASX, in the United States they have the NASDAQ and the NYSE and lots more! There are even stock exchanges in Japan and Amsterdam! But how do they actually work?</description></item><item><title>RTC16: Why keeping your money in the bank is costing you money! | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030125/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 05:30:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030125/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode we give you a kick up the b*** to stop procrastinating, and start paying closer attention to where your money is. On average the NZX50 (the NZ Stock Exchange), has only finished down 5 out of the last 20 years! That's a whole lot of positive returns across the last two decades. Vic explains why investing for 5, 10, or even 20 years from now is the best thing you can do to set your future self up for success.</description></item><item><title>Season 2 Trailer | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030126/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 21:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Raising The Curve is back for Season Two! We'll be exploring investing with a conscience, the wild world of cryptocurrency and so much more! We promise there will be no scary jargon, whether you're a seasoned investor, or starting from scratch - this podcast will help you progress towards financial freedom through investing. For more from The Curve:
Instagram
Website
TikTok
Newsletter
Disclaimer: Raising The Curve has been prepared solely for informational and educational purposes.</description></item><item><title>RTC14: Five things to look for when picking an investment | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030127/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 01:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030127/</guid><description>Podcast Description For this last episode of Season One we are putting everything we have learnt so far, into practice - it's an exciting one! In this episode, we do a deep dive into the Briscoe Group stock. Vic explains the factors that make it such a lucrative stock, so that you can look at other companies and find other successful investments.
For more from The Curve:
Instagram
Website
TikTok</description></item><item><title>RTC13: Twelve top tips when it comes to investing | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030128/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 07:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030128/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode you'll learn Vic's top 12 tips when it comes to investing. Bring a note pad, or type them out in your phone - they're tips you won't want to forget! For more from The Curve:
Instagram
Website
TikTok
Newsletter
Disclaimer: Raising The Curve has been prepared solely for informational and educational purposes. Any information provided and serviced described in this website are intended to be of general nature and provide general information only.</description></item><item><title>RTC12: How to avoid a not-so-good investment! | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030129/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 05:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030129/</guid><description>Podcast Description We invest in companies because we think the trajectory of that company is going to be a raging success. One that will hopefully earn us great returns. The sad reality is that not all companies will be the next Tesla. Some stocks you pick will be winners, and some won't be but trying to pick more winners than losers is where the magic happens! In this episode Vic, gives an example of a not so great investment.</description></item><item><title>RTC11: A deep dive into 2x very successful investments | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030130/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 04:46:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030130/</guid><description>Podcast Description We all want to be pick the new Tesla. That company that does extremely well and you make amazing returns from. In this episode you will be given two real life examples of companies that have grown super fast and in each examples Vic explains what made them such good investments, so you can spot similar opportunities!
For more from The Curve:
Instagram
Website
TikTok
Newsletter
Disclaimer: Raising The Curve has been prepared solely for informational and educational purposes.</description></item><item><title>RTC10: What's better - investing in shares or the property market? | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030131/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:25:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Most of us understand the concept of buying property. It's talked about way more than investing in stocks. But the problem is, a lot of us don't have enough for a house deposit. Does that mean we can't invest? Definitely not! With the rise of DIY platforms, you can invest with as little as $1, which means if you don't have enough for a house deposit - you can still get great returns!</description></item><item><title>RTC9: How to end up with a big nest egg of savings in retirement | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030132/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 04:25:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030132/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you'll learn how tiny changes can make a HUGE difference when it comes to your retirement fund. Vic explains why if you're younger you can *generally* take more risk, whereas if you're older you might want to take less. She also talks about how important it is to make regular contributions - even if just small ones! For more from The Curve:
Instagram
Website
TikTok</description></item><item><title>RTC8: Why it's SO important to make the most of your KiwiSaver | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030133/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 02:47:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030133/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you will learn how tiny changes can make a HUGE difference when it comes to your retirement fund. Vic gives specific so many tips and tricks to make sure you are setting your future self with a much larger nest egg. It only takes a few small changes to make a big difference. For more from The Curve:
Instagram
Website
TikTok
Newsletter
Disclaimer: Raising The Curve has been prepared solely for informational and educational purposes.</description></item><item><title>RTC7: Investing mindsets + how to actually invest in a company | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030134/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 02:27:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Now you know what a stock (also called a share) is, and a little about the stock market... but how do you actually buy a stock? Or better yet, how do you even know if a company is listed? Which means - available for investors to buy shares. In this ep Vic also speaks about investing mindsets. Just like how you would trust sober you, more than you would trust 4-margaritas-deep-you - it's important to decide on your investing strategy when you're in a level-headed.</description></item><item><title>RTC6: An introduction to stocks and the stock market | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030135/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 01:38:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030135/</guid><description>Podcast Description The stock market can seem overwhelming - especially if you've heard your brother or your bf rambling on with lots of weird jargon. But honestly - it's so much easier than you might have initially thought.nIn this episode Vic strips things back to basics and simplifies what a stock actually is, how the market moves, and why falling in love (and holding on to a stock longer than you should - just like a toxic partner), can be VERY dangerous.</description></item><item><title>RTC5: How do you spread your risk when investing in stocks? | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030136/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 01:29:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030136/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is diversification and why is it so important
Transcript</description></item><item><title>RTC4: Understanding the fundamentals of risk | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030137/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 01:36:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Understanding the fundamentals of risk
Transcript</description></item><item><title>RTC3: What are the four different asset classes | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030138/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030138/</guid><description>Podcast Description Breaking down the four different asset classes
Transcript</description></item><item><title>RTC2: Starting with the finance and investing basics | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030139/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 01:42:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Starting with the finance and investing basics
Transcript</description></item><item><title>RTC1: Getting to know The Curve | The Curve</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5881030140/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 23:49:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5881030140/</guid><description>Podcast Description Getting to know The Curve
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>