<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Stories from the Village of Nothing Much on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/stories-from-the-village-of-nothing-much/</link><description>Recent content in Stories from the Village of Nothing Much on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/stories-from-the-village-of-nothing-much/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Snow, Model Trains, &amp; Joy | Stories from the Village of Nothing Much</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1985350003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1985350003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our stories today celebrate some of the special experiences to be had as the weather turns cold and the flakes begin to fall. We’ll start with Snowed in, and spend a lazy morning making waffles and watching the landscape transform. Then we’ll bundle up and head into town to see a magical display and enjoy some fresh popcorn in Model Trains and Make Believe. Finally, we’ll spread some cheer through the neighborhood and enjoy the twinkle lights along the way in Comfort and Joy.</description></item><item><title>Twinkle Lights, Candles, &amp; Hot Drinks | Stories from the Village of Nothing Much</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1985350001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1985350001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our stories today center around the holiday season and take place downtown and in the neighborhoods surrounding it. We'll meet up with friends for the tree lighting and watch the first flakes fall in Bustle in the City. Then we'll celebrate the first night of Hannukah with family and relive a sweet memory from childhood in Light a Candle. Finally, we'll unpack our wares downtown and get a cup of something warming from a street vender in Winter Market.</description></item><item><title>Introducing: Stories from the Village of Nothing Much | Stories from the Village of Nothing Much</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1985350002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 06:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1985350002/</guid><description>Podcast Description See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>