<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated on SWIEST - Transcripts 路 Screenplays 路 Lyrics</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/categories/aware-aggravated/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Aware &amp; Aggravated on SWIEST - Transcripts 路 Screenplays 路 Lyrics</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 09:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/categories/aware-aggravated/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 69. Voids Money Can&#39;t Fill</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400069/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400069/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends, this week I&amp;rsquo;m going to tell you all the voids money can&amp;rsquo;t fill.
And the reason I really want to make this is because I&amp;rsquo;ve touched a lot of money, multiple
times now in my life.
And there are certain heartbreaks that came with it that I want to prevent you from.
Because I had so many ideas of what life would be like once I got money, everything would</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 68. Standards Keep You Safe. Stop Settling.</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400068/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400068/</guid>
        <description>Hi, friends. This week we&amp;rsquo;re talking about standards and how they keep you safe,
because there&amp;rsquo;s not been one time in my entire life when I have dropped my standards or crossed
my own boundaries for something or someone and had a good experience. It&amp;rsquo;s always bit me in the
ass. So I&amp;rsquo;m going to teach you how your standards keep you safe and how to stop fucking up. But I&amp;rsquo;m</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 67. Suicidal to Successful (My Story)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400067/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400067/</guid>
        <description>I really understand now why people don&amp;rsquo;t fucking make videos like this.
This is hard as fuck to talk about.
Y&amp;rsquo;all about to hear all my darkest shit.
Let&amp;rsquo;s do it, I guess.
Hi friends!
So, this week, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna tell you a lot of things that I&amp;rsquo;ve never told anyone.
And I&amp;rsquo;m gonna be talking about suicide, and death, and very dark shit, like the darkest
things you can imagine, so if you don&amp;rsquo;t feel like you&amp;rsquo;re in a place to hear about stuff</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 66. Doing What&#39;s Right Even When It Hurts</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400066/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400066/</guid>
        <description>Is the natural sunlight making me look fucked up or is it giving cute like is it giving like yeah
It looks good, or we look stupid. I can&amp;rsquo;t tell hi friends
So this week we&amp;rsquo;re talking about how to do what&amp;rsquo;s right even when it hurts
And I got a personal example to share with you and the reason we&amp;rsquo;re talking about it is because I&amp;rsquo;m going through it</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 65. Lack of Discipline Makes You Ugly</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400065/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400065/</guid>
        <description>This episode is gonna piss a lot of people off, but you know what? I&amp;rsquo;ll do it.
Hi friends, this week we&amp;rsquo;re talking about how lack of discipline makes you ugly.
And there&amp;rsquo;s a couple of different ways I&amp;rsquo;m gonna explain how it makes you ugly.
One is how other people see you and one is how you see yourself. We&amp;rsquo;re gonna break
all that shit down. But basically when it comes to discipline and looking and</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 64. Why You Aren&#39;t Achieving Things (Let&#39;s Get Spiritual)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400064/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400064/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends I&amp;rsquo;m gonna start this episode off real calm and real sweet because I&amp;rsquo;m
basically gonna tell you why you aren&amp;rsquo;t achieving shit and I&amp;rsquo;m gonna attack you
and I&amp;rsquo;m gonna give you a lot of honest truths that I needed to hear a long time
ago and then I&amp;rsquo;m gonna tell you how to fix it and how to actually achieve
things so all the little lessons I&amp;rsquo;ve learned about achieving things and</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 63. Cures For Gym Anxiety</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400063/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400063/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends, so this week we&amp;rsquo;re talking about gym anxiety and I&amp;rsquo;m gonna tell you
all my tips and tricks and I&amp;rsquo;m gonna give you a couple mindset shifts and
perspectives to take on so that you feel less anxious at the gym because I
remember what it&amp;rsquo;s like to be new and I struggle with it for so fucking long.
So the way that I actually started getting into fitness was I was 14 and I was a</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 62. Achieving Too Much Too Fast</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400062/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400062/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends! We&amp;rsquo;re starting this episode off with a shot because we have a lot to
celebrate a lot of things to be happy about and I&amp;rsquo;m gonna basically run you
through why am I holding it like it&amp;rsquo;s my own prized possession I&amp;rsquo;m gonna run you
through what the fuck&amp;rsquo;s happened this week because my entire reality has just
broken in the best way possible and I&amp;rsquo;m gonna literally like relive the week</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 61. Money DOES Make You Happy</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400061/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400061/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends! This week we&amp;rsquo;re talking about money and a whole bunch of it. I want to
talk about my two cents about how money does make you fucking happy because
everybody in the little entrepreneur space really anybody online anybody with
the fucking mouth be running it and saying that money doesn&amp;rsquo;t make you happy
so I&amp;rsquo;m gonna tell you all the ways it doesn&amp;rsquo;t make you happy because in</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 60. Hitting 900k Followers in 1 Year (My Story)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400060/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400060/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends! So I figured it&amp;rsquo;s time that I be honest with you and I&amp;rsquo;m gonna tell
you the whole story about how I gained over 860,000 followers on TikTok in less
than two years. I&amp;rsquo;m gonna tell you the full background of what was going on
with me and then why I started on TikTok, how I blew up, and how I still blow up
consistently. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of shit that&amp;rsquo;s gone on that y&amp;rsquo;all don&amp;rsquo;t know</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 59. Things I Hate That Most People Love</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400059/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400059/</guid>
        <description>Okay, hi friends. I&amp;rsquo;m gonna get myself in trouble with this episode maybe a little but fuck it
so one of you guys DM to me and asked me to do an episode about my hot takes and
Everything that everybody else loves that I hate and a little elaboration. So I thought it&amp;rsquo;d be fun
I do want to say these are all of my opinions and you&amp;rsquo;re allowed to have different ones</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 58. How To Stop Hating Your Body</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400058/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400058/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends, this week I&amp;rsquo;m going to teach you how to stop hate in your body, because I didn&amp;rsquo;t
always look like this, I was not always this confident, and I used to hate the fuck out
of my body.
So I have a lot to break down, a lot of things to tell you, and you know I always give it
to you straight, and I give you new perspectives, and sometimes they hurt your fucking feelings,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 57. When Trauma Revisits You (My Story)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400057/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400057/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends, we&amp;rsquo;re starting this episode off with a shot and y&amp;rsquo;all know I hate
whiskey for the fucking life of me but I saw this thing about when you&amp;rsquo;re sick
that like the old-time remedy is like to take a shot of whiskey so I bought some
whiskey I took a shot last night I don&amp;rsquo;t know if it helped or not I felt good but
we&amp;rsquo;re gonna do a shot okay cuz I&amp;rsquo;m sick like a fucking child over here I&amp;rsquo;m all</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 56. Everything I Wish I Knew Before Starting A Business</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400056/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400056/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends, today we&amp;rsquo;re talking all things business.
This is going to be everything that I wish someone fucking told me before I started my
business and lost a lot of money.
Because I&amp;rsquo;ve started a few now and I&amp;rsquo;ve probably lost close to like 35-ish thousand dollars
and I&amp;rsquo;m going to go through everything mentally, how to set up and prepare for shit and then
just some tips about how to like navigate things and save yourself some money because</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 55. Outgrowing Friends &amp; How To Handle It</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400055/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400055/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends, so shit looks different once again because I moved. It&amp;rsquo;s the same desk. It&amp;rsquo;s the same mic
It&amp;rsquo;s the same everything same me just a new apartment
And if it echoes, I&amp;rsquo;m so sorry this bitch is big
no, really, I&amp;rsquo;ve been busting my fucking ass since I moved to Houston and I wanted to upgrade my place and
I can do a full episode about
Like why I moved how I moved the whole situation because the way that it lined up was some crazy-ass shit</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 54. Realizations From Traveling Europe</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400054/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400054/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends, I&amp;rsquo;m in a bad mood. I
Don&amp;rsquo;t know why don&amp;rsquo;t fucking ask me. I
Was two seconds away from recording this episode on the couch like that ass. I was gonna fucking get my mic
I was gonna unplug it and I was gonna go make this
Handheld and like go sit on the couch and just like veg out while I talk to you about Europe, but hi friends</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 53. The Trick to Leveling Yourself Up</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400053/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400053/</guid>
        <description>Okay, hi friends, I just got home from being out, but I really want to make this episode
right now.
Like I have some important shit to say about how to truly level yourself up.
This is something heavy in my mind right now and I just kind of had a big realization around
it.
So I always say to act on your inspiration.
So I&amp;rsquo;m having to do that right now.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 52. I Got Jumped in Berlin</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400052/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400052/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends, so I&amp;rsquo;m in Europe right now and shit looks real different because I did not plan on having to make this fucking episode
So me and my friend Randy planned a trip to Europe and we were gonna come here for like three weeks
And I recorded a bunch of podcast episodes to have ready so I could just edit them and then post them while I&amp;rsquo;m away</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 51. Being The Jealous One &amp; How to Stop</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400051/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400051/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends so this week I want to talk about jealousy and not just jealousy in
relationships, jealousy in friendships too because I used to be and still am
one of the most jealous motherfuckers you can find. So first I want to
deconstruct everybody&amp;rsquo;s view of jealousy because everybody just writes it off
like it&amp;rsquo;s bad and it&amp;rsquo;s like toxic if you&amp;rsquo;re jealous. We&amp;rsquo;re gonna go into that
shit I&amp;rsquo;m gonna deconstruct it and then I&amp;rsquo;m gonna give you my tips for dealing</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 49. How to Not Get Attached to People So Fast</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400049/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400049/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends! So this week I&amp;rsquo;m going to give you all my tips for how to not get attached to people so fast.
Because my Pisces ass, please. I used to get attached to people like that.
Like it was so annoying how quick I would like plan my future with someone.
Like I&amp;rsquo;d meet them, I would see them across the room and be like, boom, we&amp;rsquo;re dating, we&amp;rsquo;re married.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 50. Feeling Alone When You&#39;re Around People</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400050/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400050/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends. This week I&amp;rsquo;m gonna talk about something that kick-started my
spiritual awakening, which was feeling alone in a room full of people. Like
being around people and still feeling alone. That feeling and that like whole
thing going on inside me is what led me to discovering the whole like
spirituality shit. So I&amp;rsquo;m gonna kind of break down what&amp;rsquo;s going on, what happens,
and then like a couple things about how to deal with it.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 48. How To Be More Productive &amp; Stop Messing Up</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400048/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400048/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends! This week we&amp;rsquo;re talking about productivity. I&amp;rsquo;m gonna give you all my
hacks that are not in the fucking books, okay? All this shit everybody&amp;rsquo;s teaching
you online, all the shit in the self-help books, that beginner type shit that
don&amp;rsquo;t actually work that long, forget about it. I&amp;rsquo;m gonna teach you the real
tricks on how to be productive. So I have a full list of tips in front of me on my</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 47. Wanting To Change Yourself &amp; How To Actually Do It</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400047/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400047/</guid>
        <description>I just hit that so pussy. I&amp;rsquo;m not gonna show my zazae.
Hi friends, so I&amp;rsquo;m real stressed right now. I don&amp;rsquo;t know fucking know why, but I&amp;rsquo;m like
real anxious. I&amp;rsquo;m giving anxiety, but I want to talk about wanting to change yourself in
this week&amp;rsquo;s episode because there&amp;rsquo;s such a stigma around wanting to change yourself and
like the self-development community and everybody&amp;rsquo;s like you need to accept yourself and love</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 46. When They Don&#39;t Like You Back</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400046/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400046/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends, this week we&amp;rsquo;re talking about how to handle someone not liking you back.
I don&amp;rsquo;t know why I&amp;rsquo;m giggling bitch, cause this is a serious topic, like this is like
very hurts your heart, like this shit will fuck you up.
But I have a lot to break down with this, because you can get stuck in playing the game.
Because there is a big game that comes with when someone doesn&amp;rsquo;t like you back, so I&amp;rsquo;m</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 45. How To Trust Yourself</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400045/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400045/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends! So this week I want to talk about trusting yourself. And we&amp;rsquo;re gonna
start off talking about how to actually repair the relationship with yourself
and how to actually trust yourself. And then I&amp;rsquo;m gonna dive into learning how to
trust your own judgment so that other people&amp;rsquo;s opinions don&amp;rsquo;t fuck with you.
I&amp;rsquo;m gonna teach you my tricks that I&amp;rsquo;ve found for that. Because a lot of people</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 44. Knowing When To Leave</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400044/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400044/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends, so shit looks a little different and it&amp;rsquo;s gonna get fixed in a second, but I recorded this episode yesterday
I&amp;rsquo;m hungover right now
But I recorded this episode yesterday and the whole fucking like beginning part of it cut out
So now I have to refilm it and usually I would just shut the fuck up refilm and add it in
But I&amp;rsquo;m gonna start letting y&amp;rsquo;all know when I&amp;rsquo;m struggling and shit&amp;rsquo;s going wrong</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 43. Tired of Being Strong</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400043/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400043/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends, so this week I want to share something I&amp;rsquo;ve been dealing with and
then teach you how I got out of it which is being tired of being strong like when
you always have to be the one to be strong and you&amp;rsquo;re like you&amp;rsquo;re aware that
everything&amp;rsquo;s in your control but you get pissed the fuck off at it I got you
cuz I was going through it real hard the last couple weeks but before we jump</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 42. Green Flags</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400042/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400042/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends, this is an episode of green flags. I gave you red flags. Okay, I gave you the full episode of what the fuck to run away from and now I&amp;rsquo;m going to give you an episode of what to run toward. So these are all the green flags you need to know. We&amp;rsquo;re going to start with funny little shit, but I&amp;rsquo;m dead ass serious. So we&amp;rsquo;re going to talk about like physical appearance.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 41. Self Control</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400041/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400041/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends this week we&amp;rsquo;re talking about self-control and I&amp;rsquo;m gonna give it to you straight as I always do I&amp;rsquo;m gay
But I give it straight
I&amp;rsquo;m here to share all the shit
I&amp;rsquo;ve learned the hard way cuz I&amp;rsquo;ve read over a hundred self-help books and I&amp;rsquo;m not being dramatic like I read a lot and this
Is everything I&amp;rsquo;ve found that&amp;rsquo;s not in the books. Okay, this is the shit</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 40. Hookup Culture</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400040/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400040/</guid>
        <description>Alright, let&amp;rsquo;s do this shit cuz I&amp;rsquo;m anxious. I&amp;rsquo;m giving anxiety and if I don&amp;rsquo;t just start talking
I&amp;rsquo;m gonna freak myself the fuck out. But hi, you can see me. Hi friends
This is our first video podcast. And of course, it&amp;rsquo;s gonna be about fucking this is gonna be hookup culture
Everything you need to know about it
I got some shit to break down and I have some things to tell you</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 39. Break Ups</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400039/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400039/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends, so this week I want to talk about breakups because people do not
fucking understand them. So I want to give you some explanations that I have
around breakups and why they feel so fucking terrible and also I&amp;rsquo;m gonna give
you some tips about how to navigate one because no one really knows what to tell
you like they fucking suck and people don&amp;rsquo;t understand how deep they actually</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 38. Influencers &amp; Misplaced Confidence</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400038/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400038/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends! So this week I want to talk some shit about social media. I&amp;rsquo;m gonna
share some realizations and then I&amp;rsquo;m gonna rant for a minute because I have
some shit going on that&amp;rsquo;s just pissing me off that I keep seeing on social media.
And one of the realizations I&amp;rsquo;m gonna share about posting online and like
being online is one of the things that actually helped me move away and change</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 37. Why You&#39;re Never Enough</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400037/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400037/</guid>
        <description>hi friends so yes you read the title right but this is not gonna be an
episode of me just reading the absolute shit out of you why nobody likes you
nobody wants you nobody chooses you this is gonna be an episode about the
awareness that I&amp;rsquo;ve gained recently and y&amp;rsquo;all this shit hit me in the face like
I&amp;rsquo;ve been hitting the face a lot but this motherfucker rocked me okay like</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 36. How To Handle Anything</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400036/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400036/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends, so recently I found a hack for life. And of course, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna share it with you
So I found out a way to always know how to handle something anything that comes up
You don&amp;rsquo;t know how to handle it. You don&amp;rsquo;t know how to conduct yourself. You don&amp;rsquo;t know the answer. I&amp;rsquo;ve got you
I&amp;rsquo;ve found the solution
This is how to always know what to do and how to never get caught in the in-between of like not knowing which</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 35. Alcohol</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400035/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400035/</guid>
        <description>hi friends I&amp;rsquo;m in a happy mood today like I&amp;rsquo;m a happy fucking dick right now
so here I am to talk my shit and I&amp;rsquo;m gonna tell you all the things you need
to know about drinking alcohol these are my requirements these are my rules bitch
like there&amp;rsquo;s so much more that goes into drinking then you realize and I&amp;rsquo;m gonna
tell you all the shit you need to know because the main thing you don&amp;rsquo;t want to</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 34. Discipline</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400034/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400034/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends, so this week we&amp;rsquo;re talking discipline.
I&amp;rsquo;m going to tell you everything I know about it, how I&amp;rsquo;ve built it, how I&amp;rsquo;ve been so strong
and pushed myself to do this shit that I don&amp;rsquo;t want to do.
I&amp;rsquo;m going to tell you all my tricks, okay?
But I am going to have to get up under your ass a little bit and push you.
In this episode, bitch, get ready.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 33. Breaking Out of A Mindset</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400033/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400033/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends, so this week I want to talk to you about breaking out of certain mindsets
You know the ones that like got you trapped to shit and you don&amp;rsquo;t know how to get out of them
I&amp;rsquo;m gonna teach you how to do it. I&amp;rsquo;ve talked about
Certain mindset shifts I&amp;rsquo;ve made in previous episodes
But I&amp;rsquo;m gonna share with you the process I go through
When I&amp;rsquo;m trying to break out of a certain mindset and I&amp;rsquo;m gonna teach you also how to identify</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 32. When You Miss Someone</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400032/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400032/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends, so I&amp;rsquo;m gonna go ahead and start this episode off with an apology
because I&amp;rsquo;m sorry for how this episode is about to fuck your shit up okay you&amp;rsquo;re
not gonna be the same after it your whole outlook&amp;rsquo;s gonna change it&amp;rsquo;s gonna
hurt your feelings about 49 times and I&amp;rsquo;m sorry about it these are all the
things I&amp;rsquo;ve learned about missing someone something missing memories
missing a certain time in your life we&amp;rsquo;re gonna get into all of it but it&amp;rsquo;s</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 31. Signs You Can Trust Someone</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400031/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400031/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends, so this is the last fucking episode
I thought I&amp;rsquo;d ever be making because I have the words trust no one tattooed on my hand
And here I am giving you a full fucking podcast of how to know you could trust someone
But that&amp;rsquo;s exactly what I&amp;rsquo;m gonna do
So as much as I want to say trust no one and I stand by that&amp;rsquo;s all the day that I die</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 30. Why Things Seem So Difficult</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400030/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400030/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends, so this week. I&amp;rsquo;m gonna deconstruct some things around why everything seems so goddamn hard
I&amp;rsquo;ve got three points or kind of like areas to deconstruct and when I say deconstruct bitch
Y&amp;rsquo;all know how I do. I&amp;rsquo;m a deconstruct the motherfucker
So my three areas are kind of like just different things to take into consideration
But what I mean by why things seem so hard
I mean like why shit seems so difficult like there&amp;rsquo;s so many things that logically</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 29. Being There For Yourself</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400029/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400029/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends, so in this episode I&amp;rsquo;m gonna give you all the things I&amp;rsquo;ve learned
about being there for yourself and all the shortcuts that are gonna get you
comforted because I know what it&amp;rsquo;s like to not have anyone to turn to and not
know what the motherfuck to do with the way that you feel okay because sometimes
shit just happens and you don&amp;rsquo;t know what to do what to think where to go who</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 28. How To Feel Inspired &amp; Motivated</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400028/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400028/</guid>
        <description>Okay, let&amp;rsquo;s fucking try this again.
Hi friends!
So, I&amp;rsquo;m trying my best to figure out the audio of this fucking podcast because last week&amp;rsquo;s
episode I was holding my phone literally just in my hand the whole time and the audio sounded
like ass for like half of it.
So I have my little phone right now propped up on a little stand above my head and I&amp;rsquo;m
hoping that the audio is good but like my closet is too big to make it not sound like</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 27. Realizations From Running Away</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400027/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400027/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends, I did it. I&amp;rsquo;m in Houston. I fucking moved. I actually
Full-blown ass did the shit. I ran away and I made it and I&amp;rsquo;m safe and I&amp;rsquo;m so
Happy I fucking did this. I hope I don&amp;rsquo;t sound echoey because my closet is fucking
Huge and I&amp;rsquo;m not trying to sound like a pretentious asshole, but like y&amp;rsquo;all my closet is massive
I just don&amp;rsquo;t make no fucking sense.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 26. My Struggles With Moving</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400026/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400026/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends, hope you&amp;rsquo;re doing great. I&amp;rsquo;m not really I am. I&amp;rsquo;m just y&amp;rsquo;all this episode is about to be
Unpacking all the trials and tribulations of me trying to fucking move. All right
This has not been a smooth experience by any means and it&amp;rsquo;s just like the littlest things keep happening and keep
Fucking up. Okay, but I&amp;rsquo;m determined and I&amp;rsquo;m a very stubborn motherfucker
And when I say I&amp;rsquo;m gonna do something do it</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 25. How to Make A Change</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400025/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400025/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends! So for this episode, I want to talk about some of the things that I&amp;rsquo;ve recently realized when it comes to making changes and changing your life.
And everything that has to do with that. And y&amp;rsquo;all, it&amp;rsquo;s fucking annoying. I&amp;rsquo;m just going to let you know.
Like, what I&amp;rsquo;ve been realizing the past couple of days, week, two weeks, is a lot to take in.
And of course, what am I going to do when I realize some new shit?</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 24. How To Make Friends</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400024/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400024/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends, so this episode is all about making you some friends. I&amp;rsquo;m gonna teach you everything
I fucking know and it&amp;rsquo;s a whole bunch
I promise and I hope I&amp;rsquo;m able to share some things that you haven&amp;rsquo;t heard of before and I really really hope at the end
of this episode you feel a little bit more excited and
prepared and like equipped with the knowledge and ideas to go out and make some goddamn friends because I know exactly how it is to</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 23. Realities People Like To Hide</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400023/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400023/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends, I don&amp;rsquo;t know where this episode is gonna go, but I&amp;rsquo;m gonna just stand here
and run my mouth and see what happens.
So the thing I want to talk about is people being a lot more intentional about what they&amp;rsquo;re
doing than you think.
I&amp;rsquo;ve kind of touched on this in other episodes, but I&amp;rsquo;ve never like really went into it.
I&amp;rsquo;ve said people are trying more than you think, putting more effort into things, but</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 22. Being Insecure &amp; How To Stop</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400022/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400022/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends! Today we&amp;rsquo;re going to talk about being insecure, alright? I&amp;rsquo;m going to give
you my kind of definition of it, and you know it&amp;rsquo;s like that feeling, like I&amp;rsquo;m going to
just go ahead and start this episode off the bat, bitch, we ain&amp;rsquo;t got no time to waste,
what if we die, you know? Let&amp;rsquo;s just get into it. So like, there&amp;rsquo;s a couple different versions
of being insecure, and everyone&amp;rsquo;s kind of got their own, but like I&amp;rsquo;m talking about</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 21. What I Learned From Rich People</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400021/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400021/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends! This is gonna be an episode of the things that I&amp;rsquo;ve learned from being
around rich people. And this is the shit you ain&amp;rsquo;t gonna find them as success
books and the self-help books and any of these books that you can fucking read or
any of this shit you see online. No. I&amp;rsquo;m gonna tell you the things that I&amp;rsquo;ve
observed from being in the lives of really rich people, from living day to</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 20. Why You Can&#39;t See Your Worth</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400020/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400020/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends, this episode is gonna be a fucking whirlwind. I don&amp;rsquo;t have a notebook. I don&amp;rsquo;t have this planned out
I don&amp;rsquo;t know what&amp;rsquo;s about to come out of my mouth, but I just need to get on here and vent a little I
Need to talk to my friends. I need to talk to the people that fucking get the way my brain works
because I
Had some real big like things to face last night with myself</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 19. Dealing With Toxic People</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400019/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400019/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends! So today we&amp;rsquo;re gonna talk about toxic people and people you can
get away from people you can&amp;rsquo;t you know because we got like family that you want
to cut them the fuck off but you can&amp;rsquo;t and then you got like friends which you
can cut off but sometimes you just don&amp;rsquo;t want to you know like a little toxic
keeps it fun but as always I&amp;rsquo;m gonna give you my like honest thoughts</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 18. The Truth About Self Love</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400018/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400018/</guid>
        <description>hi friends today we&amp;rsquo;re talking about self-love and why you ain&amp;rsquo;t got none
not really I&amp;rsquo;m gonna debunk this shit for you okay cuz everybody online be
preaching all kind of you just need to love yourself you need to love yourself
but they don&amp;rsquo;t give you steps of how to fucking do it okay and they don&amp;rsquo;t even
know what they&amp;rsquo;re talking about half the time people that&amp;rsquo;s just a good thing to</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 17. Why You Aren&#39;t Happy</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400017/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400017/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends, this week we&amp;rsquo;re gonna talk about why you&amp;rsquo;re a miserable fuck, okay?
I&amp;rsquo;m gonna start off the podcast like that. Oh, you know, we&amp;rsquo;re just gonna go with it. Okay, I&amp;rsquo;m not refilming this intro. Hi
I&amp;rsquo;m gonna share my three little theories I have on
happiness and why people are unhappy, you know, like people always talk about
Comparison is the thief of joy eat my ass. That&amp;rsquo;s some kindergarten shit.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 16. When They Try To Come Back</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400016/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400016/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends this week we&amp;rsquo;re talking about when the motherfucker tries to come back
Whether it&amp;rsquo;s a best friend or a friend that you cut off because they did some fuck shit
Or if it&amp;rsquo;s an ex like you broke up with somebody and they want to come back
Or just like a sneaky link or like anything like anytime somebody tries to come back in your life
This is the shit that you need to know and even if you&amp;rsquo;re like ah Leo.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 15. How To Actually Feel Lovable</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400015/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400015/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends, I&amp;rsquo;m back
Pastor Leo had to take a little trip. I took two trips. Actually. I went to Texas to go see my family
And then I went to TNC. I took my sale to fucking hick ass
Tennessee y&amp;rsquo;all and it was shit. Okay, Nashville. Don&amp;rsquo;t go Nashville is not fun
It&amp;rsquo;s not the fucking vibe but Texas bitch College Station. I want to go see my family.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 14. Why Nice People Finish Last</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400014/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400014/</guid>
        <description>hi friends this long-awaited episode is finally here why nice guys be finishing
last but I really want to put emphasis on the friends when I say hi friends
because I want you to know that we&amp;rsquo;re friends and I&amp;rsquo;m only gonna tell you
everything in this episode because you need to fucking hear it okay but we&amp;rsquo;re
friends we&amp;rsquo;re besties bestie for the resty but I am gonna hurt your feelings</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 13. Recent Realizations</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400013/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400013/</guid>
        <description>hi friends it&amp;rsquo;s time for Sunday service once again happy Sunday Pastor Leo here
I think it&amp;rsquo;s funny as fuck some of you guys have been commenting that on my
tick-tock you&amp;rsquo;ve been calling me like Pastor Leo and shit I think that is so
funny but anyway I need to tell you guys I have two tick-tock accounts a lot of
people don&amp;rsquo;t know that like some people just find my not Leo for legal reasons</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 12. Red Flags</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400012/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400012/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends! This episode is gonna be all about red flags, and yes, I have enough
fucking red flags to make an entire episode on them. Now these are gonna be
random things that I think are red flags. If you don&amp;rsquo;t agree, you&amp;rsquo;re wrong, but
you&amp;rsquo;re allowed to be wrong. That&amp;rsquo;s fine. If you do or are any of these things, I
don&amp;rsquo;t mean any offense to you, I just probably wouldn&amp;rsquo;t date you.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 11. Feeling Valuable</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400011/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400011/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends! Today we&amp;rsquo;re talking about value and I have to hit you where it
hurts with this one. This one&amp;rsquo;s gonna suck and there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of shit that you
need to hear that you don&amp;rsquo;t want to hear. But it&amp;rsquo;s like having a wound and you got
a band-aid on it. I have to rip the band-aid off so I can heal the wound, you
know? I gotta like fix it, but I gotta cause you a little pain first.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 10. Why Mental Disorders Are The New Trend</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400010/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400010/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends, it&amp;rsquo;s time for Sunday service, and I&amp;rsquo;m gonna start this Sunday service off with a trigger warning
Yeah, I know in my first episode. I said I&amp;rsquo;m not gonna give another one, but I&amp;rsquo;m treading in
shark infested waters today
Because I&amp;rsquo;m gonna be talking about the mental health field and why all of a sudden everybody seems to have some kind of fucking disorder
Whether it&amp;rsquo;s anxiety or depression or ADD ADHD</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 9. Caring What People Think</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400009/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400009/</guid>
        <description>hello friends if I sound a little weird and a little fucked up it&amp;rsquo;s cuz I am I&amp;rsquo;m
sick but the show must go on so this week&amp;rsquo;s episode is gonna be about caring
what other people think of you so everyone says that you&amp;rsquo;re not supposed to
but I disagree I think you should care what people think of you and I&amp;rsquo;m not
being a smartass I promise like I&amp;rsquo;m about to get into this but it just seems</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 8. Expressing You&#39;re Uncomfortable</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400008/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400008/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends, so in this episode I&amp;rsquo;m gonna get real vulnerable and I have to to
prove my point and one thing about me is I&amp;rsquo;m gonna prove my motherfucking point
no matter what I have to do so in this one I gotta expose some things about
myself and I do want to say if there is one episode of my podcast that you
listen to fully I hope it&amp;rsquo;s this one because I&amp;rsquo;m gonna share some awareness</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 7. Money</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400007/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400007/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends, so in this episode, we&amp;rsquo;re gonna talk about money the thing that everybody loves, but nobody wants to fucking talk about
I&amp;rsquo;m gonna share with you a
Lot of the things I&amp;rsquo;ve realized and a lot of the truths that I&amp;rsquo;ve come to about money
Which have made me be a lot less constricted with it because I&amp;rsquo;ve had a bad relationship with money for so long
And every time I&amp;rsquo;d have to spend money on something that I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to spend it on</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 6. Dating Apps Are Damaging</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400006/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400006/</guid>
        <description>Hello friends today, we&amp;rsquo;re talking about dating apps and all the issues that I think are wrong with them
Which is a whole bunch
And I&amp;rsquo;m gonna list them all and get all in depth with every single one because I genuinely believe that
Dating apps are fucking us up worse than anyone realizes
Also, no offense to anyone that is on dating apps or likes dating apps. I&amp;rsquo;ve been on them</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 5. Everyone is Racist</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400005/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400005/</guid>
        <description>I know, I know, the title&amp;rsquo;s a little out there, give me a fucking second to explain, okay?
Cause everybody is racist and fatphobic and transphobic and what the fuck else is there?
What other phobics is there? Cause everybody is all of it.
Skinnyphobic, whitephobic, motherfucking anti-smoking cigarettes, what&amp;rsquo;s that called, cigarettephobic bitch.
People will call you anything in the fucking book now.
They&amp;rsquo;ll just throw the word phobic on the end of it and think it&amp;rsquo;s an insult.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 4. You Look Better Than You Think</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400004/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400004/</guid>
        <description>Hi friends! So in this week&amp;rsquo;s episode I want to talk about something I used to
struggle with really bad and it was hating myself and my body and criticizing
the fuck out of it and not seeming to be able to stop. So I&amp;rsquo;ve gained some
awareness around why I did that and how to stop doing that and that&amp;rsquo;s what I
want to share in this episode. And I do want to clarify, because I&amp;rsquo;m gonna talk a</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 3. My Awakening at EDC</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400003/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400003/</guid>
        <description>Hi everyone, I&amp;rsquo;m fresh off of bawling my fucking eyes out.
I finally stopped because I turned off Rufus Dussault.
I just had him in the background just like serenading me and all my Pisces placements,
just crying my fucking eyes out.
But I just had a really good conversation with my dad who I never really talk deep to.
You know dads, you just don&amp;rsquo;t fucking get into certain shit.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 2. Why You Don&#39;t Like The Ones That Like You</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400002/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400002/</guid>
        <description>What&amp;rsquo;s up guys it&amp;rsquo;s time for episode 2 and I&amp;rsquo;m gonna rock this bitch cuz I&amp;rsquo;m gonna talk about a topic that hits
Close to home for everybody I think and it&amp;rsquo;s why you don&amp;rsquo;t like the people back that like you
I&amp;rsquo;m talking about in a relationship like it just seems like the ones that like me
Uh, like I don&amp;rsquo;t have no fucking interest and if I do it&amp;rsquo;s short-lived or I can force myself to like them</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aware &amp; Aggravated - 1. Social Media is Cancer</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1308400001/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1308400001/</guid>
        <description>In true Leo fashion, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna start off the first episode of my podcast with a
motherfucking trigger warning, okay? I&amp;rsquo;m making this podcast to talk about real
life, real shit, the real struggles and what everyone&amp;rsquo;s actually dealing with
and what no one talks about, okay? So if you like the fake bullshit you see
online, you&amp;rsquo;re not gonna like this. Go live in your fake reality and stay in</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
