<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Making Sense with Sam Harris on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/making-sense-with-sam-harris/</link><description>Recent content in Making Sense with Sam Harris on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 17:02:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/making-sense-with-sam-harris/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>#345 — Resilience | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070371/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 17:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070371/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Amanda Knox about her experience of having been falsely convicted and imprisoned for murder in Italy.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Learning how to train your mind is the single greatest investment you can make in life. That’s why Sam Harris created the Waking Up app. From rational mindfulness practice to lessons on some of life’s most important topics, join Sam as he demystifies the practice of meditation and explores the theory behind it.</description></item><item><title>#344 — The War in Gaza | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070370/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 16:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070370/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris comments on the recent testimony of university presidents before Congress, along with Elon Musk's reinstating of Alex Jones on X. He then introduces a recent episode of the Call Me Back podcast about the war in Gaza, hosted by Dan Senor. Sam really enjoyed listening to this conversation and we’re delighted to be able to share it with the Making Sense community.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#343 — What Is "Islamophobia"? | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070369/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 17:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070369/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris discusses the social and political consequences of a weaponized term. A transcript of this podcast is available on Sam’s blog.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#342 — Animal Minds &amp; Moral Truths | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070368/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 23:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070368/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Peter Singer about important problems in ethics. They discuss his career as a philosopher, the moral status of non-human animals, the ethics of moral hierarchies, speciesism, the scale of animal suffering, conscientious omnivores, animal experimentation, the tragic case of Sam Bankman-Fried, concerns about Effective Altruism, the problems with focusing on existential risk, the comparative nature of human suffering, the work of Derek Parfit, objective morality, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#341 — Gaza &amp; Global Order | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Yuval Noah Harari about the events of October 7th and the resulting war in Gaza. They discuss the unraveling of global order, the failure of the IDF, the incompetence of the Netanyahu government, the goals of Hamas, the Saudi peace treaty, the right of Israel to exist, the status of Palestinian and Jewish refugees, victim and perpetrator narratives, compromise vs justice, the Palestinian citizens of Israel, lessons from WW2, the danger of focusing on the past, the perverse significance of the al-Aqsa Mosque, the double standards to which Israel is held, false analogies to European colonialism, the rise of antisemitism, the future of politics in Israel, America’s role in preserving global order, the war in Ukraine, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#340 — The Bright Line Between Good and Evil | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 17:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks about the ongoing war in Gaza, the global rise of antisemitism, and the enduring problem of jihadism.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#339 — The Infernal Logic of Jihad | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070003/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 19:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Graeme Wood about the October 7th atrocities in Israel, the unfolding war in Gaza, and the ongoing problem of global jihadism.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#338 — The Sin of Moral Equivalence | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 14:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070004/</guid><description>Podcast Description If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#337 — The Future of Psychedelic Medicine | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 20:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Jeannie Fontana and Robin Carhart-Harris about the TREAT Initiative in California and the growing promise of psychedelics for mental health care.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Learning how to train your mind is the single greatest investment you can make in life. That’s why Sam Harris created the Waking Up app.</description></item><item><title>#336 — The Roots of Identity Politics | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 23:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Yascha Mounk about identity politics. They discuss Yascha’s concept of the “identity synthesis,” skepticism about “cancel culture,” racial segregation in schools, the ideological change on college campuses, Michel Foucault and postmodernism, the rejection of universalism, Derrick Bell, Kimberlé Crenshaw, the “permanence of racism,” the indoctrination of children, intersectionality, white privilege, institutional racism, equity vs equality, racial preferences during the Covid pandemic, the asymmetric advantage of authoritarianism, class and elitism, affirmative action, media coverage of crime and violence, social media and the business model of mainstream journalism, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#335 — A Postmortem on My Response to Covid | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070007/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 21:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070007/</guid><description>Podcast Description If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#334 — The Low-Trust Society | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 20:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with David Brooks about the state of American democracy and the liberal world order. They discuss the weakness of moral individualism, the loss of social trust, the dangers of identity politics, what happened to the Republican Party, the hatred of elites, the 2024 Presidential Election, the Trump indictments, the war in Ukraine, moral force, the roots of liberalism, the various flavors of Trump support, the Biden presidency, Hunter Biden’s laptop scandal, Biden’s prospects in 2024, Nikki Haley, economic inequality, the problems with meritocracy, the state of media and social media, the lure of conspiracy thinking, the politics of recognition, our handling of the Covid pandemic, our difficulties acknowledging uncertainty, our withdrawal from Afghanistan, the limits of American power, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#333 — Sanity Check on Climate Change | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070009/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 18:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Chris Field about climate change and its consequences. They discuss skepticism about climate change, the accuracy of climate models, the magnitude of temperature increases, how global temperatures are measured, the historical record of climate variation, the range of possibilities in the coming decades, feedback mechanisms, wildfires, water vapor, air pollution, solar geo-engineering, the biggest challenge to taking action on climate change, the costs of transitioning to a carbon-neutral economy, renewable sources of energy, nuclear power, carbon capture, hydrogen, the developing world, China and India, carbon taxes and other incentives, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#332 — Can We Contain Artificial Intelligence? | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 16:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Mustafa Suleyman about his new book, “The Coming Wave: Technology, Power, and the 21st Century’s Greatest Dilemma.” They discuss the progress in artificial intelligence made at his company DeepMind, the acquisition of DeepMind by Google, Atari DQN, AlphaGo, AlphaZero, AlphaFold, the invention of new knowledge, the risks of our making progress in AI, “superintelligence” as a distraction from more pressing problems, the inevitable spread of general-purpose technology, the nature of intelligence, productivity growth and labor disruptions, “the containment problem,” the importance of scale, Moore’s law, Inflection AI, open-source LLMs, changing the norms of work and leisure, the redistribution of value, introducing friction into the deployment of AI, regulatory capture, a misinformation apocalypse, digital watermarks, asymmetric threats, conflict and cooperation with China, supply-chain monopolies, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#331 — A Golden Age for Assholes | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070011/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 20:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070011/</guid><description>Podcast Description If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#330 — The Doomsday Machine | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 22:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Carl Robichaud about the ongoing threat of nuclear war. They discuss the film "Oppenheimer," the ethics of dropping atomic bombs on Hiroshima and Nagasaki, the false lessons of the Cuban Missile Crisis, the history and future of nuclear proliferation, the logic of deterrence, cyber vulnerabilities, the history of de-escalation, the war in Ukraine, war games, the nuclear taboo, growing tensions between the U.S. and China, artificial intelligence, getting to nuclear zero, the role for private citizens in mitigating nuclear risk, the Longview Nuclear Risk Policy Fund (https://www.</description></item><item><title>#329 — What Happened to the Republican Party? | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070013/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 00:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Bret Stephens about the current state of the Republican Party. They discuss the strange change in Republican attitudes toward Putin, the character of Tucker Carlson, the war in Ukraine, the failures of elites and experts, the tension between concerns about misinformation and free speech, the Hunter Biden laptop, the 2024 Presidential election, how Trump captured the Republican Party, the criminal charges against Trump, the future of conservatism, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#328 — Health &amp; Longevity | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Peter Attia about his book, “Outlive: The Science and Art of Longevity.” They discuss "healthspan," centenarians, diet and nutrition, sugar, macronutrients, alcohol, fasting and time-restricted eating, exercise, Zone 2 training, heart disease, blood pressure, cholesterol, cancer, brain health, metabolic disorders, proactive medical testing, medication side effects, Rapamycin, emotional health, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#327 — Transformative Experiences | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 19:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with L.A. Paul about the nature of transformative experiences. They discuss how certain experiences change the self, the nature of regret, changing belief systems, conspiracy thinking, empathy, doing good in the world, our relationship to our future selves, changing our values, the nature of possibility, the ethics of punishment, moral luck, the moral landscape, consequentialism, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#326 — AI &amp; Information Integrity | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 19:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Nina Schick about generative AI and information integrity. They discuss the challenges of regulating AI, authentication vs detection, fake video, hyper-personalization of information, the promise of generative design, productivity gains, disruptions in the labor market, OpenAI, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Learning how to train your mind is the single greatest investment you can make in life.</description></item><item><title>#325 — A Few Thoughts About RFK Jr. | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 18:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris discusses Robert F. Kennedy Jr.'s recent appearances on other podcasts.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Learning how to train your mind is the single greatest investment you can make in life. That’s why Sam Harris created the Waking Up app. From rational mindfulness practice to lessons on some of life’s most important topics, join Sam as he demystifies the practice of meditation and explores the theory behind it.</description></item><item><title>#324 — Debating the Future of AI | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 15:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Marc Andreessen about the future of artificial intelligence (AI). They discuss the primary importance of intelligence, possible good outcomes for AI, the problem of alienation, the significance of evolution, the Alignment Problem, the current state of LLMs, AI and war, dangerous information, regulating AI, economic inequality, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#323 — Science &amp; Survival | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 23:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Martin Rees about the importance of science and scientific institutions. They discuss the provisionality of science, the paradox of authority, genius, civilizational risks, pandemic preparedness, artificial intelligence, nuclear weapons, the far future, the Fermi problem, the prospect of a "Great Filter", the multiverse, string theory, exoplanets, large telescopes, improving scientific institutions, wealth inequality, atheism, the conflict between science and religion, moral realism, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>Making Sense of Meditation | Episode 10 of The Essential Sam Harris | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070020/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070020/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, we traverse a decade of Sam’s conversations on the topic of meditation. We start with the very first recorded episode from the archives: a conversation with Sam’s meditation teacher and friend, Joseph Goldstein. Goldstein recalls how his thinking was unlocked—allowing him to fully realize the power of the practice—by the utterance of one single word.
We then hear from author Richard Lang as he guides us towards a strangely obvious insight that came to be known as “the headless way.</description></item><item><title>#322 — Predicting Reality | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070021/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 00:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Andy Clark about the predictive brain, embodied cognition, and the extended mind. They discuss the structure of perception, novelty, precision, pain, psychedelics, emotion, ways to hack our predictions, hypnosis, meditation, artificial intelligence, consciousness, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Learning how to train your mind is the single greatest investment you can make in life.</description></item><item><title>#321 — Reckoning with Parfit | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 16:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with David Edmonds about the life and philosophy of Derek Parfit. They discuss Parfit’s work on identity, time bias, the “non-identity problem,” population ethics and “the Repugnant Conclusion,” the ethical importance of future people, Effective Altruism, moral truth, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Learning how to train your mind is the single greatest investment you can make in life.</description></item><item><title>Making Sense of Death | Episode 9 of The Essential Sam Harris | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070023/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 15:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070023/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, we explore Sam’s conversations about the phenomenon of death.
We begin with an introduction from Sam as he urges us to use our awareness of death to become more present in our day-to-day lives. We then hear a conversation between Sam and Frank Ostaseski, founder of the Zen Hospice Project, who shares the valuable lessons he has learned through caring for those in their very last days.</description></item><item><title>#320 — Constructing Self and World | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 16:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Shamil Chandaria about how the brain constructs a vision of the self and the world. They discuss the brain from first principles; Bayesian inference; hierarchical predictive processing; the construction of vision; psychedelics and neuroplasticity; beliefs and prior probabilities; the interaction between psychedelics and meditation; the risks and benefits of psychedelics; Sam’s recent experience with MDMA; non-duality; love, gratitude, and bliss; the self model; the Buddhist concept of emptiness; human flourishing; effective altruism; and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#319 — The Digital Multiverse | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 15:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with David Auerbach about the problematic structure of online networks. They discuss the tradeoffs between liberty and cooperation, the impossibility of fighting misinformation, bottom-up vs top-down influences, recent developments in AI, deepfakes, the instability of skepticism, the future of social media, the weaknesses of LLMs, breaking up digital bubbles, online identity and privacy, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>Making Sense of Social Media and the Information Landscape | Episode 8 of The Essential Sam Harris | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070026/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 16:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070026/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, we examine a series of Sam’s conversations centered around social media’s impact on the information landscape.
We begin with Sam’s second conversation with Tristan Harris, which was conducted shortly after the release of Tristan’s documentary, The Social Dilemma. The documentary lays out Tristan’s thesis on how social media is causing the deterioration of both individual and societal welfare. Author and technologist Jaron Lanier follows, echoing Tristan’s concerns and shifting the conversation to social media’s unique business model, addressing how perverse incentives reliably produce such detrimental outcomes.</description></item><item><title>#318 — Physics &amp; Philosophy | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070027/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 16:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Tim Maudlin about the foundations of physics and metaphysics. They talk about the nature of scientific reductionism, emergence, functionalism, the nature of time, presentism vs eternalism, causation, the nature of possibility, the laws of nature, David Lewis’s possible worlds, rival interpretations of quantum mechanics, free will, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#317 — What Do We Know About Our Minds? | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070028/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 16:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Paul Bloom about the state of psychological science. They discuss fiction as a window onto the mind, recent developments in AI, the tension between misinformation and free speech, bullshitting vs lying, truth vs belonging, reliance on scientific authority, the limits of reductionism, consciousness vs intelligence, Freud, behaviorism, the unconscious origins of behavior, confabulation, the limitations of debate, language, Koko the gorilla, mental health, happiness, behavioral genetics, birth-order effects, living a good life, the remembered and experiencing selves, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#316 — Self-Defense: Reality and Fantasy | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070029/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Matt Thornton about his new book, “The Gift of Violence: Practical Knowledge for Surviving and Thriving in a Dangerous World.” They discuss his background in martial arts, the reasons to train in combat sports, the UFC and the evolution of mixed martial arts, the fundamental principles of effective martial arts, the "street" vs "sport" fallacy, grappling vs striking, the persistence of fake martial arts, Bruce Lee’s legacy, male violence and emotional maturity, the male fear of humiliation, violence against women, the validity of instinct, the behavior of predators, weapons, avoiding violence, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>Making Sense of Existential Threat and Nuclear War | Episode 7 of The Essential Sam Harris | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070030/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 19:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070030/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, we examine the topic of existential threat, focusing in particular on the subject of nuclear war.
Sam opens the discussion by emphasizing the gravity of our ability to destroy life as we know it at any moment, and how shocking it is that nearly all of us perpetually ignore this fact. Philosopher Nick Bostrom expands on this idea by explaining how developing technologies like DNA synthesis could make humanity more vulnerable to malicious actors.</description></item><item><title>#315 — The Great Derangement | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070031/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Tim Urban about his new book, “What’s Our Problem: A Self-Help Book for Societies.” They discuss Tim’s unusual career, the finitude of life, existential risk, exponential technological change, political tribalism, the corruption of the media, how one thinks vs what one thinks, trust in institutions, the firing of James Bennet at the New York Times, digital mobs, the mechanics of cancellation, Alex Jones, election integrity, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#314 — The Cancellation of J.K. Rowling | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070032/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 16:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Megan Phelps-Roper about the new podcast series she hosts and produced, “The Witch Trials of J. K. Rowling.” The series is also produced by Andy Mills and Matt Boll for The Free Press. If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Learning how to train your mind is the single greatest investment you can make in life.</description></item><item><title>#313 — Apocalypse | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070033/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 16:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Bart D. Ehrman about the prophecies contained in the book of Revelation. They discuss his latest book, "Armageddon," and widespread Christian beliefs about the coming end of the world.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Learning how to train your mind is the single greatest investment you can make in life.</description></item><item><title>Making Sense of Belief and Unbelief | Episode 6 of The Essential Sam Harris | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070034/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 17:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070034/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, we examine a series of Sam’s conversations centered around religion, atheism, and the power of belief. First, we hear the stories of three guests who have fled their respective oppressive religious organizations. We begin with Sarah Haider, founder of the advocacy group Ex-Muslims of North America, who details how her encounters with militant atheists catalyzed her journey to secularism. Then our narrator, Megan Phelps-Roper, walks us through her story of abandoning the Westboro Baptist Church.</description></item><item><title>#312 — The Trouble with AI | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070035/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 16:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Stuart Russell and Gary Marcus about recent developments in artificial intelligence and the long-term risks of producing artificial general intelligence (AGI). They discuss the limitations of Deep Learning, the surprising power of narrow AI, ChatGPT, a possible misinformation apocalypse, the problem of instantiating human values, the business model of the Internet, the meta-verse, digital provenance, using AI to control AI, the control problem, emergent goals, locking down core values, programming uncertainty about human values into AGI, the prospects of slowing or stopping AI progress, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#311 — Did SARS-CoV-2 Escape from a Lab? | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070036/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 19:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Matt Ridley and Alina Chan about the origins of the COVID pandemic. They discuss the evidence of a lab leak from the Wuhan Institute of Virology, media and academic censorship of this topic, the history of collaboration between western scientists and Chinese labs, the risks of "gain-of-function" research, the evidence for the zoonotic origins of SARS-CoV-2, the initial complacency and denialism of the Chinese, the biosafety levels at the Wuhan Institute of Virology, molecular evidence of a lab leak, the practical constraints on synthesizing viruses, lack of international cooperation, conspiracy theories promulgated by the CCP, EcoHealth Alliance, different kinds of "</description></item><item><title>Making Sense of Free Will | Episode 5 of The Essential Sam Harris | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070037/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 17:14:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070037/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, we examine the timeless question of “free will”: what constitutes it, what is meant by it, what ought to be meant by it, and, of course, whether we have it at all. We start with the neuroscientist Robert Sapolsky who begins to deflate the widely held intuition and assumption of “libertarian free will” by drawing out a mechanistic and determined description of the universe.
We then hear from the philosopher who has long been Sam’s intellectual wrestling opponent on this subject, Daniel Dennett.</description></item><item><title>#310 — Social Media &amp; Public Trust | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070038/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 01:17:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Bari Weiss, Michael Shellenberger, and Renee DiResta about the release of “the Twitter files” and the loss of trust in the institutions of media and government. They discuss Bari and Michael’s experience of participating in the Twitter files release, the problem of misinformation, the relationship between Twitter and the federal government, Russian influence operations, the challenges of content moderation, Hunter Biden’s infamous laptop, the need for transparency, platforms vs.</description></item><item><title>Making Sense of Encounters With Violence | Episode 4 of The Essential Sam Harris | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070039/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 17:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070039/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode centers around the specter of violence and surfaces some of Sam’s most controversial positions and difficult conversations.
We begin with author and former FBI hostage negotiator Chris Voss, who delivers some potentially life-saving aspects of “tactical empathy,” which can also be applied to less extreme circumstances. Author and security expert Gavin de Becker then lays out his thesis from The Gift of Fear, which recasts this unfairly maligned emotion as an important attention-demanding, evolved signal.</description></item><item><title>#309 — Vulnerability, Politics, and Moral Worth | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070040/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 03:02:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Martha C. Nussbaum about her philosophical work. They discuss the relevance of philosophy to personal and political problems, the influence of religion, the problem of dogmatism, the importance of Greek and Roman philosophy for modern thought, the Stoic view of emotions, anger and retribution, deterrence, moral luck, sexual harassment, the philosophical significance of Greek tragedy, grief, human and animal flourishing, the "capabilities approach" to valuing conscious life, the rightness or wrongness of moral hierarchies, "</description></item><item><title>#308 — The Long Game | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070041/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 15:50:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Robert Waldinger about the Harvard Study of Adult Development. They discuss the limitations of relying on self-report to assess a person’s well-being; Daniel Kahneman’s remembering and experiencing selves; why it can be hard to figure out what makes us happy; the effects of alcohol, smoking, and exercise; the connection between work and fulfillment; the primacy of relationships; the diminishing importance of wealth; status vs feeling valued; the connection between good relationships and physical health; having kids and marital satisfaction; introversion vs extroversion; mortality and loss; collecting experiences vs things; the benefits of walking; taking relationships for granted; quantity vs quality time; the self and self states; the guru-disciple relationship; and the possibility of enlightenment.</description></item><item><title>Making Sense of Foundations of Morality | Episode 3 of The Essential Sam Harris | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070042/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 18:36:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070042/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, we try to trace morality to its elusive foundations. Throughout the compilation we take a look at Sam’s “Moral Landscape” and his effort to defend an objective path towards moral evaluation.
We begin with the moral philosopher Peter Singer who outlines his famous “shallow pond” analogy and the framework of utilitarianism. We then hear from the moral psychologist Paul Bloom who makes the case against empathy and points out how it is more often a “bug” in our moral software than a “feature.</description></item><item><title>#307 — Twitter, Elon, &amp; Free Speech | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070043/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 21:14:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris discusses Elon Musk's behavior on Twitter and the illusion of "free-speech absolutism."
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Learning how to train your mind is the single greatest investment you can make in life. That’s why Sam Harris created the Waking Up app. From rational mindfulness practice to lessons on some of life’s most important topics, join Sam as he demystifies the practice of meditation and explores the theory behind it.</description></item><item><title>Making Sense of Consciousness | Episode 2 of The Essential Sam Harris | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070044/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Filmmaker Jay Shapiro has produced a new series of audio documentaries, exploring the major topics that Sam has focused on over the course of his career.
Each episode weaves together original analysis, critical perspective, and novel thought experiments with some of the most compelling exchanges from the Making Sense archive. Whether you are new to a particular topic, or think you have your mind made up about it, we think you’ll find this series fascinating.</description></item><item><title>#306 — Psychedelics &amp; Mortality | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070045/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 19:17:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Roland Griffiths about psychedelics and mortality. They discuss the current state of psychedelic research, the timeline for FDA approvals, the risks to mental health posed by psychedelics in vulnerable populations, the use of psychedelics among the well, the relationship between psychedelics and meditation, advice for “bad” trips, microdosing, Roland’s stage-4 cancer diagnosis, reflections on death, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#305 — Moral Knowledge | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070046/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 01:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Erik Hoel about the nature of moral truth. They discuss the connection between consequentialism and Effective Altruism, the problems with implementing academic moral philosophy, bad arguments against consequentialism, the implications of AI for our morality, the dangers of moral certainty, whether all claims about good and evil are claims about consequences, the problem of moral fanaticism, difficulty in thinking about low-probability events, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#304 — Why I Left Twitter | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070047/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 15:51:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris explains why he deleted his Twitter account. He then speaks with Cal Newport about the fragmentation of modern life. They discuss the history of computer science, how information technology has changed our lives, the effects of social media, the business model of the Internet, the power of TikTok, the future of Twitter, winner-take-all dynamics in podcasting, conspiracy thinking, the way technology drives cultural change, email and the loss of productivity, the cognitive cost of context switching, deep work, the benefits of controlling one's time, the problem with the advice to "</description></item><item><title>Making Sense of Artificial Intelligence | Episode 1 of The Essential Sam Harris | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070048/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 16:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Filmmaker Jay Shapiro has produced a new series of audio documentaries, exploring the major topics that Sam has focused on over the course of his career.
Each episode weaves together original analysis, critical perspective, and novel thought experiments with some of the most compelling exchanges from the Making Sense archive. Whether you are new to a particular topic, or think you have your mind made up about it, we think you’ll find this series fascinating.</description></item><item><title>#303 — The Fall of Sam Bankman-Fried | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070049/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 17:09:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris discusses the recent Sam Bankman-Fried fiasco, the collapse of FTX, and the future of Effective Altruism.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Learning how to train your mind is the single greatest investment you can make in life. That’s why Sam Harris created the Waking Up app. From rational mindfulness practice to lessons on some of life’s most important topics, join Sam as he demystifies the practice of meditation and explores the theory behind it.</description></item><item><title>#302 — Science &amp; Civilization | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070050/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:39:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Neil deGrasse Tyson about his new book, Starry Messenger. They discuss what makes science a unique human endeavor, the tension between respecting scientific consensus and overturning it, confusion about paradigm shifts and scientific controversies, the social importance of probability and statistics, climate change, the consequences of exponential cultural change, social media, social inequality and affirmative action, identity politics and a post-racial future, the wisdom of focusing on class rather than race, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#301 — The Politics of Unreality: Ukraine and Nuclear Risk | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070051/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 16:21:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Timothy Snyder about the ongoing war in Ukraine. They discuss the effect of Russian propaganda, Putin’s motives, whether the US and NATO bear some responsibility for the war, widespread calls for de-escalation, nuclear blackmail and nuclear risk, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Learning how to train your mind is the single greatest investment you can make in life.</description></item><item><title>#300 — A Tale of Cancellation | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070052/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 23:51:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Meg Smaker about the controversy around her documentary, "The Unredacted (Jihad Rehab)." They discuss her background as a firefighter; the effect that 9/11 had on the firefighting community; her subsequent adventures in Afghanistan, Yemen, and Somalia; the deprogramming of jihadists; the organized campaign to silence her film; the capitulations Sundance, SXSW, and other festivals; and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#299 — Steps in the Right Direction | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070053/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 21:03:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Russ Roberts about decision-making and the nature of moral progress. They discuss the shortcomings of economics as a science, the power of books, the difference between "wild" and "tame" problems, Darwin’s embarrassing thoughts about the value of marriage, the utility of decision of analysis, incommensurate goods, free riding, counterfactuals, how the decisions we make change us, the difficulty of predicting future experience, changing moral norms, Effective Altruism, free speech, whether we are making moral progress, social media, truth vs comfort, problems with consequentialism, rule-based consequentialism, free will, meditation, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#298 — Leaving the Faith (Rebroadcast) | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070054/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 00:38:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Yasmine Mohammed about her book Unveiled: How Western Liberals Empower Radical Islam. They discuss her family background and indoctrination into conservative Islam, the double standard that Western liberals use when thinking about women in the Muslim community, the state of feminism in general, honor violence, the validity of criticizing other cultures, and many other topics. If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#297 — Preparing for the End | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070055/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 16:52:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with BJ Miller and Shoshana Berger about preparing for death. They discuss the difference between palliative care and hospice, the tension between getting the most out of life and not clinging to experience, planning for death while still healthy, the importance of an advance directive, navigating the healthcare system, pain control at the end of life, assisted suicide, psychedelic therapy for end-of-life anxiety, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#296 — Repairing Our Country | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070056/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 18:15:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Jonah Goldberg about the state of American politics and civil society. They discuss the hyperpartisanship of the Left and Right, what Trump has done to the Republican party, the breakdown of trust in institutions, the “new catastrophism” enabled by social media, the problem of populism, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#295 — Philosophy and the Good Life | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070057/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 15:15:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks to Kieran Setiya about the relevance of philosophy to living a good life. They discuss the existence of objective moral truths, being happy vs living well, our response to grief, the difference between "telic" and "atelic" activities, the power of reframing, FOMO, bias toward the future, regret, the asymmetry between pain and pleasure, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#294 — Status Games | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070058/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 16:24:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Will Storr about the role that status plays in human life and culture. They talk about the taboo around caring about status, egalitarianism, the perpetual insecurity of status, how we play multiple status games simultaneously, identity, social connection, dominance, virtue, success, status as an evolved mechanism, gossip, status and health, the consequences of humiliation, the role of social media, status and politics, conspiracy thinking, moral panics, status and philanthropy, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#293 — What I Really Think About Trump and Media Bias | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070059/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 20:13:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris responds to a controversy over a recent podcast appearance.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#292 — How Much Does the Future Matter? | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070060/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 16:34:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with William MacAskill about his new book, What We Owe the Future. They discuss the philosophy of effective altruism (EA), longtermism, existential risk, criticism of EA, problems with expected-value reasoning, doing good vs feeling good, why it's hard to care about future people, how the future gives meaning to the present, why this moment in history is unusual, the pace of economic and technological growth, bad political incentives, value lock-in, the well-being of conscious creatures as the foundation of ethics, the risk of unaligned AI, how bad we are at predicting technological change, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#291 — Where is Happiness? | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070061/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 17:26:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Arthur C. Brooks about what it takes to build a good life. They discuss the power of social comparison, the intelligence taboo, political dignity and ethical hierarchy, the Dalai Lama, the nature of love, fluid and crystallized intelligences, the strange case of Linus Pauling, the limits of identity, atheism and religious faith, fear of death, psychedelics, existentialism, St. Thomas Aquinas, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#290 — What Went Wrong? | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070062/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 21:23:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Marc Andreessen about the current state of Internet technology and culture. They discuss Marc's background in tech, the birth of the Internet, how advertising became the business model for digital media, the three stages of the Web, the blockchain, how successful technology reorders status and power in society, the Bitcoin white paper, the mystery surrounding the identity of Satoshi Nakamoto, the importance of distributed consensus, Bitcoin as digital gold, how society has performed during Covid, James Burnham and managerial capitalism, the principal-agent problem, negative externalities, risk and regulation, trust in institutions, WTF happened in 1971, regulatory capture, banning Trump and Alex Jones from social media, perverse incentives in philanthropy, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#289 — Time Management for Mortals | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070063/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 19:44:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris presents an unconventional perspective on time management from Oliver Burkeman. Rather than focusing on rote efficiency or productivity, Burkeman calls on us to embrace our finitude and surrender to the rhythms of life, so that we may “end our struggle with time”—and live with “more accomplishment, more success, and more time spent on what matters most.”
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#288 — The End of Global Order | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070064/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 19:25:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Peter Zeihan and Ian Bremmer about Peter's new book, The End of the World is Just the Beginning. They discuss a wide range of issues related to the deglobalization and demographic collapse, the differing fates of China and America, climate change, the war in Ukraine, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#287 — Why Wealth Matters | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070065/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 16:56:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Morgan Housel about the psychology of money and investing. They discuss how personal history shapes one’s view of economic risk, the implications of not understanding the future, being rich vs being wealthy, how we measure success, the problem of social comparison, happiness vs life satisfaction, saving and investing, Warren Buffett and the power of compounding, rational vs reasonable decisions, the role of luck, optimism vs pessimism, dollar-cost averaging, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#286 — The Paradox of Psychedelics | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070066/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 17:03:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris shares an audio essay exploring how psychedelics are, for many, the only way to glimpse "the vast firmament beyond the prison walls” of the “conceptual mind”—and often serve as the gateway to meditation. He also discusses how the very profundity of the psychedelic experience can distract us from the true purpose of mindfulness—the recognition that consciousness is always already free, in every moment. Also included are highlights from the Waking Up app created for a recent Tim Ferriss podcast.</description></item><item><title>#285 — American Division | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070067/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 20:54:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with David French about forces that are pulling American society apart. They discuss David’s experience as a JAG officer in Iraq, his experience of harassment for coming out against Trump, the way real grievances drive political derangement, the illiberalism on both the Left and the Right, the role of prophecy in Evangelical support for Trump, honor culture, the response to Hunter Biden’s laptop, the January 6th hearings, the personality cult of Trumpism, federalism, geographic sorting, group polarization, cultural divisions in sports and entertainment, the gun rights movement, the ethics of gun ownership, whether Trump will be prosecuted, the 2024 Presidential campaign, the dangers of online activism, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#284 — The Funny Business | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070068/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 14:48:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Judd Apatow about his career in comedy. They discuss his new documentary on George Carlin, why so much comedy ages badly, Carlin’s drug use, how Judd structures his work, using improv in his films, adventures in parenthood, what is worth worrying about, the downside of fame, advice for creatives, the unique properties of standup comedy, the problem of political fragmentation, the consequences of not believing in free will, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#283 — Gun Violence in America | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070069/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 21:33:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Graeme Wood about the problem of gun violence in the aftermath of the mass shooting in Uvalde, Texas.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#282 — Do You Really Have a Self? | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070070/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 16:54:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Jay Garfield about the illusion of the self. They discuss the default sense of subjectivity, the difference between absolute and conventional truth, interdependence, free will, subject-object duality, emptiness, the “mind-only” school of Buddhism, scientific realism and experiential anti-realism, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.</description></item><item><title>#281 — Western Culture and Its Discontents | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070071/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 20:52:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Douglas Murray about his new book, “The War on the West.” They discuss the problem of hyper partisanship on the Left and Right, the primacy of culture, Hunter Biden’s laptop, the de-platforming of Trump and Alex Jones, the new religion of anti-racism, the problem of inequality, the 1619 Project, history of slavery, moral panics, the strange case of Michel Foucault, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#280 — The Future of Artificial Intelligence | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070072/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 17:02:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Eric Schmidt about the ways artificial intelligence is shifting the foundations of human knowledge and posing questions of existential risk.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Learning how to train your mind is the single greatest investment you can make in life. That’s why Sam Harris created the Waking Up app.</description></item><item><title>#279 — The Rules of the Stage | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070073/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 18:01:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris and Ricky Gervais discuss the infamous Oscar slap.
We’re excited to announce the launch of the Absolutely Mental app for iOS users. All three seasons of Absolutely Mental are available for purchase on the app.
Subscribers to the Making Sense podcast will hear the episode in its entirety in their subscriber feed. If you’d like to hear this entire episode for free, you can access it by downloading the Absolutely Mental app.</description></item><item><title>#278 — The Man Who Will Be King | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070074/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 00:10:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks to Graeme Wood about Muhammed bin Salman, the crown prince of Saudi Arabia. They discuss the murder of Jamal Khashoggi, the imprisonment of Saudi elites in the Ritz Carlton, the Vision 2030 campaign, relations with Israel, the posture of the Biden administration, energy policy, Saudi efforts to deprogram jihadists, the strange case of Musa Cerantonio, John Walker Lindh, the current condition of ISIS, the war in Ukraine, Russian propaganda, how Finland has made itself invasion-proof, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#277 — How Does the War in Ukraine End? | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070075/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 19:19:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Ian Bremmer about the ongoing war in Ukraine. They discuss the current state of the war, the power of sanctions, Biden's "gaffe" about regime change, fear of nuclear war, the logic of mutually assured destruction, the role of China, the most likely outcomes of the war, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#276 — Defending the Global Order | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070076/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 23:43:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Yuval Noah Harari about the wider implications of Russia’s war of conquest in Ukraine. They discuss different forms of war, Putin’s miscalculation regarding the internal divisions of America and the EU, the problem of misinformation, international norms of behavior, the role of China, the civilizational importance of trust, globalization and de-globalization, existential risk, the role of India, Ukrainian leadership, the danger of nuclear war, regime change in Russia, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#275 — The Russian War in Ukraine | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070077/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 20:31:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Garry Kasparov about Putin’s war of aggression in Ukraine. They discuss Putin’s larger objectives, the perception of the war inside Russia, whether US and EU foreign policy is to blame, the expansion of NATO, American weakness, Republican support for Putin, the sanctions regime, whether the US and EU should impose a no-fly zone over Ukraine, whether to openly seek regime change in Russia, how we can avoid WW3, what post-Putin government in Russia might look like, Western economic entanglement with autocracies, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>Absolutely Mental Season 3 | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070078/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 19:17:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam shares an episode from the third season of Absolutely Mental, his audio series with Ricky Gervais. All 10 episodes have been released today (Wednesday, March 2, 2022) and are available for purchase now at AbsolutelyMental.com.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Special Episode: Recipes for Future Plagues | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070079/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 18:35:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070079/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of the podcast, Rob Reid and Kevin Esvelt discuss USAID’s new “Deep VZN” program, which aims to discover new pandemic-grade viruses and publish their genomes to the world. Esvelt estimates that there are currently around 30,000 people who could then easily build them.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#274 — The Future of American Democracy | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070080/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 18:16:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Anne Applebaum, David Frum, Barton Gellman, and George Packer about the ongoing threat to American democracy posed by Republican misinformation and disinformation regarding the 2020 Presidential Election and the attack on the Capitol on January 6th, 2021.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Learning how to train your mind is the single greatest investment you can make in life.</description></item><item><title>#273 — Joe Rogan and the Ethics of Apology | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070081/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 20:19:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam responds to the controversy over his friend Joe Rogan's use of the N-word and his subsequent public apology.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Vaccine Mandates, transgender athletes, billionaires… (AMA #19) | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070082/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 20:26:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Questions:
What is your position on vaccine mandates, school closures, etc.?
Do you think painful memories remain painful because there is something left unresolved?
How can you forgive a consequential lie?
Can you clarify your plans to support effective altruism with NFTs?
What are your views on transgender women in sports?
How can we combat disinformation and misinformation coming from friends and family?
You’ve said that we shouldn’t demonize billionaires, but is it really possible to become that wealthy without perpetuating the evils of capitalism?</description></item><item><title>#272 — On Disappointing My Audience | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070083/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 01:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam discusses some of the topics he has and hasn't covered, to the disappointment of many Making Sense listeners.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Learning how to train your mind is the single greatest investment you can make in life. That’s why Sam Harris created the Waking Up app. From rational mindfulness practice to lessons on some of life’s most important topics, join Sam as he demystifies the practice of meditation and explores the theory behind it.</description></item><item><title>#271 — Earning to Give | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070084/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Dec 2021 19:16:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070084/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of the podcast, Sam Harris speaks with Sam Bankman-Fried about effective altruism. They discuss how he became the wealthiest self-made billionaire under 30, what might go wrong with cryptocurrency, the Giving What We Can pledge, how SBF thinks about using his resources to do the most good in the world, how not to stigmatize wealth, wealth redistribution, norms of generosity among the ultra-wealthy, pandemic preparedness, impact through lobbying, how ambitious should we be in doing good, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#270 — What Have We Learned from the Pandemic? | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070085/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 17:37:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Nicholas Christakis about the lessons of the COVID pandemic. They discuss our failures to coordinate an effective response, the politics surrounding vaccination, vaccine efficacy, vaccine safety, how to think about scientific controversies, the epidemiology of excess deaths, transmission among the vaccinated, natural immunity, selection pressures and new variants, the failure of institutions, the lab-leak hypothesis, the efficacy of lockdowns, vaccine mandates, boosters, what would happen in a worse pandemic, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#269 — Deep Time | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070086/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 18:18:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Oliver Burkeman about our relationship to time. They discuss the perils of efficiency, being vs becoming, the illusion of time as a resource, parenting and childhood, work-life balance, the loss of leisure, the planning trap, social isolation, a modern Sabbath, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#268 — The Limits of Self-Knowledge | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070087/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 17:53:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Stephen Fleming about the neuroscience of self-awareness. They discuss the nature and limits of metacognition, the relationship between self-knowledge and intelligence, error monitoring, theory of mind, mirror neurons, deception and self-deception, false confidence, probabilistic reasoning, where metacognition fails, cognitive decline, calibrating one’s confidence, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#267 — The Kingdom of Sleep | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070088/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 18:50:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Matthew Walker about the nature and importance of sleep. They discuss sleep and consciousness, the stages of sleep, sleep regularity, light and temperature, the evolutionary origins of sleep, reducing sleep, the connection between poor sleep and all-cause mortality (as well as Alzheimer’s disease, diabetes, obesity, and heart disease), sleep across species, learning and memory, mental health, dreams as therapy, lucid dreaming, heart-rate variability, REM-sleep behavior disorder and parasomnias, meditation and sleep, sleep hygiene, different types of insomnia, caffeine and alcohol, sleep efficiency, bedtime restriction, cognitive-behavioral therapy, napping, sleep tracking, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#266 — The Limits of Pleasure | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070089/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 19:29:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Paul Bloom about the role that pain and suffering play in living a good life. They discuss the limitations of hedonism, the connection between chosen suffering and meaning, the research of Daniel Kahneman on well-being, integrating the experiencing and remembering selves, moral motivations, the effects of parenthood on happiness, unchosen suffering, the asymmetry of loss and gain, Nozick’s “experience machine” thought experiment, effective altruism, valuing the future more than the past, the power of contrast, false ideals of happiness, polyamory, money and status, the role of the imagination, boredom, the power of apology, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#265 — The Religion of Anti-Racism | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070090/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 16:08:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with John McWhorter about his new book “Woke Racism: How a New Religion has Betrayed Black America.” They discuss how the “social justice” narrative of the Left has become a religion, how this new faith has taken over institutions, and what to do about it.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#264 — Consciousness and Self (Rebroadcast) | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070091/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 17:36:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Anil Seth about the scientific study of consciousness, where consciousness emerges in nature, levels of consciousness, perception as a “controlled hallucination,” emotion, the experience of “pure consciousness,” consciousness as “integrated information,” measures of “brain complexity,” psychedelics, different aspects of the “self,” conscious AI, and many other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#263 — The Paradox of Death | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070092/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 15:56:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris reflects on the subjective continuity of consciousness, the nature of identity, and the possibility that death isn’t the end of experience.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Learning how to train your mind is the single greatest investment you can make in life. That’s why Sam Harris created the Waking Up app.</description></item><item><title>#262 — The Future of American Democracy | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070093/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 23:21:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Andrew Yang about the state of American democracy. They discuss Andrew’s run for the Presidency, the humiliations of campaigning, the manipulation of politics by the media, Andrew's run for the mayor's office in NYC, the power of bad incentives, open primaries, rank-choice voting, the Forward Party, the weakness of a two-party system, inequality, the child tax credit, enhanced unemployment, UBI, worries about inflation, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#261 — Belief &amp; Identity | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070094/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 23:19:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Jonas Kaplan about the neuroscience of belief change. They discuss the illusory truth effect, the backfire effect, failures of replication, “The Fireplace Delusion,” the connection between reason and emotion, wishful thinking, persuasion and the sense of self, conspiracy theories, the power of incentives, in-group loyalty, religion, mindfulness, cognitive flexibility, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>Absolutely Mental Season Two | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070095/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 19:25:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam shares a clip from the second season of Absolutely Mental, his audio series with Ricky Gervais. All 10 episodes have been released today (Friday September 24th, 2021) and are available for purchase at AbsolutelyMental.com.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ask Me Anything #18 | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070096/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 16:09:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Questions answered:
Why won’t you discuss COVID vaccines and Ivermectin with Bret Weinstein on the podcast?
What do you think about the recent prosecution of a 100-year-old Nazi in Germany?
How can we understand voluntary behavior without free will?
Does aid to the developing world do more harm than good?
Have your views about the risk of artificial general intelligence changed in recent years?
What did you think of Simon Biles’s decision to drop out of the Olympics?</description></item><item><title>#260 — The Second Plane | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070097/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 21:43:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris recalls his experience of September 11th, 2001, and considers the future of American foreign policy.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#259 — The Reckoning to Come | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070098/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 01:11:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Balaji Srinivasan about several civilizational challenges and possible paths forward. They discuss the evidence of American decline, the rise of India and China, centralizing and decentralizing trends in politics, the relationship between politics and technology, the failures of the FDA and TSA, how regulation preserves monopolies, the significance of Bitcoin and blockchain technology, the problem of cybersecurity, the Chinese government’s attack on Bitcoin, the threat of US regulation of cryptocurrency, blockchain scalability, creator coins, life in Singapore, virtual government, the future of decentralized journalism, independent replication in science, wealth inequality, ubiquitous investing, social status, non-zero-sum capitalism, “start-up countries”, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#258 — The Fall of Afghanistan | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070099/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 01:06:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Peter Bergen about the US exit from Afghanistan, the resurgence of the Taliban, and his new book, “The Rise and Fall of Osama bin Laden.” They discuss the Neo-isolationist consensus on the Right and Left, the legitimacy of our initial involvement in Afghanistan, our ethical obligations to our Afghan allies, Biden’s disastrous messaging, the weakness of the Afghan army, the advantages of the Taliban, the implications for global jihadism, the relationship between the Taliban and al-Qaeda, how Osama bin Laden came to lead al-Qaeda, bin Laden’s sincere religious convictions, our failure to capture bin Laden at Tora Bora, the distraction of the war in Iraq, the myth that the CIA funded al-Qaeda, bin Laden’s wives, his years of hiding in Pakistan, his death at the hands of US Special Forces, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#257 — The State of the World | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070100/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 22:11:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Dambisa Moyo about the state of the world. They discuss public goods, economic growth, capitalism, American economic history, bad public-policy choices, inequality, tax avoidance among the wealthy, government inefficiency, the problems with democracy, the breakdown of trust in institutions, failures of transparency, voter participation, future automation and unemployment, identity politics, the reality of racism in America, the problems with affirmative action, competition with China, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>Ask Me Anything #17 | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070101/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 16:25:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070101/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of the podcast, Sam takes your questions. He begins by addressing the blowback that followed his previous podcast on “vaccine hesitancy” with Eric Topol. And then he answers the following questions:
How can I inoculate my biracial children against identity politics?
In what way is journalism broken, and how can we fix it?
Have you read the research suggesting that the effects of microdosing psychedelics are indistinguishable from taking placebos?</description></item><item><title>#256 — A Contagion of Bad Ideas | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070102/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 16:33:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Eric Topol about vaccine hesitancy and related misinformation. They discuss the problem of political and social siloing, concerns about mRNA vaccines, the Emergency Use Authorization by the FDA, the effectiveness of the COVID vaccines, vaccine efficacy vs effectiveness, the Delta variant, the misuse of the Vaccine Adverse Event Reporting System (VAERS), concerns about long-term side effects from vaccines, bad incentives in medicine, ivermectin, government and corporate censorship, vaccine mandates, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#255 — The Future of Intelligence | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070103/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 17:36:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Jeff Hawkins about the nature of intelligence. They discuss how the neocortex creates models of the world, the role of prediction in sensory-motor experience, cortical columns, reference frames, thought as movement in conceptual space, the future of artificial intelligence, AI risk, the “alignment problem,” the distinction between reason and emotion, the “illusory truth effect,” bad outcomes vs existential risk, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#254 — The Mating Strategies of Earthlings | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070104/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 20:20:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with David Buss about the differential mating strategies of men and women. They discuss the controversy that surrounds evolutionary psychology, the denial of sex differences, cross-cultural findings in social science, the replication crisis in psychology, the biological definition of sex, why men and women have affairs, ovulatory shifts in mate preference, sex differences in jealousy and infidelity, the sources of unhappiness in marriage, mate-value discrepancies, what we can learn from dating apps, polyamory and polygamy, the plight of stepchildren, the “Dark Triad” personality type, the MeToo movement, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#253 — Corporate Courage | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070105/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 20:01:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Jason Fried about the recent controversy over the “no politics” policy at his company Basecamp. They discuss his business philosophy, the surrender of institutions to "social-justice" activism, how politics has acquired a religious fervor, some of the cultural risks of remote work, keeping activists out of one’s company, social media use as analogous to smoking cigarettes, antitrust regulations for big tech, how social media might be improved, the tax-avoidance schemes of the richest Americans, the prospect of implementing a wealth tax, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#252 — Are We Alone in the Universe? | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070106/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 19:40:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Neil deGrasse Tyson about our place in the universe. They discuss our current understanding of extra-solar planets, the prospect that there is complex life elsewhere in the galaxy, the Fermi problem, the possibility that all advanced civilizations self destruct, how we can detect life on exoplanets, recent media interest in UFOs, whether a direct encounter with alien life would change our world, the flat-Earth conspiracy, the public understanding of science, the problem of political partisanship, racial inequality, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#251 — Corporate Cowardice | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070107/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 22:50:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Antonio García-Martínez about his recent firing at Apple. They discuss his experience in tech, his book "Chaos Monkeys," the controversy at Apple, cancel culture, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Learning how to train your mind is the single greatest investment you can make in life.</description></item><item><title>#250 — Broken Conversations | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070108/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 17:17:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Jesse Singal about a variety of controversial topics. They discuss fragmentation in the media, bad incentives in journalism, Jesse’s encounters with cancel culture, transgender activism, the case of J.K. Rowling, the capture of cultural institutions by the far Left, racism, class inequality, the conflict between Israel and the Palestinians, whether Jesse should try psychedelics, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#249 — Distance &amp; Arrival | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070109/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 14:31:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris and David Whyte further explore his work in his book Consolations: The Solace, Nourishment and Underlying Meaning of Everyday Words.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#248 — Order &amp; Freedom | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070110/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 20:04:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Michele Gelfand about the difference between tight and loose cultures. They discuss the primacy of cultural norms in governing human behavior, the trade-offs between order and freedom, conservatism vs liberalism, sensitivity to threat, scarcity, the COVID pandemic, the Jeffrey Toobin affair, political polarization, the problem of extreme stereotypes, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>Special Episode: Engineering the Apocalypse | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070111/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 00:35:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070111/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this nearly 4-hour SPECIAL EPISODE, Rob Reid delivers a 100-minute monologue (broken up into 4 segments, and interleaved with discussions with Sam) about the looming danger of a man-made pandemic, caused by an artificially-modified pathogen. The risk of this occurring is far higher and nearer-term than almost anyone realizes. Rob explains the science and motivations that could produce such a catastrophe and explores the steps that society must start taking today to prevent it.</description></item><item><title>#247 — Constructing Minds | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070112/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 01:32:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Lisa Feldman Barrett about the origins and function of the human brain. They discuss how brains evolved, the myth of the “triune brain,” the brain’s network organization, the predictive nature of perception and action, the construction of emotion, concepts as prescriptions for action, culture as an operating system, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#246 — Police Training &amp; Police Misconduct | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070113/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 14:52:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Rener Gracie about police procedure and about the special relevance of Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu for safely controlling resisting suspects.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#245 — Can We Talk About Scary Ideas? | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070114/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 23:13:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Peter Singer, Francesca Minerva, and Jeff McMahan about the newly launched Journal of Controversial Ideas. They discuss the ethics of discussing dangerous ideas, the possibility of having a market in vaccines, the taboo around the topic of race and IQ, the relationship between activism and academia, the shallow-pond argument for doing good, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#244 — Food, Climate, and Pandemic Risk | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070115/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 23:52:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Bruce Friedrich and Liz Specht from the Good Food Institute about the way the problems of climate change and pandemic risk are directly connected to animal agriculture. The Good Food Institute is an international nonprofit reimagining protein production.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#243 — A Few Points of Confusion | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070116/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 15:03:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070116/</guid><description>Podcast Description If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#242 — Psychedelics and the Self | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070117/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 23:47:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with James Fadiman about the psychedelic experience. They discuss who should and shouldn’t take psychedelics, set and setting, the role of a guide, the effects of microdosing, the difference between MDMA and true psychedelics, “good” and “bad” trips, the power of thought, the fiction of a unified self, changing states of self, compassion, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#241 — Final Thoughts on Free Will | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070118/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 23:33:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070118/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris presents his full argument on the illusoriness of free will—and explores its ethical and psychological implications.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#240 — The Boundaries of Self | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070119/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 22:45:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam speaks with poet David Whyte about his new and on-going series for the Waking Up app, based on his book, Consolations: The Solace, Nourishment and Underlying Meaning of Everyday Words.
With the imagery of a poet and the reflection of a philosopher, David turns his attention to ordinary words, each a doorway into the underlying currents of human life.
They discuss 4 tracks from the first installment—Friendship, Honesty, Ambition, and Alone.</description></item><item><title>#239 — Yet Another Call from Ricky Gervais | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070120/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 22:36:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070120/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ricky Gervais calls Sam to ask if AI will replace comedians. They also discuss the implications of not having free will and if a chimp has ever asked, "what does it all mean?" They agree that bears are dangerous.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#238 — How to Build a Universe | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070121/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 00:48:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Frank Wilczek about the fundamental nature of reality. They discuss the difference between science and non-science, the role of intuition in science, the nature of time, the prospect that possibility is an illusion, the current limits of quantum mechanics, the uncertainty principle, space-time as a substance, the “unreasonable effectiveness” of mathematics in science, the possibility that we might be living in a simulation, the fundamental building blocks of matter, the structure of atoms, the four fundamental forces, wave-particle duality, the electromagnetic spectrum, the many-worlds interpretation of quantum mechanics, the implications of infinite space-time, dark energy and dark matter, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#237 — Another Call from Ricky Gervais | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070122/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 23:56:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070122/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ricky Gervais calls to discuss Sam's monster joke from their last conversation and then other things happen...
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#236 — Rebooting New York City | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070123/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 22:34:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070123/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with mayoral candidate, Andrew Yang, about the future of New York City.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#235 — A Call from Ricky Gervais | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070124/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 17:59:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ricky Gervais calls Sam to ask why we dream? They discuss why puns are terrible and breakdown some of the mechanics of comedy.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#234 — The Divided Mind | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070125/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 23:27:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Iain McGilchrist about the differences between the right and left hemispheres of the human brain. They discuss the evolutionary history of the divided brain, research on surgically divided brains, popular misconceptions about the differences between the hemispheres, the left hemisphere's propensity for confabulation, the prospect that consciousness might be partitioned in an intact brain, the difference between consciousness and attention, the boundary between the conscious and unconscious mind, how face-to-face encounters differ between the hemispheres, the unique deficits resulting from damage to the left and right hemispheres, the ascendancy of the left-hemisphere in modern culture, the possibility that the brain is a mere receiver of mind, the prospect of surviving death, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#233 — The Groves of Misinformation | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070126/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 01:38:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Zeynep Tufekci about the problem of misinformation and group-think. They discuss the Covid-19 pandemic, the early failures of journalists and public health professionals to make sense of it, the sociology of mask wearing, the problem of correcting institutional errors, Covid as a dress rehearsal for something far worse, asymmetric information warfare, failures of messaging about vaccines, the paradox of scientific authority, the power of incentives, how to reform social media, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#232 — Inequality and Revolution | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070127/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 03:22:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Jack Goldstone about the rise in social inequality and political instability in the United States. They discuss how wealth is deployed, the loss of social mobility, comparative judgments of well-being, cosmopolitanism and the isolation of the rich, decreased life expectancy, taxation, the need for government to solve problems, success and social obligation, the causes of revolution, universal basic income (UBI), and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#231 — Crossing the Abyss | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070128/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 19:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070128/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with General Stanley McChrystal and Chris Fussell about the radicalization of the far Right under Trump. They discuss the events of January 6, 2021, the behavior of the Capitol police, the history of white supremacy in the US, the effect of banning extremists from social media, the logic of insurgency, the consequence of public lies, what should happen to Trump and his enablers, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#230 — An Insurrection of Lies | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070129/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 19:57:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070129/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris discusses two dangerous misconceptions about the siege of the Capitol.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#229 — A Few Thoughts for a New Year | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070130/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 00:37:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070130/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris analyzes a few disturbing trends and shares his hopes for 2021.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#228 — Doing Good | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070131/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 20:35:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Will MacAskill about how to do the most good in the world. They discuss the "effective altruism" movement, choosing causes to support, the apparent tension between wealth and altruism, how best to think about generosity over the course of one's lifetime, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#227 — Knowing the Mind | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070132/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 21:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070132/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stephen Laureys interviews Sam Harris about meditation practice and the scientific study of the mind. They discuss why Sam began to practice meditation, the difference between dualistic and nondualistic mindfulness, the search for happiness, wisdom vs knowledge, our relationship with death, the Buddhist doctrine of rebirth, the hard problem of consciousness, the role of introspection in science, meditation and free will, the self and the brain, the difference between voluntary and involuntary actions, dangerous knowledge, the mystery of being, the power of hypnosis, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>Making Sense with Sam Harris | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070133/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 15:55:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join Sam Harris as he explores some of the most important questions about the human mind, society, and current events.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#226 — The Price of Distraction | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070134/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 23:04:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Adam Gazzaley about the way our technology is changing us. They discuss our limited ability to process information, our failures of multitasking, "top-down" vs "bottom-up" attention, self-interruptions and switching costs, anxiety, boredom, "digital medicine," neuroplasticity, video games for training the mind, the future of brain-machine interface, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#225 — Republic of Lies | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070135/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 22:54:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris discusses President Trump's failure to concede the 2020 presidential election.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#224 — The Key to Trump's Appeal | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070136/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 02:20:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070136/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris describes his new understanding of why people support President Trump.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#223 — A Conversation with Andrew Sullivan | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070137/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 20:58:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris and Andrew Sullivan sing the praises of President Trump.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#222 — A Pandemic of Incompetence | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070138/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:18:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070138/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Nicholas Christakis about the Covid-19 pandemic. They discuss the breakdown of trust in institutions and experts, the corruption of science by politics, the ineptitude of the Trump administration in handling the pandemic, whether the gravity of Covid-19 has been exaggerated, preparing for future pandemics, whether Covid deaths are being over-reported, bad incentives in the medical system, tracking "excess death" statistics, the prospect that the novel coronavirus will evolve to become more benign, the efficacy of current treatments, safety concerns about a rushed vaccine, the importance of public health communication, when life might return to normal, the economic impact of the pandemic, long term social changes, the future of universities, Nicholas's personal habits during the pandemic, the importance of rapid testing, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#221 — Success, Failure, &amp; the Common Good | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070139/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 21:10:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Michael Sandel about the problem with meritocracy . They discuss the dark side of the concept of merit, the pernicious myth of the self-made man, the moral significance of luck, the backlash against "elites" and expertise, how we value human excellence, the connection between wealth and value creation, the ethics of the tax code, higher education as a sorting mechanism for a caste system, alternatives to 4-year colleges, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#220 - The Information Apocalypse | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070140/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2020 16:25:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070140/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Nina Schick about the growing epidemic of misinformation and disinformation. They discuss the coming problem of “deep fakes,” the history of Russian “active measures” against the West, the weaponization of the EU migration crisis, Russian targeting of the African-American community, the future of Europe, Trump and rise of political cynicism, QAnon, the prospect of violence surrounding the 2020 Presidential election, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#219 — The Power of Compassion | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070141/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 23:21:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with James R. Doty about his memoir “Into the Magic Shop.” They discuss the significance of childhood stress, the possibility of changing one’s core beliefs about oneself, the relationship between surgeons and their patients, the nature of compassion, the Dalai Lama, the relationship between wealth and empathy, the worsening problem of social inequality, the physiology of compassion, the broken healthcare system in the U.S., and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#218 — Welcome to the Cult Factory | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070142/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 23:51:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070142/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of the podcast, Sam Harris speaks with Tristan Harris about the ways in which social media is fracturing society. They discuss the rise in teen depression and suicide, political polarization, conspiracy theories, information warfare, the decoupling of power and responsibility, the distinctions between platforms and publishers, the cancellation of Alex Jones, social media-inspired ethnic cleansing, concerns about the upcoming presidential election, culture as an operating system, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#217 — The New Religion of Anti-Racism | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070143/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 22:45:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070143/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with John McWhorter about race, racism, and “anti-racism” in America. They discuss how conceptions of racism have changed, the ubiquitous threat of being branded a “racist,” the contradictions within identity politics, recent echoes of the OJ verdict, willingness among progressives to lose the 2020 election, racism as the all-purpose explanation of racial disparities in the U.S., double standards for the black community, the war on drugs, the lure of identity politics, police violence, the enduring riddle of affirmative action, the politics of “black face,” and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#216 — A Conversation with Graeme Wood | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070144/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 22:13:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070144/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Graeme Wood about the breakdown of social order in the U.S. They discuss the recent eruptions of violence, the loss of trust in the media, the cases of Jacob Blake and Kyle Rittenhouse, how to understand police videos, the risks of vigilantism, the politicization of race, the problem of deep fakes, Trump not actually wanting to be president, the prospect that Trump might attempt to pardon himself, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#215 — A Conversation with David Miliband | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070145/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 21:54:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070145/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with David Miliband about his work with the International Rescue Committee. They discuss the crisis of internally displaced peoples and refugees, the problem with open borders, the vetting of refugees, the limits of nation-building and diplomacy, the realities of globalization, global risks, defending human rights, a “post-values and post-competence” America, the breakdown of trust in institutions, the prospects of a second Trump term, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#214 — A Conversation with Siddhartha Mukherjee | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070146/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 21:01:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070146/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Siddhartha Mukherjee about our ongoing failure to adequately respond to the Covid-19 pandemic. They discuss the significance of asymptomatic spread, the lack of Chinese cooperation, the failures of testing, travel restrictions, the missteps of the FDA and the CDC, controversy around masks, the lack of coordination among the states, conspiracy thinking about mortality statistics, the political contamination of public health information, electronic medical records, preparing for the next pandemic, the immunology of Covid-19, the long term consequences of the disease, concerns about a vaccine, the coming prospect of school openings, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#213 — The Worst Epidemic | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070147/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 01:06:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070147/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Gabriel Dance about the global epidemic of child sexual abuse. They discuss how misleading the concept of “child pornography” is, the failure of governments and tech companies to grapple with the problem, the tradeoff between online privacy and protecting children, the National Center for Missing and Exploited Children, photo DNA, the roles played by specific tech companies, the ethics of encryption, “sextortion,” the culture of pedophiles, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#212 — A Conversation with Kathryn Paige Harden | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070148/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 22:59:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070148/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Kathryn Paige Harden about public controversy over group differences in traits like intelligence and ongoing research in behavioral genetics. They discuss Harden’s criticism of the Making Sense episode featuring Charles Murray, the mingling of scientific thinking with politics and social activism, cancel culture, environmental and genetic contributions to individual and group differences, intellectual honesty, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#211 — The Nature of Human Nature | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070149/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 17:53:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070149/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Robert Plomin about the role that DNA plays in determining who we are. They discuss the birth of behavioral genetics, the taboo around studying the influence of genes on human psychology, controversies surrounding the topic of group differences, the first law of behavior genetics, heritability, nature and nurture, the mystery of non-shared environment, the way genes help determine a person's environment, epigenetics, the genetics of complex traits, dimensions vs disorders, the prospect of a GATTACA-like dystopia and genetic castes, heritability and equality of opportunity, the implications of genetics for parenting and education, DNA as a fortune-telling device, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#210 — The Logic of Doomsday | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070150/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 18:12:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070150/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with William J. Perry and Lisa Perry about the ever-present threat of nuclear war. They discuss the history of nuclear weapons, the bombing of Hiroshima and Nagasaki, the Cuban Missile Crisis, the present threat of accidental nuclear war, nuclear terrorism, unilateral disarmament, the psychology of deterrence, tactical nuclear weapons, cybersecurity, details of command and control, nuclear proliferation, the steps we could take toward safety, strategic missile defense, nuclear winter, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#209 — A Good Life | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070151/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 23:50:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070151/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Scott Barry Kaufman about human well-being. They discuss intelligence and creativity, wisdom and transcendence, the history of humanistic psychology, Maslow's hierarchy of needs, the connection between well-being and ethics, self-esteem, psychedelics and meditation, peak and plateau experiences, mortality salience, the pre-trans fallacy, fear of uncertainty, work and meaning, intrinsic vs. extrinsic rewards, pathological altruism, intimacy vs. belonging, two aspects of self-transcendence, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#208 — Existential Risk | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070152/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 20:14:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070152/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Toby Ord about preserving the long term future of humanity. They discuss moral biases with respect to distance in space and time, the psychology of effective altruism, feeling good vs doing good, possible blindspots in consequentialism, natural vs human-caused risk, asteroid impacts, nuclear war, pandemics, the potentially cosmic significance of human survival, the difference between bad things and the absence of good things, population ethics, Derek Parfit, the asymmetry between happiness and suffering, climate change, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#207 — Can We Pull Back From The Brink? | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070153/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2020 00:09:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070153/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam discusses the recent social protests and civil unrest, in light of what we know about racism and police violence in America.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#206 — A Conversation with David Frum | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070154/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 21:03:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070154/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with David Frum about the shifting political landscape. They discuss the secularization of politics, distrust of the media and other institutions, voter suppression, the 2020 elections, what happens if Trump gets a second term, the role of money in politics, conspiracy theories around Covid-19, the Michael Flynn controversy, the prospect that Trump will refuse to leave office, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#205 — The Failure of Meritocracy | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070155/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 19:40:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070155/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Daniel Markovits about the problems with meritocracy. They discuss the nature of inequality in the United States, the disappearance of the leisure class, the difference between labor and capital as sources of inequality, the way the education system amplifies inequality, the shrinking middle class, deaths of despair, differing social norms among the elite and the working class, the ethics of taxation, scales of philanthropy, universal basic income, the need for a wealth tax, the relationship between meritocracy and political polarization, the illusion of earned advantages, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#204 — A Conversation with Jonathan Haidt | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070156/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 14:31:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070156/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Jonathan Haidt about the maintenance of a healthy society. They discuss the problem of orthodoxy, the history of political polarization in the US, the breakdown of public conversation, remaining uncertainty about Covid-19, motivated reasoning, the 2020 election, the future prospects for Gen Z, the effect of social media on the mental health of girls, Jonathan's experience with psychedelics, positive psychology, loss of self, the experience of awe, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#203 — A Conversation with Caitlin Flanagan | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070157/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 23:40:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070157/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Caitlin Flanagan about her cancer recurrence and the response to her recent article in The Atlantic discussing it. They discuss the dynamics of apologies and forgiveness, the #MeToo movement and the allegations against Biden, modern feminism, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#202 — A Conversation with Andrew Yang | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070158/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 16:22:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070158/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Andrew Yang about the Covid-19 pandemic. They discuss the future of the middle class, Andrew’s experience campaigning for President, the need to build new digital infrastructure, universal basic income (UBI), concerns about the Biden’s age and #MeToo allegation, hostility between the United States and China, problems with the global supply chain, concerns about social cohesion, market failures, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#201 — A Conversation with Yuval Noah Harari | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070159/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 20:06:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070159/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Yuval Noah Harari about the Covid-19 pandemic and its future implications. They discuss the failures of global leadership, the widespread distrust of institutions, the benefits of nationalism and its current unraveling in the U.S., politics as a way of reconciling competing desires, the consequences of misinformation, the enduring respect for science, the future of surveillance, the changing role of religion, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#200 — Creatures of Habit | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070160/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 21:47:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070160/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with James Clear about habit formation. They discuss the difference between creating good habits and discontinuing bad ones, the role of the environment, the misalignment between immediate and long term outcomes, the remembering self vs the experiencing self, goals vs systems, the compounding of incremental gains, the role of attention, the four laws of behavior change, “temptation bundling,” and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#199 — A Conversation with Caitlin Flanagan | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070161/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 00:09:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070161/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris and Caitlin Flanagan discuss the ethics of abortion, the fact that universities with immense endowments are laying off staff during the Covid-19 pandemic, the Woody Allen autobiography, the moral hypocrisy of Hollywood, the lessons of "Tiger King," and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#198 — A Conversation with Paul Bloom | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070162/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 22:41:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070162/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris and Paul Bloom discuss the false tradeoff between the economy and public health, putting a price on human life, framing effects for moral questions, how Covid-19 may change human behavior, "turn-key totalitarianism," the future of education, the long term psychological effects of the pandemic, the 2020 election, the prospect that Sanders supporters won't vote for Biden, and what Sam means when he says "the self is an illusion,"</description></item><item><title>#197 — A Conversation with Caitlin Flanagan | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070163/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 23:04:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070163/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Caitlin Flanagan. They discuss the different sorts of experiences people are having during the Covid-19 pandemic, what it has exposed about our education system, the 2020 election and the many problems with Joe Biden, why the press has been slow to cover Biden’s #MeToo allegation, the perceived double standards in the press and within feminism, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#196 — The Science of Happiness | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070164/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 19:30:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070164/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Laurie Santos about the scientific study of happiness. They discuss people’s expectations about happiness, the experiencing self vs the remembered self, framing effects, the importance of social connections, the effect of focusing on the happiness of others, introversion and extroversion, the influence of technology on social life, our relationship to time, the connection between happiness and ethics, hedonic adaptation, the power of mindfulness, resilience, the often illusory significance of reaching goals, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#195 — Social Cohesion is Everything | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070165/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 18:25:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070165/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with General Stanley McChrystal and Chris Fussell about the Covid-19 pandemic. They discuss the nature of the ongoing crisis, the threat of a breakdown in social order, the problem of misinformation, the prospects of a nationwide lockdown, the trade off between personal freedom and safety, the threat of tyranny, the concerns about the global supply chain, concerns about the price of oil, safeguarding the 2020 Presidential election, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#194 — The New Future of Work | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070166/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 01:27:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070166/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Matt Mullenweg about the evolution of distributed work. They discuss the benefits of working from home, the new norms of knowledge work, relevant tools and security concerns, the challenges for managers, the importance of written communication, the necessity of innovating in response to the Covid-19 pandemic, delivery networks as critical infrastructure, economic recovery, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#193 — Meditation in an Emergency | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070167/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 18:09:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070167/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks about social contagion and about the importance of understanding one's own mind in an emergency.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#192 — A Conversation with Paul Bloom | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070168/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 21:55:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070168/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris and Paul Bloom speak about the psychology of adapting to the coronavirus pandemic, the disastrous analogy between coronavirus and flu, the political siloing of information, true and false concerns over "panic," pressuring China to close down their live animal markets, the economic implications and possible silver linings of the pandemic, what our response suggests about our ability to deal with climate change, Biden vs Sanders, the ethics of praising one's enemies, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#191 — Early Thoughts on a Pandemic | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070169/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 15:55:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070169/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Amesh Adalja about the spreading coronavirus pandemic. They discuss the contagiousness of the virus and the severity of the resultant illness, the mortality rate and risk factors, vectors of transmission, how long coronavirus can live on surfaces, the importance of social distancing, possible anti-viral treatments, the timeline for a vaccine, the importance of pandemic preparedness, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#190 — How Should We Respond to Coronavirus? | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070170/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 13:07:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070170/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Nicholas Christakis about the coronavirus pandemic. They discuss the likely effects on society, proactive vs reactive school closures, community transmission, false comparisons between coronavirus and flu, the imperative of social distancing, the timeline of the pandemic, Trump’s political messaging, the widespread distrust of expertise, the importance of "flattening the curve" of the epidemic, the possible failure of our healthcare system, gradations of personal response to this threat, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#189 — Wealth &amp; Happiness | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070171/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 20:24:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070171/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Scott Galloway about the connection between wealth and happiness. They discuss the problem of wealth inequality, the transfer of wealth from the young to the old, class warfare in Democratic politics, deficit spending, means testing Social Security, Bloomberg’s campaign and “stop and frisk,” breaking up big tech, privacy absolutism, meditation, mortality, atheism, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#188 — A Conversation with Paul Bloom | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070172/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 14:34:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070172/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris and Paul Bloom speak about the virtues of President Trump, the campaign prospects of Bloomberg and Sanders, the asymmetrical norms of the Democratic and Republican parties, the marginal role that parents play in the development of their children, wealth inequality and the breakdown of the nuclear family, whether Paul should take LSD, the deplatforming of Peter Singer, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#187 — A Conversation with Paul Bloom | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070173/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 00:26:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070173/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris and Paul Bloom speak about the epidemic of child sexual abuse, the ethics of loyalty, eugenics, existential risk, the Bloomberg and Sanders campaigns, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#186 — The Bomb | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070174/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 00:22:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070174/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Fred Kaplan about the ever-present threat of nuclear war. They discuss the history of nuclear deterrence, U.S. first-strike policy, preventive war, limited nuclear war, tactical vs. strategic weapons, Trump’s beliefs about nuclear weapons, the details of command and control, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#185 — A Conversation with Paul Bloom | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070175/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 19:52:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070175/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris and Paul Bloom speak about "Trump Derangement Syndrome," inequality, the relationship between wealth and happiness, the downside of fame, psychological impediments to noticing progress, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#184 — The Conversational Nature of Reality | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070176/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 22:05:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070176/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with poet David Whyte about the importance of work and relationships, the balance between training and expressing of one's talents, the lessons of mortality, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#183 — A Conversation with Paul Bloom | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070177/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 21:41:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070177/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris and Paul Bloom discuss topics in the news including the tragic death of Kobe Bryant. They also explore the paradoxes of moral responsibility.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#182 — Unlearning Race | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070178/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 22:17:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070178/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Thomas Chatterton Williams about the reality and politics of race. They discuss his book “Self Portrait in Black and White,” race as a social and biological construct, the prospects of achieving a “post-racial” society, interracial marriage, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#181 — The Illusory Self | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070179/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 19:02:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070179/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Richard Lang about how to experience the world beyond the illusion of the self.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#180 — Sex &amp; Power | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070180/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 00:53:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Meghan Daum about her book “The Problem with Everything.” They discuss contemporary feminism, violence against women, campus sexual assault, moral panics, new norms of conversation, the 2020 Presidential campaign, and other topics. If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#179 — The Unquiet Mind | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070181/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 14:21:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070181/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Judson Brewer about addiction, craving, and mindfulness. They discuss the nature of reward-based learning, the role of subjective bias in addiction, the neuroscience of craving, the neural correlates of the sense of self, real-time neuroimaging, effort and effortlessness in meditation, smoking cessation through mindfulness, the difference between dopamine-driven reward and happiness, how to make meditation a habit, working with anxiety, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#178 — The Reality Illusion | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070182/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 21:36:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070182/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam and Annaka Harris speak with Donald Hoffman about his book “The Case Against Reality.” They discuss how evolution has failed to select for true perceptions of the world, his “interface theory” of perception, the primacy of math and logic, how space and time cannot be fundamental, the threat of epistemological skepticism, causality as a useful fiction, the hard problem of consciousness, agency, free will, panpsychism, a mathematics of conscious agents, philosophical idealism, death, psychedelics, the relationship between consciousness and mathematics, and many other topics.</description></item><item><title>#177 — Psychedelic Science | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070183/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 17:59:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070183/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Roland Griffiths about the current state of research on psychedelics. They discuss the historical prohibition against their use; the clinical and scientific promise of psilocybin, mescaline, LSD, DMT, MDMA, and other compounds; the risks associated with these drugs; the role of “set and setting”; the differences between psychedelics and drugs of abuse; MDMA and neurotoxicity; experiences of unity, sacredness, love, and truth; the long-term consequences of psychedelic experiences; synthetic vs natural drugs; the prospects of devising new psychedelics; microdosing; research on psilocybin and long-term meditators; the experience of encountering other apparent beings; psilocybin treatment of addiction; and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#176 — Knowledge &amp; Redemption | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070184/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2019 20:23:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070184/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Lynn Novick about her four-part documentary "College Behind Bars." The film follows the progress of students in the Bard Prison Initiative (BPI) as they pursue their undergraduate degrees. Sam and Lynn are joined by Jule Hall, a BPI graduate who served a 22-year sentence and is now working for the Ford Foundation.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#175 — Leaving the Faith | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070185/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 18:32:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070185/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Yasmine Mohammed about her book "Unveiled: How Western Liberals Empower Radical Islam." They discuss her family background and indoctrination into conservative Islam, the double standard that Western liberals use when thinking about women in the Muslim community, the state of feminism in general, honor violence, the validity of criticizing other cultures, and many other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#174 — Life &amp; Mind | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070186/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 16:46:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070186/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Richard Dawkins. They discuss the strangeness of the “gene’s-eye view" of the world, the limits of Darwinian thinking when applied to human life, the concept of the extended phenotype, ideologies as meme complexes, whether consciousness might be an epiphenomenon, psychedelics, meditation, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#173 — Anti-Semitism and Its Discontents | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070187/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 17:10:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070187/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Bari Weiss about her book “How to Fight anti-Semitism.” They discuss the three different strands of anti-Semitism (rightwing, leftwing, and Islamic), the Tree of Life shooting in Pittsburgh, the difference between anti-Semitism and other forms of racism, “Great Replacement Theory,” the populist response to globalization, the history of anti-Semitism in the U.S., criticisms of Israel, the fate of Jews in Western Europe, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#172 — Among the Deplorables | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070188/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 19:52:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070188/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Andrew Marantz about his book “Antisocial: Online Extremists, Techno-Utopians, and the Hijacking of the American Conversation." They discuss the effect of social media on politics, the distinction between publishers and platforms, the problem of guilt by association, getting too close to interview subjects, the confusing nature of troll culture, the notion of “dog whistles,” how to respond to the current reality of racism, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#171 — Escaping a Christian Cult | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070189/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 21:33:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070189/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Megan Phelps-Roper about her book "Unfollow: A Memoir of Loving and Leaving the Westboro Baptist Church."
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#170 — The Great Uncoupling | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070190/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 17:28:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070190/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Andrew McAfee about the history of human progress and the modern uncoupling of our prosperity from resource consumption. They discuss the pitfalls and hidden virtues of capitalism, technological progress, environmental policy, the future of the developing world, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#169 — Omens of a Race War | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070191/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 13:04:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070191/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Kathleen Belew about the white power movement in the United States. They discuss white supremacy, white nationalism, white separatism, the militia movement, “The Turner Diaries,” the connection between the white power movement and war, the significance of Ruby Ridge and Waco, the Christian Identity movement, the significance of “leaderless resistance,” the failures of the justice system in prosecuting white power crimes, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#168 — Mind, Space, &amp; Motion | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070192/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 18:13:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070192/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Barbara Tversky about how our senses of space and motion underlie our capacity for thought. They discuss the evolution of mind prior to language, the importance of imitation and gesture, the sensory and motor homunculi, the information communicated by motion, the role of “mirror neurons,” sense of direction, natural and unnatural categories, cognitive trade-offs, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#167 — A Few Thoughts on White Supremacy | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070193/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 16:22:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070193/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris addresses listener concerns that he uses a "double standard" to evaluate the relative threats of white supremacy and jihadism.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#166 — The Plague Years | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070194/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 04:57:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070194/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Matt McCarthy about his book "Superbugs: The Race to Stop an Epidemic." They discuss the problem of drug resistant bacteria, fungi, parasites, and viruses, and the failure of the pharmaceutical industry to keep pace with evolution.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#165 — Journey into Wokeness | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070195/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 01:18:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070195/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Caitlin Flanagan about her work as a writer. They discuss controversies on social media, the contradictions within feminism, media bias, #MeToo, the new norms of sexuality, the wokeness of academia, affirmative action, college admissions, HR departments, sexual harassment, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.</description></item><item><title>#164 — Cause &amp; Effect | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070196/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 13:02:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070196/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Judea Pearl about his work on the mathematics of causality and artificial intelligence. They discuss how science has generally failed to understand causation, different levels of causal inference, counterfactuals, the foundations of knowledge, the nature of possibility, the illusion of free will, artificial intelligence, the nature of consciousness, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#163 — Ricky Gervais | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070197/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 16:23:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070197/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Ricky Gervais. They discuss fame, the effect of social media, the changing state of comedy, offensive jokes, Louis CK, political hypocrisy, Brexit and Trump, the state of journalism, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#162 — Medical Intelligence | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070198/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 15:43:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070198/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Eric Topol about the way artificial intelligence can improve medicine. They talk about soaring medical costs and declining health outcomes in the U.S., the problems of too little and too much medicine, the culture of medicine, the travesty of electronic health records, the current status of AI in medicine, the promise of further breakthroughs, possible downsides of relying on AI in medicine, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#161 — Rise &amp; Fall | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070199/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 15:21:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070199/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Jared Diamond about the rise and fall of civilizations. They discuss political polarization, disparities in civilizational progress, the prospect that there may be biological differences between populations, the precariousness of democracy in the US, the lack of a strong political center, immigration policy, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#160 — The Revenge of History | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070200/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 15:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070200/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Michael Weiss and Yascha Mounk about the state of global politics. They discuss the rise of right-wing populism in Europe, the prospect that democracy could fail in the US, Trump’s political instincts, the political liability of “wokeness,” the Left’s failure to re-think its support of Chavez, the dangers of political polarization, the attractions of extreme partisanship, cancel culture, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#159 — Conscious | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070201/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 01:08:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070201/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with his wife, Annaka Harris, about her new book, "Conscious: A Brief Guide to the Fundamental Mystery of the Mind."
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#158 — Understanding Humans in the Wild | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070202/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 04:04:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070202/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Adam Grant about the social science of the workplace. They discuss how teams work effectively, the nature of power, personality types and fundamental styles of interaction, the critical skill of saying “no,” creativity, resilience, the strange case of Jonas Salk, the nature of mindfulness, the power of cognitive reappraisal, reflections on mortality, the replication crisis in social science, and other topics. If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#157 — What Does the Mueller Report Really Say? | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070203/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 15:31:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070203/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Benjamin Wittes about both volumes of the Mueller Report.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#156 — The Evolution of Culture | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070204/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 16:03:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070204/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Nicholas Christakis about his new book, "Blueprint: The Evolutionary Origins of a Good Society."
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#155 — Mental Models | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070205/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 21:53:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070205/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Shane Parrish about some of the mental models that should guide our thinking and behavior.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#154 — What Do Jihadists Really Want? (2019) | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070206/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 00:14:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070206/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris reads from an issue of Dabiq, the magazine of ISIS, and discusses the beliefs and goals of jihadists worldwide.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#153 — Possible Minds | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070207/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 14:33:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070207/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris introduces John Brockman's new anthology, "Possible Minds: 25 Ways of Looking at AI," in conversation with three of its authors: George Dyson, Alison Gopnik, and Stuart Russell.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#152 — The Trouble with Facebook | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070208/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 18:34:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070208/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Roger McNamee about his book Zucked: Waking Up to the Facebook Catastrophe.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#151 — Will We Destroy the Future? | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070209/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 16:32:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070209/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Nick Bostrom about the problem of existential risk. They discuss public goods, moral illusions, the asymmetry between happiness and suffering, utilitarianism, "the vulnerable world hypothesis," the history of nuclear deterrence, the possible need for "turnkey totalitarianism," whether we're living in a computer simulation, the Doomsday Argument, the implications of extraterrestrial life, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#150 — The Map of Misunderstanding | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070210/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 20:08:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070210/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Daniel Kahneman at the Beacon Theatre in NYC. They discuss the replication crisis in science, System 1 and System 2, where intuitions reliably fail, expert intuitions, the power of framing, moral illusions, anticipated regret, the asymmetry between threats and opportunities, the utility of worrying, removing obstacles to wanted behaviors, the remembering self vs the experiencing self, improving the quality of gossip, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#149 — The Problem of Addiction | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070211/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 16:41:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070211/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Sally Satel about addiction. They discuss whether addiction should be considered a disease, the opiate epidemic in the U.S., the unique danger of fentanyl, the politicization of medicine, PTSD, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#148 — Jack Dorsey | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070212/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 16:30:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070212/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Jack Dorsey about how he manages his dual CEO roles at Square and Twitter, the role that Twitter plays in journalism, how it’s different from other social media, what makes a conversation healthy, the logic by which Twitter suspends people, the argument for kicking Trump off the platform, Jack’s practice of meditation, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#147 — Stephen Fry | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070213/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 16:44:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070213/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Stephen Fry about comedy, atheism, political correctness, meditation, ambition, empathy, psychedelics, Christopher Hitchens, Stephen's experience of manic depression, and much else.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#146 — Digital Capitalism | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070214/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 20:36:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070214/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Douglas Rushkoff about the state of the digital economy.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#145 — The Information War | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070215/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 18:35:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070215/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Renee Diresta about Russia's "Internet Research Agency" and its efforts to amplify conspiracy thinking and partisan conflict in the United States.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Drive Interview with Peter Attia | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070216/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 14:51:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070216/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Peter Attia about meditation and the nature of mind. They discuss types of meditation, the difference between pain and suffering, the difference between joy and wellbeing, the half-life of negative emotions, thinking and dreaming, the power of culture, the power of language, letting go of anger, MDMA, loving one's enemies, moral luck, the ethics of lying, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#144 — Conquering Hate | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070217/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Dec 2018 19:41:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070217/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Deeyah Khan about her groundbreaking films "Jihad" and "White Right." They discuss her history as a target of religious intolerance, her adventures with neo-Nazis and other white supremacists, the similarities between extremist groups, the dangers of political correctness, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.</description></item><item><title>#143 — The Keys to the Mind | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070218/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 14:48:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070218/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Derren Brown about his work as a "psychological illusionist." They discuss the power of hypnosis, the power of expectations, the usefulness of Stoic philosophy, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#142 — Addiction, Depression, and a Meaningful Life | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070219/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 01:08:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070219/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Johann Hari about his books "Chasing the Scream" and "Lost Connections."
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#141— Is #MeToo Going Too Far? | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070220/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 14:28:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070220/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Rebecca Traister about her new book "Good and Mad: The Revolutionary Power of Women's Anger."
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The TED Interview | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070221/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 23:05:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070221/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam talks to the head of TED, Chris Anderson, about using reason to build our morality. Sam makes the case that reason can indeed answer moral questions, and then explores the many controversies that emerge from that claim. Moral superiority? Cultural superiority? Moral progress? Chris and Sam dig in to discuss the right ways to think about defining right from wrong, and reason’s role in it all.
This is an episode of The TED Interview, a new podcast from TED.</description></item><item><title>#140 — Burning Down the Fourth Estate | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070222/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 19:13:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070222/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Matt Taibbi about the state journalism and the polarization of our politics. They discuss the controversy over Steve Bannon at the New Yorker Festival, monetizing the Trump phenomenon, the Jamal Kashoggi murder, the Kavanaugh hearing, the Rolling Stone reporting on the UVA rape case, the viability of a political center, the 2020 Presidential election, the Russia investigation, our vanishing attention span, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#139 — Sacred &amp; Profane | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070223/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 17:26:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070223/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris gets together with Bill Maher and Larry Charles to celebrate the 10th anniversary of their film "Religulous." They discuss religion, politics, comedy, and other dangerous topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Introducing Waking Up | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070224/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 02:45:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070224/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of the podcast, Sam Harris introduces Waking Up. More information can be found at WakingUp.com.
You can support the Making Sense podcast and receive subscriber-only content at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#138 — The Edge of Humanity | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070225/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 02:32:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070225/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Yuval Noah Harari about his new book “21 Lessons for the 21st Century.” They discuss the importance of meditation for his intellectual life, the primacy of stories, the need to revise our fundamental assumptions about human civilization, the threats to liberal democracy, a world without work, universal basic income, the virtues of nationalism, the implications of AI and automation, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#137 — Safe Space | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070226/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 02:53:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070226/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Jonathan Haidt about his new book "The Coddling of the American Mind." They discuss the hostility to free speech that has grown more common among young adults, recent moral panics on campus, the role of intentions in ethical life, the economy of prestige in “call out” culture, how we should define bigotry, systemic racism, the paradox of progress, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#136 — Digital Humanism | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070227/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 04:01:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070227/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Jaron Lanier about the economics, politics, and psychology of our digital lives. They discuss the insidious idea that information should be free, what we should want from an advanced economy, the role of advertising, libertarianism in Silicon Valley, the problems with social media, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#135 — Navigating Sex and Gender | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070228/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 15:41:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070228/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Martie Haselton about sex and gender, the role of hormones in human psychology, “Darwinian feminism,” the unique hormonal experience of women, transgenderism, the Google Memo, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#134 — Beyond the Politics of Race | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070229/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 14:57:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070229/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Coleman Hughes about race, racism, and identity politics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#133 — Globalism on the Brink | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070230/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 22:12:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070230/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Ian Bremmer about the failure of globalism and rise of populism. They discuss immigration, trade, automation, wealth inequality, Trump, identity politics and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#132 — Freeing the Hostages | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070231/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 17:06:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070231/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Chris Voss about his experience as a hostage negotiator for the FBI. They discuss different types of hostage crises, along with many of the lessons that apply to negotiating in normal life.
SUBSCRIBE to listen to the rest of this episode and gain access to all full-length episodes of the podcast at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#131 — Dictators, Immigration, #MeToo, and Other Imponderables | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070232/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 00:31:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070232/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Masha Gessen about Vladimir Putin, the problem of gauging public opinion in Russia, Trump's fondness for dictators, the challenges of immigration, comparisons between Christian and Muslim intolerance, "fake news" and the health of journalism, the #MeToo movement, and other topics. If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#130 — Universal Basic Income | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070233/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 00:52:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070233/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with presidential candidate Andrew Yang about "universal basic income" (UBI). They discuss the state of the economy, the rise of automation and AI, the arguments for and against UBI, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#129 — An Insider’s View of Medicine | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070234/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 03:30:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070234/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Dr. Nina Shapiro about the practice of medicine. They discuss the unique resiliency of children, the importance of second opinions, bad doctors, how medical training has changed in recent years, medical uncertainty, risk perception, vaccine safety, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#128 — Transformations of Mind | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070235/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 22:17:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070235/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Geoffrey Miller about evolutionary psychology. They discuss sexual selection, virtue signaling, social media, public shaming, monogamy and polyamory, taboo topics in science, genetic engineering, gender differences and the “Google memo,” moral psychology, existential risk, AI, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#127 — Freedom from the Known | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070236/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 03:15:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070236/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Michael Pollan about his new book “How to Change Your Mind.” They cover the the resurgence of interest in psychedelics in clinical practice and end-of-life care, the “betterment of well people,” the relationship between thinking and mental suffering, the differences between psychedelics and meditation, the non-duality of consciousness, the brain’s “default mode network,” their experiences with various psychedelics, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#126 — In Defense of Honor | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070237/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 04:25:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070237/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Tamler Sommers about cultures of honor. They discuss the difference between honor and dignity, “justice porn,” honor killings, honor and interpersonal violence, prison and gang culture, collective responsibility and collective punishment, retributive vs restorative justice, the ethics of forgiveness and redemption, #metoo, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#125 — What Is Christianity? | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070238/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 23:05:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070238/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks to Bart Ehrman about his experience of being a born-again Christian, his academic training in New Testament scholarship, his loss of faith, the most convincing argument in defense of Christianity, the status of miracles, the composition of the New Testament, the resurrection of Jesus, the nature of heaven and hell, the book of Revelation, the End Times, self-contradictions in the Bible, the concept of a messiah, whether Jesus actually existed, Christianity as a cult of human sacrifice, the conversion of Constantine, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#124 — In Search of Reality | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070239/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 06:43:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070239/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Sean Carroll about our understanding of reality. They discuss consciousness, the many worlds view of quantum mechanics, the arrow of time, free will, facts and values, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#123 — Identity &amp; Honesty | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070240/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070240/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Ezra Klein, Editor-at-Large for Vox Media, about racism, identity politics, intellectual honesty, and the controversy over his podcast with Charles Murray (Making Sense #73). If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#122 — Extreme Housekeeping Edition | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070241/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 16:19:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070241/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris responds to the ongoing controversy over his interview with Charles Murray and discusses his upcoming conversation with Ezra Klein. He also announces a change he will be making to the format of the podcast.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#121 — White Power | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070242/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 02:50:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070242/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Christian Picciolini about his experience as a neo-Nazi skinhead. They discuss how Christian got out of the movement, the limits of shame and forgiveness, the cult-like dynamics of white supremacy, the alt-Right, Russian support for white supremacy in the US, “fake news”, the significance of Charlottesville, the SPLC, and many other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#120 — What Is and What Matters | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070243/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 00:02:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070243/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Rebecca Goldstein and Max Tegmark about the foundations of human knowledge and morality.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#119 — Hidden Motives | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070244/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 18:09:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070244/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Robin Hanson about our hidden motives in everyday life. They discuss selfishness, hypocrisy, norms and meta-norms, cheating, deception, self-deception, education, the evolutionary logic of conversation, social status, signaling and counter-signaling, common knowledge, AI, and many other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title># 118 — The View from Trumpistan | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070245/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 23:34:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070245/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Preet Bharara about President Trump and the Russia investigation. If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#117 — Networks, Power, and Chaos | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070246/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 00:11:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070246/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Niall Ferguson about his new book "The Square and the Tower." They discuss his career as a writer, networks and hierarchies, how history gets written, the similarity between the 16th century and the 21st, the role of social media in the 2016 Presidential election, the influence of advertising on the public sphere, Trump, the Russian investigation, Islamic extremism, counterfactuals, what would have happened if Clinton had won the presidency, immigration in Europe, conspiracy theories, capitalism, globalization, communism, wealth inequality, universal basic income, Henry Kissinger, the prospect of a US war with China, cyberwar, and other topics.</description></item><item><title>The Russell Brand Interview | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070247/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 01:15:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070247/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode of the Making Sense podcast features an interview that Sam did with Russell Brand on the Under the Skin podcast. They speak about religion, terrorism, politics, meditation, psychedelics, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#116 — AI: Racing Toward the Brink | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070248/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2018 00:38:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070248/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Eliezer Yudkowsky about the nature of intelligence, different types of AI, the "alignment problem," IS vs OUGHT, the possibility that future AI might deceive us, the AI arms race, conscious AI, coordination problems, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#115 — Sam Harris, Lawrence Krauss, and Matt Dillahunty (1) | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070249/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 04:48:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070249/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Lawrence Krauss and Matt Dillahunty about the threat of nuclear war, Christian support for Trump, science and a universal conception of morality, the role of intuition in science, the primacy of consciousness, the nature of time, free will, the self, meditation, and other topics. If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#114 — Politics and Sanity | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070250/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 07:08:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070250/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with David Frum and Andrew Sullivan about the Trump presidency, hyper-partisanship, how democracies fail, immigration, the lowering life expectancy in the U.S., racism, social media, the opioid crisis, marijuana legalization, religion, what a healthy politics might look like, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#113 — Consciousness and the Self | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070251/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2018 03:54:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070251/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Anil Seth about the scientific study of consciousness, where consciousness emerges in nature, levels of consciousness, perception as a “controlled hallucination,” emotion, the experience of “pure consciousness,” consciousness as “integrated information,” measures of “brain complexity,” psychedelics, different aspects of the “self,” conscious AI, and many other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#112 — The Intellectual Dark Web | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070252/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 04:28:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070252/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Eric Weinstein and Ben Shapiro about the breakdown of shared values, the problem with identity politics, religion, free will, the primacy of reason, and many other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#111 — The Science of Meditation | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070253/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 05:33:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070253/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Daniel Goleman and Richard J. Davidson about the current scientific understanding of meditation practice. They speak about the original stigma associated with meditation, the history of introspection in eastern and western cultures, the recent collaboration between Buddhism and western science, the difference between altered states and altered traits, an alternate conception of mental health, “meta-awareness,” the relationship between mindfulness and “flow,” the difference between pain and suffering, mindfulness-based stress reduction (MBSR), and other topics.</description></item><item><title>#110 — The Change Artist | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070254/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2017 19:43:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070254/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with AJ Jacobs about religion, gossip, polyamory, health advice, our past and future selves, “radical honesty,” human genealogy, tribalism, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#109— Biology and Culture | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070255/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 01:39:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070255/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Bret Weinstein about the moral panic at Evergreen State College, the concept of race, genetic differences between human populations, intersectionality, sex and gender, “metaphorical truth,” religion and “group selection,” equality, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#108 — Defending the Experts | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070256/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 01:25:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070256/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Tom Nichols about his book The Death of Expertise. They discuss the “Dunning-Kruger Effect,” the growth of knowledge and reliance on authority, when experts fail, the repudiation of expertise in politics, conspiracy thinking, North Korea, Trump, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#107 — Is Life Actually Worth Living? | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070257/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 00:46:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070257/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with David Benatar about his philosophy of “anti-natalism." They discuss the asymmetry between the good and bad things in life, the ethics of existential risk, the moral landscape, the limits and paradoxes of introspection, the “experience machine” thought experiment, population ethics, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#106 — Humanity 2.0 | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070258/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 02:43:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070258/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Jennifer Doudna about the gene-editing technology CRISPR/cas9. They talk about the biology of gene editing, how specific tissues in the body can be targeted, the ethical implications of changing the human genome, the importance of curiosity-driven science, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#105 — Richard Dawkins, Sam Harris, and Matt Dillahunty | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070259/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 03:54:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070259/</guid><description>Podcast Description The following conversation between Richard Dawkins, Sam Harris, and Matt Dillahunty was recorded at the Orpheum Theatre in Vancouver on November 2, 2017.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#104 — The Lessons of Death | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070260/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 03:25:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070260/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Frank Ostaseski about death and dying—and about how the awareness of death can improve our lives in each moment.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#103 — American Fantasies | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070261/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 01:03:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070261/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Kurt Andersen about the American aptitude for unfounded belief, the religious lunacy of the Puritans, populist mistrust of authority, the link between postmodernism and religious fundamentalism, the unique history of American religious entrepreneurship, the Trump phenomenon, the effect of fame on politics, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#102 — Is Buddhism True? | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070262/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 18:05:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070262/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Robert Wright about his book Why Buddhism is True: The Science and Philosophy of Meditation and Enlightenment.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#101 — Defending the Republic | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070263/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 06:31:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070263/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Cass Sunstein about the polarization and fragmentation of American society, “choice architecture,” the importance of face-to-face interactions for problem solving, group polarization and identity politics, virtuous extremism, the wisdom of crowds, direct democracy, the limits of free speech, the process of Presidential impeachment, and other topics. If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#100 — Facing the Crowd | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070264/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 23:50:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070264/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Nicholas Christakis about mob behavior, moral panics, and current threats to free speech.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The "After On" Interview | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070265/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 03:50:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070265/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode of the Making Sense podcast features an interview that Sam Harris did with Rob Reid on the After On podcast. They speak about publishing, psychedelics, terrorism, meditation, free speech and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#99 — What Happened to Liberalism? | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070266/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 06:24:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070266/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Mark Lilla about the fate of political liberalism in the United States, the emergence of a new identity politics, the role of class in American society, wealth inequality, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#98 — Into the Dark Land | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070267/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 02:17:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070267/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Siddhartha Mukherjee about his Pulitzer Prize-winning book, The Emperor of All Maladies: A Biography of Cancer. If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#97 — The Impossible War | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070268/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2017 00:06:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070268/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Ken Burns and Lynn Novick about their latest film, The Vietnam War.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#96 — The Nature of Consciousness | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070269/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 22:16:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070269/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Thomas Metzinger about the scientific and experiential understanding of consciousness. They also talk about the significance of WWII for the history of ideas, the role of intuition in science, the ethics of building conscious AI, the self as an hallucination, how we identify with our thoughts, attention as the root of the feeling of self, the place of Eastern philosophy in Western science, and the limitations of secular humanism.</description></item><item><title>#95 — What You Need to Know About Climate Change | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070270/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 19:08:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070270/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Joseph Romm about how the climate is changing and how we know that human behavior is the primary cause. They discuss why small changes in temperature matter so much, the threats of sea-level rise and desertification, the best and worst case scenarios, the Paris Climate Agreement, the politics surrounding climate science, and many other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#94 — Frontiers of Intelligence | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070271/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 16:18:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070271/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Max Tegmark about his new book Life 3.0: Being Human in the Age of Artificial Intelligence. They talk about the nature of intelligence, the risks of superhuman AI, a nonbiological definition of life, the substrate independence of minds, the relevance and irrelevance of consciousness for the future of AI, near-term breakthroughs in AI, and other topics. If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#93 — Identity &amp; Terror | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070272/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 22:11:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070272/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Douglas Murray about identity politics, the rise of white nationalism, the events in Charlottesville, guilt by association, the sources of western values, the problem of finding meaning in a secular world, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#92 — The Limits of Persuasion | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070273/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 16:39:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070273/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with David Pizarro and Tamler Sommers about free speech on campus, the Scott Adams podcast, the failings of the mainstream media, moral persuasion, moral certainty, the ethics of abortion, Buddhism, the illusion of the self, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#91 — The Biology of Good and Evil | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070274/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 15:40:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070274/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Robert Sapolsky about his work with baboons, the opposition between reason and emotion, doubt, the evolution of the brain, the civilizing role of the frontal cortex, the illusion of free will, justice and vengeance, brain-machine interface, religion, drugs, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.</description></item><item><title>#90 — Living With Violence | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070275/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 16:09:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070275/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Gavin de Becker about the primacy of human intuition in the prediction and prevention of violence.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#89 — On Becoming a Better Person | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070276/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 17:39:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070276/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with David Brooks about his book The Road to Character, the importance of words like “sin” and "virtue," self-esteem vs. self-overcoming, the significance of keeping promises, honesty, President Trump, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#88 — Must We Accept a Nuclear North Korea? | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070277/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 17:09:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070277/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Mark Bowden about the problem of a nuclear-armed North Korea.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#87 — Triggered | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070278/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 06:38:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070278/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris and Scott Adams debate the character and competence of President Trump.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#86 — From Cells to Cities | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070279/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 15:27:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070279/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Geoffrey West about how biological and social systems scale, the significance of fractals, the prospects of radically extending human life, the concept of “emergence” in complex systems, the importance of cities, the necessity for continuous innovation, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#85 — Is this the End of Europe? | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070280/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 17:14:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070280/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Douglas Murray about his book The Strange Death of Europe: Immigration, Identity, Islam.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#84 — Landscapes of Mind | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070281/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2017 06:08:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070281/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Kevin Kelly about why it’s so hard to predict future technology, the nature of intelligence, the “singularity,” artificial consciousness, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#83 — The Politics of Emergency | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070282/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2017 07:19:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070282/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Fareed Zakaria about his career as a journalist, Samuel Huntington's "clash of civilizations," political partisanship, Trump, the health of the news media, the connection between Islam and intolerance, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#82 — The End of the World According to ISIS | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070283/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 16:20:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070283/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Graeme Wood about his experience reporting on ISIS, the myth of online recruitment, the theology of ISIS, the quality of their propaganda, the most important American recruit to the organization, the roles of Jesus and the Anti-Christ in Islamic prophecy, free speech and the ongoing threat of jihadism, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#81 — Leaving Islam | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070284/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 23:54:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070284/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Sarah Haider about her organization Ex-Muslims of North America, how the political Left is confused about Islam, "rape culture" under Islam, honesty without bigotry, stealth theocracy, immigration, the prospects of reforming Islam, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#80 — The Unraveling | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070285/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2017 06:26:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070285/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with David Frum about political partisanship, recent security leaks, Trump's foreign policy, the Russia investigation, Kathy Griffin's joke, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#79 — The Road to Tyranny | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070286/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2017 23:39:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070286/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Timothy Snyder about his book On Tyranny: Twenty Lessons from the Twentieth Century.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#78 — Persuasion and Control | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070287/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 17:50:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070287/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Zeynep Tufekci about "surveillance capitalism," the Trump campaign's use of Facebook, AI-enabled marketing, the health of the press, Wikileaks, ransomware attacks, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#77 — The Moral Complexity of Genetics | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070288/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2017 16:40:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070288/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Siddhartha Mukherjee about the human desire to understand and manipulate heredity, the genius of Gregor Mendel, the ethics of altering our genes, the future of genetic medicine, patent issues in genetic research, controversies about race and intelligence, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#76 — The Path to Impeachment | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070289/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 20:07:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070289/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Anne Applebaum and Juliette Kayyem about the unfolding Russia scandal in the White House.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#75 — Ask Me Anything 7 | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070290/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 20:36:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070290/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris answers questions from listeners about the illusion of the self, his podcast with Charles Murray, the future of brain-machine interfaces, his BJJ practice, reasoning with the extreme Left, mindfulness and parenting, his experience of going back to school after a long break, transgenderism, increasing one’s vocabulary, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#74 — What Should We Eat? | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070291/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2017 20:30:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070291/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Gary Taubes about his career as a science journalist, the difficulty of studying nutrition and public health scientifically, the growing epidemics of obesity and diabetes, the role of hormones in weight gain, the controversies surrounding his work, and other topics. If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#73 — Forbidden Knowledge | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070292/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2017 06:32:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070292/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Charles Murray about the controversy over his book "The Bell Curve," the validity and significance of IQ as a measure of intelligence, the problem of social stratification, the rise of Trump, universal basic income, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#72 — Privacy and Security | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070293/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2017 23:38:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070293/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with General Michael V. Hayden about the reality of spying, the difference between the NSA and the CIA, the ethics of secrecy, Edward Snowden, the Russian Hacking of the 2016 US Presidential election, and other topics. If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#71 — What Is Technology Doing to Us? | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070294/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 21:30:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070294/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Tristan Harris about the arms race for human attention, the ethics of persuasion, the consequences of having an ad-based economy, the dynamics of regret, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#70 — Beauty and Terror | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070295/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 07:50:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070295/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with physicist Lawrence Krauss about the utility of public debates, the progress of science, confusion about the role of consciousness in quantum mechanics, the present danger of nuclear war, the Trump administration, the relative threats of Christian theocracy and Islamism, and realistic fears about terrorism.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#69 — The Russia Connection | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070296/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 05:55:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070296/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Anne Applebaum about Russia's meddling in the U.S. Presidential election and Trump's troubling affinity for Vladimir Putin.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#68 — Reality and the Imagination | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070297/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2017 16:24:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070297/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Yuval Noah Harari about meditation, the need for stories, the power of technology to erase the boundary between fact and fiction, wealth inequality, the problem of finding meaning in a world without work, religion as a virtual reality game, the difference between pain and suffering, the future of globalism, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#67 — Meaning and Chaos | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070298/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2017 20:51:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070298/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris and Jordan Peterson discuss science, religion, archetypes, mythology, and the perennial problem of finding meaning in life.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#66 — Living with Robots | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070299/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070299/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Kate Darling about the ethical concerns surrounding our increasing use of robots and other autonomous systems.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#65 — We're All Cucks Now | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070300/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 16:50:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070300/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with David Frum about the presidency of Donald Trump.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#64 — Ask Me Anything 6 | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070301/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 04:48:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070301/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris answers questions from listeners about his conversation with Jordan Peterson, the reaction to Milo Yiannopoulos at U.C. Berkeley, the “Muslim ban,” the echo chamber of social media, Trump’s lies, the value of the humanities, the ethics of ending aging, whether consciousness can be an illusion, evolution and morality, free speech and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#63 — Why Meditate? | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070302/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 17:12:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070302/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris and Joseph Goldstein answer questions about the practice of mindfulness. They discuss the nature negative emotions, the importance of ethics, the concept of enlightenment, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#62 — What is True? | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070303/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2017 15:55:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070303/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with psychologist Jordan B. Peterson about freedom of speech and the nature of truth.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#61 — The Power of Belief | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070304/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 17:00:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070304/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with author Lawrence Wright about al-Qaeda &amp; ISIS, Arab culture, 9/11 conspiracy theories, the migrant crisis in Europe, Scientology, parallels between L. Ron Hubbard and Donald Trump, the Satanic cult panic, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#60 — An Evening with Richard Dawkins and Sam Harris (2) | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070305/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 07:47:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070305/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Richard Dawkins at a live event in Los Angeles (second of two). They discuss Richard’s experience of having a stroke, the genetic future of humanity, the analogy between genes and memes, the “extended phenotype,” Islam and bigotry, the biology of race, how to find meaning without religion, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#59 — Friend &amp; Foe | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070306/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 08:23:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070306/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Maajid Nawaz about the Southern Poverty Law Center, Robert Spencer, Keith Ellison, moderate Muslims, Shadi Hamid’s notion of “Islamic exceptionalism," the migrant crisis in Europe, foreign interventions, Trump, Putin, Obama’s legacy, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#58 — The Putin Question | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070307/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2016 17:27:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070307/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Garry Kasparov about the problem of waning American power, the rise of Putin, the coming presidency of Donald Trump, computer chess, the future of artificial intelligence, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#57 — An Evening with Richard Dawkins and Sam Harris (1) | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070308/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2016 01:47:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070308/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Richard Dawkins at a live event in Los Angeles (first of two). They cover religion, Jurassic Park, artificial intelligence, elitism, continuing human evolution, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#56 — Abusing Dolores | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070309/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2016 17:09:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070309/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Paul Bloom about empathy, meditation studies, morality, AI, Westworld, Donald Trump, free will, rationality, conspiracy thinking, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#55 — Islamism vs Secularism | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070310/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 05:31:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070310/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Shadi Hamid about the power of religious belief, the failure of the Left, Islamist democracy, free speech, profiling, white nationalism, Obama’s foreign policy and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#54 — Trumping The World | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070311/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 20:14:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070311/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with journalist James Kirchick about the coming Trump presidency, liberalism vs illiberalism, fake news, Russia, Syria, Iran, and the future of American power.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#53 — The Dawn of Artificial Intelligence | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070312/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2016 00:40:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070312/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with computer scientist Stuart Russell about the challenge of building artificial intelligence that is compatible with human well-being.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#52 — Finding Our Way in the Cosmos | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070313/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2016 21:10:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070313/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with physicist David Deutsch about the foundations of knowledge, the moral landscape, possible futures for conscious beings, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#51 — The Most Powerful Clown | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070314/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2016 21:23:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070314/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris talks about the results of the 2016 presidential election and the prospects of a President Trump.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#50 — The Borders of Tolerance | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070315/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 18:41:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070315/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Ayaan Hirsi Ali about Islamism, the migrant crisis in Europe, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#49 — The Lesser Evil | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070316/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 19:05:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070316/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Andrew Sullivan about the 2016 presidential election.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#48 — What Is Moral Progress? | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070317/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 20:50:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070317/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with philosopher Peter Singer about the foundations of morality, expanding the circle of our moral concern, politics, free speech, conspiracy thinking, Edward Snowden, the importance of intentions, WWII, euthanasia, eating “happy cows,” and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#47 — The Frontiers of Political Correctness | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070318/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2016 17:35:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070318/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Gad Saad about political correctness, academic taboos, Islam, immigration, Donald Trump, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#46 — The End of Faith Sessions 3 | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070319/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 06:27:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070319/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris reads and discusses the third chapter of "The End of Faith." Topics covered: Christianity, Judaism, the Inquisition, witchcraft, anti-Semitism, and the Holocaust.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#45 — Ask Me Anything 5 | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070320/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2016 20:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070320/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris answers questions from listeners about how 9/11 changed his life, Brazilian jiu-jitsu, free will, why he podcasts, Milo and the alt-Right, identity politics, Clinton vs. Trump, vegetarianism, and the Hannibal Buress episode.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#44 — Being Good and Doing Good | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070321/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2016 18:30:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070321/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Oxford philosopher William MacAskill about effective altruism, moral illusions, existential risk, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#43 — What Do Jihadists Really Want? | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070322/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2016 15:02:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070322/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris reads from the latest issue of "Dabiq," the magazine of ISIS, and discusses the beliefs and goals of jihadists worldwide.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#42 — Racism and Violence in America | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070323/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2016 02:48:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070323/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris talks to economist Glenn C. Loury about racism, police violence, the Black Lives Matter movement, and related topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#41 — Faith in Reason | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070324/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 18:40:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070324/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Eric Weinstein about the relationship between faith and reason and about some of the factors that make conversations on important topics so difficult.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#40 — Complexity &amp; Stupidity | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070325/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 06:36:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070325/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris talks to biologist David Krakauer about information, complex systems, and the future of humanity.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#39 — Free Will Revisited | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070326/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2016 02:47:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070326/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with philosopher Daniel Dennett about free will.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#38 — The End of Faith Sessions 2 | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070327/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2016 19:12:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070327/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris reads and discusses the second chapter of "The End of Faith." However, the first hour of this podcast focuses on Donald Trump, Hillary Clinton, and the political implications of the recent terrorist attack in Orlando. Discussion of The End of Faith begins at 1:04:30.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.</description></item><item><title>#37 — Thinking in Public | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070328/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2016 15:21:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070328/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with astrophysicist Neil deGrasse Tyson about the public understanding of science, his career as an educator, political atheism, racism, artificial intelligence, alien life, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#36 — What Makes Us Safer? | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070329/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2016 17:11:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070329/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Juliette Kayyem, a leading expert on homeland security, about the war on terror, profiling, Islamism, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#35 — The End Of Faith Sessions 1 | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070330/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2016 18:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070330/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris reads and discusses the first chapter of "The End of Faith."
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#34 — The Light of the Mind | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070331/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2016 16:35:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070331/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with philosopher David Chalmers about the nature of consciousness, the challenges of understanding it scientifically, and the prospect that we will one day build it into our machines.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#33 — Ask Me Anything 4 | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070332/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2016 07:19:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070332/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris answers questions from listeners about the recent attacks in Brussels, dealing with anxiety, the science of immortality, fame, liberalism, the Golden Age of Islam, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#32 — The Best Podcast Ever | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070333/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 19:24:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070333/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris talks to Omer Aziz about Islam, Islamism, free speech, and related topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#31 — Evolving Minds | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070334/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 05:04:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070334/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris responds to Omer Aziz and Salon magazine, and then speaks with Jonathan Haidt about the scientific study of morality, the problem of political correctness, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#30 — Inside the Crucible | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070335/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2016 17:06:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070335/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris briefly revisits the Apple-FBI controversy and then speaks with Michael Weiss about ISIS and the ongoing civil war in Syria. If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#29 — Throw Open the Gates | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070336/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 20:53:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070336/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris responds to criticism of his views on the Apple-FBI controversy and then speaks with Maryam Namazie about friendly fire among secularists, profiling, the immigration crisis in Europe, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#28 — Meat Without Misery | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070337/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2016 15:33:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070337/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris offers a few more thoughts on Clinton vs Sanders, as well as on the ethics of strong encryption. He then speaks with Uma Valeti, cardiologist and CEO of Memphis Meats, about the future of food production. If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#27 — Ask Me Anything 3 | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070338/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2016 00:35:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070338/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris answers questions from listeners about free will, meditation, Noam Chomsky, the illusion of the self, Clinton vs. Sanders, the de-platforming of Richard Dawkins, wealth inequality, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#26 — The Logic of Violence | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070339/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 20:30:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070339/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with retired Navy SEAL and author, Jocko Willink. They discuss U.S. foreign policy, war, human evil, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#25 — Behind the Gun | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070340/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2016 17:17:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070340/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with former SWAT operator and lead weapons and tactics instructor for the LAPD Metro Division, Scott Reitz. They discuss guns, gun control, police violence, and related topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#24 — Ask Me Anything 2 | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070341/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2016 03:51:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070341/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris answers questions from listeners about Islamism, free will, honesty, vegetarianism, why he doesn’t publish more in academic journals, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#23 — Islam and the Future of Tolerance (Audiobook Excerpts) | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070342/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 22:31:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070342/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris introduces the audio edition of his book with Maajid Nawaz, "Islam and the Future of Tolerance: A Dialogue."
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#22 — Surviving the Cosmos | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070343/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2015 15:41:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070343/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris talks to physicist David Deutsch about the reach and power of human knowledge, the future of artificial intelligence, and the survival of civilization.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#21 — On the Maintenance of Civilization | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070344/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2015 22:00:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070344/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with author Douglas Murray about Islamism, liberalism, civil society, and the migrant crisis in Europe.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#20 — Still Sleepwalking Toward Armageddon | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070345/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2015 23:54:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070345/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris reflects on the recent terrorist attacks in Paris.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#19 — The Riddle Of The Gun (Revisited) | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070346/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2015 18:40:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070346/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris discusses his views about guns and gun control in light of a recent mass shooting.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#18 — The Multiverse &amp; You (&amp; You &amp; You &amp; You...) | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070347/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 19:41:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070347/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with MIT cosmologist Max Tegmark about the foundations of science, our current understanding of the universe, and the risks of future breakthroughs in artificial intelligence.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#17 — What I Really Think About Profiling | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070348/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 23:47:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070348/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris responds to misrepresentations of his views (again).
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#16 — The Dark Side | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070349/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 04:02:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070349/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris and Paul Bloom talk about Donald Trump, torture, trophy hunting, and other terrors.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#15 — Questions Along the Path | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070350/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2015 20:28:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070350/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris and Joseph Goldstein discuss the practice of meditation and answer questions that came from listeners in response to their first conversation, "The Path and the Goal."
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#14 — The Virtues of Cold Blood | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070351/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2015 22:28:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070351/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with psychologist Paul Bloom about the limitations of empathy as a guide to moral reasoning.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#13 — The Moral Gaze | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070352/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2015 06:09:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070352/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with the filmmaker Joshua Oppenheimer about his remarkable documentaries, "The Act of Killing" and "The Look of Silence."
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#12 — Leaving the Church | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070353/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2015 21:18:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070353/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Megan Phelps-Roper, granddaughter of Fred Phelps of the infamous Westboro Baptist Church.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#11 — Shouldering the Burden of History | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070354/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2015 08:11:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070354/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris and Dan Carlin (host of the Hardcore History and Common Sense podcasts) discuss American interventionism, the war on terror, and related topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#10 — Faith vs. Fact | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070355/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2015 21:35:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070355/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris interviews biologist Jerry Coyne about his new book, "Faith vs. Fact: Why Science and Religion are Incompatible."
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#9 — Final Thoughts On Chomsky | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070356/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 03:34:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070356/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris reflects on his failure to have a productive conversation with Noam Chomsky.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#8 — Ask Me Anything 1 | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070357/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2015 22:35:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070357/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris talks about atheism, artificial intelligence, rape, public speaking, meditation, consciousness, free will, intellectual honesty, and other topics.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#7 — Through the Eyes of a Cult | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070358/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 03:47:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070358/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris discusses the Heaven's Gate suicide cult and argues that we all have something important to learn from them about the power of belief.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#6 — The Chapel Hill Murders and 'Militant' Atheism | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070359/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2015 00:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070359/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris responds to the charge that "militant" atheism is responsible for the murder of three Muslim students in North Carolina.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#5 — After Charlie Hebdo and Other Thoughts | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070360/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2015 04:42:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070360/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris answers reader questions in the wake of the terrorist attacks in Paris.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#4 — The Path and the Goal | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070361/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2014 17:23:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070361/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Harris speaks with Joseph Goldstein about the practice of meditation.
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#3 — WAKING UP — Chapter One | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070362/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2014 17:06:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070362/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the complete first chapter of Waking Up: A Guide to Spirituality Without Religion by Sam Harris.
To purchase the audiobook: http://amzn.to/1v1NEIK
To purchase the print edition: http://amzn.to/1mqiAKL
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#2 — Why Don't I Criticize Israel? | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070363/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2014 16:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070363/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the wake of the recent war in Gaza, many readers have asked "Why don't you criticize Israel?" Here is my response. You can read an annotated transcript of this podcast at: https://www.samharris.org/podcasts/making-sense-episodes/why-dont-i-criticize-israel
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#1 — Drugs And The Meaning Of Life | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070364/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 06:18:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070364/</guid><description>Podcast Description The full text of this essay can be read here:
http://www.samharris.org/blog/item/drugs-and-the-meaning-of-life
If the Making Sense podcast logo in your player is BLACK, you can SUBSCRIBE to gain access to all full-length episodes at samharris.org/subscribe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to talk to a Christian | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070365/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2013 04:38:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070365/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is an edited excerpt from remarks that Sam Harris made in a debate with a Christian apologist at Notre Dame University in 2011. The full debate can be viewed here: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yqaHXKLRKzg
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Looking for the Self (26 Minutes) | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070366/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 19:46:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070366/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a 26-minute mindfulness meditation, led by Sam Harris. For more information visit www.samharris.org.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mindfulness Meditation (9 Minutes) | Making Sense with Sam Harris</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3055070367/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 19:46:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3055070367/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a 9-minute mindfulness meditation, led by Sam Harris. For more information visit www.samharris.org.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>