<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/table-manners-with-jessie-and-lennie-ware/</link><description>Recent content in Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 04:00:55 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/table-manners-with-jessie-and-lennie-ware/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>S16 Ep 9: Kadiff Kirwan | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 04:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our latest guest has been waiting to meet ‘Dame Lennie’ for a while, and this week his dream finally came true! The absolutely gorgeous and talented actor, Kadiff Kirwan, joined us for a showstopping - if I say so myself - Dutch Baby round at mine. His stories were a total delight; born on the Caribbean island of Montserrat, he told us all about delicious meals his mum cooked him while growing up, how he was once in a Christian acapella boyband, that being naughty at school helped him find his love of acting, and he also does a good job of trying to convince us to try a Caribbean Souse… Kadiff, the trip to Montserrat must happen and can we join please?</description></item><item><title>S16 Ep 8: Cher | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 04:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190002/</guid><description>Podcast Description There was only ever going to be one guest we would travel all the way to Paris to meet and that’s Cher! An icon meets another icon; Mum&amp;rsquo;s Chicken Soup travelled all the way on the Eurostar &amp;amp; thanks to the brilliant room service team we served it up in a hotel suite for our favourite diva. Cher treated us to tales of fabulous nights dancing to Donna Summer at Studio 54, the delicious southern food her mum made her while growing up, how she became a star in the UK before anywhere else, and stories about her brand new Cherlato ice cream brand (and her thoughts on the Avocado flavour!</description></item><item><title>S16 Ep 7: Girls Aloud | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 04:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Don’t say we never spoil you listeners, because this is a biggie: Cheryl, Kimberley, Nadine &amp;amp; Nicola - Girls Aloud! They’re back &amp;amp; they’ve come round to New Cross to join me and mum for lunch. This episode is loud, exciting, chaotic, but mostly it’s just brilliant!
We hear all about the exciting news of their new tour, what it was like living together when they first formed as a band (and forgetting to pay the utility bills), lovely stories about their beautiful bandmate, the late Sarah Harding, and to top it off quite an unbelievable story about microwaving bacon!</description></item><item><title>S16 Ep 6: Princess Eugenie | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 04:00:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190004/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s a royally good week on Table Manners, we have our very first royal on the podcast; Princess Eugenie popped round for brunch! She was an absolute delight and we couldn’t wait to ask all about table manners in the royal household. We found out all about how she spends half the year living in Portugal, that she thinks she could win an Olympic Gold medal for sleeping, her love of tequila on the rocks, learning the art of small talk from her granny (The Queen), and how she navigated getting a job while being a member of the royal family, plus the revelation that she has never heard of an air fryer!</description></item><item><title>S16 Ep 5: Ravinder Bhogal | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 04:00:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190005/</guid><description>Podcast Description The wonderful, beautiful and generous chef &amp;amp; restauranteur Ravinder Bhogal brought us some absolutely delicious food when she came round for this weeks episode! As the owner of the fabulous Marylebone restaurant Jikoni, Ravinder’s Comfort &amp;amp; Joy delivery boxes got us through the never-ending lockdowns (Sam still says it’s his best home cooked meal ever!). She told us all about how she set up the restaurant, growing up in Kenya, how she started her career on Gordon Ramsey’s ‘F Word’ and that she’s known to hang out with Stanley Tucci &amp;amp; cook for Sir Paul McCartney.</description></item><item><title>S16 Ep 4: Matt Lucas | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 04:00:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190006/</guid><description>Podcast Description He’s the star of the iconic Little Britain, Bridesmaids, Come Fly With Me and soon to be seen on the big screen in Wonka. This week we have the one and only Matt Lucas joining us for dinner. Matt has recently written his first children’s book and with all his wonderful stories from growing up you can see where all the inspiration comes from! We discovered that he was given his first big break by Bob Mortimer, he's notorious for his very own Chicken Soup recipe (which takes him 36 hours!</description></item><item><title>S16 Ep 3: Ed Gamble | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 04:00:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Usually we ask what is on the menu, this week the question is what is ‘off&amp;rsquo; the menu! On one of the hottest days of the year, we adored having comedian, podcaster and all round mensch Ed Gamble round to mum&amp;rsquo;s for lunch. Ed has mum’s absolute dream job (being a judge on Great British Menu) and he shared all the secrets from the filming, including how he once had to eat 8 desserts in one sitting!</description></item><item><title>S16 Ep 2: Zoe Ball | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 02:00:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mamma Mia! Fresh from our fabulous month in Corfu filming &amp;lsquo;Mamma Mia: I Have a Dream’, the one and only Zoe Ball joins us this week for a Greek Mezze inspired brunch. Zoe came straight from her early morning BBC Radio 2 show over to New Cross, laden with all sorts of delicious food. She confessed to us that she is a self proclaimed ‘terrible cook’, told us all about her star studded nights out in the 90s (pole dancing with Sheryl Crow being a favourite memory), the struggles of growing her own sprouts, how she wishes humans hibernated in the winter, and how she won ‘pig of the year’ at school for eating 19 spam fritters in one sitting!</description></item><item><title>S16 Ep 1: Miriam Margolyes | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 03:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190009/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re back! We’ve made it all the way to Series 16 and we’re bringing you a corker for our first episode in the shape of the iconic Miriam Margolyes! Never in the history of Table Manners have we had a guest with so much… wind…! Despite that, Miriam was a true delight, sharing stories of the food her mummy made her while growing up, where to find the best ice cream in Clapham, and the unbelievable revelation that she has never liked bagels as ’the hole is wasted bread’!</description></item><item><title>Second Helpings - Kylie Minogue | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190010/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 03:00:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Padam! For the final instalment of our Second Helpings series, we’re taking it back to 2020 when the ultimate pop princess and style icon Kylie Minogue popped round to Clapham, followed by paparazzi on a hump day.&amp;nbsp;
Kylie was the first concert I ever went to and we named our guinea pigs after her (and Jason) so who can blame me for the fangirl situation! Kylie tells us all about her upbringing in Australia and her journey to fame, where Charlene's famous overalls are now &amp;amp; how she’ll only have a questionable half sized cup of tea.</description></item><item><title>Second Helpings - Michael McIntyre | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190011/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 03:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190011/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re 4 weeks into our Second Helpings season and this week we’re looking back at our evening with the wonderful Mr Michael McIntyre - we knew we’d love him but now we are absolutely HOOKED! Michael finally broke my fear of watching comedy with this front row seat to his hilarity and three hours of laughing &amp;rsquo;til we cried! From the moment Michael walked in (thermometer in hand) we did not stop laughing.</description></item><item><title>Second Helpings - Alan Carr | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 03:00:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190012/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re bringing back the ultimate guest for our Second Helpings series, the one and only Alan Carr. We knew we were in for a treat but this might have been our funniest guest yet?! From the moment he walked in discussing his farm animals&amp;rsquo; sexual exploits to his eventual &amp;lsquo;Come Dine with Me&amp;rsquo; scoring of 1/10 for us - my GOD we laughed. And drunk. This was such a pleasure to listen back to and I hope you enjoy it too!</description></item><item><title>Second Helpings - Nigella Lawson | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190013/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 03:29:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190013/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s week 2 of our summer Second Helpings series, and this week we take a look back at when the ultimate kitchen goddess joined us… Nigella Lawson. She had been top of our list since day one, and finally in season 4 we got her! We talk midnight snacks, her being a fussy eater as a child (there’s hope for all our children), eating rice pudding for breakfast… and she even changed my views on Vegemite, Nigella 4 President!</description></item><item><title>Second Helpings - Sam Smith | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 03:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190014/</guid><description>Podcast Description For the first of our Second Helpings episodes we take a trip down memory lane with the wonderful Sam Smith. We recorded this episode with Sam in 2017 and it was the very first Table Manners to exist! Over mum&amp;rsquo;s turkey meatballs we talked about Sam&amp;rsquo;s childhood food experiences, living without booze and what they would choose for their last supper. And they did a very scary impression of a movie icon too…!</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode: Lionesses - Ellen White and Lyn Hale | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 08:56:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Surprise!! A little added bonus before we take a break for the summer!&amp;nbsp;
You all know Mum &amp;amp; I LOVE football, and the World Cup is on right now, so this was mega. Our first footballers on Table Manners!!&amp;nbsp;
This special episode in partnership with The National Lottery is in support of Good Causes and specifically women’s football.&amp;nbsp;
We chat to two Lionesses (or goddesses as mum calls them) , England legend Ellen White MBE &amp;amp; one of the England National teams legacy players, Lyn Hale.</description></item><item><title>S15 Ep 23: Keir Starmer | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 03:07:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190016/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s our final episode of this series, and we’ve decided to finish it off by inviting the leader of the opposition, Sir Keir Starmer, to mum&amp;rsquo;s for dinner. The leader of the Labour Party told us all about his love of experimental cooking, his mum&amp;rsquo;s jam sandwiches, eating fish &amp;amp; chips on the road, the controversy over his Desert Island Discs song choices and the tradition of Friday night shabbat with his family.</description></item><item><title>S15 Ep 22: Andrew Ridgeley | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 03:00:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190017/</guid><description>Podcast Description It was an absolute joy to cook elevenses for the one and only Andrew Ridgeley last week. Never before has a guest been more thorough and specific when we asked about their last supper. Arriving by bus, he told us all about the wonderful Wham! documentary, about his time in the band, his perfectionism when cooking, his epic 10-day bike ride across the UK and we discovered that not only are Club Tropicana drinks free….</description></item><item><title>S15 Ep 21: Raven Smith | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 03:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our latest guest Raven Smith is a writer, columnist, best selling author, man about town and a meme king. This week he popped round for dinner, I barbecued some pink sea bream, we got a special ‘Hot Jessie’ pizza delivery from Dinner For One Hundred &amp;amp; we topped the whole evening off with an array of Gengelly&amp;rsquo;s delicious desserts. Raven brought us a bottle of his very own Top Cuvee collab rosé, we swapped stories about drinking Cosmos and making the ultimate trifle, he shared tales about his Dad’s Jamaican cooking and we hear about his book ‘Raven Smith’s Men’.</description></item><item><title>S15 Ep 20: Loreen | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 03:00:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190019/</guid><description>Podcast Description A Table Manners EUPHORIA! The Queen of Eurovision has arrived in Clapham! She’s the only female (and only the second person ever) to have won Eurovision twice, the one and only Loreen joins us this week. Loreen told us all about her lifelong spirituality, the Moroccan meals her mother used to cook her when she was young, her huge sweet tooth, her unique dressing room rider, and the special meaning behind her latest Eurovision performance outfit.</description></item><item><title>S15 Ep 19: Jon Batiste | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 03:05:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190020/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we have a musician, singer, songwriter, composer, TV star and political campaigner - there is nothing he cannot do - it’s Jon Batiste! He’s won Grammys, a Golden Globe, a BAFTA, and even an Oscar, and now he’s popped round to mine for a Middle Eastern Mezze inspired brunch. A New Orleans native, music &amp;amp; food have always been a huge part of Jon’s life, and he told us all about his love of Red Beans &amp;amp; Rice, Po Boy Sandwiches, Crawfish Boils and Pepperoni Pizza with a dollop of honey.</description></item><item><title>S15 Ep 18: Jaime Winstone | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190021/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 03:04:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actress extraordinaire, activist, podcaster, and all round general delight Jaime Winstone joins us this week on Table Manners. Usually I bump into Jaime in a festival field or in a club, so it’s a lovely change to have her round for a spot of lunch at mine! Despite being a massive foodie, Jaime admits she isn’t the best cook… but she told us all about her food adventures in Sicily, her total love of a farm shop and why bread sauce and cherry brandy ice lollies are absolute essentials!</description></item><item><title>S15 Ep 17: Anne-Marie | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 03:00:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190022/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we have popstar, TV coach, and 3 time karate champion, Anne-Marie joining us on Table Manners. Ahead of the release of her brand new album ‘Unhealthy’, Anne-Marie told us all about her dressing room rider at The Voice, the entire room at her house dedicated to her Lego collection, and a sorry story involving battery acid… just wait! It was an absolute pleasure to have you round Anne-Marie, promise next time we will have a breakfast burrito or a peanut butter sandwich to serve up for you!</description></item><item><title>S15 Ep 16: Noel Gallagher | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 03:00:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mum was over the moon this week to be joined by fellow Mancunian and music legend Noel Gallagher for a spot of brunch ahead of the release of his new album &amp;lsquo;Council Skies&amp;rsquo;. Mum and Noel got on like a house on fire sharing all their tales from up north. Noel shared a few vital revelations; that he always drinks tea with goats milk, he’s only ever had one driving lesson, he didn’t try a boiled egg until he turned 30 (!</description></item><item><title>S15 Ep 15: Jake Shears | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 03:00:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ahead of the release of his epic new album 'Last Man Dancing’ this Friday, we have the one and only Jake Shears joining us for a spot of dinner. Mum served up a delicious healthy turbot and samphire for main with poached pears for pud. Jake was utterly charming, he told us all about the various places he lived while growing up, including the island his family moved to off the coast of Seattle where it's inhabited by foot long Banana Slugs (Google it, they’re gross!</description></item><item><title>S15 Ep 14: Marina Hyde | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190025/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 03:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190025/</guid><description>Podcast Description As avid followers of her column, mum &amp;amp; I were very excited about this weeks guest, the wonderful Marina Hyde.
Marina talks to us about her upbringing and experience of boarding school, her love of schnitzel, deliberately not making friends with politicians, living in Notting Hill &amp;amp; her penchant for penny sweets.
What a glorious evening! Her hysterical book ‘What Just Happened? Dispatches from Turbulent Times’ is out now, go and have a read.</description></item><item><title>S15 Ep 13: Alison Roman | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190026/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 03:05:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our cooking inspiration… Alison Roman on Table Manners this week!&amp;nbsp;
The two time bestselling author and New York Times cooking columnist talks to us about her journey on becoming the queen of home cooking!&amp;nbsp;
We talk about why she moved to New York, starting out as a pastry chef, eating artichokes in California, her mum's Garlic Butter, the reason she’ll never open a restaurant and why Balsamic is over…</description></item><item><title>S15 Ep 12: Alison Goldfrapp | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190027/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 03:00:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ahead of the release of her debut solo album 'The Love Invention' this Friday, we have the fabulous icon Alison Goldfrapp joining us for a spot of Ottolenghi inspired dinner. Alison told us all about her mum's home made liver &amp;amp; mash being a regular staple in their household while growing up, her years at a convent school where she found her musical talents, and she even sold us on her absolute favourite drink, Nettle tea!</description></item><item><title>S15 Ep 11: Dannii Minogue | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 03:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190028/</guid><description>Podcast Description What’s better than one Minogue? TWO!! This week, we welcome the totally wonderful Ms Dannii Minogue on Table Manners. She came over laden with Italian deli gifts and we chatted over some griddled Salmon and panna cotta. Dannii talks to us about life on the Melbourne farm with sister Kylie, her time spent cleaning windows in London, how she is celebrating 20 years of her album ‘Neon Nights’ &amp;amp; she gives me ALL the tips on how to be a mentor on telly!</description></item><item><title>S15 Ep 10: Ramy Youssef | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190029/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 03:02:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190029/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week actor, comedian, writer, director and all round brilliant person Ramy Youssef joins us on Table Manners.
I’m on the food, serving up butter sage fried eggs with pickled chillis and homemade sourdough (courtesy of my yoga teacher Helen Russell-Clarke) along with lapsang souchong plums, yoghurt and homemade granola.&amp;nbsp;
We talk about his upbringing in New Jersey, eating his parents delicious Egyptian food, how to make the perfect Koshary, eating his way around Palestine while shooting his Emmy award-winning TV show ‘Ramy’ and the joy of eating with small cutlery and chopsticks.</description></item><item><title>S15 Ep 9: George and Larry Lamb | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190030/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 09:20:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190030/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’ve got another duo for you! The incredibly charismatic George and Larry Lamb! They arrived with armfuls of bread - perfect to mop up Lennie's lamb harissa meatballs with.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Father and son tell us all about endless family holidays in Normandy, selling secret burgers, isolating with exes &amp;amp; there was potential oversharing on why oysters taste so good!
To find out more about Wildfarmed - please visit wildfarmed.co.uk</description></item><item><title>S15 Ep 8: Phil Rosenthal | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190031/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 03:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190031/</guid><description>Podcast Description The kindest face of food and travel… the man with the job made of dreams.. this week, we welcome star of Netflix’s 'Somebody Feed Phil' - Phil Rosenthal. It was my turn to cook and what better meal for Phil than a full English fry up. We recorded this on his birthday so we followed up with a good old British tradition of Colin The Caterpillar. We discuss choosing childhood favourites as his last meal, the best cheese toastie he’s ever eaten, how he could live off pizza &amp;amp; his pet peeve in restaurants.</description></item><item><title>S15 Ep 7: Joel &amp; Hannah Cooper Dommett | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190032/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 03:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190032/</guid><description>Podcast Description We love a couple on Table Manners… this week we have Joel &amp;amp; Hannah Cooper Dommett join us for dins!&amp;nbsp;
Mum cooked delicious chicken with miso, lime, ginger and chilli &amp;amp; whisked up a Cote Brasserie inspired coffee and chocolate Eton mess - delish!&amp;nbsp;
We chatted all about their podcast adventures, plane spotting, smuggling chocolate sprinkles, how they met &amp;amp; who’s the best cook.&amp;nbsp;
What a laugh! Love these two.</description></item><item><title>S15 Ep 6: Carol Vorderman | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190033/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 03:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190033/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we welcome the iconic queen of numbers and letters, Carol Vorderman to Table Manners.
Over a lunch of scallops, pea purée and fresh bread we discuss her upbringing in North Wales, sharing Mars bars with her siblings, being introduced to olive oil &amp;amp; the joy of a long lunch.&amp;nbsp;
We talk all about her hugely successful TV career, flying planes &amp;amp; not giving a damn what people think!</description></item><item><title>S15 Ep 5: Andy Serkis | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190034/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190034/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you haven’t seen it already… there is a brand new Luther film out on Netflix - and this week we have star &amp;amp; psychopathic villain of the show, the glorious Andy Serkis on Table Manners.&amp;nbsp;
Andy talks to us about his&amp;nbsp;Iraqi influenced upbringing, eating Wimpy's with his mum, where to get the best tiramisu in London &amp;amp; first dates in character.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
We discover his musical hobbies, his love of mountaineering and we don’t even ask him for a Gollum impression!</description></item><item><title>S15 Ep 4: Alastair Campbell | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190035/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 04:00:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mum hasn’t been this excited since Ed Miliband came over to Clapham, this week we have the formidable Alastair Campbell over for dinner! Alastair talks to us about his new book 'But What Can I Do?', a book that encourages us to keep fighting the good fight even when everything feels bleak and hopeless.&amp;nbsp;We talk about Gary Lineker and the BBC, his fantastic podcast 'The Rest is Politics', having dinner with Princess Diana, his ketchup phobia, a deep love of Fish Soup and Chocolate Mousse, a hatred of fine dining and amuse bouches.</description></item><item><title>S15 Ep 3: Kim Petras | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190036/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 04:19:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Spinach pie, bouyourdi eggs and florentines for Kim Petras!!
Straight off the back of her big Grammy win with friend of the podcast, Sam Smith - Kim popped over to Clapham for a glass of champagne and a chit chat.
She told us all about her upbringing in Germany, eating Greek food on Christmas Day, holidaying in Disneyland and she introduced us to a drink even more divisive than marmite!</description></item><item><title>S15 Ep 2: Russell T Davies | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190037/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 04:00:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190037/</guid><description>Podcast Description We have the legendary Russell T Davies on Table Manners this week. We’ve wanted him for so so long and finally, here he is - one of the greatest TV writer/producers of our time - eating a fish cake and having a brew in Lennie's kitchen.&amp;nbsp;
Russell talks to us about his return to Doctor Who, his life changing experience making ‘It’s A Sin’ and his latest 3 part drama ‘Nolly’ featuring a sublime performance by Helena Bonham Carter.</description></item><item><title>S15 Ep 1: P!nk | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190038/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 04:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190038/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re back, it’s Series 15, and we have an absolute corker for our first episode. Superstar P!nk popped round to mum’s for a perfectly ‘pink' meal of Pink Salmon with Salsa Verde, followed by mum’s delicious Pink Raspberry &amp;amp; Champagne Possets. We had the best evening with P!nk who told us all about her magical live shows, her love of Kugel &amp;amp; Matzo Ball soup while growing up, the psychic she visited in Australia who revealed how her daughter and her go back lifetimes and being mistaken for Gwen Stefani in a supermarket.</description></item><item><title>S14 Ep 15: Katherine Ryan | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 04:00:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy New Year! It’s our final episode of this series, and this time the Canadian Queen of comedy popped over for lunch just before she gave birth to her 3rd child. With just 2 weeks to go Katherine was absolutely glowing and was unbelievably calm and chilled, in fact so calm she thinks she’s actually already dead and this is her afterlife! Katherine gave us her story of growing up in Canada, the Ice Cream Barbie cakes she would have for her birthdays, the story of her Louis Theroux documentary, and her… big… theory about Pete Davidson!</description></item><item><title>S14 Ep 14: Rita Wilson | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190040/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 03:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190040/</guid><description>Podcast Description She’s a Hollywood actress, a singer, a hugely successful film producer, and this week we managed to get Rita Wilson to New Cross to join us for lunch. Rita told us all about her love of everything Greek and her shared love of Skopelos (where they filmed her Mamma Mia films!), her new duets album ’Now &amp;amp; Forever’, her favourite dessert of Lime Jello mixed with cream cheese (!</description></item><item><title>S14 Ep 13: Christmas Extravaganza | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190041/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 03:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190041/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s become an annual Table Manners tradition now, so here it is.. voila.. our Christmas Extravaganza! We catch up with a handful of our favourite guests to see how they spend the festive period. Joining us are Mel C, Tom Daley, David Schwimmer, Paul Hollywood and the King of Christmas himself Michael Buble! Grab yourself a mince pie &amp;amp; a glass of bubbly &amp;amp; tune in! Sending all our listeners lots of love and hope you all have a wonderful Christmas!</description></item><item><title>S14 Ep 12: Olly Murs | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190042/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 04:01:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190042/</guid><description>Podcast Description 10 mins in and he had his top off! Olly and his abs joined us in Clapham this week to eat Ottolenghi's Courgette Frittata and florentines and what fun it was.&amp;nbsp;
Olly talks to us all about his X Factor journey, his obsession with McDonalds facts, his no.1 fan - John the pub landlord, Lewis Capaldi’s ’The Sexy Meaty’ pizza &amp;amp; and his special chosen karaoke song in honour of Caroline Flack.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode: Nadiya Hussain | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190043/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 05:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190043/</guid><description>Podcast Description What a lovely morning of coffee and cake with the divine Nadiya Hussain! Thanks to L'Or &amp;amp; Acast, we returned to Spring Studios for a special recording as part of the Secret Podcast Experience.&amp;nbsp;
The baking Queen Nadiya spoke to us (and a wonderful live audience) about the secret to the most delicious brownies (instant coffee!), what it’s like being part of a huge family, feeding 3000 people at her wedding, how she secretly entered the Bake Off, baking birthday cakes for everyone she knows &amp;amp; her questionable last supper (instant mash and tomato soup anyone?</description></item><item><title>S14 Ep 11: Paul Hollywood | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 04:16:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190044/</guid><description>Podcast Description By now you know that mum’s chicken soup only comes out for the big guns… and this week was exactly that.. no pressure mum - we finally got Paul Hollywood!
Despite mums soggy bottom Tart Nomande, we somehow managed to win him over &amp;amp; had the most wonderful afternoon talking a LOT about food.&amp;nbsp;Lennie even got a handshake.&amp;nbsp;
Paul told us all about how he learnt to bake on the job in his dads bakery, his love of custard, snuggling steak out of work in loaves of bread, how he made it on the Telly and sucking on salty chips!</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode: Alison Hammond | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190045/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 05:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190045/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s December! Christmas is right round the corner, so we thought we’d give you an extra festive offering this week… a special bonus episode with the wonderful, hysterical Alison Hammond!&amp;nbsp;
Thanks to our friends at @Sainsbury's we tucked into a delicious Taste the Difference Crimbo feast, sipped cocktails and laughed A LOT.&amp;nbsp;
We discuss Christmas Eve takeaways, the joys of an air fryer, her mum’s ‘Jamlish’ food, Barbie Girl - and whether to pud or not pud!</description></item><item><title>S14 Ep 10: Bjorn Ulvaeus | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190046/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 04:55:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190046/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we have an actual real life member of ABBA on Table Manners.&amp;nbsp;
Only a few days after we went to see Abba Voyage, the legend, Bjorn Ulvaeus came over to Clapham for lunch.
Bjorn told us all about how the Abba Voyage show came to fruition and how he and his band mates were turned into avatars.&amp;nbsp;
We spoke about Abba’s Eurovision win back in 1974 and what food they ate to celebrate!</description></item><item><title>S14 Ep 9: Rose Matafeo | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190047/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 05:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190047/</guid><description>Podcast Description From one Starstruck favourite to another…Rose Matafeo everyone !!&amp;nbsp;
I’m back in old rainy Blighty, and returning - in fine form if I say so myself - to cooking duty! Whilst gazing at the Matafeo powerhouse,&amp;nbsp;I made a lovely slow roast chicken from Alison Roman's book ‘Nothing Fancy’ and mum did a Saffy's LA inspired salad - it was perfect and minimal effort.&amp;nbsp;Rose spoke to us about growing up in New Zealand, resenting reggae in her teens and her love of Goat Curry.</description></item><item><title>S14 Ep 8: Nikesh Patel | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190048/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 05:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190048/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we welcome Nikesh Patel to Table Manners.&amp;nbsp;We all fell in love with him as Tom Kapoor in Starstruck, and now we can watch him play a cop in the new crime thriller ‘The Devil’s Hour’, starring opposite Peter Capaldi. Nikesh came over, before a kids birthday party, for a spot of Lennie’s ultimate….vegan cuisine. Whilst eating a stew, we talked about his mum’s fabulous Gujarati food and her famous yellow Dahl, falling in love, bleaching his hair at school, Eminem and everything else in between.</description></item><item><title>S14 Ep 7: Theo James | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190049/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 05:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190049/</guid><description>Podcast Description I’m still on tour but was missing mum and the podcast so she hopped on a flight (with my three kids, thanks ma) and got the recorder out. &amp;nbsp;
We also bagged a star of The White Lotus s2, Theo James!&amp;nbsp;After a morning of surfing, he arrived very promptly, thanks to his wife Ruth who knew what would happen if he was late (immediate judgement). We had a good old natter about wine, being the youngest child, The White Lotus (of course) all whilst eating delicious Greek food thanks to our favourites at Greekmans.</description></item><item><title>S14 Ep 6: Big Zuu | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190050/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 04:02:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Big Zuu meets Big Len!!
This week we have double BAFTA winner and all round hilarious person, Big Zuu, on Table Manners. We chatted all about Big Eats over mum’s - rather tough -&amp;nbsp;short rib beef &amp;amp; baked potatoes with sour cheese and chive stuffing.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Big Zuu talks to us about his mum's Okra soup, his love of Beyoncé and Karaoke &amp;amp; what he ate after his big BAFTA win.</description></item><item><title>S14 Ep 5: Robert De Niro, Nobu Matsuhisa and Meir Teper | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190051/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 03:00:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yes, we are talkin’ to you!!! It’s only Robert De Niro,&amp;nbsp;Mr Nobu and Meir Teper on the podcast this week.&amp;nbsp;We were invited over to the new fabulous Nobu Portman Square Hotel for some sushi where we sipped Sake &amp;amp; challenged the three of them on their best Table Manners.&amp;nbsp;
We heard all about De Niros’ famous martinis, Nobu’s experience of cooking for Princess Diana and how he became a chef.</description></item><item><title>S14 Ep 4: Baz Luhrmann | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190052/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 03:48:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190052/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a blockbuster Table Manners episode.&amp;nbsp;Having seen Romeo + Juliet 7 times in the cinema, and frequently quoting Strictly Ballroom, to have the genius, Baz Luhrmann in our kitchen was an absolute honour. Both of us are huge fans of his work so we were thrilled to ask him a hundred questions about Elvis, Romeo + Juliet, Moulin Rouge and all the other brilliant projects he has been involved in.</description></item><item><title>S14 Ep 3: John Torode | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190053/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 03:00:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190053/</guid><description>Podcast Description What do you cook for a Masterchef judge?!? That is the question.&amp;nbsp;
This week we are joined by mum’s favourite, John Torode. And it’s about time. After a LOT of back and forth on the menu, mum settled on some staples; her infamous chicken soup followed by Lebanese lamb then a damson galette and olive oil ice cream. It was very gorgeous.
This is a foodie episode, where we talk about John’s favourite chefs, the dish he was most proud of making, his wife’s sausage and sourdough bake and his secret tip for making cheese toasties extra crispy (I can confirm it works).</description></item><item><title>S14 Ep 2: Rina Sawayama | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190054/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 03:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rina Sawayama everyone… I am a huge fan of this amazing woman, we met in Paris years ago on a front row (daaaahling) and I have watched her become a complete icon. We are THRILLED to have her on Table Manners.&amp;nbsp;
Rina educates us about Japanese cuisine; chirashi bowls, eating fresh Kinmedai fish, and her mum’s signature dish of Tonkatsu… delicious! And we learn her poaching technique.&amp;nbsp;
We talk about the time she met Lady Gaga, lactose, art being her hobby &amp;amp; karaoke with Harry Styles.</description></item><item><title>S14 Ep 1: Shania Twain | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190055/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 03:10:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Summer is over, school is no longer out, and it’s time to get back to our important job of eating and being nosey. We are thrilled to be back!! It’s been a while but what a series we have lined up for you... kicking off with none other than the Queen of Country, an international icon, the only one we run to, the one, the only Shania Twain.&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode: Vick Hope | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190056/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 08:07:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190056/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are wrapping up this series of Table Manners with a very special bonus episode thanks to our pals at Sainbury’s. Last week, we hosted a summer soirée in London to celebrate the Taste the Difference summer range. What was not to love? Plenty of picky bits, ‘lo-fi dining’, a generous amount of rosé, a very loud - and well read and opinionated - audience &amp;amp; the wonderful Vick Hope as our guest.</description></item><item><title>S13 Ep 23: Table Manners Live : Question Time pt. 2 | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190057/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 03:29:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190057/</guid><description>Podcast Description We had the Mercury nominated (!!!) Self Esteem, Rebecca Lucy Taylor join us in Birmingham and finished with Julian Clary &amp;amp; Vanessa Feltz in London - fabulous guests, fabulous audiences.&amp;nbsp;In this final instalment of Table Manners live, we round up the series with some more of our favourite audience questions from Birmingham &amp;amp; London.
Dr Alex makes an appearance &amp;amp; Rebecca roams the audience a la Debbie McGee!</description></item><item><title>S13 Ep 22: Table Manners Live : Question Time | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190058/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 03:00:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190058/</guid><description>Podcast Description As part of our live shows, we held a little Q&amp;amp;A in the second half… well I tell you what listeners - you are all really quite filthy !! For the next two weeks we’ve put together some of our favourite moments from the Q&amp;amp;As, and we have been cackling!&amp;nbsp;We hope they make you laugh as much as they did us. In this week’s episode, there’s a ‘shag, marry, avoid’ theme going on &amp;amp; we discuss what mum’s boxing ring music would be… oh we do have a laugh with you lot!</description></item><item><title>S13 Ep 21: Vanessa Feltz | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190059/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 03:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190059/</guid><description>Podcast Description The live show finale.. our second night from the London Palladium with the one and only Vanessa Feltz. Now seasoned West End pros, we put our feet up and let our guest do most of the talking. And frankly, I was completely grateful.&amp;nbsp;If mum's red lip and leopard print are going to be upstaged by anyone, let it be Ms Feltz; rockin up in a sequin ball gown, along with a tower of Challah made by her daughter.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode: Blossoms | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190060/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 03:00:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Serving up an extra pint of podcast today! We teamed up with @birramoretti at this years @iowfestival to record a special live recording of Table Manners with Tom &amp;amp; Joe from @blossomsband.
Live from their Italian piazza on site at the festival, we gobbled our way through sourdough pizzas and beer and chatted all about the search for the best Spaghetti Bolognaise, Shepherd's Pie fights, pizzas as wedding food &amp;amp; how they set up their own podcast inspired by their favourite pub, called Pubcast.</description></item><item><title>S13 Ep 20: Julian Clary | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190061/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 03:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190061/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Table Manners Live tour continues to it’s final destination: the world famous, London Palladium. And even better, on a Sunday night! With Lennie in full tour mode, it was an honour &amp;amp; complete treat to share our podcast in front of such a wonderful audience and with THE King of the Palladium, Julian Clary.
Julian talks to us about what it takes to become a Palladium Hall Of Fame honouree (Lennie believes she is on her way), what’s eaten whilst playing poker with Joan Collins and pure nostalgia through broad beans!</description></item><item><title>S13 Ep 19: Self Esteem | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190062/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 03:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190062/</guid><description>Podcast Description LIVE from Birmingham Town Hall, the divine power house that is Self Esteem joined us in front of a wonderful audience.
Back in the city mum went to University, we chat over delicious food from Brum’s very own Joe Lycett’s recommended restaurant Zindiya - and talk all about how she became a pop star, her love of Mexican food, honey and toast nights with her family &amp;amp; her grandma's shiny scones.</description></item><item><title>S13 Ep 18: Adam Kay | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190063/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 03:00:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190063/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’ve waited a LONG time to get this weeks guest on the podcast, and finally - LIVE in Manchester we got him!! The wonderful Adam Kay joined us at Bridgwater Hall for Lennie's homecoming show and what a laugh it was.
Adam chatted vending machine hospital snacks, growing up eating spleen, leaving the polystyrene in his oven for 3 years, his obsession with cheesy chips &amp;amp; how he says the only home delivery anyone should have is pizza!</description></item><item><title>S13 Ep 17: Sophie Ellis Bextor | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190064/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 03:00:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190064/</guid><description>Podcast Description For the next few weeks we’re serving something slightly different as we present our Table Manners live on tour episodes. We opened the tour at the Queens Hall in Edinburgh, the wonderful Sophie Ellis Bextor was our first guest and the crowd were raucous! Sophie chatted Monster Munch, Nanny Claire’s chocolate cake, what it’s like to cook for a family of 7 and how her kitchen mantra is “this is not a café!</description></item><item><title>S13 Ep 16: Nigel Ng | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190065/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 03:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190065/</guid><description>Podcast Description HAIYAA! Lennie’s infamous microwave rice is put up to the test this week. Comedian Nigel NG aka Uncle Roger turned up to Clapham in his orange polo shirt,&amp;nbsp;ready to try mum’s food and talk rice fuck bois, nieces, nephews, Jamie Oliver and making people cackle through lockdown. We laughed a LOT and chatted all about dating a vegan, how to do karaoke, the best sparkling sake and we think maybe Uncle Roger should become Father Roger we loved him so much.</description></item><item><title>S13 Ep 15: Jennifer Saunders | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190066/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ahead of her starring role in the West End production of Sister Act, we were honoured to welcome the wonderful Jennifer Saunders onto Table Manners this week.&amp;nbsp;
We cracked opened the Bolly darling and chatting everything from frozen peas to the dream dinner party that went hideously wrong.
Jennifer told us about her discovery of rock oysters in Australia &amp;amp; her pocket money habits as a child.&amp;nbsp;
It was really just a gorgeous Friday evening with an absolute legend.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode: Jack Monroe and Nureen Glaves | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190067/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 09:22:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190067/</guid><description>Podcast Description ﻿A double helping this week! We recorded a very special episode of Table Manners with two amazing women; campaigner and author Jack Monroe &amp;amp; Nureen Glaves, the founder and CEO of National Lottery-supported Feed Me Good.
In this Good Causes special, made possible by National Lottery players, we didn’t need to cook! Jack brought her delicious ‘chicken porridge’ &amp;amp; Nureen brought her famous rum cake – what a treat!</description></item><item><title>S13 Ep 14: Mabel | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190068/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 03:00:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190068/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s Mabel’s turn on Table Manners! We welcome superstar pop star Mabel to mum’s for a home cooked meal of grilled fish &amp;amp; a knock out Banoffee pie that she took home for her dad.&amp;nbsp;
We talk all about family Christmases in Thailand, her love of Congee, different ways to cook Jollof, the reason she doesn’t eat chicken &amp;amp; what food to eat on tour!
Nowadays you will find her mucking out in the stables but a whole new record is ready for us to enjoy very soon.</description></item><item><title>S13 Ep 13: LA Special - Christine Quinn | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190069/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 03:03:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190069/</guid><description>Podcast Description For this final LA episode, we have none other than the Queen bee of real estate, the ultimate ‘boss bitch’ with the best one liner stings &amp;amp; star of Selling Sunset, Christine Quinn.
We forgive the gorgeous Christine for joining us an hour late for bagels because she’s incredibly lovely and we talk all about BBQs in Texas, her mum’s Hungarian food, the best Lobster in France &amp;amp; her addiction to soda.</description></item><item><title>S13 Ep 12: LA Special - Nancy Silverton | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190070/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 03:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Up this week… another slice of LA with none other than a national treasure, superstar chef, author &amp;amp; queen of the American artisanal loaf - Nancy Silverton.&amp;nbsp;
Famed for her sourdough starter, Nancy talks to us about her rise to the top, growing up in the valley, her obsession with pistachios &amp;amp; loving TV dinners at her grandmas.&amp;nbsp;
We recorded this episode from Nancy's famous ‘Osteria Mozza’ restaurant on Melrose Avenue and were lucky enough to taste her famous chopped salad and also had a first in eating shrimp on a pizza.</description></item><item><title>S13 Ep 11: LA Special - Jordan Firstman | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190071/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 03:00:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Writer, film maker, king of impressions and the banana bread's publicist, Jordan Firstman joins us on this weeks special episode of Table Manners.
Mum made a delicious sirloin steak salad (shout out to Jess Damuck for the accompanying pea, cucumber and asparagus salad ) &amp;amp; we sipped leftover Greekmans natural wine. Jordan told us about his secret mash potato recipe, his ‘Wicked’ themed Barmitzvah, what life was like growing up in Long Island &amp;amp; where to get the best chicken wings in LA.</description></item><item><title>S13 Ep 10: LA Special - Tony Hawk | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190072/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 03:00:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rosé at the ready! In this first LA special, we were joined poolside by&amp;nbsp;a sporting legend &amp;amp; probably the most influential skateboarders of all time, Tony Hawk.
Tony talks to us about growing up in San Diego &amp;amp; food as fuel whilst skating as a kid, the best bourbon whiskey, multi-use of Skateboard grip tape and expensive sushi,&amp;nbsp;all whilst eating mum's delicious homage to River Café’s chicken with tomatoes and olives, followed by delicious crystalized chocolate oranges!</description></item><item><title>Taking flight to La La Land | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190073/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 04:00:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lennie and I became California girls for a couple of weeks and took Table Manners to La La Land! Thanks to Virgin Atlantic, we travelled in style and documented our journey in the air! We recorded part of this special episode at 35,000 feet.&amp;nbsp;
Two weeks of food, drinks, guests and palm trees!&amp;nbsp;Table Manners the Los Angeles Affairs begins this Wednesday.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>S13 Ep 9: Thomasina Miers | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190074/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 03:23:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190074/</guid><description>Podcast Description I’ve admired the wonderful chef Thomasina Miers for a long time so we were thrilled to welcome her to Table Manners.&amp;nbsp;
Tommi kindly brought pud, but before we devoured her delicious chocolate cake with tequila and chilli, we discussed food activism, the importance of soil, Chefs for Schools, eating seasonally, food education &amp;amp; how to cook the perfect omelette, along with her love of Mexico and chillis.&amp;nbsp;
Mum made a delicious Ottolenghi courgette frittata and it really was an inspiring lunch with this Wonder Woman.</description></item><item><title>S13 Ep 8: Jamie Demetriou | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190075/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 03:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Greek-Cypriot comedian, actor, writer and all round brilliant funny guy Jamie Demetriou joins us on Table Manners this week.&amp;nbsp;
Over a rather delightful butternut squash galette (if I say so myself) and few other overzealous dishes in an attempt to wow the vegetarian, we talk about cooking for himself as a child, his dad being a chef, the importance of a good tomato sauce, pickled onion monster munch &amp;amp; him being in a band.</description></item><item><title>S13 Ep 7: Diplo | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190076/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 03:35:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190076/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we welcome American DJ &amp;amp; superstar record producer Diplo to Clapham.&amp;nbsp;
We talk all about him growing up in Florida, eating endless amounts of shrimp, growing his own Avocados, eating canned food as a child &amp;amp; how to make the most of an all-you-can-eat buffet.&amp;nbsp;
Chatting over a delicious cheese &amp;amp; charcuterie board (to be discussed in the pod!) Diplo even treated us to a potentially Grammy award winning Table Manners rap… enjoy!</description></item><item><title>S13 Ep 6: Michael Bublé | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190077/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 03:29:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190077/</guid><description>Podcast Description We did EVERYTHING in our power to get this guy in mum's kitchen, but covid had other ideas…however - the man, the legend, THE Michael Buble joins us on Table Manners on Zoom this week and he did not disappoint. We spoke about Michael’s discovery of Dishoom in London, his Nonna’s red sauce risotto, Sunday BBQs in Buenos Aires, how he met his wife, his children being bilingual &amp;amp; McDonald’s nostalgia with his grandfather.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode: Candice Brathwaite | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190078/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 03:22:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190078/</guid><description>Podcast Description AD. Thanks to PayPal we’re serving up an extra episode this week – a special bonus ep with the wonderful Candice Brathwaite who joins us to talk about her recent mission in empowering and encouraging people to open up conversations about money.&amp;nbsp;In this honest podcast, we talk about her Carribean heritage, Saturday soup, her love of oysters &amp;amp; seafood, her obsession with macaroons &amp;amp; how she knows more about Sex &amp;amp; The City than Lennie!</description></item><item><title>S13 Ep 5: Olia Hercules &amp; Alissa Timoshkina | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190079/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 04:00:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190079/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today's special episode we speak to Ukrainian chef and activist Olia Hercules and Russian chef, podcaster and writer Alissa Timoshkina. Olia and Alissa are best friends who have joined forces and set up #CookforUkraine, a culinary campaign encouraging people to cook traditional Ukrainian and eastern European food to raise money to support the humanitarian effort in Ukraine.
Cook for Ukraine's donation page has raised more than £300,000 in donations already, with the money going to Unicef to support children and families impacted by the fighting.</description></item><item><title>S13 Ep 4: Joanna Lumley | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190080/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 05:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190080/</guid><description>Podcast Description We have wanted this woman since the start of Table Manners.. she’s been on the hit list since day one and finally, we have her!&amp;nbsp;
The one, the only, Dame Joanna Lumley popped over to Clapham for a vegetable pie &amp;amp; some poached pears and it was quite frankly, absolutely fabulous.
Joanna talks to us about growing up in India, being addicted to limes, her love of the Queen &amp;amp; cocktail nights at home.</description></item><item><title>S13 Ep 3: Martin Compston | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190081/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 04:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bleary eyed after our big win, we welcomed our first AC12 guest,&amp;nbsp;Steve Arnott.. better known as Martin Compston onto Table Manners. As Line of Duty’s biggest fan, mum was in her element serving up delicious lamb &amp;amp; pistachio and only slightly disappointed not to hear an Essex accent from our Scottish guest.
We talk to Martin about his obsession with chicken wings, eating Chinese takeaway on Christmas Day, how living in Las Vegas compares to living in Glasgow &amp;amp; winning over his (now) wife via an Irish promise ring, a song and all at an 11am Happy Hour!</description></item><item><title>S13 Ep 2: Elvis Costello | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190082/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190082/</guid><description>Podcast Description We have a living legend on the podcast this week, Mr Elvis Costello OBE!
Jessie was in charge of cooking this time so Lennie was relaxed and raring to go. We talk about his musical family background, meeting his wife Diana Krall for the first time in front of an audience of millions, eating his mum’s Goulash as a child &amp;amp; paying for his first guitar from his wages as a fruit and veg boy.</description></item><item><title>S13 Ep 1: James Nesbitt | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190083/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190083/</guid><description>Podcast Description And just like that, we are BACK! LIVE from my new kitchen, finally - Clapham, we’re out, New Cross, we’re in!
And what better way to kick off the series than to spend a tequila- fuelled afternoon with today’s guest James Nesbitt (this may become a habit in this series, just call me José).
Mum and I are huge fans of James, so we’re thrilled to finally have him join us for Jamie oliver’s trusted pulled chilli brisket, a ‘moist’ clementine cake and a good old chin wag.</description></item><item><title>S12 Ep 12: Rob Brydon | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190084/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190084/</guid><description>Podcast Description What a belter of a guest for our series finale! The wonderful, charming and funny&amp;nbsp;Rob Brydon came to see us midway through his huge UK tour; he popped over to mum’s for some spatchcock chicken, pecan pie (we recorded this episode on thanksgiving), a right old gossip and sing song. We spoke about Rob growing up in Wales, eating his grandma’s custard tarts, his comedy heroes, favourite food spots in London, ‘The Trip’, ‘mucus’ topping ‘moist’ as the worst word &amp;amp; life with 5 children!</description></item><item><title>S12 Ep 11: Christmas Cracker - Listener Special with Joe Lycett and Nick Grimshaw | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190085/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 04:00:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190085/</guid><description>Podcast Description We decided to do something a bit different for Christmas this year; we wanted to feature you beautiful lot on Table Manners and hear all about your Christmas traditions, recipes &amp;amp; highlights. With the help of our pals Joe &amp;amp; Nick, we exchange holiday hacks and stories. Thank you to everyone who contributed. Maybe this is our New Years resolution! Grab a mince pie and tune in! Xx</description></item><item><title>S12 Ep 10: Claudia Roden | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190086/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 04:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190086/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a huge huge deal. We have the&amp;nbsp;living legend, the queen of the cookbook, Claudia Roden, join us on Table Manners this week.&amp;nbsp;
Much to mum’s delight (and instruction), Claudia provided the dish! She bought a delicious fish soup and mum made Claudia’s light as a feather yogurt cake for pud.&amp;nbsp;Claudia talks to us about her latest book ‘Med’ for which she traveled around France, Spain and Italy to collect recipes.</description></item><item><title>S12 Ep 9: Elizabeth Day | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190087/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190087/</guid><description>Podcast Description She’s a huge fan of our podcast and after several failed attempts (😜) we finally got the elegant, divine Elizabeth Day round to mums.&amp;nbsp;Author, journalist, presenter &amp;amp; host of the hugely successful HOW TO FAIL podcast, Elizabeth talks to us about growing up in Northern Ireland, her love of potato cakes, eating Buddha bowls on repeat, being a cheese fanatic &amp;amp; falling in love.&amp;nbsp;
Elizabeth’s latest novel ‘Magpie’ is heading for the big screen and we can’t wait!</description></item><item><title>S12 Ep 8: Max Martin | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190088/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190088/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you don’t know who Max Martin is - well, you should -&amp;nbsp;and you will quickly realise that you do in fact know most of his chart topping songs.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
We invite the enigmatic Swedish songwriter over to mum's for his first ever podcast.&amp;nbsp;We talk about&amp;nbsp;getting ready for his new musical '&amp;amp; Juliet' to finally get back to the West End, his love for Kiss the band, life in Los Angeles and growing up outside the cow border.</description></item><item><title>S12 Ep 7: Billy Porter | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190089/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190089/</guid><description>Podcast Description A Dutch baby and champagne was only right for this week’s guest, even if it was before noon….the iconic Billy Porter.
We spoke to Billy about moving from New York and living his new life in Long Island, falling in love with musical theatre after watching ‘The Whizz’, his turkey burger speciality, working with Jade Thirlwall and MNEK on his debut single &amp;amp; his many many projects! But most importantly we discussed who would play Billy’s bodyguard if we remade the movie.</description></item><item><title>S12 Ep 6: Reggie Yates | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190090/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190090/</guid><description>Podcast Description The man that does everything!! This week we welcome the wonderful Reggie Yates to Table Manners. Reggie talks to us about his West African heritage; his mum’s Ghanian cooking - we all want a bit of her special peanut soup - his love of apple crumble &amp;amp; growing up in north London. We chat about his wondrous career; from hosting radio shows in his bedroom aged 10, to becoming a TV and Radio favourite &amp;amp; now writing and directing his first feature film ‘Pirates’ (out now and well worth a watch!</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode - Laura Jackson | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190091/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190091/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's officially Autumn – our favourite time of the year – and what better way to celebrate it than to get my good pal Laura Jackson over to mum's for a good old hearty seasonal meal. This bonus episode is sponsored by Sainsbury's &amp;amp; their fantastic new Autumn Edition Taste The Difference range. We tucked into truffle houmous, chicken with a delish truffle mash potato and root vegetable gratin and for pud the most delightful Winter Berry Crumble.</description></item><item><title>S12 Ep 5: Emily Ratajkowski | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190092/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Zooming in from New York, this week we have American supermodel and actress Emily Ratajkowski on Table Manners.&amp;nbsp;
Born in London, raised in California &amp;amp; childhood summers spent in Europe, Emily talks to us about her favourite food across the globe.
We discuss baby led weaning with her son, pumpkin pie pregnancy cravings &amp;amp; where to get the best gin martini in New York.&amp;nbsp;
Emily’s new book ‘My Body’ is out now.</description></item><item><title>S12 Ep 4: Jade Thirlwall | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190093/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190093/</guid><description>Podcast Description It was an HONOUR to have our first little mixer in the house! We welcome the wonderful Jade Thirlwall to mum's for her fave meal, a roast chicken dinner with all the trimmings.&amp;nbsp;
Jade turned up in full glam after a long photo shoot so it was just what the doctor ordered for our girl. She talks about her mum’s mince pies - and not the Christmas kind - her penchant for putting crisps in a tuna sarnie, drinking Malibu and always wanting the economy meal on the aeroplane.</description></item><item><title>S12 Ep 3: Jack, Hilary &amp; Michael Whitehall | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190094/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190094/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we welcome mum’s new best friend, Hilary Whitehall with husband Michael, son Jack and a doll called Winston round to Clapham for a spot of Lebanese lamb.&amp;nbsp;
Jack talks to us about his lockdown venture Food Slut, his misjudged drinks &amp;amp; canapés parties at Manchester University &amp;amp; how he got into stand up comedy. We talk about Hilary’s home cooking, La Poule Au Pot &amp;amp; 10 things you can do with Marmalade, sadly not included in&amp;nbsp;Jack’s new book ‘How To Survive Family Holidays’ which is out now and will definitely come in handy in our house X</description></item><item><title>S12 Ep 2: Tom Daley | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190095/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190095/</guid><description>Podcast Description So this week is absolutely golden in every sense of the word … we welcome the king of knitting &amp;amp; GOLD Olympic award winner Tom Daley to mum's for lamb and dauphinois. The Plymouth born diver talks to us about his Tokyo Olympics experience, his childhood desire to be a pilot, how he met his husband Lance and their first kiss. We chat about the importance of parenthood; losing his dad at 16 years old and the relationship he has with his own son.</description></item><item><title>S12 Ep 1: Stanley Tucci | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190096/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190096/</guid><description>Podcast Description And just like that, we are BACK and ready to take over your Wednesdays!&amp;nbsp;
We hope you all had a lovely summer; Mum has enjoyed plenty of holidays and I had a baby.&amp;nbsp;
We’ve got some AMAZING guests lined up for you for this series and what better way to start that with fellow foodie, Hollywood star and absolute gent, Stanley Tucci.
Stanley talks to us about growing up in New York, filming his latest TV show ‘Searching For Italy’ &amp;amp; his fight against cancer.</description></item><item><title>S11: Extra Helpings 2 | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190097/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190097/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we have one more serving of extra helpings for you. This second episode includes some more of our favourite bits from the past year and a previously unheard conversation with Dan Levy. Hear will.i.am telling us about his Mum’s cooking and Lennie getting the giggles about muff diving @themuffkitchen! Tom Jones lets us in on some of Elvis’s unusual eating habits, Dawn French tells us about falling in love and Angela Hartnett chats about how her cooking journey began.</description></item><item><title>S11: Extra Helpings 1 | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190098/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Despite the different lockdowns and restrictions we’ve had over the past year, we’ve kept going and it’s been an absolutely stellar year of Table Manners with such fabulous guests from all around the world.&amp;nbsp;
Whilst we gear up to Series 12 (how did that happen?!) we’ve put together a couple of episodes of highlights to serve up as an extra helping.&amp;nbsp;
In this first episode, listen back to hear Dolly Parton’s room service order, Michael McIntyre’s embarrassing dad behaviour, Yungblud ordering pints at Noma, Take That’s game of ‘King Naan’, me fangirling over Kylie Minogue &amp;amp; Lydia West’s gem of knowledge about ordering cookie dough from Pizza Hut.</description></item><item><title>S11 Ep 32: Munya Chawawa | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190099/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190099/</guid><description>Podcast Description To end the series we have another first for Table Manners... a Satirist, the hilarious Munya Chawawa on this week's podcast. Munya talks to us about his Zimbabwean upbringing &amp;amp; his love of Sadza. We discuss crying over Blue songs, crashing Tinder, Watermelon Daiquiris, his wish to marry Baby Spice &amp;amp; falling in love on the radio. We love his parodies and we love him.&amp;nbsp;
A couple of episodes of highlights from the past year are coming up in the next two weeks then we’ll be back with the snazziest series yet on October 13.</description></item><item><title>S11 Ep 31: Ed Sheeran | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190100/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190100/</guid><description>Podcast Description We welcome back one of our very first Table Manners guests this week.. a relatively unknown - but cracking chap - the one and only Ed Sheeran. Gorgeous Ed joins us over zoom for an almighty catch-up. We discuss his wedding food (that I really indulged in), how to drink vintage wine, cups of tomato soup before bed, his wife Cherry’s vegetable garden &amp;amp; teaching his daughter Lyra to have good Table Manners.</description></item><item><title>S11 Ep 30: Lauren Mayberry (Chvrches) | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190101/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190101/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we welcome my daughter’s absolute favourite, Lauren Mayberry from the fantastic Chvrches to Table Manners.
The Scottish singer zooms in from LA and talks to us all about living in California, searching LA for the best curry, her mums ‘rats-pooey’, eating nachos with her dad, her love of creme eggs and she introduced me to ice cream clowns! We chat about the hopeful return of live music &amp;amp; Chvrches upcoming album ‘Screen Violence’ which is out on Aug 27th x</description></item><item><title>S11 Ep 29: Maisie Williams | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190102/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Arya Stark is in the kitchen!! We’ve been after the brilliant Maisie Williams for a long time and finally she’s here. Fashionista and queen of Game Of Thrones talks to us about her upcoming role in Danny Boyle's ‘Pistol’, spending lockdown in France, going to Pizza Express with her mum and growing her own vegetables. She’s been in GOT since the age of 12 (her very first acting job!</description></item><item><title>S11 Ep 28: Ruby Wax | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190103/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190103/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode was recorded a while back but its worth the wait. Actress, author, comedian, writer, mental health activist &amp;amp; all round fabulous woman Ruby Wax popped over to mums for some Salmon&amp;nbsp;&amp;amp; Ginger coriander crumb - from the cook book of yours truly.&amp;nbsp;We discuss how she only ate sausages as a child, not leaving the house without honey in her handbag, inviting Obama over for dinner, hanging out with Alan Rickman &amp;amp; how she created the fantastic Frazzled Cafe meetings.</description></item><item><title>S11 Bonus: Tom Grennan | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190104/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Thanks to Jameson, we’re serving you an extra tipple this week – a special bonus ep with the wonderful Tom Grennan.&amp;nbsp;
Whilst mum sips on a delicious Whiskey Sour cocky t (a mocktail for me!), Tom tells us about what festivals he’s hoping to play this summer, how he’s hoping to get to a Nao show and what’s he most looking forward to doing now things are opening up.</description></item><item><title>S11 Ep 27: Emerald Fennell | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190105/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190105/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we welcome actress, director and writer, the phenomenal Emerald Fennell round to Lennie’s for Tarragon Chicken and banana ice cream! We chat everything from her time in Call The Midwife, to writing &amp;amp; directing the absolute must - see Promising Young Woman and now her latest venture, writing Andrew Lloyd Webber&amp;rsquo;s new musical &amp;lsquo;Cinderella’. She talks about meeting her husband in Paris, the art of getting a free Pret coffee and what she’s working on next.</description></item><item><title>S11 Ep 26: Lianne La Havas | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190106/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190106/</guid><description>Podcast Description What a joy it was to be reunited with the wonderful Lianne La Havas this week. We met way back when I supported Lianne on her tour in 2012 &amp;amp; now she joins us round the table at mums for a vegan feast.&amp;nbsp;
She tells us all about growing up &amp;amp; eating with her Jamaican family in South London, her great grandmas red pea soup, her Greek heritage &amp;amp; love of Spanikopita, how she hates chocolate custard &amp;amp; her supermarket shopping trips with the one and only Prince.</description></item><item><title>S11 Ep 25: Annie Murphy | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190107/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190107/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, we zoom into Central Park to chat to the delightful Annie Murphy! We talk to dear Annie about the fact she nearly gave up on acting before getting the role of&amp;nbsp;everyone’s favourite sister, Alexis Rose in Schitt's Creek.&amp;nbsp;Growing up in Canada, Annie tells us about adoring Fawlty towers and Columbo, her Mum’s edible ‘contraption’ and dreaming of fondue in Paris. All washed down with a good glug of beer as Annie teaches Lennie what IPA is.</description></item><item><title>S11 Ep 24: Zac Posen | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190108/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Zooming in from New York, this week we welcome American fashion designer Zac Posen to Table Manners. He’s dressed the likes of Naomi Campbell, Rihanna and Princess Eugenie to name but a few, and now he’s here chatting to us about his favourite type of lettuce and where to get the best oysters.&amp;nbsp;
We discuss his love of British culture, Notting Hill hedonism, baking birthday cakes with his mum, dressing Miss Piggy for the Oscars &amp;amp; being the emperor of ice cream.</description></item><item><title>S11 Ep 23: Andrew Wong | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190109/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190109/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we invite over the 2* Michelin chef Andrew Wong to Lennie’s. He kindly brings over the main, his cod head dish (which mum was incredibly nervous about) and showers ma with gifts! We chat about leaving Oxford uni, instant noodles and growing up working in his family’s restaurant (where he met his wife). He also talks about his Mum’s sugar sandwiches and how his kids hate his food.</description></item><item><title>S11 Ep 22: Jack and Clare Penate | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190110/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190110/</guid><description>Podcast Description To celebrate my new book, Omelette coming out tomorrow, we thought it only right to invite the original Friday Night Dinner guests at the Ware Household, musician Jack Peñate and his mum Clare Penate. We celebrate 25 years of friendship and meals together, our ‘silver anniversary’ and memories of 90s dinner parties, what Jack and I dined on whilst touring America back when I was his backing singer and I discover what Fray Bentos is!</description></item><item><title>S11 Ep 21: Ed Miliband | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190111/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190111/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we welcome the ex leader of the opposition, labour MP Ed Miliband.&amp;nbsp;We talk about his refugee parents and his Polish mothers food, his love for Chinese food and his new passion, cold water swimming!
He is candid about his times as leader of the Labour Party the challenges and some regrets.&amp;nbsp;We chat about his book Go Big, he has seconds of Mum’s main and chuckles at her pudding, an Eton mess.</description></item><item><title>S11 Ep 20: Michelle Visage | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190112/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190112/</guid><description>Podcast Description We recorded this beaut of an episode with the one and only Michelle Visage, who came over to mums for a ‘Thai Pie’.&amp;nbsp;Michelle talks about growing up in New Jersey, being adopted by a Jewish family and moving to NYC to be taken into the House of Magnifique where she became a part of a voguing troupe and later best friends with Ru Paul.&amp;nbsp;She chats about her 90s girl group, working with Ru and the story behind her iconic name.</description></item><item><title>S11 Ep 19: St Vincent | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190113/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190113/</guid><description>Podcast Description We welcome the phenomenal St Vincent to Table Manners. Talking to Annie in her LA studio&amp;nbsp;over zoom, we chat about going blonde, growing up in Dallas with her family and eating - by her own admission - some questionable canned food and meat.&amp;nbsp;
Mum manages to coax her into agreeing that&amp;nbsp;nobody really likes kale and we hear about her step dad's 'Schloop', working in a Mexican restaurant and being a gal who doesn't like her salad dressed.</description></item><item><title>S11 Ep 18: Paul and Mary McCartney | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190114/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190114/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do you behave when you have a music icon on your podcast? Well, you have a massive fight in front of him of course!
Aside from a small bout of bickering, we had lunch with Sir Paul and Mary McCartney&amp;nbsp;and talked&amp;nbsp;about 30 years of Linda McCartney's legacy in the vegetarian food market. We hear about Mary’s adventurous childhood&amp;nbsp;on tour with Wings,&amp;nbsp;Paul talks about life after The Beatles and they&amp;nbsp;share memories of becoming vegetarian with Linda cooking a macaroni turkey so Paul could carve something at Christmas.</description></item><item><title>S11 Ep 17: Guy Garvey | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190115/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190115/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we welcome Manchester mensch Guy Garvey over for lunch. We chat to Guy over Ottolenghi lamb and pistachio patties about being dragged to black pudding stalls in Bury market growing up, his original worker bee tattoo and the importance of eating pies up north. He tells us how he met his wife Rachel at a wedding over cigarettes, having dinner with Joan Collins and his secret ingredient - instant coffee - in his spag bol sauce.</description></item><item><title>S11 Ep 16: Tom Jones | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190116/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190116/</guid><description>Podcast Description We were delighted to have our most requested guest, Sir Tom Jones, over to Lennie’s for lamb shanks, a lemon curd roulade and a chat about his new album ‘Surrounded By Time’. We go way back and talk about Tom growing up in the 50’s, playing marbles, falling in love and getting married at 16. We also hear about his beloved mother’s corned beef pie. He reminisces about meals shared with Elvis Presley, Las Vegas bourbons with Frank Sinatra &amp;amp; Tom’s son / manager Mark even makes an appearance, telling us how his Dad isn’t a very good cook.</description></item><item><title>S11 Ep 15: Laura Mvula | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190117/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190117/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we invite Laura Mvula over for lunch. Laura is about to bring out her third record on July 2, Pink Noise, so to celebrate Lennie made a sumptuous chicken, spiced potatoes, salad and Nigella's salted chocolate chunks!
We talk about the ‘changing landscape’ in the music industry, her musically gifted siblings and her podcast series ’So You Wanna Be A Musician’ she launched with her sister.&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>S11 Ep 14: Benny Blanco | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190118/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190118/</guid><description>Podcast Description We welcome back one of my favourite people in the world, Benny Blanco to TM. Mum didn&amp;rsquo;t get to be in the episode we recorded in LA years ago so it felt only right to chat to Benny again! He talks about his new album Friends Keep Secrets 2, working with Gracie Abrams, his 2 cooking shows about eating (hence why Ben and I get on so well) and being the king of slow cooked meat.</description></item><item><title>S11 Ep 13: Naomi Scott | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190119/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Now that we can record outside, it was a pleasure to have over the treasure that is Naomi Scott for a Tuna Nicoise salad and Orange &amp;amp; Almond cake.
We first met at a Vogue x Tiffany fashion party for the&amp;nbsp;BAFTAs and I adored her. Everyone knows her for playing Princess Jasmine in the Aladdin remake, but now she has turned her hand to fictional podcasting, producing and starring in 'Soft Voice' alongside Olivia Cooke and Bel Powley.</description></item><item><title>S11 Ep 12: will.i.am | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190120/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190120/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fill up my cup! We have will.i.am&amp;nbsp;on TM!&amp;nbsp;Will talks about his ‘pancizza' creation (a pancake pizza), being a vegan over the past 4 years, how he loves a song with ‘boom’ in the lyrics and growing up eating his Mum’s goulash. We get to learn how 'Ordinary People' came about with John Legend, Black Eyed Peas record label stories, his involvement with Beats and singing ‘mazal tov’ around the world!</description></item><item><title>S11 Ep 11: Jon Sopel | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190121/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190121/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a GREAT episode.&amp;nbsp;Zooming in from Washington DC, we talk to BBC North America Editor Jon Sopel about his new book ‘UnPresidented'.
Jon reveals that he was known to Trump as 'the guy who asks stroppy questions in the briefing room’. We get to hear about Obama's Christmas parties and the exquisite food laid on compared to the fries and chicken wings at Trump's do. He's been - and reported from - everywhere and we hear what family life is like for an international correspondent.</description></item><item><title>S11 Ep 10: Hannah Ware | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190122/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190122/</guid><description>Podcast Description The time has come for the world to meet Lennie's number one, The One's leading lady and the one who knocked her little sister's front tooth out. Zooming in from LA, and making a classic Ware effort in her dressing gown, Hannah Ware joins Table Manners!&amp;nbsp;
Boyfriend Jonah (who runs the fab Freedman’s LA restaurant) is on hand to be sound tech and meal translator whilst Han talks about having heart palpitations when sharing a takeaway meal with Jessie.</description></item><item><title>S11 Ep 9: Dan Levy | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190123/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190123/</guid><description>Podcast Description This guest has not only won every award under the sun, now he's had Lennie get the ring light on and quote every line of his global television phenomenon,&amp;nbsp;Schitt's Creek to him! We welcome with wide, open, Jewish motherly arms the sensational Dan Levy to TM!
Fresh off the back of Golden Globe wins, we natter with this Toronto mensch from his childhood home and discuss his love of Heat magazine, London and working with his family.</description></item><item><title>S11 Ep 8: Lydia West | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190124/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190124/</guid><description>Podcast Description "La!" We've got the divine Lydia West from the extraordinary C4 show 'It's A Sin' on this week's Table Manners.
But we must thank Olly Alexander for putting a good word in for us!
Currently filming an Apple TV series called Suspicion, Lydia dazzled us with her smile and maybe her fabulous zoom lighting that mum instantly bought online.
Aged 25 when she got into acting, Lydia talks about growing up in Barnet with her mother the feeder, her dad the amazing chef and her Irish granny round the corner who does a mean lamb roast and pineapple upside down cake.</description></item><item><title>S11 Ep 7: Fearne Cotton | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190125/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190125/</guid><description>Podcast Description With over 40 million listens on her podcast, it felt only right to celebrate the wonder of Fearne Cotton as she starts a new series of Happy Place this week.
A voice and personality we all know and love, Fearne talks about everything from her Happy Place Festival, being in the public eye and loving an early night to writing books, including her new Sunday Times Bestseller Speak Your Truth which is out now.</description></item><item><title>S11 Ep 6: Andrew Lloyd Webber | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190126/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190126/</guid><description>Podcast Description We welcome our 2nd EGOT guest (Emmy, Grammy, Tony, Oscar), the musical LEGEND Andrew Lloyd Webber!
Andrew talks to us over zoom about his new musical Cinderella opening in spring and written by Emerald Fennell (side note watch Promising Young Woman!).
Mum and Andrew bond over their loathing of kale and we salute his campaign for getting theatres open safely. We also learn about his brilliantly rude Aunt Viola, one of the first TV chefs who wrote one the rudest cookbooks he’s ever read.</description></item><item><title>S11 Ep 5: Jenna Coleman | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190127/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190127/</guid><description>Podcast Description This weeks guest is the glorious star of &amp;lsquo;The Serpent’ Jenna Coleman! She tells us all about how she had to learn French for the role of Marie-Andree, taking a 1970’s pencil sharpener home from the set as a memento and filming in Bangkok &amp;amp; wait for it&amp;hellip;. Tring!! We discuss her upbringing in Blackpool, hiding cream cheese sandwiches in vases, childhood karaoke sessions with @charlottechurch and what she&amp;rsquo;d have on her last day of food.</description></item><item><title>S11 Ep 4: Slowthai | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190128/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190128/</guid><description>Podcast Description With Mum being a huge connoisseur of hip hop and rapping, this week we invited the brilliant Slowthai to join us over Zoom from his studio basement at his Mum’s in Northampton. We chat about recording his brand new album, ‘Tyron&amp;rsquo; during lockdown, Sunday roasts, his Mum’s secret ingredients for the perfect roast potatoes and his go to meal to impress his fiancé. Mum asks about award shows and alcohol and we find out that he&amp;rsquo;s still owed 50 quid for a hot sauce challenge he won.</description></item><item><title>S11 Ep 3: Angela Hartnett | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190129/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190129/</guid><description>Podcast Description Big week! Mum had her vaccine, Joe Biden is now president, Mum also discovers Muff Kitchen and her first drag name is suggested (thanks Martha Delacey).&amp;nbsp;
But more importantly, we have the incomparable Angela Hartnett on TM! Talking to us from her Spitalfields home, we chat about what's for tea, being in a culinary 'power couple' with her partner, working for Gordon Ramsey and we discuss the difficulty the hospitality sector is facing during the pandemic.</description></item><item><title>S11 Ep 2: Eva Longoria | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190130/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190130/</guid><description>Podcast Description Back in September, we talked to the delightful Eva Longoria.&amp;nbsp;At the time of our chat over Zoom, she was working hard campaigning for Joe Biden to become President.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;With her own cookbook having come out in 2011, we talked recipes, cooking after long flights and she taught us how to make her ‘4 minute chicken taco recipe’.&amp;nbsp;The Desperate Housewives star offered up tips on how to make banana bread and she loves a strawberry rhubarb pie, stockpiling&amp;nbsp;rhubarb in her freezer.</description></item><item><title>S11 Ep 1: Elizabeth Olsen | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190131/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190131/</guid><description>Podcast Description New year, new series and TIER 5000 ain't gonna stop us bringing you Table Manners, no siree! We have got a great series lined up for you, kicking off with none other than the queen of Marvel &amp;amp; Table Manners' biggest fan - Elizabeth Olsen.&amp;nbsp;
Elizabeth talks about growing up in the Californian Valley, her mums 70’s food habits, her friendship with HAIM &amp;amp; being the younger sister to Mary Kate &amp;amp; Ashley.</description></item><item><title>S10 - Christmas Nibbles | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190132/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190132/</guid><description>Podcast Description To round off 2020, I invited a handful of our favourite Table Manners guests back for our very own little Christmas drinks do! (Via zoom of course ) I didn’t tell mum who was coming...hence the screams!!&amp;nbsp;
Who listens to Mariah Carey ‘All I Want For Christmas’ all year round?? Who missed out on a main role in the school nativity? Who normally spends Christmas in Norway &amp;amp; who’s going to be dressing the whole family in Disney PJs this year?</description></item><item><title>Bonus Episode - Sam Fender | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190133/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Thanks to Jameson, we’re serving you an extra tipple this week – a special bonus ep with the wonderful Sam Fender. Whilst sipping on delicious cocktails, Sam tells us where he’s most excited about performing when things go back to normal and for one of his Nights Worth Waiting For he is longing for a ‘staff curry’ at his favourite restaurant in North Shields. He tells us about recording his new album in Ireland and why he chose to cover Lindisfarne&amp;rsquo;s’ ‘Winter Song’ for his new single.</description></item><item><title>S10 Ep 14: Robbie Williams | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190134/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190134/</guid><description>Podcast Description I used to have his posters plastered on my walls (and ceilings), cry at his concerts and now I’m spending my Friday evening zooming him with my mum. This week we chat to the one and only @robbiewilliams.&amp;nbsp;
Robbie tells us all about who in @takethat can handle the spiciest curry aka ‘King Naan’,&amp;nbsp;his love of Coke Zero, what happens when you eat too much tuna, Stokey Oatcakes &amp;amp; just how much he loves his wife.</description></item><item><title>S10 Ep 13: Gemma Arterton | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190135/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190135/</guid><description>Podcast Description The greatest compliment I have ever received is that my doppelgänger is this week's guest Gemma Arterton, so obviously I discussed that with her, as well as our shared love of marmite and peanut butter and how we both have a sister called Hannah.&amp;nbsp;
Gemma tells us about growing up in Gravesend, eating Yak, her love of baking, filming in the Nepalese mountains &amp;amp; cheese being her one true love.</description></item><item><title>S10 Ep 12: Dolly Parton | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190136/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190136/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a BIG one!!! Straight out of Nashville, the one and only Country ICON Dolly Parton joins us on Table Manners.
We chatted to Dolly - dressed head to toe in festive gear - back in October, before her beautiful book Storyteller had reached these shores and before we knew she had potentially helped cure covid with her generous donation to help fund a covid vaccine.&amp;nbsp;
As well as telling us all about cosying up with Michael Buble on her new christmas record ‘A Holly Dolly Christmas’ she talks to us about her upbringing in the mountains, being one of 12 children, her speciality of Chicken and Dumplings, that Glastonbury show and the very first time she heard Whitney Houston sing her song on the radio.</description></item><item><title>S10 Ep 11: Meghan Trainor | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190137/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dialling in from sunny LA, Meghan Trainor joined us on Table Manners dressed in her best festive get up to talk about her new Christmas album ‘A Very Trainor Christmas’.
As well as music, we chat about pregnancy cravings, her love of Pop Tarts, double dates with Chloe Moretz &amp;amp; how nothing beats Pizza Express in London. To top it all off, we were treated to a rendition of Beyonce - Single Ladies by mum (Meghan's Karaoke song) – enjoy!</description></item><item><title>S10 Ep 10: Yungblud | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190138/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190138/</guid><description>Podcast Description (Warning, I think this guest&amp;nbsp;swears more than me)&amp;nbsp;
Before we entered Lockdown 2.0, we had the pleasure of high tea’ing with a young gentleman by the name of&amp;nbsp;Yungblud at mum's.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Whilst sipping on champagne and eating sausage rolls, Dominic talks all about Hobnobs, Yorkshire tea &amp;amp; his mum’s Doncaster cake shop ‘Jaffa &amp;amp; Cakes’, named after the family sausage dog.
He tells us about his rockstar lifestyle; hanging out in 'Hollyweird', nights out with Brooklyn Beckham, elephant tattoos &amp;amp; just wanting a pint of lager at Noma, the best restaurant in the world.</description></item><item><title>S10 Ep 9: Simon Rogan | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190139/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190139/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we welcome Michelin star chef Simon Rogan to Table Manners. We recorded this back in September when Simon came round to mum's for a socially distanced Prawn Saganaki and a Simon Rogan Apple Tart. We talk about The Lake District, learning his trade in a Greek restaurant, getting starstruck at Tears For Fears, his farm, where he produces the finest local ingredients for his restaurant L’Enclume and his move away from a sports career!</description></item><item><title>S10 Ep 8: Cat Deeley | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190140/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190140/</guid><description>Podcast Description I think this week's guest loves Champagne even more than mum does! Queen of the telly @catdeeley came over for scallops and plenty of champers and we had a jolly good laugh. Cat talks to us about growing up in Birmingham, meeting her husband on Fame Academy, his movie style declaration of love, making it stateside &amp;amp; we reminisce about SMTV days with @antanddec&amp;nbsp;
She swapped her pudding for another glass of champagne and proudly admitted to having bad table manners - Cat, we salute you!</description></item><item><title>S10 Ep 7: Shea Coulee | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190141/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190141/</guid><description>Podcast Description "Her name is Shea Couleé, and she didn't come to play, she came to slay!” &amp;amp; THAT THEY DID!!! We were lucky enough to get RuPaul's Drag Race All Stars Winner on Table Manners this week and what a dream it was. I've been a HUGE fan of Drag Race (Mama Ru please can I be a guest judge) so it was a pleasure to have the generous, kind and BEYOND fabulous reigning champ Shea tell us about the creation of Ms Couleé, learning to do makeup &amp;amp; who’s their best drag queen friend.</description></item><item><title>S10 Ep 6: Dawn French | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190142/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190142/</guid><description>Podcast Description As you know - mum's chicken soup comes out for the big guns and this week's guest is no exception. Soup was demanded and joyfully served for the brilliant Dawn French to commence an evening of intriguing and confessional conversation.&amp;nbsp;
A fellow foodie, Dawn tells us all about what makes the Cornish pasty, her favourite eating spots in Cornwall, making ‘breakfast cake’ in lockdown and her experience of boarding school dinners and butter.</description></item><item><title>S10 Ep 5: Grace Dent | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190143/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190143/</guid><description>Podcast Description The fantastically glamorous Grace Dent arrived in Clapham having already won mum over with her leopard print dress as soon as she step through the door.&amp;nbsp;The broadcaster, author and restaurant critic joined us round the dinner table for mum's delicious harissa meatballs whilst mum and I fawned over her every word.
We heard about her dad’s famous ‘Sketty’, her love of Angel Delight and a drink she describes as ‘Happiness In A Glass’ - a Pina Colada.</description></item><item><title>S10 Ep 4: Chris and Rosie Ramsey | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190144/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190144/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we welcome wonderful fellow podcasters Chris &amp;amp; Rosie Ramsey to Table Manners. We recorded it on publication day of their brand new book, ‘Sh**ged.Married.Annoyed.&amp;rsquo; which has been a HUGE success (Sunday Times bestseller). The excellent couple join us on Zoom to talk about eating too fast, who has better Table Manners and never getting full on a Pizza. Who knew that Rosie sang at a Leek &amp;amp; Onion Show?</description></item><item><title>S10 Ep 3: Kylie Minogue | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190145/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190145/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is big. This is huge!!!!!
The one and only ultimate pop princess and style icon arrived in Clapham, followed by paparazzi on a hump day.&amp;nbsp;
Kylie was the first concert I ever went too and we named our guinea pigs after her (and Jason) so who can blame me for the fangirl situation! Kylie tells us all about her upbringing in Australia and her journey to fame, where Charlene's famous overalls are now &amp;amp; how she’ll only have a questionable half sized cup of tea.</description></item><item><title>S10 Ep 2: James Bay | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190146/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190146/</guid><description>Podcast Description He didn't wear the hat,&amp;nbsp;but Lennie still loved having James Bay round for dinner. The 'Hold Back The River' heart-throb joined us at mum's for Some Coq Au Riesling (thanks for the recommendation Mr McIntyre), a Passionate Eton mess and plenty of the most delicious red wine courtesy of James. We spoke about busking, his legendary Grammys performance, jumping up and down on a trampoline with Rosie Huntingdon Whiteley, writing his 3rd album and eating cold Heinz Five Beanz.</description></item><item><title>S10 Ep 1: Michael McIntyre | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190147/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190147/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's season 10 and we bagged a podcast newbie! Mr Michael McIntyre - we knew we’d love you but now we are absolutely HOOKED!&amp;nbsp;You have finally broken my fear of watching comedy, with this front row seat to your hilarity and three hours of laughing 'til we cried!&amp;nbsp;From the moment Michael walked in (thermometer in hand), we did not stop laughing.&amp;nbsp;We spoke about fridge habits, restaurant etiquette, egg-offs with his wife and his mum, excitable Rosé, trying to be cool for his children &amp;amp; food pronunciation!</description></item><item><title>Extra Helpings ep. 2 | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190148/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190148/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are serving you another episode of extra helpings before series 10 starts next week. This week we have BAFTA winner Aisling Bea and mum have a discussion about dogging, Jo Brand talks about her worst ever heckle and Scary Spice reveals she has fainting goats.
We also have Kiefer Sutherland's excellent Hollywood anecdotes, Mel and Sue on sourdough starters and Florence Pugh keeps it clean with dildos and dog toys.</description></item><item><title>Extra Helpings ep. 1 | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190149/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190149/</guid><description>Podcast Description Whilst we gear up for Series 10 we’ve put together a couple of episodes to serve up as an extra helping - some of our favourite moments from Table Manners over the last few series.&amp;nbsp;
In this first special highlights episode, listen back to blow-torch gate with Hayley Squires, singalongs with Haim &amp;amp; mum asking Antoni Porowski to strip off! From David Schwimmer rinsing Dr Alex’ banana bread to London Hughes on vegans and Roisin Murphy beating her meat - it’s all in there!</description></item><item><title>S9 Ep 30: Melanie C | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190150/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190150/</guid><description>Podcast Description I tell you what I want....Sporty Spice in mum's back garden dressed in her best sports gear, midriff showing with a&amp;nbsp;champagne in her hand. Well, for our last episode of the series (don’t worry we’ll be back with another serving VERY soon!) The wonderful Melanie C came over for afternoon tea, for a real life, face-to-face chat &amp;amp; it was such a treat. Melanie spoke about leaving home at 16, initially missing out on getting into the Spice Girls, being in the studio with the legendary Left Eye Lopez and how she can’t resist a Tommy’s Margarita.</description></item><item><title>S9 Ep 29: James Blunt | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190151/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190151/</guid><description>Podcast Description Not only has this week’s guest sold over 20 million records, but he also owns his very own pub and a restaurant in Verbier.&amp;nbsp;
Best known for his hit ‘You’re Beautiful’ (don’t worry, there is a rendition from mum), James Blunt came over to Clapham at the end of last year &amp;amp; joined us for some delicious Eggs Arnold Bennett (thanks for the recipe Felicity Cloake!) James talks about his service in the army, living in Ibiza, how he can’t resist an In &amp;amp; Out Burger and why he doesn’t have any food on his rider.</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode - Roman Kemp | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190152/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2020 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190152/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, thanks to our friends at Nespresso, we’re giving you an extra shot of Table Manners with the dish of the airwaves &amp;amp; coffee enthusiast, Roman Kemp.
With pop royalty as parents, Roman tells us about his musical upbringing (and his mum demanding family harmonies), having a Kray as a father &amp;amp; George Michael being his godfather! From pleasurable pizza in Positano, to eating fish eyes in the Jungle – this episode has it all.</description></item><item><title>S9 Ep 28: Twiggy | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190153/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190153/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Table Manners this week, we welcome the iconic Twiggy. Mum was particularly excited about this one; they both grew up in the swinging 60's &amp;amp; mum admits to having dressed up as Twiggy in her school days.&amp;nbsp;Twiggy spills the tea on her days of touring the world; winning 2 golden globes, turning down Steve McQueen for a dance and the time Sonny &amp;amp; Cher threw her a party in Los Angeles.</description></item><item><title>S9 Ep 27: Alanis Morissette | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190154/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190154/</guid><description>Podcast Description Isn't it ironic having a zoom date with Alanis Morrisette? No - but that doesn't matter!!! This was a moment for us. Mum &amp;amp; I are both HUGE fans of this international goddess so it was&amp;nbsp;an honour and delight to have her on the podcast.
Born in Canada, raised in LA &amp;amp; now living in San Francisco – Alanis tells us about her upbringing, being a twin, her family life and her journey to success.</description></item><item><title>Ovie Soko Live From #SamsungKX | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190155/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190155/</guid><description>Podcast Description #AD | Welcome to Casa Amor aka #SamsungKX! We’re serving up an extra helping this week with the help of @samsunguk &amp;amp; it’s Connected Living experience! Samsung gave us free reign of their top notch kitchen for the day where we cooked up our onion quiche (a la Carly Rae Jepsen!) &amp;amp; hosted a special episode of Table Manners with the charming Ovie Soko.&amp;nbsp;
Since winning the heart of the nation, on what his mum called ‘Vanity Island’, Ovie has gone on to become one of the Island’s most well known contestants.</description></item><item><title>S9 Ep 26: Adam Lambert | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190156/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190156/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode was recorded last year but is worth the wait. Probably one of our most glamorous guests to dates; Adam Lambert arrived in Clapham in his blue platforms fit for a Spice Girl or Marc Bolan and the most divine velvet suit. The Indiana born superstar tells us all about his experience on American Idol &amp;amp; his more recent worldwide touring with Queen. We talk all about the importance of a tour outfit, having tequila on the rider and his favourite food spots from around the world&amp;hellip;.</description></item><item><title>S9 Ep 25: George Alagiah | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190157/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190157/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week's guest has topped the leaderboard for mum and what a pleasure it was to have the charming &amp;amp; delightful George Alagiah on Table Manners.&amp;nbsp;
Zooming in from Hackney, the long standing BBC broadcaster, journalist and best-selling author tells us about his upbringing in Ghana, his experiences of being a foreign correspondent, interviewing Nelson Mandela &amp;amp; his love for writing thrillers!
We hear all about George’s Nando's order, his mum's Sri Lankan cooking &amp;amp; how he learnt his Table Manners from his aunt Greta.</description></item><item><title>S9 Ep 24: Jake Bugg | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190158/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190158/</guid><description>Podcast Description From Pot Noodles to Nobu, this week’s guest is our kind of guy! Hugely successful singer, songwriter Jake Bugg tells us about his musical journey so far; being signed at 17, touring with Noel Gallagher, Karaoke in Japan &amp;amp; being the theme tune for BBC TV Series Happy Valley (but he hasn't even seen it yet).&amp;nbsp;
We talk plenty drinks and school 'lunches' back home sneaking a quick beer before&amp;nbsp;maths lessons!</description></item><item><title>S9 Ep 23: Michael Sheen | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190159/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190159/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tuning in from South Wales, this week on Table Manners we welcome superstar screen actor, theatre don and fellow UNICEF ambassador Michael Sheen.&amp;nbsp;
Sheen talks to us about growing up in Wales, eating his grandmother's famous Cawl and tinned potatoes.
Having become an international star (despite being scouted by Arsenal Football club Youth team as a child!) Sheen tells us about his USA go-to diner recommendations, his obsession with coffee &amp;amp; doughnuts &amp;amp; missing Welsh food whilst living in LA.</description></item><item><title>S9 Ep 22: David Lammy | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190160/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190160/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we welcome Tottenham-bred Labour MP David Lammy to Table Manners. It was a pleasure to zoom him in from across London and talk all about his 20 years of serving as a member of parliament for Tottenham, the Lammy review on BAME representation in the criminal justice system and the fact that Boris has not implemented enough of his 35 recommendations.&amp;nbsp;He tells us all about his Guyanese parents; his mum's famous pepper pot &amp;amp; patties, coach trips to Skegness &amp;amp; his new book ’Tribes’.</description></item><item><title>The Tables Have Turned with Zane Lowe | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190161/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190161/</guid><description>Podcast Description Here’s a little amuse-bouche for you - let’s call it a Friday treat. Today, my fourth record is out &amp;lsquo;What’s Your Pleasure?&amp;rsquo; and to celebrate we did something a bit different. One of the best interviewers I know, Zane Lowe joins us for a special (and completely unorthodox) ‘Tables Have Turned’ episode and we talk all things music (&amp;amp; of course a bit about food). We’ll have Zane back for a proper dinner soon.</description></item><item><title>S9 Ep 21: Emily Eavis | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190162/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190162/</guid><description>Podcast Description If we can’t get to Glastonbury Festival, we thought we’d bring a little bit of Glastonbury to you.&amp;nbsp;
What an honour to have the Queen of Worthy farm, Emily Eavis on Table Manners on the week where Glasto would have been celebrating 50 years with all of us in the SUNNY fields.
We delve right into Glastonbury food; how they choose the food stalls, specialities (the secret Goan Curry by West Holts), artist's private chefs, and of course mum has secured&amp;nbsp;a Chicken Matzoh ball soup stand for next year&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>S9 Ep 20: Munroe Bergdorf | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190163/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190163/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we have the incredible activist and model Munroe Bergdorf on Table Manners. We were so lucky to have one of the UK’s leading black trans queer voices on our podcast at this pivotal time, straight off her massive victory and reconciliation with L’Oreal after being dropped for speaking out about racism and white privilege three years ago.&amp;nbsp;We find out how her name started off on the drag scene, her transition at 24, whilst also discussing forgiveness, progress and Octopus.</description></item><item><title>S9 Ep 19: Joe Lycett | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190164/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190164/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we welcome the joyous Joe Lycett onto Table Manners. Cheering us up from his living room in&amp;nbsp;Birmingham, the TV presenter and comedian talks to us all about how he became a comedian, his mum's faggots and mash, writing sitcoms in lockdown &amp;amp; his affinity for ‘stodge’. Formerly known as Hugo Boss (it's a long but excellent story), Joe cracks the cheesiest of jokes (courtesy of his big sister) and admits to having Eminem as his karaoke song.</description></item><item><title>S9 Ep 18: Homo Sapiens Podcast - Alan Cumming &amp; Chris Sweeney | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190165/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 03:04:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190165/</guid><description>Podcast Description Its Pride month and the events in America have shown that solidarity of all creeds is needed today just as much as when Pride was&amp;nbsp;born out of the Stonewall riots back in June 1969.
A pioneer of the Pride Movement was Marsha P. Johnson, a black trans woman,&amp;nbsp;who devoted her life to fighting for equality and gay rights before being murdered.&amp;nbsp;She was thought to be the person who threw the first brick at the Stonewall Riots in 1969.</description></item><item><title>S9 Ep 17: JoJo | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190166/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190166/</guid><description>Podcast Description She was that voice we all knew, sung the songs that were always on the radio, her first support tour was for Usher and all at the age of 13. This week we talk to Boston born JoJo and hear her tough, frustrating and honest story about her dealings with the music industry that ended up with her not being able to be heard for years.
Fast forward to 2020, she's won a Grammy, her current record was top of the R&amp;amp;B charts in the US and she's currently in lockdown with her mum.</description></item><item><title>S9 Ep 16: Ellie Goulding | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190167/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190167/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a dramatic start where a door-to-door salesman (not following social-distance guidelines!) threatened to smash through Lennie’s window, we welcomed our most-requested guest Ellie Goulding to Table Manners this week.&amp;nbsp;
Ellie shares her bio-hack veggie lockdown eating must-haves, how to prep for lockdown grocery store queues and her fears of the essential-item trolley police!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
We hear the origins of her romance with husband Caspar, her multiple wedding day outfits that saw the singer end up in Vogue for the first time, and missing out on trying her wedding cake or any of the food.</description></item><item><title>S9 Ep 15: Joe Wicks | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190168/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190168/</guid><description>Podcast Description In between his daily PE lessons, we managed to lock down the king of quarantine, Joe Wicks AKA The Body Coach to join us on Table Manners and what a joy it was! Straight out of A&amp;amp;E and onto the podcast, Joe chatted to us about his lockdown routine, his newly appointed teaching assistant (his wife!), his gin collection, nothing beating a burger and chips, his brand new book ‘Wean In 15’ &amp;amp; we discuss our shared mutual respect for the Moana soundtrack.</description></item><item><title>S9 Ep 14: Florence Pugh | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190169/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190169/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lockdown you are spoiling us!!
We managed to zoom in to the delightful British actress, Oscar nominated star of Little Women, Florence Pugh's Los Angeles garden studio for a chat.&amp;nbsp;
We talk about her sourdough starter 'Maggie', family and how her ma made the best dressed mum's list at the Oscars.&amp;nbsp;
We bond over Tiramisu and hear what's she growing in her veg patch, being the 'Queen of the cheeseboard’, lockdown Los Angeles and her new puppy finding a dildo in the backyard.</description></item><item><title>S9 Ep 13: John Legend | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190170/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190170/</guid><description>Podcast Description Zooming straight in from LA, this week John bloody Legend joins us on Table Manners. The EGOT winner (Emmy, Grammy, Oscar &amp;amp; Tony award winner&amp;hellip;mum didn&amp;rsquo;t know what that meant either) sat down to chat to us whilst eating his wife’s home cooked chicken soup and dumplings. John talks about being in charge of breakfast in the Legend/Teigen household, growing up in Ohio, stockpiling A1 sauce, being a pro chair dancer and we get to the bottom of the ‘eating chicken wings before a show’ situation!</description></item><item><title>S9 Ep 12: Josh Groban | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190171/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190171/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we had our first guest zoom in from across the pond; American singer, songwriter, actor and record producer Josh Groban joins us on the podcast from sunny Los Angeles.
Josh talks us through his musical journey, from starting in musical theatre, duetting with Celine Dion when he was&amp;nbsp;only 16 to making a 4 year album with the master, Rick Rubin. Quarantine has awoken a new found passion for cooking; he makes a ‘mean’ beans on toast &amp;amp; has realised he enjoys singing in the shower, even with a puffer on.</description></item><item><title>S9 Ep 11: Mel and Sue | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190172/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190172/</guid><description>Podcast Description We were SO thrilled to get the UK’s finest - the greatest and warmest comedic duo Mel &amp;amp; Sue on Table Manners this week, via our new friend Zoom.
'Perky' &amp;amp; 'Melly', as they call each other, dialled in – Mel live from inside her wardrobe – and made mum and I feel so much better about another week in lockdown.&amp;nbsp;The fabulous twosome talk to us about their brand new Sky Originals/Now TV show 'Hitmen', they Mrs &amp;amp; Mrs each other's last supper,&amp;nbsp;tell us what they’re eating in lockdown, what a ‘special purse’ is &amp;amp; they reminisce about their Bake Off days!</description></item><item><title>S9 Ep 10: Emily Maitlis | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190173/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190173/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the midst of this lockdown we managed to have lunch with Dr Alex&amp;rsquo;s favourite, award winning broadcaster and Newsnight presenter Emily Maitlis. We talk about Corona, of course, that Prince Andrew interview, being a flexitarian, the cake and cookie counter at the Newsnight studio and her love for a dirty vodka martini with 3 olives (my kind of woman). She hates a pud, her favourite food is Vietnamese and our Emily is insistent on having napkins on the dinner table.</description></item><item><title>S9 Ep 9: Dua Lipa | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190174/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190174/</guid><description>Podcast Description So it may be week 2 of lockdown but we have something to celebrate. We have been trying to get this star for aaaaages and finally we did! Popstar sensation Dua Lipa shares a virtual dinner with mum and I whilst she is stuck in London quarantine with her excellent second album Future Nostalgia just out.
We talk stockpiling hot sauces, Nutella sandwiches in her lunchbox, Pez rider requests, where she goes for good sushi dates in NYC and mum and Dua bond over gel nails.</description></item><item><title>S9 Ep 8: Nick Grimshaw | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190175/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190175/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's lockdown. But that isn't going to stop us serving you Tables Manners, even in special circumstances.
I've moved the family out to an Airbnb to make sure Corona can't get her mitts on Lennie, Dr Alex is on the frontline, so it's a quiet (and clean) house for mum and means this is our first episode recorded remotely.
Via the internet the wonderful, funny and gorgeous Grimmy joined us for a virtual dinner with mum and I.</description></item><item><title>S9 Ep 7: Riz Ahmed | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190176/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190176/</guid><description>Podcast Description It was our biggest delight to cook a Monday vegetarian risotto for one of this country&amp;rsquo;s absolute treasures, actor, musician and all round excellent person, Riz Ahmed (even if he then did tell us he had chicken for lunch). We elbow bump and discuss growing up in London, school, PPE at Oxford, his mum&amp;rsquo;s Nihari being on his last supper, Naughty Boy being a good cook and Asma Khan&amp;rsquo;s Darjeeling Express being one of his favourite London restaurants.</description></item><item><title>In Conversation, live at Waterstones Piccadilly | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190177/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190177/</guid><description>Podcast Description A little something for the weekend! Last week we celebrated the publication of &amp;lsquo;Table Manners: The Cookbook&amp;rsquo; with an &amp;lsquo;In Conversation&amp;rsquo; at Waterstones Piccadilly, we met some of our lovely listeners, for those who couldn&amp;rsquo;t make it here is a chance to listen in&amp;hellip; enjoy!
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>S9 Ep 6: Zawe Ashton | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190178/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190178/</guid><description>Podcast Description We welcomed the beautiful and brilliant Zawe Ashton to ours last Friday with an unexpected guest, Fresh Meat co-star Charlotte Richie (who Jessie used to babysit back in the day!).
The author and actress devoured mums sticky short ribs (even kindly put them on her last supper meal!), spoke all about being a child actor, being bullied, The Handmaids Tale and her new book Character Breakdown. We chatted about the go to places to eat after you've stepped off stage on Broadway, how savoury porridge saved her life, the thrills of cheap red wine and being a devotee of Terry's Chocolate Orange.</description></item><item><title>S9 Ep 5: Jo Brand | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190179/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190179/</guid><description>Podcast Description Queen comic Jo Brand turned up at our doorstep laden with gifts; a nativity tote bag and shoes to polish the floor with! We tucked into an effortless mid-week roast whilst discussing hairy gooseberries, sandwich spread, road rage, being heckled and Paul Hollywood! This wonderful woman can do no wrong, and it was an absolute pleasure finally getting her on the pod after a drunken proposal two years ago at Jools Holland&amp;rsquo;s Hootenanny (god do I sound like I&amp;rsquo;m Jessica in Love is Blind?</description></item><item><title>S9 Ep 4: Vanessa Williams | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190180/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Legend of stage and screen Vanessa Williams joined us for dinner and we could NOT believe we had a Grammy, Tony and Emmy nominee in our kitchen. The Desperate Housewives star tells us all about her new West End show ‘City Of Angels’ and we chat about Vanessa’s incredible worldwide travels, her outrageous Thanksgiving turkey-basting traditions and the Ugly Betty wedding that took place at her LA house! We had an honest chat about her misunderstood Miss America resignation and even got a singalong of the total karaoke classic ‘Save The Best For Last’.</description></item><item><title>S9 Ep 3: David Schwimmer | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190181/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190181/</guid><description>Podcast Description When David Schwimmer needs you to come to a hotel for a food chat you run there!!
We talk to our global friend about Gouda, his magic themed barmitzvah, Jewish delis, caccio e pepe, NY &amp;amp; the UK, his new Sky One show 'Intelligence', Bake off, coffee, his theatre company in Chicago...and then there's that chat about Dr Alex's dry banana bread.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;This is a golden episode and we love you David.</description></item><item><title>S9 Ep 2: Callum Turner | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190182/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190182/</guid><description>Podcast Description We invited British actor, Callum Turner over for a fish dinner. After a mesmerising performance as Sean Emery in the BBC&amp;rsquo;s The Capture, he&amp;rsquo;s now in the brand new film &amp;lsquo;Emma&amp;rsquo; playing Frank Churchill. We talk to the Londoner about growing up on a Chelsea estate with his Mum, who was a night club promoter, supporting Chelsea ( 🥴) all whilst eating sherry cod with tomatoes and butter beans, @dustyknuckle sourdough and Panettone Bread &amp;amp; Butter pudding.</description></item><item><title>S9 Ep 1: Aisling Bea | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190183/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190183/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are back for Series 9 and with a lot of good craic! We’ve been trying to nail down this week's guest ever since we became friends on a Love Island WhatsApp group. I have laughed and swooned at her wit and grace from afar for a while now so it was my total pleasure to offer a hoodie and a green tea to&amp;nbsp;Irish actress, writer, and all round hilarious human, Aisling Bea.</description></item><item><title>S8 Ep 11: Emilia Clarke | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190184/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190184/</guid><description>Podcast Description To close this series of Table Manners we decided to get an absolute Christmas cracker in, the Mother of ALLLL mothers, the Mother of Dragons! After hearing this lady was a fan of the podcast I swooped in like a baby dragon and coaxed her with the promise of chicken soup (her request!) and she even broke her gluten free policy to sample mum&amp;rsquo;s matzoh balls. We talk to our dream girl about her dear late dad&amp;rsquo;s passion for food, salad in a bag, boarding school meals and setting up her charity, &amp;lsquo;Same You&amp;rsquo; with her mum after having 2 brain aneurysm in her twenties.</description></item><item><title>S8 Ep 10: Jamie Oliver | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190185/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190185/</guid><description>Podcast Description We were only going to do meals on wheels and travel to someone else's place&amp;nbsp;if they were someone we have been angling for since series 1. And of course they were most certainly going to get THE chicken soup (I had a massive cold so it was selfishly suggested by moi). It's JAMIE OLIVER!! The Naked Chef, the people's champ, the person who taught most of us millennials how to cook.</description></item><item><title>S8 Ep 9: Nicole Scherzinger | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190186/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190186/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's December and that means we can start eating Xmas dinners on the regular. Knowing full well this puddycat Anglophile loves a roast with all the trimmings, we offered up a full on festive feast for the stunning Nicole Scherzinger (nice one Waitrose and John Lewis) Not only did we teach her what a nut roast &amp;amp; bread sauce was, we served up the best Christmas turkey she’s ever had!</description></item><item><title>S8 Ep 8: Rick Astley | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190187/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190187/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mum was beside herself when this guest was suggested and demanded we make this chat over cake happen, so, we put in the call and welcomed Lancashire born hitmaker Rick Astley to Clapham! Rick tells us about teaching Mary Berry to play the drums, rickrolling, that performance with Dave Grohl, his own beer and his wife’s speciality of making curried herring (!). He charmed mum over an afternoon tea of pumpkin cake and finger sandwiches - we&amp;rsquo;re never gonna give you up Rick, you&amp;rsquo;re too much of a gent.</description></item><item><title>S8 Ep 7: Haim | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190188/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190188/</guid><description>Podcast Description I want to be a Haim sister.
Feel lucky enough to have known these sublime women for a while. We have written songs together, eaten sushi, drunk hot chocolate, swapped doctor's details, celebrated birthdays, apologised to firemen...basically, every time you're with a Haim, it's a damn good memorable time.
We treat them to their first home cooked meal in Blighty (of course with Lennie's medicinal chicken soup and Matzoh balls) and talk about being paid in matzoh balls, grapes in fruit salad, Bewitched, family, tacos and mum auditions to be the fourth member.</description></item><item><title>S8 Ep 6: Luke Evans | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190189/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190189/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week’s guest flew straight into mum’s kitchen from Los Angeles, where he’d been for his new film premiere, armed with his mother&amp;rsquo;s banana and nut loaf! Hollywood actor and singing heart-throb, Luke Evans tells us all about his upbringing in the Welsh valleys, how he lives for a Dalston Doner kebab and who his favourite on-screen kisser is. We are treated to an award winning karaoke performance around the kitchen table, with only a &amp;rsquo;little&amp;rsquo; wine.</description></item><item><title>S8 Ep 5: Charlotte Tilbury MBE | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190190/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190190/</guid><description>Podcast Description Well daaaaaaarrrrling, if there’s ever a time to crack open the bubbly over breakfast, it&amp;rsquo;s when ultimate goddess Charlotte Tilbury pops over to mums! The Queen of glam, and our first makeup artist on Table Manners talks to us about growing up in Ibiza, sleeping in her make-up, jet setting round the world and painting A-lister&amp;rsquo;s faces. As if mum couldn’t love her anymore, she arrived with champagne &amp;amp; homemade gazpacho in hand and a suitcase full of lippie.</description></item><item><title>S8 Ep 4: Yannis Philippakis | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190191/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190191/</guid><description>Podcast Description A lesson was learnt here - don&amp;rsquo;t invite a rock star into your home on a Friday night and expect mum to hold back on the wine, or hold back on baiting me to drink more. Currently number 1 with their new record, we welcomed the wonderful Foals front man Yannis through our doors. We celebrate the band&amp;rsquo;s marriage, talk a LOT about Greece and his Greek Jewish heritage (much to mum&amp;rsquo;s delight), the reason he couldn&amp;rsquo;t perform at the Mercury Music prize this year and his love for Creme Fraiche.</description></item><item><title>S8 Ep 3: Jess Phillips MP | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190192/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190192/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we welcomed&amp;nbsp;Birmingham-bred Labour MP Jess Phillips for brunch. Brother Alex hid upstairs (as he does when one of his favourites is downstairs) whilst we ate Turnip and Sweet Potato Fritters with Fried Eggs on top and an Ottolenghi Apple cake.
We talked about watching Scandal whilst writing her second book 'Truth to Power', getting the blue tick on Instagram, her 'instagrammable'&amp;nbsp;husband, home made Rhubarb Vodka and her son and his friends updating her wikipedia page to say that she ate Quavers in the bath.</description></item><item><title>S8 Ep 2: Liam Payne | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190193/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190193/</guid><description>Podcast Description After showing mum that underwear pic, she couldn't hide her delight and enthusiasm at having our first ex One-Directioner at the Table Manners table. Although on a strict diet and fitness regime, Liam was a perfect guest enjoying what he could of the fantastic Beef and Mushroom pies we made him using a Waitrose &amp;amp; Partners recipe with their No. 1 range ingredients. We talk to him about dealing with fame, his terrible karaoke song choice, being a dad, finding love and happiness, tattoos and his favourite food being airport lounge calamari.</description></item><item><title>S8 Ep 1: Antoni Porowski | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190194/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190194/</guid><description>Podcast Description Well, we are back and this time I've brought my whole family to live with mum for the foreseeable future, or until she gets tired of my slobbish ways. So as a sweetener for mother dearest, I decided to bring a real life Disney Prince to Clapham.&amp;nbsp;The dreamy Antoni provides a real share all episode; we talk coffee fixes, guacamole, champagne grapes and he doesn't choose a last supper, he demands a last day of food.</description></item><item><title>S7 Ep 3: Grace Campbell - Live from the Edinburgh Festival Fringe | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190195/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190195/</guid><description>Podcast Description What better way to end our Edinburgh special, than to get rising stand-up star, Grace Campbell on the show to discuss feminism and competing with Tony Blair.
It was such a pleasure chatting to fellow podcaster Grace about why she’s never going into politics, her love of fish tacos, protest shenanigans &amp;amp; trying to get a date with Jeremy Corbyn's son.
Thanks so much to everyone who came along to see us in Edinburgh (and those who bought a tea towel) - we had a ball!</description></item><item><title>S7 Ep 2: London Hughes - Live from the Edinburgh Festival Fringe | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190196/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190196/</guid><description>Podcast Description How we cackled and gasped at South London&amp;rsquo;s funniest feminist London Hughes. With 5* reviews for her Edinburgh show all over the gaff, we talk to the brilliant and wild Ms Hughes about a lot of d*ck, having the longest name, vegans, bad table manners, saying no to a Nandos Black card and eating Maccy D&amp;rsquo;s in Chelsea. Props to London for devouring our sausage rolls and not wanting to share them with the audience.</description></item><item><title>S7 Ep 1: Heidi Regan - Live from the Edinburgh Festival Fringe | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190197/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190197/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a nervy ride up to Scotland with a sweaty savoury Cheesecake, hot off our book shoot, what better way to start our Edinburgh series with an award winning comedian and writer Heidi Regan to ease the pressure!&amp;nbsp;
We talk to the Australian Stand up about poaching eggs, surviving on microwave meals, misophonia and debate over a 'self-saucing' pudding. Shout out to previous table manners darling Joe Dempsie and his family for being fabulous co-hosts!</description></item><item><title>S6 Ep 12: Olly Alexander | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190198/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190198/</guid><description>Podcast Description Following his triumph at Glastonbury, we’ve managed to&amp;nbsp;bag Years &amp;amp; Years frontman, Olly Alexander for the season finale of Table Manners Series 6. Olly talks about his coming out experience, Pride, his obsession with Kylie, how he only drinks champagne and the band's global search for the best doughnut! Even mum’s flat tyre didn’t stand in the way of a gorgeous lunch with Olly. Despite being a vegetarian, mum says Olly can come over again, anytime, she loves you!</description></item><item><title>S6 Ep 11: Deborah Frances-White | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190199/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190199/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Guilty Feminist herself, Deborah Frances-White joins us round the dinner table for today’s episode.&amp;nbsp;With over 65m podcast downloads under her belt, a Royal Albert Hall gig this weekend and an army of followers, Deborah is inspiring, charming and hysterical. With fingers in the Eton mess and whilst downing champagne, we talk about her ‘fading’ from being a Witness, her mum’s incredible Pavlova, searching for her birth parents and Table Manners Olympics.</description></item><item><title>S6 Ep 10: Neneh Cherry | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190200/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190200/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we have music, fashion and feminist icon, Neneh Cherry.&amp;nbsp;
What an honour to have Neneh over for lunch. We talk about the 80s, music, being a woman, love and partying on aeroplanes, Swedish living, vegetarian eating, carnival going...everything and more!&amp;nbsp;
This episode is full of fantastic stories and we loved every mouthful and moment of Ms Cherry intoxicating our kitchen with warmth, sisterhood and wisdom.&amp;nbsp;Enjoy x</description></item><item><title>S6 Ep 9: Greg James and Bella Mackie | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190201/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190201/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’ve got another first this week&amp;hellip; our first couple on Table Manners &amp;amp; a total power duo - Greg James &amp;amp; Bella Mackie. With Prosecco at midday, we chat wedding food, stockpiling wine, compare hours of sleep and now we understand what a &amp;rsquo;tailender&amp;rsquo; is. And I ruin pudding. Again. Enjoy x
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>S6 Ep 8: Richard Curtis | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190202/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190202/</guid><description>Podcast Description All in aid of Comic Relief, Table Manners is joined by the legendary comedy screenwriter and co-founder of Comic Relief, Richard Curtis. He’s written some of the greatest films &amp;amp; TV shows ever made; Notting Hill, Love Actually, Black Adder... But Richard Curtis can’t get enough of Love Island and particularly Lucie... it is what it is!
In this week’s special, we’re joined not only by Richard, but by his fabulous partner - and babysitter -&amp;nbsp;Emma Freud, along with 2 Comic Relief competition winners, who entered the Table Manners chaos with mum and I and even brought a starter!</description></item><item><title>S6 Ep 7: Hayley Squires | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190203/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190203/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week&amp;rsquo;s guest is a national treasure. Since watching her in &amp;lsquo;I, Daniel Blake&amp;rsquo; I&amp;rsquo;ve been obsessed with BAFTA nominated actress, Hayley Squires, so was delighted to finally have her join us for dinner! A blow torch disaster ensued resulting in soggy brûlées and mum literally on fire. Good job Hayley came to the rescue by bringing us a delicious home baked banana bread. We talk all about Hayley&amp;rsquo;s love of cereal, how she eats a chocolate bar a day &amp;amp; her new love of baking.</description></item><item><title>S6 Ep 6: Noomi Rapace | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190204/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190204/</guid><description>Podcast Description Super star actress and all round amazing lady Noomi Rapace, tells us all about her upbringing on a Swedish farm, how she grew up on cornflakes &amp;amp; toast before moving to London and joining the foodie crew whilst bonding with mum over their shared love for leopard print. We chat in great detail about the greatness of eggs, truffle salt and how to throw a Bondesque cavier party. And I may attack her on her &amp;lsquo;guilty pleasure&amp;rsquo; food.</description></item><item><title>S6 Ep 5: Róisín Murphy | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190205/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190205/</guid><description>Podcast Description I had every intention of dressing to seriously impress one of my musical and style icons however, when Róisín&amp;nbsp;Murphy arrives an hour early, she gets work-out gear, greasy hair and she has to hold the baby whilst I sort the toddler's dinner. Good thing she doesn’t believe in showering every day and also shares my passion for the beloved baked potato. We talk Met Gala lewks, boiled eggs, her mum's Irish stew and her Italian partner 'beating his meat' whilst also discussing the music industry.</description></item><item><title>S6 Ep 4: Raymond Blanc | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190206/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190206/</guid><description>Podcast Description Salut! This week mum shows off her best French with chef extraordinaire, Raymond Blanc. As well as answering our demands of bringing pud, the Michelin starred chef couldn’t resist taking over mum’s kitchen to show us how it&amp;rsquo;s done; from corkscrews and emulsions to apricot trees and gardens, we learnt it all! Raymond tells us all about his journey into becoming a chef, frog hunting as a child, why he’ll never eat strawberries in winter &amp;amp; the brilliance of using water in his iconic recipes.</description></item><item><title>S6 Ep 3: Carly Rae Jepsen | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190207/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190207/</guid><description>Podcast Description Through some incredibly crossed wires, this Canadian superstar was granted Quiche for this week&amp;rsquo;s Table Manners - the delightfully charming Carly Rae Jepsen chats to us over Rosé about quiche, homemade pasta, on-the-road eating habits, the best things to do in Canada and how cheese should be banned on flights. We delve into our childhood musical roles, whilst talking about her time on broadway and her brand new album.</description></item><item><title>S6 Ep 2: Mark Ronson | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190208/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190208/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mum’s famous chicken soup always comes out for the big dogs, so it was the obvious choice for this week’s guest, artist/producer/every award winning Mark Ronson.
Over a meal of matzoh balls &amp;amp; latkes, we compare Bar Mitzvah celebrations, hear all about Mark’s mums famous casserole, what it is like working with Gaga, and his go-to meal after having won all the awards this season. Eat it up x</description></item><item><title>S6 Ep 1: Kiefer Sutherland | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190209/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 03:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190209/</guid><description>Podcast Description …And we are BACK!! With a brand new baby in tow, we kick off Series 6 with a Hollywood icon; none other than Canadian actor, producer, director and singer/songwriter Kiefer Sutherland (AKA Jack Bauer)
We bond over Scotch whisky, gasp at his antics with Kevin Bacon &amp;amp; Robert Downey Jr &amp;amp; his picky eating habits as a child.&amp;nbsp;Other than eating goldfish and changing his food preferences last minute, this man can do no wrong!</description></item><item><title>NYC Season - Ep 6: Sara Bareilles | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190210/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190210/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's about to hit the West End so what better way to celebrate than to chat to 7-time Grammy nominee Sara Bareilles, the woman behind the original music and lyrics of Tony nominated musical, Waitress.&amp;nbsp;
We chat tour rider requests ( I realise I am totally neurotic on tour whilst she's rock n' roll), where to get the best pizza in NYC, why you shouldn’t order sushi takeaway &amp;amp; writing love songs about Obama.</description></item><item><title>NYC Season - Ep 5: Tom Payne | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190211/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190211/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we meet The Walking Dead’s &amp;lsquo;Jesus&amp;rsquo;, British actor Tom Payne. We chat British vs American table manners, favourite restaurants in LA, home cooking and we practised our American accents whilst serving up the perfect ‘hangover brunch’ of Kimchi fried rice aka fermented cabbage via my darling @eatwithgrace&amp;hellip;bottoms up!!
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>NYC Season - Ep 4: Ian Schrager | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190212/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190212/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, we have a New York Icon, someone who has many an incredible story to tell. Despite the fact that he didn’t eat ANYTHING and he thinks food can ruin a party (we totally disagree), the disco legend and hotelier Ian Schrager tells us all about the history of Studio 54, dancing with Diana Ross, where to eat chicken soup in New York, jail food and how he set up his hotel empire.</description></item><item><title>NYC Season - Ep 3: Gregory Porter | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190213/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190213/</guid><description>Podcast Description I like to describe this man’s voice as being like Christmas. This week’s guest is the super talented and equally delightful Gregory Porter. Making my husband most jealous that we got him in NYC and not in Dalston, we chat Sticky Toffee pud, pre-performance rituals &amp;amp; family traditions, all whilst munching on mum’s very American Buttermilk Chicken – eat up! X
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>NYC Season - Ep 2: Samin Nosrat | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190214/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190214/</guid><description>Podcast Description Beyond excited that we managed to bag this week’s guest. I read her book the moment I got my hands on it and am addicted to her Netflix original series, 'Salt Fat Acid Heat'. Samin Nosrat loves food just as much as we do, so get ready for an episode completely full to the brim of food and everything to do with it.&amp;nbsp;
We talk about all about her new found fame, our shared love of ice cream, where we’re going wrong on Mexican food and her favourite London restaurants.</description></item><item><title>NYC Season - Ep 1: Zachary Quinto | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190215/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 04:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190215/</guid><description>Podcast Description We kick off NYC with the ridiculously talented and velvet voiced Zachary Quinto. The Broadway and Star Trek star gets served Jessie&amp;rsquo;s cherished Marbella Chicken and we talk American table manners, the rights and wrongs of sweet and sour whilst Lennie and Zachary&amp;rsquo;s rejoice at their shared love of plane food. Dinner is served! Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>S4 Ep 10: John Bishop | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190216/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190216/</guid><description>Podcast Description What better way to end the series than to do a extra special live episode of Table Manners with mum’s ultimate crush John Bishop, live from Google’s fantastic Curiosity Rooms.&amp;nbsp;
In a festive special, John tells us how he does Christmas ‘vegan style’, fish guts, his massive ‘talent’ as well as how he runs a farm (what is it with comedians?!). Listen until the end to hear John's Uber rating reveal.</description></item><item><title>S4 Ep 9: Mel B | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190217/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190217/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s not very often you can say you’ve got a Spice Girl in your kitchen... but this week’s guest and season finale is none other than Ms Melanie Brown.&amp;nbsp;Mum pulls out a winning roast dinner whilst Mel ogles over her stuffing and we ply my daughter with cake so she doesn’t interrupt the juicy parts of Mel’s tumultuous story.&amp;nbsp;Yorkshire puddings, fainting goats (?!?) and which Spice Girl has the worst table manners are all on the menu.</description></item><item><title>S4 Ep 8: Sir Paul Smith | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190218/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190218/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we have a first for Table Manners, Nottingham’s finest, SIR Paul Smith talks to us about his love of early mornings, ‘hospital food’, style, his beloved Pauline and London hotspots. What a treat. (Side note: I was particularly pleased with my dish this week if I say so myself). Sir Paul is served!
Produced by Alice Williams
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>S4 Ep 7: Cariad Lloyd | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190219/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190219/</guid><description>Podcast Description Not only is she an award winning podcaster, an actor, a comedian and a writer, this week’s guest claims to be the queen of the meringues and dirty dancing. We discuss growing up, grief, celebrating life and all things sweet. The delicious Cariad Lloyd up on Table Manners!
Produced by Alice Williams
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>S4 Ep 6: Tim Dowling | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190220/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190220/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we speak to Author, Guardian columnist and part time rock star Tim Dowling. And we see how Mum’s obsession with this charming (albeit slow eating) columnist comes a little too close to Kathy Bates in ‘Misery’. We delve into the truth behind his relationship with his wife, TV dinners and the perfect brunch.&amp;nbsp;And I realise I eat far too quickly.
Produced by Alice Williams
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>S4 Ep 5: Cheryl | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190221/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190221/</guid><description>Podcast Description She’s back.&amp;nbsp;And wanting seconds of mum’s Key Lime Pie. We talk to the peoples’ princess, Cheryl, about Stottie cake, her perfect roast potatoes, the only man in her life, tattoos and her first bit of music in 4 years. It’s a big one!
Produced by Alice Williams
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>S4 Ep 4: Stefflon Don | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190222/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190222/</guid><description>Podcast Description According to mum, this week’s guest has more of a potty mouth than me. Stefflon Don joins us for this week’s Table Manners, proving she really is quite the don. We talk music industry, poetry, eating jerk, speaking Dutch and munching on ice (!)
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>S4 Ep 3: Russell Tovey | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190223/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 03:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190223/</guid><description>Podcast Description After watching his recent show-stopping Pinter performance in the West End, we invited actor Russell Tovey and his trusty sidekick, French Bulldog Rocky, over for a quiet Friday night in. We talk all things art, ‘bags of gold’, our favourite childhood meals &amp;amp; his never ending love for Rocky …whilst also discovering that he has an even lower Uber rating than Jessie.
Produced by Alice Williams
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>S4 Ep 2: Dolly Alderton | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190224/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190224/</guid><description>Podcast Description Since reading her book, 'Everything I Know About Love', I feel like Dolly Alderton is a friend I was always meant to have. We talk oysters, champagne, a little bit of love, her real name (!) and everything fabulous in between.&amp;nbsp;
Produced by Alice Williams
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>S4 Ep 1: Nigella Lawson | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190225/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190225/</guid><description>Podcast Description Table Manners is back!! And what better way to start series 4 than with the ultimate kitchen goddess… Nigella Lawson. She has been top of our list since day one, so brace yourselves for mum and me melting over her. We talk midnight snacks, her being a fussy eater as a child (there’s hope for all our children), eating rice pudding for breakfast...and apart from her love of Vegemite, she can do no wrong.</description></item><item><title>Best of Table Manners | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190226/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190226/</guid><description>Podcast Description Whilst we gear up for a new season of Table Manners,&amp;nbsp;we’ve created a little amuse bouche of all the best bits from Table Manners so far! From Sam Smith’s Gollum impression to the&amp;nbsp;George Ezra short rib disaster, Stacey Dooley’s - as she puts it - dump in a box, and the wonderful Sandi Toksvig rewriting women’s history, this episode can tide you over 'til you hear from us, very soon for Season 4.</description></item><item><title>S3 Ep 10: Michelle Keegan | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190227/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190227/</guid><description>Podcast Description We loved her as Georgie in 'Our Girl' and now we love her as actual-real-life Michelle Keegan. We talk Corrie, paparazzi and her all time favourite ice breaker question. And she’s a girl after my own heart: she doesn’t just love food, she loves DIRTY food!&amp;nbsp;
What a lovely episode to finish to the series. Keep sending in your guest suggestions and Table Manners will return very soon with your next serving - cheers!</description></item><item><title>S3 Ep 9: Adam Buxton | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190228/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190228/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our first live podcast! Thank you SO much to everyone that came and also a huge thanks to our exceptional guest Adam Buxton for showing us how it’s done and also sharing the recipe for his delicious sounding tuna, pasta and ketchup dish... Continuing the theme of getting our guests to work for us - Adam created one of his famous jingles for Table Manners and now we want it played wherever we go.</description></item><item><title>S3 Ep 8: Alan Carr | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190229/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 03:00:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190229/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alan Carr. We knew we were in for a treat but could this be our funniest guest yet?! From the moment he walked in discussing his farm animals' sexual exploits, to his eventual 'Come Dine with Me' scoring of 1/10 for us - my GOD we laughed. And drunk. This was such a pleasure to listen back to and I hope you enjoy it too!
Produced by Alice Williams</description></item><item><title>S3 Ep 7: Yotam Ottolenghi | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190230/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190230/</guid><description>Podcast Description What do you do when you have the god that is Ottolenghi round? Well, you make him bring dessert and ask him enough questions until he eventually cooks the main too! I can also confirm that friendships can be made through persistence or even stalking. We speak about his children, his husband and their surrogacy process and (finally!) simplifying his dishes. L’chaim!
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>S3 Ep 6: MIST | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190231/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190231/</guid><description>Podcast Description MIST. We knew when he requested Coffee Patron as his dinner drink of choice we were in for a good night. As mum swoons over his looks and rocks, we talk prison, getting your hair cut at 3am, what it&amp;rsquo;s like to rap with a Birmingham accent, and his penchant for curry powder. FIRE IN THE BOOOOOTH! Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>S3 Ep 5: Tom Kerridge | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190232/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190232/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tom Kerridge. Glad we asked him to bring a pud because his Strawberry Bakewell was so good we talked about it for weeks! Tom spoke to us about everything and anything - his diet, working alongside his wife, water being a secret cooking weapon and he even judged a Labneh competition between mum and I. What a lovely man
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>S3 Ep 4: Sadiq Khan | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190233/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190233/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hear ye! Hear ye! Mayor Sadiq Khan announces he’ll stand for re-election! We were honoured to welcome The Mayor of London to mum’s house to break his Ramadan fast. Brushing over the fact that the cat was sick on his first bowl of dates, over a fresh bowl we discuss nightlife in London, Trump’s impending visit, Aswad, rising crime rates, racism within football and not forgetting his penchant for fish and chips.</description></item><item><title>S3 Ep 3: Tracey Thorn | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190234/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190234/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tracey Thorn. Singer, songwriter, novelist, one half of Everything but the Girl - I absolutely loved chatting to her. As a singer we have been likened to each other but I hadn’t realised how many similarities we actually had. We talk about stage fright, hypnotherapy, taking your family on tour and the one question journalists always annoy us with. This episode is best served alongside a martini, a dose of summer sunshine and Everything But The Girl’s ’Missing” on the speakers.</description></item><item><title>S3 Ep 2: My Dad Wrote A Porno | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190235/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190235/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alice, Jamie &amp;amp; James from My Dad Wrote a Porno&amp;hellip; what a riot we had! I’m surprised we managed to record a podcast at all. This evening reminded me so much of the dinners we used to have at my mum&amp;rsquo;s growing up - everyone howling with laughter and staying until the wee hours. So wee that mum left hours before we finished recording. If you’ve listened to MDWAP you’ll know what to expect: adult themes, sexual content and strong language.</description></item><item><title>S3 Ep 1: Randy Jackson | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190236/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 07:51:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190236/</guid><description>Podcast Description Recorded at my sister&amp;rsquo;s house in LA, to celebrate 4/20, we brought a slice of Britain to Table Manners newest guest Randy Jackson. Over Pimms, scones and cucumber sandwiches, we speak about managing Mariah Carey, 13 years on American Idol, working with Simon Cowell, his “morsel diet” and Randy’s favourite gumbo recipe. It’s a yes from us dawg!
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 9: Stacey Dooley | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190237/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 02:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190237/</guid><description>Podcast Description So it's the SEASON FINALE with Stacey Dooley! And what a guest she was. We’d barely taken the chicken out of the oven and mum was already won over. Stacey has carved out a name for herself that is respected amongst the best. A woman with a knack for disarming subjects in the most hostile of situations. We get some tips on squeezing information out of guests, where to eat in Brighton and even the best tactics for shitting in shoeboxes.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 8: Felix White | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190238/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2018 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190238/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felix White. Some of you know him from The Maccabees, some of you know him from his cricket journalism but I know him as the new boy at school who I forced to go out with me at 9 years old. Since then we’ve shared many experiences; a few teenage snogs, our first TV appearance and even our first mugging.&amp;nbsp;He’s had countless dinners at Mum's over the years and here pops over to mine for one more.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 7: Jay Rayner | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190239/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190239/</guid><description>Podcast Description How does one prepare a dinner party for a food critic?! After the initial flapping Mum took off to make sure her hair looked fabulous and I put my Paxman hat on and whipped out hard hitting questions such as “Would you do Greg Wallace?”&amp;nbsp;
This week its Jay Rayner making us feel all nervous about our hosting abilities. We like to think the three helpings of lemon ice cream secured us a solid 4 stars.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 6: Dermot O'Leary | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190240/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190240/</guid><description>Podcast Description Oh Dermot. Not since mum cooked for Ottolenghi has the Ware household been so flustered to host a guest. Utterly charming, definitely deserving of his ‘nicest man in showbiz’ tag and potentially the biggest secret foodie we’ve had so far. Points were only lost by not divulging the X Factor gossip that mum so desperately wanted. What a true professional. 9/10.&amp;nbsp;
Produced by Alice Williams for Cup and Nuzzle</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 5: George Ezra | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190241/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190241/</guid><description>Podcast Description Oh George Ezra. What can I say? The night had so much potential... Mum was looking forward to a Budapest duet and instead it ended in a catastrophe that my pelvic floor definitely wasn’t strong enough for and our first emergency Deliveroo order. We’re so sorry George.&amp;nbsp;
Produced by Alice Williams for Cup and Nuzzle
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 4: Amol Rajan | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190242/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190242/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is there anything Amol Rajan hasn’t done? Presenter of The One Show, youngest editor of the Independent newspaper, judge on Masterchef, and now currently the BBC’s Media Editor. Over a savoury cheesecake he manages to makes us laugh with his penchant for Del Boy dinners and nearly gives mum a heart attack with his last minute vegetarian request. Pass the piña coladas, let&amp;rsquo;s get started! Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 3: Ralf Little | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190243/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190243/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ralf Little. The most intensely brilliant guest and Twitter debatee. What you don’t see here is the three hours after we stopped recording sitting around the table setting the world to rights. What you do see is the lowdown on the Royle Family, ruined pancake days and our invite to Jeremy Hunt to finish the NHS debate once and for all. What a night!
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 2: Paloma Faith | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190244/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190244/</guid><description>Podcast Description Paloma Faith - inspiring woman, powerful voice, beautiful hair. She taught us so much in this episode. Giving celebrities food poisoning. Random acts of kindness. And most of all: never trust your guest's temporary dietary requirements!
Produced by Alice Williams
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 1: Ed Sheeran | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190245/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190245/</guid><description>Podcast Description Table Manners returns with Ed Sheeran and an even more ferocious appetite!&amp;nbsp;Yes, mum and I are back and still arguing over who does the dishes. Four helpings later, we're talking death row dinners, Lion bars, rotting shark and pizza butties…&amp;nbsp;
Produced by Alice Williams for Cup and Nuzzle
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 8: Clara Amfo | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190246/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190246/</guid><description>Podcast Description Superwoman of the airwaves Clara Amfo pops over for this week’s Table Manners and before we know it we’re talking Fifty Shades sex scene music, blocking your mum on WhatsApp, deadly spiders and Prince, a lot of Prince… By the way this is the last show of the current series, thanks so much for listening and stand by for more Table Manners in 2018! xxx
Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>Ep 7: Sandi Toksvig | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190247/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190247/</guid><description>Podcast Description Radio 4’s finest, QI darling, radical history rewriter&amp;nbsp;and one of the most inspiring women I have ever met... Sandi Toksvig drops by&amp;nbsp;mum’s for this week’s Table Manners. The Bake-Off drinking game, Wikipedia's male bias, Paul Hollywood's eyes, Christmas dinner in Denmark… Trust me, we cover it ALL.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
Produced by Alice Williams for Cup and Nuzzle
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 6: Loyle Carner | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190248/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2017 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190248/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Mercury-nominated man-of-the moment Loyle Carner pops round to mum’s for a special Hannukah feast. Over chopped liver, a LOT of latkes and a pasta pudding we talk ADHD, hanging with Heston and the time he got to meet his hero Eric Cantona. Chag Sameach! Happy Hanukkah! Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 5: Benny Blanco | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190249/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190249/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week’s ep is brought to you from LA with producer Benny Blanco. You may know him from working on tunes with Katy Perry, Ed Sheeran and The Weeknd but we know him from letting our whole family descend on his house whenever we stay in LA. Here’s one small taste of the mad house - featuring my husband Sam, my baby girl and a little bit of California’s finest&amp;hellip; Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Ep 4: Annie Mac | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190250/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190250/</guid><description>Podcast Description Businesswoman, tastemaker, mother, and champion of the sorority; this week we chat to Annie Mac about veganism, taking your kids on tour, and the time her mother punched someone on a plane.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 3: Joe Dempsie And Daniel Kaluuya | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190251/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190251/</guid><description>Podcast Description Game Of Thrones, dieting for sex scenes, Christmas in Uganda&amp;hellip; It all went off when GOT&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;porno blacksmith&amp;rdquo; Joe Dempsie and Daniel &amp;ldquo;Get Out&amp;rdquo; Kaluuya joined me and mum for dinner. Love those boys! xxx
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 2: Will Young And Chris Sweeney | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190252/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190252/</guid><description>Podcast Description So for Ep 2 I thought it was only right and proper that I invite over my dear, dear family friend and awesome promo video director Chris Sweeney, along with his partner in podcast crime and Cabaret star Will Young, a.k.a. the Homo Sapiens boys! Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep1: Sam Smith | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190253/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190253/</guid><description>Podcast Description So for the very first episode of Table Manners, I invited over my old mate and pop superstar Sam Smith. Over mum&amp;rsquo;s turkey meatballs we talked about Sam&amp;rsquo;s childhood food experiences, living without booze, and what he would choose for his death row dinner. Oh and he gave his very scary impression of a movie icon&amp;hellip; Get stuck in people! Jessie x
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Table Manners Teaser | Table Manners with Jessie and Lennie Ware</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7870190254/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 16:40:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7870190254/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to Table Manners! Here&amp;rsquo;s a little amuse-bouche to whet your appetites for my new podcast, which launches on 8 November with my mum Lennie and the one and only Sam Smith. Also coming on the show we&amp;rsquo;ve got Annie Mac, the Homo Sapiens boys, Daniel Kaluuya, GOT&amp;rsquo;s Joe Dempsie and loads more. Oversharing - and overeating - are guaranteed. Get stuck in! Love, Jessie x
Hosted on Acast.</description></item></channel></rss>