<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Real Dictators on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/real-dictators/</link><description>Recent content in Real Dictators on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/real-dictators/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Saddam Hussein Part 5: The War on Terror | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100001/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the aftermath of 9/11, President Bush and Prime Minister Blair send troops back into Iraq. In a highly symbolic moment, beamed around the world, a giant statue of Saddam comes crashing down. But as the Iraqi dictator performs his vanishing act, how soon can they track him down? And after Saddam’s toppling, how will ordinary Iraqis fare? A Noiser production, written by Duncan Barrett. This is Part 5 of 5.</description></item><item><title>Saddam Hussein Part 4: The First Gulf War | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100002/</guid><description>Podcast Description After Iraq’s invasion of Kuwait, US forces are deployed to the region. For some Iraqis, it seems like the perfect time to rise up against their dictator. As economic sanctions bite, Saddam treats himself to a bit of retail therapy. All the while, his sons are becoming terrifying figures in their own right. A family crisis is about to snowball into a murderous feud… A Noiser production, written by Duncan Barrett.</description></item><item><title>Saddam Hussein Part 3: Oil and the Ayatollah | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Saddam nationalises the Iraq Petroleum Company and clashes with the new leader of Iran. A man called ‘Chemical Ali’ commits one of the most heinous atrocities of modern times. Meanwhile, sculptures of the Iraqi dictator are commissioned across the land. With his personality cult firmly established, Saddam is ready for war… A Noiser production, written by Duncan Barrett. For more on Saddam and his cook, listen to our bonus episode on Dictators’ Chefs.</description></item><item><title>Saddam Hussein Part 2: Enforcer, Frontman, Mafia Godfather | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Saddam consolidates his own power base, appointing friends and relatives to key positions. We hear a remarkable account from a woman whose own family was targeted by his secret police. Soon, the deputy will be in pole position to move against his mentor. And after that, Saddam will shore up the loyalty of his party with an act of political theatre for the ages… A Noiser production, written by Duncan Barrett.</description></item><item><title>Saddam Hussein Part 1: Son of the Alleyways | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100005/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the spring of 1937, a child dies and his brother is born. Translated from Arabic, the newborn’s name - Saddam - means ‘one who confronts’. As his life will demonstrate, it couldn’t be more appropriate. So how does a boy from a tough peasant background go on to rise to the very top of Iraq’s leadership? How does his journey towards global infamy begin? Narrated by Paul McGann.</description></item><item><title>Macías Nguema Part 2: Hiding in the Jungle with all the Money | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100006/</guid><description>Podcast Description With President Macías in power, educated Equatoguineans come under attack, as a bizarre vendetta is pursued against teachers, lawyers and doctors. Things take a turn for the metaphysical, as Macías declares himself God. Finally, as paranoia completely overwhelms him, his inner circle will take matters into their own hands… Narrated by Paul McGann. A Noiser production, written by Sean Coleman. This is Part 2 of 2. Get every episode of Real Dictators a week early with Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Macías Nguema Part 1: The Dachau of Africa | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100007/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the extraordinary, blood-curdling story of a dictator you may never have heard of. From 1968-1979, the African nation of Equatorial Guinea was helmed by its first, and to date only, freely elected president. Initially, Francisco Macías Nguema was seen by the Spanish colonial authorities as a safe choice. He proved to be anything but. Things went off the rails at an astonishing rate, as Macías rapidly turned the country into what would be called the ‘Dachau of Africa’.</description></item><item><title>Hitler: The Bunker and the End | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100008/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100008/</guid><description>Podcast Description We reach the dramatic conclusion of Hitler’s downfall. With the Battle of Berlin raging, the Führer makes his last stand. Underground, in a bunker beneath the Chancellery, he will conduct the final act of his life: a macabre ritual of marriage, murder and suicide… A Noiser production, written by Jeff Dawson. This is Part 25 of the Hitler Story. Scroll down the Real Dictators feed for earlier episodes. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Hitler: Operation Valkyrie, Blowing up the Führer | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100009/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100009/</guid><description>Podcast Description A delusional Hitler downplays the Normandy Landings. A group of generals, meanwhile, attempts an audacious military coup. And with Allied bombers pounding the Fatherland, Germany’s dictator plays his next card… Scientific wonder-weapons that will turn the war back his way… A Noiser production, written by Jeff Dawson. This is Part 24 of the Hitler Story. Scroll down the Real Dictators feed for earlier episodes. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Hitler: Mussolini’s Prison Break | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100010/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100010/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Italy, Il Duce is overthrown. So Hitler stages a daring mission to rescue his fascist partner. With the Red Army rampant, another epochal battle sends the Wehrmacht on the retreat. Soon, more bad news will reach the Berghof, as Allied troops start landing in Normandy. But with the Führer fast asleep in his quarters, will anyone dare to break it to him? A Noiser production, written by Jeff Dawson.</description></item><item><title>Hitler: The Battle of Stalingrad | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100011/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100011/</guid><description>Podcast Description The myth of the Nazi war machine is blown apart in one of the pivotal battles of World War 2. Serious questions arise as to Hitler’s leadership, encouraging a growing German resistance. As Allied forces eye Sicily, a paranoid Führer retreats further into himself. His war of conquest is becoming a war of defence… A Noiser production, written by Jeff Dawson. This is Part 22 of the Hitler Story.</description></item><item><title>Adolf Hitler: The Final Solution | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100012/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100012/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is Part 21 of the Hitler Story. You can start listening here. Or, scroll down the Real Dictators feed for earlier episodes. We pick up the story in 1942. World War 2 is well underway and the Führer is still in the box seat. But he is not as untouchable as he used to be. Nazi high-ups gather at the Wannsee Conference, honing a plan to exterminate an entire race.</description></item><item><title>Introducing: Real Survival Stories - Glacier Escape | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100013/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Noiser presents a brand-new podcast. Real Survival Stories brings you astonishing tales of ordinary people thrust into extraordinary survival situations. In this taster episode, two friends embark on an awe-inspiring trip into the mountains. But then, one false step sends Jim Davidson and Mike Price plummeting into a crevasse. Trapped deep beneath the surface of a glacier, surrounded by sheer walls of ice, Jim will come to realise there’s only one way he can possibly escape… If you enjoy this taster episode, search ‘Real Survival Stories’ in your podcast app and hit follow to get new episodes every Thursday.</description></item><item><title>Attila the Hun Part 2: The Scourge of God | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100014/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100014/</guid><description>Podcast Description We track Attila’s progress as he rampages through Gaul. A family bust-up sparks an extraordinary alliance, as Attila gets engaged to the Roman Emperor’s sister. With the Huns storming deep into Western Europe, their king is on a collision course with his old friend Aetius. Will the Romans’ fragile coalition hold? Or will the prophecy of the Sword of Mars be realised? A Noiser production, written by Mark Piesing.</description></item><item><title>Attila the Hun Part 1: The Sword of Mars | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100015/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re in south-eastern Europe in the 400s AD. The once mighty Roman Empire is riven in two. And on the Great Hungarian Plain a fearsome enemy is rising. The Huns’ king, Attila, will become a terrifying, iconic figure. A byword for plundering and pillaging. The archetypal warlord. But who was he really, according to those who observed him? What did Attila do that was so significant? And is his bloody reputation entirely deserved?</description></item><item><title>Manuel Noriega Part 3: Bush Invades Panama | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100016/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Americans go all-in, deploying stealth bombers, helicopters and tens of thousands of troops to Panama. Meanwhile, agents attempt to penetrate the dictator’s inner circle, as a US operative befriends Noriega’s mistress. Will the missions succeed? Or will Noriega slip away again? A Noiser production, written by Duncan Barrett. This is Part 3 of 3. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+. Now available for Apple and Android users.</description></item><item><title>Manuel Noriega Part 2: A Tale of Two Spy Chiefs | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shielded by a puppet president, Noriega takes power. But the spymaster struggles in his new role as dictator. The war on drugs escalates in dramatic fashion. As the tide turns against Noriega, he will find himself on a collision course with the man about to assume the US presidency: George H.W. Bush… A Noiser production, written by Duncan Barrett. This is Part 2 of 3. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Manuel Noriega Part 1: The Narco Dictator | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100018/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100018/</guid><description>Podcast Description For two decades, Manuel Noriega stamped his authority on Panama - first as the country’s brutal intelligence chief, and later, from 1983-89, as its de facto military ruler. A gangster up to his neck in drug trafficking, gun running and organised crime. But also, a key asset of the CIA. How did a poor boy from Panama grow up to become such a chameleon on the world stage? And why does so much of the Noriega story remain in the shadows?</description></item><item><title>BONUS: Dictators’ Chefs | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100019/</guid><description>Podcast Description For this special bonus episode, Noiser writer Duncan Barrett sat down for a chat with Witold Szabłowski, author of How to Feed a Dictator: Saddam Hussein, Idi Amin, Enver Hoxha, Fidel Castro and Pol Pot Through the Eyes of Their Cooks. The role of personal chef to a dictator is a fascinating one. It’s an extremely intimate relationship. These cooks have literally nourished tyrants. They’ve satisfied their culinary cravings, altered their moods for better and worse, and even influenced their policies.</description></item><item><title>Introducing: Detectives Don’t Sleep - The Nazi Art Mystery (Part 1 of 3) | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100020/</guid><description>Podcast Description The makers of Real Dictators present a brand-new podcast: Detectives Don’t Sleep. Step beyond the police tape to shadow the real detectives who worked history’s most intriguing cases. In this taster episode, we’re hot on the heels of international art detective Arthur Brand. He is hunting down a pair of lost statues… Two giant bronze horses that were once beloved by none other than Adolf Hitler. But a case of missing artworks quickly spirals into something far more dangerous - a deadly neo-Nazi conspiracy… If you enjoy this taster episode, search ‘Detectives Don’t Sleep’ in your podcast app and hit follow to get new episodes every Tuesday.</description></item><item><title>Hitler: Attack on Russia, War with America… | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100021/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100021/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Führer’s deputy embarks on an astonishing secret mission. After baling out Mussolini in the Balkans, German troops finally march into the Soviet Union. Undeterred by the bloodshed, Hitler will sign off 1941 by declaring war on the United States… A Noiser production, written by Jeff Dawson. Scroll down the Real Dictators feed for episodes on Hitler’s early years and rise to power. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Adolf Hitler vs Winston Churchill | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Installed in Downing Street, Churchill arrives with a bang. The Battle of Britain rages in the skies, while the Nazis plot a seaborne invasion across the English Channel. And Hitler extends his network of allies, seeking to bring the Spanish and Japanese strongmen to the table… A Noiser production, written by Jeff Dawson. Scroll down the Real Dictators feed for episodes on Hitler’s early years and rise to power.</description></item><item><title>Hitler: A Brush With Death… | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100023/</guid><description>Podcast Description World War Two begins. After the invasion of Poland, Hitler sets his sights on Scandinavia. A devastating lightning war rolls over Western Europe, as the German panzers arrive in Paris. Meanwhile, the Führer’s British lover makes an attempt on her own life. And a lone clockmaker decides to bump off Hitler once and for all… A Noiser production, written by Jeff Dawson. Scroll down the Real Dictators feed for episodes on Hitler’s early years and rise to power.</description></item><item><title>Hitler’s Birthday, Poland’s Doom | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hitler continues his Godfather act, ignoring the Munich settlement and gobbling up the rest of Czechoslovakia. As he turns 50, the Führer is showered with extravagant birthday gifts. Meanwhile, behind the scenes, the finishing touches are put to a shock pact with Stalin. But Britain and France draw a line. An invasion of Poland will mean war… A Noiser production, written by Jeff Dawson. Scroll down the Real Dictators feed for episodes on Hitler’s early years and rise to power.</description></item><item><title>Hitler: The Gathering Storm... | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100025/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hitler expands the Third Reich, annexing Austria and the Sudetenland. Britain and France seek a diplomatic solution at the Munich Conference. But how long will appeasement keep war at bay? Meanwhile, the Nazis stir up an orgy of anti-Jewish violence, Kristallnacht&amp;hellip; A Noiser production, written by Jeff Dawson. This is Part 16 of the Hitler Story. Scroll down the Real Dictators feed for episodes on Hitler’s early years and rise to power.</description></item><item><title>Adolf Hitler: Unassailable Führer | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100026/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100026/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is Part 15 of the Hitler Story. You can start listening here. Or, scroll down the Real Dictators feed for episodes on Hitler’s early years and rise to power. We pick up the tale in the mid-1930s. From struggling artist to veteran soldier of the trenches, now Hitler is transformed into Germany’s dictator. The new Third Reich is in the spotlight at the Berlin Olympics. Behind the scenes, the armed forces expand at an alarming rate.</description></item><item><title>Robert Mugabe Part 4: A Game of Thrones | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100027/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100027/</guid><description>Podcast Description At the age of 93, Mugabe’s days in office are numbered. But the succession crisis threatens to tear Zimbabwe apart. In South Africa, exiles hatch an extraordinary plan to oust him. And when the dictator’s own wife throws her hat into the ring, Mugabe’s house of cards will begin tumbling down… A Noiser production, written by Duncan Barrett. This is Part 4 of 4. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Robert Mugabe Part 3: Zimbabwe’s Tsunami | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100028/</guid><description>Podcast Description After two decades in office, Mugabe has already shown himself to be a tyrant. At the dawn of the 21st century, the outside world sits up and takes notice. Mugabe seizes white-owned farms and drags his country into the greatest economic crisis since the Wall Street Crash. But the resistance is growing stronger… A Noiser production, written by Duncan Barrett. This is Part 3 of 4. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Robert Mugabe Part 2: The Leopard’s True Spots… | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100029/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mugabe is now the leader of independent Zimbabwe. But behind the façade of democracy, he is already governing through fear. Emboldened, he unleashes a campaign of genocide on his opponents. For now, for the most part, the international community turns a blind eye. But the arrival of a new prime minister - not in Zimbabwe but in faraway Britain - will herald Mugabe’s first great crisis… A Noiser production, written by Duncan Barrett.</description></item><item><title>Robert Mugabe Part 1: The Young Scholar | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100030/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100030/</guid><description>Podcast Description For almost four decades, Robert Mugabe held the reins of power in Zimbabwe with an iron grip. As a youthful idealist, he led a revolutionary movement that put his country back in African hands. But once in power, he presided over a regime of brutality and jaw-dropping corruption. So what events helped form Mugabe? And how did he manoeuvre himself from obscurity to power? A Noiser production, written by Duncan Barrett.</description></item><item><title>Robert Mugabe: Coming Soon on Real Dictators… | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100031/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Beginning Wednesday November 9th. We’re in Zimbabwe for the extraordinary story of Robert Mugabe. Early access to new episodes for Noiser+ subscribers. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Lenin Part 4: Ghost at the Kremlin | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100032/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100032/</guid><description>Podcast Description With power finally in Bolshevik hands, state terror arrives in Russia. The Soviet Union is born. But, installed in Red Square, Lenin’s health is ailing. Will his creation live on beyond his death? And which of his lieutenants, jostling for position, will take up the baton? A Noiser production, written by Dan Smith. This is Part 4 of 4. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Lenin Part 3: First Russia, Then the World… | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100033/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100033/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Tsar is deposed as the people of the Russian Empire rise up. Marooned in Switzerland, Vladimir Lenin prepares for an extraordinary journey home, by land and sea. It will involve the closest of shaves, multiple disguises, and the covert help of Russia’s deadliest enemy… A Noiser production, written by Dan Smith. This is Part 3 of 4. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Lenin Part 2: Underground, On the Run | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100034/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vladimir Lenin meets Joseph Stalin. Turning to crime to pay their way, the revolutionaries struggle to stay ahead of the authorities. As the First World War upends Russia, the Bolsheviks wait for their moment. In the meantime, Lenin’s love life takes an unconventional turn&amp;hellip; A Noiser production, written by Dan Smith. This is Part 2 of 4. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Lenin Part 1: The Revolution is Born | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100035/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vladimir Lenin changed the course of history like very few ever have. He turned Russia upside down and created the first communist state. As the founder of the Soviet Union, he ensured the world would never be the same again. But long before his time in power, his life is something straight out of a spy thriller. Young Vladimir enjoys a happy, comfortable childhood. That is, until a double tragedy puts him on a very different path&amp;hellip; A Noiser production, written by Dan Smith.</description></item><item><title>Vladimir Lenin: Coming Soon on Real Dictators… | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100036/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100036/</guid><description>Podcast Description The story of Lenin - leader of the Russian Revolution, founder of the Soviet Union - begins Wednesday September 28th. Early access to new episodes for Noiser+ subscribers. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Napoleon Part 6: Showdown at Waterloo | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100037/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100037/</guid><description>Podcast Description With Napoleon deposed and in exile, it appears to be game over. But even now he is planning a comeback. After the mother of all prison breaks, Napoleon marches back up through France. Reinstating himself as emperor, he will rally his troops for one last battle&amp;hellip; A Noiser production, written by Jeff Dawson. This is Part 6 of 6. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Napoleon Part 5: Downfall in Russia | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100038/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Napoleon’s blockade of Britain begins. Amidst the fall-out, France launches an invasion of Spain. The Duke of Wellington arrives on the scene. After another dispute with Russia, Bonaparte assembles his biggest ever army. It will do the unthinkable and march on Moscow&amp;hellip; A Noiser production, written by Jeff Dawson. This is Part 5 of 6. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+. Now available for Apple and Android users.</description></item><item><title>Napoleon Part 4: The Emperor Strikes Back | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100039/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonaparte storms back into Italy, reconquering all that had been lost. Back home, in Notre-Dame Cathedral, thousands of dignitaries watch on as the untouchable general crowns himself emperor. Intent on destroying Britain, he plans a seaborne invasion. But Lord Nelson has other ideas… A Noiser production, written by Jeff Dawson. This is Part 4 of 6. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Napoleon Part 3: The Egyptian Adventure | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100040/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Napoleon sails for the Middle East. After the Battle of the Pyramids, a scientific mission makes remarkable findings, introducing the Western world to the mysteries of Ancient Egypt. But after a drubbing from Britain’s naval supremo, Horatio Nelson, Napoleon does a runner. His return to Paris is timed to perfection. Almost by accident, Bonaparte will seize power&amp;hellip; A Noiser production, written by Jeff Dawson. This is Part 3 of 6.</description></item><item><title>Napoleon Part 2: The Italian Job | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100041/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100041/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a quickie wedding, Napoleon Bonaparte dashes south to take command of the French Army in Italy. Here he announces himself with a devastating display of battlefield brilliance. In Milan, he gets a taste for political rule and good living. Napoleon will return to Paris both as a military hero and a budding statesman&amp;hellip; A Noiser production, written by Jeff Dawson. This is Part 2 of 6. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Napoleon Part 1: The Humble Corsican | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100042/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100042/</guid><description>Podcast Description You’ve heard the name Napoleon Bonaparte. But who was he, really? In 1769 a boy is born on the Mediterranean island of Corsica. He will go on to become an emperor - a virtual god in his adopted homeland, a nemesis to his international foes. So how does Napoleon become the most powerful man on Earth? And why doesn’t he stop, even once he has it all? A Noiser production, written by Jeff Dawson.</description></item><item><title>Napoleon: Coming Soon on Real Dictators… | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100043/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100043/</guid><description>Podcast Description The story of Napoleon Bonaparte begins Wednesday August 3rd. Early access to new episodes for Noiser+ subscribers. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Pol Pot Part 4: The Killing Fields | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100044/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pol Pot constructs a secretive one-party state. Cambodia descends into hell as his twisted social experiment begins. Finally, the shifting sands of geopolitics will create challenges for the Khmer Rouge. Pol Pot will be forced back into the jungle. But even then, the man with untold blood on his hands will somehow evade justice. A Noiser production, written by Dan Smith. Many thanks to Elizabeth Becker and University of Washington Libraries for archive audio.</description></item><item><title>Pol Pot Part 3: Vietnam War, Cambodian Revolution | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100045/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100045/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Khmer Rouge launch their revolution against Sihanouk… until Sihanouk himself is stabbed in the back. America’s action in Vietnam escalates, spilling over the border with catastrophic consequences. The enigmatic Pol Pot will emerge from the bloodshed to become the most powerful man in the land. At the outset of ‘Year Zero’, the true horror will begin&amp;hellip; A Noiser production, written by Dan Smith. This is Part 3 of 4.</description></item><item><title>Pol Pot Part 2: Welcome to the Jungle | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100046/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 23:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Saloth Sar, the young man who will become Pol Pot, arrives in France in 1949. In just a few short months, he will be transformed into a die-hard communist rebel. Meanwhile, in Cambodia, things are coming to the boil. Returning from Europe, Sar goes to ground with the Vietnamese communists. He begins to prepare his very own revolution… A Noiser production, written by Dan Smith. This is Part 2 of 4.</description></item><item><title>Pol Pot Part 1: Tyrant in the Shadows | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100047/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cambodia today is many people’s idea of heaven on earth. But in the 1970s it was a netherworld of death and despair. Under Pol Pot and the Khmer Rouge, in just four years around a quarter of the population perished. Pol Pot was a uniquely anonymous dictator - a man who preferred to operate in the shadows. So who was he? And how did he come to lead such a staggeringly bloody regime?</description></item><item><title>Pol Pot: Coming Soon on Real Dictators… | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100048/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100048/</guid><description>Podcast Description The story of the Cambodian dictator, Pol Pot, begins Wednesday June 22nd. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Introducing: Real Outlaws - Billy the Kid Part 1 | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100049/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100049/</guid><description>Podcast Description From Noiser, Real Outlaws is the new podcast that travels back in time to when rogues and bandits followed a code all of their own. In this taster episode, we’re on the trail of Billy the Kid - perhaps the best-known outlaw in American history. Hero or villain? You decide. Follow Real Outlaws to get Part 2 now. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Julius Caesar Part 3: Murder in the Senate | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100050/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Caesar departs Egypt with his lover, Cleopatra, secure on the throne. After crushing Pompey’s allies, he returns to Rome. His rule proves popular with the masses. But senators grow concerned by his increasing megalomania. With the Ides of March approaching, conspirators hatch an historic assassination plot… A Noiser production, written by Jeff Dawson. This is Part 3 of 3. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Julius Caesar Part 2: Rendezvous With Cleopatra | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100051/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Caesar’s campaign in Gaul begins. An invasion on an epic scale, it will also include two missions to the rain-lashed island of Britain. Back home, however, the collapse of the Triumvirate pushes Rome towards civil war. The conflict will spill across the Mediterranean, driving Julius Caesar into the arms of a certain Queen Cleopatra… A Noiser production, written by Jeff Dawson. This is Part 2 of 3. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Julius Caesar Part 1: The Roman Dictator | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100052/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Politician, writer, warrior, lover&amp;hellip; Julius Caesar was the dictator-for-life who became the absolute ruler of Rome and its domains. His life was a series of extraordinary and gruesome adventures. The young student kidnapped by pirates. The general who butchered the people of Gaul and led the Roman legions into Britain. The lothario famously entranced by Cleopatra. But how much truth do the legends contain? A Noiser production, written by Jeff Dawson.</description></item><item><title>Julius Caesar: Coming Soon on Real Dictators... | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100053/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join us on a trip to Ancient Rome. The first of three episodes on the legendary Roman general drops Wednesday May 4th. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Genghis Khan Part 2: Rise of the Mongols | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100054/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100054/</guid><description>Podcast Description The leader brings reforms to his newly unified Mongol nation. The man formerly known as Temüjin will now conquer an empire bigger than any before in recorded history. But what are the innovations that underpin his supremacy? And how will history judge him - as a cruel tyrant, or a great leader? A Noiser production, written by Dan Smith. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Genghis Khan Part 1: Underdog to Emperor | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100055/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100055/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;rsquo;re in the Mongol lands of Central Asia in the late 1100s. This is a place of nomadic warriors, a region divided between tribes. But one man will emerge to unite them. Armed with the greatest military mind of his age, he will lead the Mongol peoples far beyond their own borders. A terror to his enemies, he will build a reputation unmatched for cruelty and barbarism. So how does a boy from humble origins come to rule an empire twice the size of Ancient Rome&amp;rsquo;s?</description></item><item><title>Hitler: Night of the Long Knives | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100056/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100056/</guid><description>Podcast Description To ward off the Western Allies, Hitler takes a trip to Venice to visit Mussolini. At home, meanwhile, Hitler’s paramilitaries, the SA, are growing restless. In a final savage act, the mother of all purges, Hitler will liquidate anyone who has ever wronged him. Under the unassailable German Führer, the Third Reich will begin… A Noiser production, written by Jeff Dawson. Scroll to Season 2 for episodes on Hitler’s early years.</description></item><item><title>Hitler: The Reichstag Fire | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100057/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Installed as Chancellor, Hitler briefs his army chiefs to prepare for war. But first, he must deal with enemies at home… After the German parliament building is set ablaze, Hitler seizes the opportunity to eliminate all political opposition. His opponents will be dragged away to the first of the infamous camps. A Noiser production, written by Jeff Dawson. Scroll to Season 2 for episodes on Hitler’s early years. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Adolf Hitler Seizes Power | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100058/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100058/</guid><description>Podcast Description As Hitler-mania sweeps the land, the Nazis win an election landslide. But Hitler finds himself shut out by the Prussian elite, at least until he can grind them into submission. Finally, the unthinkable happens. Adolf Hitler becomes Chancellor of Germany. A Noiser production, written by Jeff Dawson. Scroll to Season 2 for episodes on Hitler’s early years. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Hitler's Secret Family | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100059/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100059/</guid><description>Podcast Description After the Wall Street Crash, the German economy nosedives. The Nazis find themselves within grasp of government. As Adolf Hitler makes headlines across Europe, secret relatives come out of the woodwork. With Hitler’s newfound fame comes the whiff of scandal, and a personal tragedy that could derail everything. A Noiser production, written by Jeff Dawson. Scroll to Season 2 for episodes on Hitler’s early years. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Hitler's Women &amp; Joseph Goebbels | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100060/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adolf Hitler, at large once again, finds himself barred from public life. Retreating to the mountains, he finds a new home and a female companion. It won’t be the last of Hitler’s relationships to end in an attempted suicide. Meanwhile, backed by Joseph Goebbels, the self-proclaimed führer plots his comeback as a respectable politician. A Noiser production, written by Jeff Dawson. Scroll to Season 2 for episodes on Hitler’s early years.</description></item><item><title>Introducing: Short History Of... Bonnie and Clyde | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100061/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 02:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100061/</guid><description>Podcast Description From the creators of Real Dictators we present Short History Of&amp;hellip; Hosted by Paul McGann, this show gives you a front-row seat as history’s most incredible moments play out right before you. Forged by the Great Depression, Bonnie and Clyde became icons of lawlessness, thrilling and shocking America with their crime sprees and doomed romance. But what drove them to lives of such violence? And with the full might of the police against them, how did it all end?</description></item><item><title>Hitler in Prison &amp; Mein Kampf | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100062/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adolf Hitler, now a national celebrity, begins his jail term. Besieged by well-wishers, he has faith his time inside will be short. To keep the Nazi flame burning, he decides to write a new book. “Mein Kampf” will one day make Hitler a best-selling author and a multi-millionaire. But how will it be received right now, in the new thriving Germany? A Noiser production, written by Jeff Dawson. This is Part 9 of the Hitler Story.</description></item><item><title>Adolf Hitler's Day in Court | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100063/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Munich, Germany. November 1923. The Nazis have just attempted to launch a revolution. But instead, Adolf Hitler now finds himself on the run from the law. Unless he makes it to the border, the firing squad beckons. But in fact, as unlikely as it seems, Hitler is about to take Germany by storm. A Noiser production, written by Jeff Dawson. This is Part 8 of the Hitler Story. You can start listening here.</description></item><item><title>Turkmenbashy Part 2: Putin, Taliban, Internet Shutdown | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100064/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100064/</guid><description>Podcast Description As the new Turkmen leader, Saparmurat Niyazov has absolute power. He uses it to construct one of history’s most surreal regimes. Rebuilding the capital city in white marble, he puts his own mother at the forefront of public life. A series of absurd policies begins. Even as the War on Terror lands on his doorstep, the tyrant seems unstoppable. But, somehow, opposition will emerge, culminating in a dramatic attempt on his life.</description></item><item><title>Turkmenbashy Part 1: Soviet Stooge, Hermit Tyrant | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100065/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 10:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Turkmenistan in Central Asia. Somewhere unremarkable, you might assume. But you’d be wrong. Away from prying eyes, an extraordinary story unfolded here. In the early 1990s, a man called Saparmurat Niyazov creates a brand-new state from the rubble of the Soviet Union. His regime will be a case study in modern tyranny, filled with bizarre pronouncements and barely believable laws. As ‘Turkmenbashy’, or ‘Head of the Turkmen’, Niyazov rules into the 2000s, turning Turkmenistan into a North Korea 2.</description></item><item><title>Idi Amin Part 6: The Entebbe Raid | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100066/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Four Israeli jets descend on Uganda under cover of night. An audacious commando mission begins. It will spark the beginning of the end for Idi Amin. After a fatally ill-judged war with Tanzania, the tyrant will be ousted. Leaving a grim legacy behind him, he’ll begin a surreal retirement thousands of miles away. A Noiser production, written by Jeff Dawson. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Idi Amin Part 5: Husband, Father, Movie Star | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100067/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100067/</guid><description>Podcast Description We delve into Amin’s private life, taking in his many marriages, mistresses and children. The President makes a triumphant return to the boxing ring, seemingly in his element. He participates in a barely believable film about his own life. But, away from the limelight, the Ugandan people have had enough. A Noiser production, written by Jeff Dawson. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Idi Amin Part 4: Expulsion of the Asians | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100068/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100068/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a speech, Amin makes an extraordinary announcement – something he claims came to him in a dream. All Ugandans of Asian origin must leave the country within 90 days. Thousands of citizens scramble to respond. Meanwhile, out in the countryside, supporters of Obote are massacred in their hundreds. An army of exiles prepares to launch the first serious attempt on Big Daddy’s rule. A Noiser production, written by Jeff Dawson.</description></item><item><title>Idi Amin Part 3: ‘Big Daddy’ Seizes Power | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100069/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amin wages war on Buganda’s king. The administration strengthens its grip on power. But after Obote survives an assassination attempt by mere inches, rumours swirl as to the perpetrator’s identity. Brigadier Amin goes on an army recruitment drive. Soon, Obote must depart Uganda to do business abroad. And when he does, who knows what might happen in his absence&amp;hellip; A Noiser production, written by Jeff Dawson. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Idi Amin Part 2: Warlord In-Waiting... | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100070/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100070/</guid><description>Podcast Description The curtain falls on the British Empire in Africa. Uganda is free. Idi Amin becomes the right-hand man of the nation&amp;rsquo;s new leader, Milton Obote. Committing unspeakable atrocities against civilians, Amin dodges the law and sets himself up as a rogue arms dealer. Obote had better watch his back. A Noiser production, written by Jeff Dawson. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Idi Amin Part 1: The Butcher of Uganda | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100071/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100071/</guid><description>Podcast Description From 1971 to 1979, President Idi Amin Dada devastated Uganda. The military dictator sank the economy and deported an entire ethnic class. He slaughtered up to half a million of his fellow citizens. All with the persona of &amp;lsquo;Big Daddy&amp;rsquo;, the playful joker. His image as a buffoon, however, belied his extraordinary charisma and his mastery of communication. In a continent ravaged by empire, his bloody tale is part of a much larger story.</description></item><item><title>Introducing: History Daily | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100072/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 15:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100072/</guid><description>Podcast Description On History Daily, we do history, daily. Every weekday beginning November 1st, host Lindsay Graham (American Scandal, American History Tellers) takes you back in time to explore a momentous event that happened on this day in history. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Introducing: Short History Of... | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100073/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100073/</guid><description>Podcast Description From the creators of Real Dictators comes a brand-new weekly show. Short History Of&amp;hellip; gives you a front-row seat as history&amp;rsquo;s most incredible moments play out right before you. In this taster episode, we&amp;rsquo;re in Cuba. It&amp;rsquo;s October 1962. Three men – Kennedy, Khrushchev and Castro – hold the fate of the planet in their hands. A dispute over missiles spirals out of control. All sides brace for war.</description></item><item><title>Colonel Gaddafi Part 8: The Arab Spring | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100074/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100074/</guid><description>Podcast Description By early 2011, Libya is changing. The Arab Spring is underway. A young lawyer from Benghazi organises a protest. Before long, it will become a full-blown rebellion. Colonel Gaddafi, the man who has dominated Libya for four decades, will become a fugitive, soon to meet one of the grisliest ends of any dictator in history. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+. Now available for Apple and Android users.</description></item><item><title>Colonel Gaddafi Part 7: 9/11 and a New Ally | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100075/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100075/</guid><description>Podcast Description On September 11th, 2001, life in the West is transformed in an instant. Amidst the fall-out, Gaddafi spots an opportunity. To the surprise of many, he makes it his mission to re-join the international fold. The Libyan dictator pitches his Bedouin tent on the front lawns of palaces and parliaments across the world. Muammar Gaddafi - the man of many masks - is transforming into the West’s most eccentric friend.</description></item><item><title>Colonel Gaddafi Part 6: The Lockerbie Bombing | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100076/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100076/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1988, Gaddafi takes his terror to the skies, bringing down a passenger flight over Lockerbie, Scotland. Staffers at the Pentagon team up with Hollywood executives to shore up public opinion against the tyrant. Meanwhile, the Colonel himself looks south - across the Sahara - and prepares to be crowned &amp;lsquo;King of Kings&amp;rsquo;. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+. Now available for Apple and Android users.</description></item><item><title>Colonel Gaddafi Part 5: Reagan vs Gaddafi | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100077/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gaddafi takes his terror onto the streets of London and Berlin. Libyan agents hunt down his opponents across the globe. The Reagan administration launches airstrikes, targeting the dictator and his inner circle. With the stakes higher than ever, Gaddafi&amp;rsquo;s security network works overtime to stamp out dissent. Thousands of schoolchildren bear witness to a gruesome lesson in tyranny. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Colonel Gaddafi Part 4: The Munich Olympic Massacre | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100078/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100078/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the summer of 1972, at the Munich Olympic Games, a festival of sport becomes a terrifying nightmare. The Libyan leader tightens his grip on power at home, while exporting terror abroad. Tension with America is reaching breaking point. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+. Now available for Apple and Android users. Click the Noiser+ banner on Apple or go to noiser.</description></item><item><title>Colonel Gaddafi Part 3: Vengeance Day | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100079/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Muammar Gaddafi can’t quite believe his luck. Still in his twenties, he finds himself leader of an oil-rich country. The Colonel wastes no time kicking out the Americans and the Brits. He instigates a &amp;lsquo;Vengeance Day&amp;rsquo; to deal with Libya’s colonial oppressors. Living standards soar for ordinary Libyans. But the cracks are already appearing. Things are about to spin off in a very different direction&amp;hellip; For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Colonel Gaddafi Part 2: Gaddafi in London | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100080/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100080/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the 1960s, Libya gets rich on oil. But, with the wealth squandered, many question the King’s authority. Among them is young Muammar Gaddafi. Sent to England as a military cadet, Gaddafi roams the streets of Swinging London in flowing Bedouin robes. With his training complete, he readies himself for an audacious seizure of power. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+. Now available for Apple and Android users.</description></item><item><title>Colonel Gaddafi Part 1: Son of the Desert | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100081/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100081/</guid><description>Podcast Description ‘Brother Leader’, ‘King of Kings’, ‘Falcon of Africa’… ‘The Most Dangerous Man in the World&amp;rsquo;. Colonel Gaddafi was the Libyan tyrant who abused his people on an industrial scale, until he was murdered by them as they rose up against him. A revolutionary who freed his country from empire, only to squander its riches. Terrorist sponsor one moment, Western ally the next. At the height of World War Two, a Bedouin child is born in Libya’s desert.</description></item><item><title>Franco Part 5: Life After a Dictator | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100082/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100082/</guid><description>Podcast Description The horrors of the past are buried. After 20 years in power, Franco embraces capitalism and declares himself a moderniser. Spain becomes a leading holiday destination. Later, Franco plans his own succession. The ailing Generalissimo headhunts a dashing young heir. But it remains to be seen whether this successor will keep to Franco’s script. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+. Now available for Apple and Android users.</description></item><item><title>Franco Part 4: The Cold War &amp; the President | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100083/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100083/</guid><description>Podcast Description The ‘White Terror’ continues. Spain’s strongman assumes power in Madrid, herding his defeated enemies into concentration camps. Franco commissions a movie to tell his own life story. Up in the mountains, die-hard rebels continue to resist. After World War Two, Franco seeks to re-brand. ‘El Caudillo’ sets about seducing a brand-new ally: the United States. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+. Now available for Apple and Android users.</description></item><item><title>Franco Part 3: The Spanish Civil War | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100084/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100084/</guid><description>Podcast Description In July 1936, Spain erupts into civil war. But Francisco Franco is marooned far away in the Canary Islands. A devious rescue mission ensues. Back on Spanish soil, Franco begins the process of conquering his homeland, butchering his enemies as he goes. Mussolini and Hitler lend a hand. Closing in on Madrid, Franco lays the groundwork for a decades-long dictatorship. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Franco Part 2: Murder in Africa | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100085/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100085/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1917, Franco is posted to northern Spain. He courts a local schoolgirl named Carmen. But soon, a charismatic army superior convinces Franco to return to Africa. In Morocco, he brutalises the local population. Climbing the military ranks, Franco becomes something of a celebrity. Meanwhile, Spain itself spirals towards civil war. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+. Now available for Apple and Android users.</description></item><item><title>Franco Part 1: Spain’s Buried Past | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100086/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, Spain is Europe’s holiday capital. But under the sand lie sinister secrets. From 1939 to 1975, Francisco Franco ruled as the nation’s dictator. Despite his bloody reign, the General died peacefully in his bed at a ripe old age. How was he able to get away with such atrocities? The story begins in the 1890s. Francisco Franco is born and raised on Spain’s Atlantic coast. After joining the army, he’s posted to north Africa.</description></item><item><title>Adolf Hitler Part 7: The Day of Treason | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100087/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100087/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the final part of Hitler’s Early Years, the Nazi leader launches his very own assault on power: the Munich Putsch. Under cover of darkness, the SA prepare to storm locations across Munich. Hitler himself prepares to kidnap a senior politician. Will the Nazis take over Germany? Or will they fail and fade back into obscurity? For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Adolf Hitler Part 6: Hitler’s Secret Book | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100088/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100088/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Nazis kickstart their media operation. Desperate to be an icon, Hitler pens a secret autobiography, where he compares his own rise to Jesus’s resurrection. French and Belgian troops cross the German border, while the economy goes into meltdown. Amidst the turmoil, the Nazis plot their very own coup d’état. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+. Now available for Apple and Android users.</description></item><item><title>Adolf Hitler Part 5: The Stormtroopers Arrive | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100089/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hitler decides he needs an army of his own. The Nazis create a new paramilitary unit – the Sturmabteilung, or SA. These hooligans take National Socialism onto the streets. Hitler assembles an executive team of deputies. They include Ernst Röhm - an army insider with a stockpile of weapons. And a celebrity fighter pilot called Hermann Göring&amp;hellip; For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Adolf Hitler Part 4: The Spy Becomes the Nazi Leader | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100090/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 20:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hitler is sent undercover, tasked with spying on a band of extremists. But he soon falls under their spell and breaks cover to join their ranks. They will soon become the Nazi Party, and this new recruit their leader. Under a new mentor, Adolf Hitler finds his voice. His march towards power is grinding into gear. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Adolf Hitler Part 3: The 'Stab in the Back' | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100091/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100091/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Great War ends. Hitler despairs. The Kaiser does a runner. Revolutions break out across Germany. Discharged from hospital, Hitler returns home to Munich, desperate to keep his army job. The Allies gather in Paris to settle the tab for the War. Hitler drinks in far-right conspiracy theories. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+. Now available for Apple and Android users. Click the Noiser+ banner on Apple or go to noiser.</description></item><item><title>Adolf Hitler Part 2: Hitler in the First World War | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100092/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100092/</guid><description>Podcast Description June 1914, Sarajevo. An assassination on the street disrupts the entire balance of power in Europe. The First World War explodes into action. Adolf Hitler relocates to Munich. After dodging the draft, he later embraces life as a soldier. But then, serving in Flanders in 1918, a traumatic injury threatens to end his rise to power before it’s even started. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Adolf Hitler Part 1: Birth of a Führer | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100093/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100093/</guid><description>Podcast Description You may know something of the Hitler story. But there’s a decent chance you don’t know the half of it. We begin a deep dive into the early years of a man who became the very embodiment of evil. Peeling away Hitler’s own myths about his childhood, we explore how he emerged from obscurity. The future German Führer isn’t born in Germany. Growing up in Austria, he clashes with his father but idolises his mother.</description></item><item><title>Introducing: Real Narcos Season 2 - Félix Gallardo | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100094/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 17:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100094/</guid><description>Podcast Description From the creators of Real Dictators comes Real Narcos, the show that takes you to the front line of the war on drugs. For Season 2, we&amp;rsquo;re in Mexico. In 1985, Kiki Camarena is a US DEA agent on the trail of Félix Gallardo - the man known as the Mexican Godfather. But Camarena&amp;rsquo;s kidnapping at the hands of the cartel will send shockwaves around the world. Search &amp;lsquo;Real Narcos&amp;rsquo; in your podcast app and hit follow for more episodes.</description></item><item><title>General Tojo Part 4: The Atom Bombs | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100095/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 13:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100095/</guid><description>Podcast Description The walls close in on Hideki Tojo. The General turned Prime Minister takes hands-on control of the military, with catastrophic consequences. Emperor Hirohito pulls the plug. With Tojo forced out of office and on the run from the Allies in Tokyo, the end of World War Two arrives. But its final chapter will change the world forever more. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>General Tojo Part 3: Attack on Pearl Harbor | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100096/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 09:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Japan attacks Pearl Harbor. The Pacific War is underway. In Tokyo, Prime Minister Tojo moves to take every significant government job for himself. Japanese troops sweep through the Malay Peninsula. Thousands of Allied soldiers are interned in prisoner of war camps, in conditions that beggar belief. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+. Now available for Apple and Android users. Click the Noiser+ banner on Apple or go to noiser.</description></item><item><title>General Tojo Part 2: Terror in China | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100097/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Major General Hideki Tojo takes command of the secret police - the Kempeitai. The Imperial Japanese Army invades China and terrorises the civilian population. Kempeitai operatives set up a secret lab where they carry out horrific medical and weapons experiments. This is only the beginning. Before long, Prime Minister Tojo will ready the nation for war with the United States. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>General Tojo Part 1: The Young Samurai | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100098/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 00:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100098/</guid><description>Podcast Description General Hideki Tojo led Japan into World War Two and oversaw some of the most horrific war crimes in recorded history. Tojo did not hold absolute power, but he more than earns his place at this table. Ruling under a compliant Emperor, Tojo gathered power to himself. He was the minister who outgrew his master, the bureaucrat whose relentless work ethic took him to the apex of government. Hideki Tojo is born in 1884.</description></item><item><title>Papa Doc Part 3: Vampire of the Caribbean | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100099/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 17:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100099/</guid><description>Podcast Description François Duvalier puts the finishing touches to his terrifying cult of personality. The President for Life declares himself an immaterial being - a spirit that will hover over Haiti even after his body dies. Thoughts turn to succession. His son - &amp;ldquo;Baby Doc&amp;rdquo; - waits in the wings. Our contributors reflect on the legacy of Papa Doc - a name that will forever haunt the nightmares of Haitians. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Papa Doc Part 2: Haiti’s Dictator vs JFK | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100100/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 06:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Haitian dictator “Papa Doc” Duvalier crushes an attempted coup without mercy. Spooked by this near miss, Duvalier forms his own private militia called the Tonton Macoute. They take their name from a terrifying bogeyman of Haitian mythology. As the horrors of the regime become impossible to ignore, President Kennedy decides to lay down a marker. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+. Now available for Apple and Android users.</description></item><item><title>Papa Doc Part 1: The Voodoo Tyrant | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100101/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 08:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Just a few hundred miles south of Florida, across the Caribbean Sea, lies Haiti. From 1957 to 1971, this tropical island nation was ruled by a would-be demigod. François Duvalier - better known as “Papa Doc” - wielded the twin powers of state violence and voodoo. Real Dictators takes you behind the scenes of Papa Doc’s maniacal regime. His victims and adversaries tell the story of the medical doctor who became the butcher of his people.</description></item><item><title>Mao Zedong Part 3: The Cultural Revolution | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100102/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mao’s ‘Cultural Revolution’ sets out to purge the minds of an entire population. Meanwhile, the Supreme Leader himself leads a life of debauchery and excess - as his former doctor remembers. The Chairman seems invincible. But as his health deteriorates, his legacy is anything but assured. Eyewitnesses to his brutality reflect on what Mao means to China today, more than 40 years after his death. For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Mao Zedong Part 2: The ‘Great Leap Forward’ | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100103/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 22:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mao Zedong&amp;rsquo;s Communists come down from the mountains to do battle with the Nationalists. After clinching victory, Mao is greeted by many as a hero. But life under the new Chairman is about to get a whole lot worse. Installed as Supreme Leader, Mao sets about revolutionising the way his people live, work, and even think. His ‘Great Leap Forward’ is intended to be an economic masterplan. Instead, it will drive people across China to the wildest extremes of human behaviour.</description></item><item><title>Mao Zedong Part 1: Peasant’s Son, Communist Rebel | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100104/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 22:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100104/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the centre of China’s capital city, Beijing, lies a corpse that no one dares remove. It’s been 44 years since Mao Zedong’s body was laid to rest in the grandiose Chairman Mao Memorial Hall. He may be gone but he is not forgotten. To some, he’s the father of modern China. To many others, he’s a sadistic thug - a man willing to sacrifice millions of lives in pursuit of power.</description></item><item><title>Joseph Stalin Part 3: Hitler Attacks | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100105/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 22:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stalin’s regime hits the rocks when Adolf Hitler launches Operation Barbarossa and invades Russia. Nazi tanks plough towards Moscow in a devastating advance. Stalin’s legacy is forged in this fight to the death. In his final years, the strongman succumbs to cardiac problems. His tools for progress have been famine, slavery and execution. Yet to this day, some of his countrymen and women lionise him as the man who turned Russia into a superpower.</description></item><item><title>Joseph Stalin Part 2: The Secretary Becomes Dictator | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100106/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 12:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100106/</guid><description>Podcast Description With the First World War underway, Stalin’s journey to dictatorship grinds into gear. After the War, Russia is turned upside down. Stalin thrives in the chaos, masterminding a string of elaborate takedowns of his rivals. Rising to party leader, he visits a ruthless purge on his enemies. But Stalin’s brutality does not go unchallenged. The peasants revolt, while a showdown with his own wife at a dinner party has tragic consequences.</description></item><item><title>Joseph Stalin Part 1: The Young Bank Robber | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100107/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joseph Stalin - the “man of steel” - was the party secretary who plotted a route to absolute power, becoming head of the Eastern Bloc and chief nemesis of the United States. But how did a man from the Georgian frontier of the Russian Empire do it? In 1917, the 300-year-old Romanov Dynasty collapses. The communist Bolsheviks storm the Winter Palace and seize power. From this band of revolutionaries, a future bloody dictator - a man with an extraordinary backstory - begins to emerge&amp;hellip; For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Kim Jong-il Part 3: Nuclear Armed | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100108/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Installed as dictator, Kim Jong-il builds an all-powerful state that dominates the lives and minds of its people. North Korea is wracked by famine. The people adapt to survive - we hear from one man who flouted the rules and paid a horrific price. Lurid rumours emerge about how the ‘Dear Leader’ spends his leisure time. And Kim Jong-il begins work on an arsenal of nuclear weapons that will spook the world and pave the way for his own son’s ascent to power.</description></item><item><title>Kim Jong-il Part 2: Time to Make a Movie… | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100109/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kim Jong-il has risen to become propaganda chief under the rule of his father. Now, he hatches an audacious plan to turn North Korea into a filmmaking powerhouse. South Korea’s finest actress and leading director are kidnapped and find themselves on boats bound for the North. Elsewhere, Kim launches a charm offensive at the armed forces, readying the ground for his coronation. And his father dies, leaving the path to power seemingly clear&amp;hellip; For ad-free listening, exclusive content and early access to new episodes, join Noiser+.</description></item><item><title>Kim Jong-il Part 1: Birth of North Korea | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100110/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kim Jong-il built a rogue state with nuclear missiles trained on its enemies – all while living a life of the utmost luxury. In the first episode of Real Dictators, we piece together the early life of this tyrant and that of the country he came to rule. Kim Jong-il is born during World War Two. His father – Kim Il-sung – fights the Japanese and helps found the state of North Korea.</description></item><item><title>Trailer: Real Dictators | Real Dictators</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2216100111/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 17:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2216100111/</guid><description>Podcast Description How does a single human being convince thousands to kill for them and millions to turn a blind eye?
Real Dictators is the new podcast series hosted by Paul McGann (Dr Who, Luther, Withnail and I) that explores the hidden lives of history’s tyrants.
We encounter the American-trained doctor, “Papa Doc” Duvalier, who used modern medicine to convince the people of Haiti that he was a Voodoo god. There’s Kim Jong-il, who developed nuclear warheads alongside blockbuster movies.</description></item></channel></rss>