<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Rotten Mango on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/rotten-mango/</link><description>Recent content in Rotten Mango on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 01:12:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/rotten-mango/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>#321: Girl went missing in boarding school, found dead in a LOCKED boy’s restroom 33 days later | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440335/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 01:12:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440335/</guid><description>Podcast Description 16-year-old Gao was one of the most popular girls in the entire boarding school - till she went missing. All the students had their own little theories on what happened. Some believed she ran off with a guy she met online. Others speculated her ex-boyfriend had something to do with it. Or her best friend. Her best friend was the last one to see her alive. But they all agreed - wherever she was now… she was far away from the school.</description></item><item><title>#320: Twin Police officers accused of “inappropriate relationship” with 15-yr-old girl, later found dead while pregnant | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440001/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 01:12:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440001/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s normal to cringe when you think back to your middle school crush. Jane hated thinking about Robert. She had an obsession with him when she was 12 years old. She remembered everyone in the class would fight over him, try to get alone time with him, and he seemed to love all the attention he was getting. When Jane found out he was dating another girl - she was so devastated she didn’t know what to do with herself.</description></item><item><title>#319: Korean TV show accidentally CAUGHT a SERIAL husband killer | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440002/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 15:34:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440002/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 7 “friends” were going to spend the entire day with each other cliff jumping at a local waterfall but the entire day there would be filled with tension. Eunhae was the glue of the group, she was the one that organized the whole trip, and she was there with her boyfriend Joe. But her ex-boyfriend and his new girlfriend were also in attendance. Oh - and Eunhae’s husband was also there and he had no idea Eunhae was dating other people.</description></item><item><title>#318: 7 Husbands Drugged &amp; Assaulted Each Other’s Wives &amp; Live-Streamed It For Their “Boy Chatroom” | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 16:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440003/</guid><description>Podcast Description They each had a fantasy of watching their wives be intimate with other men. The only problem was that their wives were not open to the idea. The 7 husbands gathered on an online forum to talk about how they weren’t going to let their own wives get in the way of fulfilling their dreams. They felt they were entitled to this. For the next 8 years, the men would plot, drug, and facilitate the assaults of their own wives all the while filming it for their online chatrooms.</description></item><item><title>#317: Congresswoman Adopted 55 Children &amp; Turned Them Into Killers | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440004/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 23:17:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Congresswoman Flor was a lot of things - politician, pastor, gospel singer, wife, and mother of 55 adopted children. From a campaign standpoint she was unstoppable. She appealed to every possible demographic. The only thing standing in her way was the pesky rumor that she attended “swap” parties. The rumor was Congresswoman Flor and her husband would show up to these explicit parties wearing masks and watch each other with other partners… and sometimes… they would even bring their adopted children with them to watch.</description></item><item><title>#316: Elite Korean Matchmaking Service For Ultra Wealthy Ends With Marriage, Incest, and Murder | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 18:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Madame Ddu makes money off of love. For every match (marriage) she creates between ultra wealthy families - she gets paid $100k as a matchmaking fee. Madame Ddu united two powerful families through the marriage of their children, and she expected to be compensated for it. When the groom’s side refused to pay their share of her matchmaking fees - Madam Ddu was willing to play dirty to get them to break up.</description></item><item><title>#315: Big-Pharma Billionaires’ Bodies FOUND Hanging By The Pool During A House-Showing | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 15:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440006/</guid><description>Podcast Description She was one of the top realtors in all of Toronto, and that day she was going to be showing a $6.9M house to potential buyers. She gracefully toured the 12k square foot mansion with them before getting to the deepest corner of the basement level. The indoor lap pool. She pressed the button to let them in, and the room had this eerie glow to it. The only light on was the pool light - reflecting a blue back hue to the ceiling.</description></item><item><title>#314: College girl murdered by Special Ops for being an “International Spy" | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440007/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 23:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lily’s instructions were clear. She was to wait at the bottom of the mountain in the dark till she saw the light. The flashlight would beam down the mountain, leading her to where she needed to go. She was nervous, but she knew she needed to follow the directions. When she got to the top of the mountain - Lily saw the light led directly into a pre-dug 5-foot grave.</description></item><item><title>#313: The Beast Of Colombia - Serial Killer That Literally Sold His Soul To The Devil &amp; Sacrificed 221 Children | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 17:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440008/</guid><description>Podcast Description He had sold his soul and now to keep the devil happy he needed to make sacrifices with dead bodies &amp;amp; his Ouija board. 200+ bodies were found in Colombia brutally assaulted, tortured, and dismembered. Some were certain the serial killer was a priest that participated in satanic activities at night. Others stated it was a local crazy man that had gone criminal. Some even believed that it was a local witch that was going around killing to make sacrifices….</description></item><item><title>#312: Help Us Find Nancy - 12 Went To Yoga Retreat Only 11 Returned &amp; Nobody Will Tell What Happened | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440009/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 16:32:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440009/</guid><description>Podcast Description The yoga retreat was supposed to be a week of relaxation, connecting with nature, and peace. It was going to be held at the beautiful volcanic Lake Atitlán in Guatemala. 12 people were going to be at the week-long retreat together. Eating together, doing yoga together, hiking together - till one of them goes missing. The mysterious circumstances surrounding Nancy’s disappearance still have no answers. Where and how did she go missing?</description></item><item><title>#311: Top K-Pop Stars Opened a Night Club to Drug &amp; Sell Women to Overseas Investors | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440010/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 14:05:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440010/</guid><description>Podcast Description An IT specialist working at a data forensics company came across something odd. He was employed by the police to recover any missing files from a phone. He was good at his job - so he recovered it all. But when he took a look at the recovered data - he saw 200k text messages, photos, and videos of women being drugged and sold to the highest bidder in sinister group chats.</description></item><item><title>#310: She Tracked Down Her Brother's Killer Through Facebook | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440011/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 22:46:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440011/</guid><description>Podcast Description There were 5 people “trapped” on the boat, and 1 of them was a serial killer in the making. By the time the boat came back to shore, two people would be dead. They would have been mentally and physically tortured for two days straight. The serial killer would play games with the two victims. He wanted to torture them not only physically and sexually but also mentally. He wanted to pit them up against each other and make them fight so only one could live.</description></item><item><title>#309: She Went From Ivy League Student to Having IQ of 6 Year Old - Jealous Evil Classmate? | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 22:02:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440012/</guid><description>Podcast Description What would Ivy League students do to be on top? Or the better question - what wouldn’t they do? Ling was a chemistry major at the top university in China. The Harvard of China, if you will. One day, Ling went into the shower and saw fist-sized clumps of hair fall to her feet. By the end of the semester - Ling would be wheelchair-bound, unable to speak, unable to use the restroom on her own, completely bald, and nearly blind.</description></item><item><title>#308: “Anime Girl” Goes Viral For Stabbing Crush &amp; Now Has Fanclub of Men Wanting To Be Killed Next | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440013/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 18:08:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440013/</guid><description>Podcast Description A candid photo of 21-year-old Yuka had gone viral. She was sitting on the floor in her short t-shirt dress, phone up to her ear, and a cigarette relaxed between the fingers of her hand. She looked relaxed and causal. Pretty but in an effortless, almost innocent way. This photo would inspire people to make Fanclubs, donation links, and even fan art for Yuka. They were taken aback by her beauty and youth.</description></item><item><title>#307: Disturbing Cult Leader That Likes To Play Surgeon &amp; Mutilate All His Followers | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 23:10:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440014/</guid><description>Podcast Description There were things that fascinated him: surgery, polygamy, and torture. He decided the only way to have all 3 was if he started his own cult in the isolated woods of Canada. He gathered 40 followers in a small cabin, convinced them that the apocalypse was coming and the only way they could be saved was if they followed his every word. His male followers’ private parts were cut off, teeth were pulled out with pliers, and they were creatively beaten on a daily basis.</description></item><item><title>#306: Honor Roll Student Kills Mom With Cast Iron Skillet &amp; Steak Knife To Hide Her College Secrets | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 10:34:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Every college student has their secrets - but Sydney’s was that she was no longer in college. She had been suspended but hadn’t told a single person. She stayed in her dorm, pretended to go to class, studied with friends in the library, even attended sorority meetings. She was living a lie - and it was all about to come crashing down because her mom was on the phone with her school.</description></item><item><title>#305: Chef Brother Caught With Missing Sister’s DNA Inside His Rice Cooker | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lucy had just moved in with her new husband. Though she didn’t marry for love she felt like it would be easy to fall in love with this man. He cooked her 3 meals a day and got upset whenever she stepped foot in the kitchen. He said he just wanted her to rest and be happy. It was sweet. But soon Lucy noticed that even stepping foot near the kitchen would send her newlywed husband on edge… it felt like there was something in that kitchen she wasn’t allowed to see.</description></item><item><title>#304: Asian Obsessed Man Pushed 2 Girls Off Cliff Near “Disney” Castle | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440017/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 21:24:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440017/</guid><description>Podcast Description The real-life Cinderella Castle is situated on a steep cliff in Germany. It’s one of the most breathtaking tourist spots that has over 6k visitors per day. It was a symbol of romance, fairytales, and happy endings. Until a 21-year-old college graduate was murdered there. Two Asian-American college grads, Eva &amp;amp; Kelsey, were thrown off the 165-foot cliff by a man who was obsessed with Asians.
Full Source Notes: rottenmangopodcast.</description></item><item><title>#303: Parents Paid For Their Teens To Be Kidnapped From Bed &amp; Taken To Elite Torture Academy | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 16:19:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440018/</guid><description>Podcast Description They were all taken from their beds in the middle of the night. Four men standing over them, ready to hogtie them, and throw them into vans. The teenagers were being kidnapped, and their parents had paid the kidnappers. They were going to be taken to an elite academy where all the bad traits of being a kid were going to be tortured out of them. They would be thrown into isolation cells for 2 weeks, beaten, assaulted, and mentally manipulated till they became blank slates.</description></item><item><title>#302: TikToker Killed 2 People To Help Hide Her Mom’s Affair &amp; Save Her Career | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 18:14:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ansreen’s daughter was a rising TikToker that was gaining followers by the day. May loved showcasing her dancing, fashion, and even religion on her platform to inspire others. Even Ansreen was getting attention from joining May in some dancing TikToks. And with fame - comes people who want to cross boundaries to be with you. Ansreen had what she deemed a stalker. He was far from harmless. He had videos of her that would end her life, marriage, family, and even her daughter’s career if they were ever leaked.</description></item><item><title>#301: Japanese Dad-Daughter Duo Decapitate Victim In Love Motel | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 20:30:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440020/</guid><description>Podcast Description A lot of love motels are themed - and they are exactly what you imagine they would be used for. Couples coming and staying for a few hours to have their alone time. Runa, a 29-year-old living in Japan, was in an all-pink room of the local love motel. He was waiting for her in the bathroom, but she had a few things she had to prepare first. She reached into her suitcase and pulled out her raincoat.</description></item><item><title>#300: Korea’s Death Mall - 502 Dead &amp; 40 Missing Inside High End Department Store | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440021/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 13:44:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440021/</guid><description>Podcast Description There had been rumors floating around that children were pulling their parents out of the high-end mall. Some of them reported seeing bloody ghosts trying to climb onto the backs of the employees. Parents brushed off their children because this was one of the most luxurious malls in the entire nation. A coat can easily sell for $1k here. This was not a place where there would be ghosts… especially not bloody ones.</description></item><item><title>#299: Woman Whines “Why Me??” After Killing Bride On Her Wedding Day | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 17:45:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jamie (25) was getting emotional talking about her cat. If anything, she was getting riled up. Her parents decided to give her cat to her grandma, and that was just unacceptable. Her grandma could get her own cat. This one was hers! She ranted on the phone about it - as well as other things that had been weighing on her mind. Jamie complained about the food. Colored pencils.</description></item><item><title>#298: Daughter of Diplomat Found Beheaded In Nepo Baby’s Mansion | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440023/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 16:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440023/</guid><description>Podcast Description The team of therapists was making their way over to the mansion. They never really did house calls, but when one of the most powerful business tycoons in the entire city calls you - you pick up. They were going to talk to the businessman’s son to see how they could help him. Once they arrived at the house, they realized it was much more serious than they originally thought.</description></item><item><title>#297: Victim Singing K-Pop Song (2NE1’s - I Don’t Care) Leads To Double Murder | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440024/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 22:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440024/</guid><description>Podcast Description The mob was forming outside the 13 year old’s house. They were there day and night screaming her name, cursing, and some just silently crying. She was the most hated person in the Philippines right now. A video was circulating of the little girl pulling the hair of a woman moments before her murder. She asked the woman - “do you know who my dad is?” Her dad was a killer and he was about to commit a double homicide right in front of his teenage daughter.</description></item><item><title>#296: Two Sisters Dead After 12 K-Drama Directors’ Sexual Assault &amp; Torture | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440025/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 09:50:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440025/</guid><description>Podcast Description 12 K-Drama Directors that had worked on sets behind some of the most beloved, wholesome, shows were predators in disguise. They preyed on the extras. The ones that were desperate for work and just getting their foot in the door. They “passed them around” as if they were all some objects they had control over. For 3 months, Sora, was tortured at the hands of 12 casting directors. By the end of this case - Sora will die.</description></item><item><title>#295: Death Of Pop Star Leads To The EVIL Truth Behind The Voice Of China | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440026/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 15:19:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Coco Lee was more than just a singer - she was an absolute legend in most Chinese households. She was known for her talent, but her signature was her big smile and fiery personality. And after 28 years in the industry, she wasn’t slowing down now. Her most recent project - she was a judge on The Voice Of China. June 2, 2023 - Coco Lee left a voice message for her fan group telling them how much she loves them, thanks them for their support, and misses them.</description></item><item><title>#294: “Good Girl” Nurse Killed 7 Babies To Get Doctor’s Attention &amp; Sympathy | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440027/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 20:29:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Crush and Lucy Letby would always lean on each other for support during the tough times. They always prided themselves on being a good team. Even when times were tough, which they often were in the NICU, their bond remained strong. Chester Hospital was facing a dangerously significant uptick in infant deaths in its NICU unit. It felt like every other week, the nurses and doctors had to go home and weep with their families.</description></item><item><title>#293: Serial Killer Watched Podcasts About His Murders - CAUGHT After 13 Years | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 22:36:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shannon’s driver had a few roles. He would drive her to the client’s home, wait outside, and make sure she made it out of the house in one piece. He was security if you will and in this line of work (escorting) - security was everything. He wasn’t expecting the client to come rushing out demanding that Michael get Shannon out of his house. Confused, he went inside to see that Shannon was already on the phone with 911.</description></item><item><title>#292: TikToker in Perfect Relationship Accused Of Cleaning Up Crime Scene For Her BF’s Alleged Double Murder | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440029/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 15:16:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440029/</guid><description>Podcast Description She had the perfect “soft girl lifestyle” on TikTok. Kathy would share tidbits of her life on social media where she amassed thousands of fans who were all interested in her new luxury apartment, pastel-colored decor, and ultimately, her perfect relationship. Many of her TikToks were about how to find a partner that actually values you, cherishes you, and even showers you with the gifts that you deserve. She inspired a lot of viewers to want to have a perfect boyfriend and not settle for anything less.</description></item><item><title>#291: Pregnant Wife Pushed Off 110ft Cliff While Visiting National Park With Loving Husband | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440030/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 16:52:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440030/</guid><description>Podcast Description A young Chinese couple were vacationing at a National Park in Thailand. It was the husband’s gift to his pregnant wife with one last trip before their family grew! But during their sunrise hike the husband claimed his wife wandered off and fell off a 110 foot cliff. He screamed in Thai at the first responders - “You must help my wife! Please save my precious wife, she’s my everything!</description></item><item><title>#290: The Silent Killer of South Korea That Murdered 1500 Young People | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440031/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440031/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a South Korean emergency room a young family anxiously waited for help. Their 3 month old baby had been perfectly healthy but now his X-rays showed evidence that his lungs were literally solidifying and turning into rock. He was dying and there was nothing they could do to save him. They walked in a family of 3 - walked out a family of 2. Just a few days later the same family of 2 walked back in - and only 1 walked out alive.</description></item><item><title>#289: Young Chinese Couple Tortured &amp; Murdered In 5-Star Bali Resort | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440032/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 13:13:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nobody was seen entering or exiting the couple’s hotel room, but now they were both dead. The girlfriend was found in the bathtub strangled to death by her own pajamas. It was clear she had been murdered. Her boyfriend was found naked, crawling down the hallway groaning for help. He had 20 wounds all over his body including on his back - they were inflicted using a sharp, jagged edge of a broken beer bottle.</description></item><item><title>#288: Death Of Beloved Bollywood Star Leads To Dark Conspiracies About His Famous GF &amp; The “Bollywood Mafia" | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440033/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 15:21:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440033/</guid><description>Podcast Description When two cases of very public, very mysterious deaths are linked together - the public is bound to have questions. June of 2020, Disha Salian allegedly slipped off the 14th floor balcony and passed away. She was a manager in the mystifying world of Bollywood. Just 6 days later, Sushant Singh Rajput, a beloved actor she had once managed, passed away mysteriously. People couldn’t help but draw a connection between the two suspicious deaths.</description></item><item><title>#287: She Tried To Turn 2 Boyfriends Into “Human Kimchi” | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440034/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 17:00:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kimchi is a Korean spicy fermented cabbage side dish. It is traditionally prepared in big red buckets… The two detectives were standing staring at one of those kimchi buckets. But they knew there was more than just kimchi inside otherwise, they wouldn’t be in a morgue right now. They slowly opened the lid to the massive kimchi bucket and inside they were confronted with 2 bodies. From this point on, the clock started ticking.</description></item><item><title>#286: US Student Arrested In North Korea During Vacation &amp; Mysteriously “Brain Dead” 18 Months Later | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440035/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 23:26:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Otto and his tour group were staying at a 5-star luxury hotel where all their needs were met. They had a barbershop, pool, casino, multiple restaurants, and even a bowling alley inside the hotel. They had no reason to ever want to leave. The only strange thing was - ALL GUESTS WERE PROHIBITED FROM ENTERING LEVEL 5 OF THE HOTEL. It was strictly forbidden. But in early 2016 - a guest supposedly entered the restricted floor and tried to steal a poster off the wall.</description></item><item><title>#285: Korean Influencer Took Break From Social Media &amp; Found Murdered 2 Months Later | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440036/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 20:21:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ah-young, a popular Korean live-streamer, took to Instagram to tell her devoted followers that she was suddenly taking a break. In a long post, she wrote about how she wanted just to be a “normal person” for a little while. After seeing her post, one of Ah-Young’s friends texted her to see if she had any big plans during her break. Ah-Young responded - “I am leaving the country because of my stalker.</description></item><item><title>#284: World’s Youngest Serial Killer - 8 Year Old Amarjeet Sada | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440037/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 16:18:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Parul was just catching her breath as she stepped through her front door. She had left her 8-year-old son to watch her 6-month-old nephew all alone while she ran errands. She saw her son playing with his toys but didn’t see the baby anywhere. So she asked her son- “Where is the baby?” He smiled. She asked again till he finally responded “I killed him. I smashed his head with a brick and buried him.</description></item><item><title>#283: Missing Boy Discovered After 8 Years - Turns Out His Family Was Holding Him Captive The Whole Time | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440038/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rosa was in her 80s and struggling with dementia. But recently, it seemed like things had gotten worse. Rosa would point at the door at the end of the hallway and whisper to her family - “Rudy is here. He’s there. He’s in that room.” Her adult children would all glance at one another before comforting Rosa that there was no way Rudy was there. Rudy Farias was a boy that had gone missing 5 years ago.</description></item><item><title>#282: He Spin Kicked A Woman Nearly Killing Her - All Because She Gave Him A “Dirty Look” | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440039/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 21:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440039/</guid><description>Podcast Description May of 2022, 26-year-old “Minhee,” was walking home after meeting up with friends. She didn’t realize someone was following her home. When she walked inside her apartment building and waited for her elevator- the stalker came up behind her and kicked her in the head 6 times. She was knocked unconscious… he then dragged her limp body to a dark corner of the lobby that didn’t have CCTV cameras.</description></item><item><title>#281: Fraternity Pledge Tortured To Death For 48 Hours - Forced To Eat Live Eels &amp; Mice | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440040/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 20:18:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440040/</guid><description>Podcast Description December 2018, 20 year-old Sanda Dia was brought into the emergency room by his so-called “college friends.” He was unconscious and cold to the touch. His friends did not give doctors any information on what was wrong with him. They didn’t tell doctors that for the past 48 hours, they had tortured Sanda to the point of his death. After fighting for his life in the hospital - Sanda died of multiple organ failure.</description></item><item><title>#280: The Horrific Korean Boarding School That Abused Disabled Students - Real Life Story Of The Movie “Silenced” | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440041/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:43:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440041/</guid><description>Podcast Description The boarding school of nightmares shouldn’t have been open for as long as it was. The Inhwa Boarding School was for students that had mental, physical, and intellectual disabilities. It was nestled in the mountains of South Korea - and it was keeping a dark secret. It was filled with what the students called “perverts.” The perverts would force students into empty classrooms to sexually assault them. The perverts would play movies in class and drag students to the back to assault them in front of their friends.</description></item><item><title>#279: Woman Vanished After Spotting Toddler On The Side Of The Highway - LATEST UPDATES! | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440042/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 18:05:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440042/</guid><description>Podcast Description What would you do if you saw a child on the side of the highway at night? What if the child was in distress, alone, and in a diaper? July 13, 2023, Carlee Russell saw a small toddler on the side of the highway. She stopped her car, called 911, and while on the phone with her friend, she got out to check on the child. She would go missing, and the whole nation believed she was human trafficked by evil people who used a child to lure her out of her car.</description></item><item><title>#278: 7-Year-Old Girl SA’d, Killed, &amp; Thrown In Garbage - Pakistan’s Worst Serial Killer Caught | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440043/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 17:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440043/</guid><description>Podcast Description This was the first hit that Zainab’s family got after she went missing. The shop owner said he didn’t see her personally but he had CCTV cameras outside his shop. The family sat around holding their breath - eyes scanning the grainy footage. Some of the others were comforting them that they would find her in the footage and realize she was just lost. She would come home safe.</description></item><item><title>#277: The Indonesian Girl That Killed Her Best Friend With Poisoned Coffee Because Of Jealousy | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 13:34:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440044/</guid><description>Podcast Description In an upscale cafe in Jakarta - 3 women sat in a booth. Jessica, Hani, and Mirna had been friends since college and decided to reunite to catch up. One had gotten married and was ready to start her own family. Another had just landed a new job. Another was going to live full-time in Australia with her boyfriend. And by the end of the coffee date - one would be dead in the booth.</description></item><item><title>#276: Angry Korean Son “Casually” Kills 6 People After Fight With Mom &amp; Got Away With It | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440045/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 13:44:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440045/</guid><description>Podcast Description The house was on fire, and it was going to collapse. The firefighters stood in front of it doing everything they could to put out the angry flames. There was a 66-year-old lady screaming at them. “Please my son is in there! You have to go back in and get my son!” They knew the house was going to collapse any minute now - but the firefighters always sacrificed their own lives in an attempt to save another.</description></item><item><title>#275: Teen Threw Baby in Trash Can After Giving Birth in Hospital Bathroom | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440046/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Within the busy halls of a hospital, a terrifying story unfolded. Alexee Trevizo, 19 years old, raced towards the restroom, clutching her backside in a desperate struggle. She locked the bathroom door behind her and time stretched on—5 minutes, then 10, and eventually 20—fueling the growing apprehension among the nursing staff. When Alexee swung open the door - the nurses saw the entire bathroom was covered in red blood.</description></item><item><title>#274: Chinese Vlogger Set On Fire During Livestream (Case of La Mu) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440047/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 20:10:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440047/</guid><description>Podcast Description National DV Hotline: (800) 799 - 7233 National DV Website: https://www.thehotline.org (https://www.thehotline.org) La Mu’s livestream started with her singing, dancing and interacting with her viewers as usual. Her lives were always a safe space on the internet. Everyone loved La Mu for being a wholesome influencer.
But suddenly, on camera, La Mu’s expression changed. She went from smiling to looking fearful. She stood up abruptly, knocked over her phone, but the live never disconnected.</description></item><item><title>#273: A Submarine Went Missing &amp; Body Parts Were Found A Week Later In The Water | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440048/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 06:20:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kim Wall Foundation - https://www.rememberingkimwall.com/ The submarine went missing, and the whole world stopped to watch. Two people were trapped inside - underwater with only hours of oxygen left. Would it be possible to find them in time? People wondered if it was engine failure - or maybe the sub had imploded. But the mysteries kept piling up - why did the submarine sink? Why did only one person make it out alive?</description></item><item><title>#272: Korean True Crime Fan Commits Murder To Know “What It Feels Like” | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440049/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 16:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440049/</guid><description>Podcast Description May 27, 2023. 3AM. South Korea. A taxi driver pulled over to put up a young girl and her suitcase. He watched her struggle to load it into his trunk, but when he offered to help she refused. They got in the car and silently drove towards the park near the river. How odd, he thought. The park at this hour? With a heavy suitcase? And she looks as young as a middle schooler - what could she be doing?</description></item><item><title>#271: Hong Kong Tourists Trapped In Bus With Unhinged Man Who Tries To Kill Them One By One | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440050/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 21:12:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440050/</guid><description>Podcast Description 11 hours - 25 hostages. An unhinged man had boarded a Hong Kong tour bus and started waving his rifle around. He told them if everyone stayed still and did what he said he would not kill them. He lied. For 11 hours, the bus was parked in the middle of the busy street. Police, media, journalists, and civilians were all surrounding the bus. The hostage negotiators were in charge of preventing loss of life, but they would make mistake after mistake that would cost lives.</description></item><item><title>#270: Children’s Book Author Writes About Losing Husband - Then Gets Arrested For His Murder | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440051/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 16:09:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440051/</guid><description>Podcast Description March of 2023, a local news station interviewed a new children’s book author, Kouri Richins. She had just written a book for kids on grief. She said she pulled from her experience of losing her own husband and trying to help her 3 kids move on. She talked about how she wanted to help other kids and parents cope with their pain. The news anchor felt tears pool in her eyes, listening to a grieving widow.</description></item><item><title>Introducing: The Set | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440052/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 09:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440052/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s the crack era. The most violent time in New York City history. The NYPD is fighting a losing battle and instead of protecting the city from drug dealers, some police officers have become them. The Set is the never-before told, first-person documentary of the biggest police corruption scandal in NYPD history and the investigation that uncovered it all. From Audacy Originals and Zak Levitt, the Emmy, Peabody, and NY Press Club Investigative Journalism Award winning creator of Root of Evil, Gangster Capitalism, and Relative Unknown.</description></item><item><title>#269: 2 Girls Accidentally Killed Kim Jong Un’s Brother Thinking It Was a YouTube Prank | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440053/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 14:29:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440053/</guid><description>Podcast Description He was on his way to airport security when the girls came up to him. The first one came up behind him and covered his eyes. She ran off. Then almost immediately after, another woman came up and put her hand on his mouth and ran off.
The two girls, who had never met prior to this, had just executed a near perfect assassination. They had a deadly chemical agent VX on their hands that was now on his face.</description></item><item><title>#268: The TikTok Star Who Killed His Wife (Case of Ali Abulaban) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440054/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2023 15:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440054/</guid><description>Podcast Description The famous TikTok star strained to hear the conversation through his phone. He knew the voices - one was his soon-to-be ex-wife and the other was a male voice. They had no idea that he had installed spyware in her home and was listening to every part of the conversation as he sped on the highway to go meet them. He felt rage. How could she give up their fame, followers, and career for something like this?</description></item><item><title>#267: Filipino Girl Went Missing In A Mall - Taken By Secret Tunnels In Fitting Room? Case of Jovelyn Galleno | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440055/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 14:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440055/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a 22 year old mall employee vanishes without any trace - netizens can’t help but bring up the dark whispers of the past. “How is it possible that there is no footage of her leaving the mall?” - people wondered. Then does that mean she’s still in the mall? When there are no answers to the case - people start to wonder if the tunnels were back. Rumor has it, the mall had an underground tunnel system that connected to each of the fitting rooms.</description></item><item><title>#266: Viral Video Exposed Korean CEO Running Massive “Revenge Video” Site - The Real Life K-Drama “Taxi Driver” | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440056/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 09:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440056/</guid><description>Podcast Description A video went viral in South Korea of a CEO slapping an employee on the face in front of all his employees. Netizens were enraged - but as new details emerged, they realized the truth was even darker. The sadistic CEO would force his employees to decapitate live chickens during company retreats, force them to drink beer till they urinated themselves, he force-feed them multivitamins till they threw up, and shoot at them with BB guns for fun.</description></item><item><title>#265: University Students Abducted To Be GIFTED To A Politician To Be Gang Raped| Murders of Eileen Sarmenta and Allan Gomez | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440057/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 12:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440057/</guid><description>Podcast Description They say a dead body smells like rotting meat - but with a thick, syrupy, sweet undertone. It’s the sweet part that makes most people want to vomit. But these days heavy chemicals are used in morgues to neutralize those smells - but working in a morgue is far from easy. The students at the University of the Philippines sacrificed partying on the weekends to work at the University hospital - inside the morgue.</description></item><item><title>#264: Bollywood Actress’s Mysterious Death &amp; Her Diary That Exposed Secret Relationship With Elite Family Son | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440058/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 11:14:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kavita was on a flight from London to Mumbai, India to visit her older sister and mom. Her sister was a successful actress in Bollywood but she managed to carve out time in her schedule to celebrate Kavita’s birthday. When she landed - she connected to the airport wifi and all the text messages, DM’s, calls, that she had missed while in the air kept flooding in. She collapsed on the airport floor.</description></item><item><title>#263: 15 Yr Old Student Vanished In Boarding School &amp; Found Mysteriously Dead 3 Months Later On Campus | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440059/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 10:50:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440059/</guid><description>Podcast Description In January 2023, a guard and his faithful dog patrolled the grounds of a Chinese boarding school. His routine was typically mundane, involving occasional chases after stray chickens. However, something had changed. A student had vanished three months earlier, casting an unsettling aura over the surrounding woods.
On a fateful day, the guard&amp;rsquo;s dog suddenly erupted into a frantic bark, diverting his attention. Intrigued and apprehensive, he cautiously followed the dog&amp;rsquo;s lead, arriving at an abandoned shed on campus.</description></item><item><title>#262: Killer Breaks Down Crying After 8-Year-Old Victim is Found ALIVE (Case of Jennifer Schuett) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440060/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 17:11:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440060/</guid><description>Podcast Description For two decades, Dennis Bradford concealed a haunting secret, a secret so sinister that it remained hidden from every soul on this planet—his ex-wife, his current wife, his own children. The only person that knew, died with his secret 20 years ago. Yet 20 years later, he was unexpectedly summoned to an interrogation room, Dennis found himself under scrutiny, bewildered as to why the authorities had suddenly turned their gaze upon him.</description></item><item><title>#261: The Sewol Ferry Tragedy - Coward Captain Left 350 Students To Die In A Sinking Ship | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440061/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 02:51:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440061/</guid><description>Podcast Description In that dark and gloomy room, the rescuers stumbled upon two students who had sought refuge together. Maybe they even held hands or offered comforting words.
There&amp;rsquo;s some debate about their relationship status - some say they were dating, while others claim they barely knew each other. But one thing&amp;rsquo;s for sure: when faced with their last moments, they didn&amp;rsquo;t want to face it alone. They cleverly tied their life jacket strings together, refusing to be separated as the room flooded with water.</description></item><item><title>#260: Korean Billionaire “With No Face” Mysteriously Linked To 32 Dead People In Attic | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440062/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 21:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440062/</guid><description>Podcast Description In June 2014, a strange event occurred in South Korea. A man, seemingly homeless, was discovered deceased in an apricot orchard wearing a lavish Italian jacket. Beside him lay a book, an empty bottle of shark liver oil, and numerous alcohol bottles. However, DNA testing would later unveil that this vagrant was, in fact, a vanished billionaire. His passing was so puzzling that many speculated he was still alive, lurking in the shadows.</description></item><item><title>#259: The “Godfather Of J-Pop” Assaulted Male Trainees In Exchange For Making Them Stars (Johnny Kitagawa) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440063/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 22:30:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Johnny was a legendary figure in the world of J-Pop, known for his uncanny ability to turn unknown talents into superstars. He held the music industry, media, and A-listers of Japan under his spell, making his every command a golden ticket to success. Some saw him as a genius businessman and marketing mastermind, while others whispered that he was more akin to a devil, preying on the souls of his chosen trainees.</description></item><item><title>#258: Chinese Live Streamer Died On Stream, Then Someone Stole Her Body &amp; Sold It | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440064/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 13:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440064/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2021, a well-known live streamer named &amp;ldquo;Little Kitty&amp;rdquo; took her life on camera, sparking public outrage against cyberbullying. The story made national headlines and dominated social media feeds for weeks. Yet just when people thought they had heard it all, the case took an even stranger turn. It was later revealed that three men had stolen Little Kitty&amp;rsquo;s remains, all in the hopes of marrying her ghost. And as chilling as this tale might be, it&amp;rsquo;s only the tip of the iceberg when it comes to the gruesome underworld of human trafficking involving dead bodies.</description></item><item><title>#257: The Most EVIL Middle-Schoolers In South Korea That Got Away With Murder | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440065/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 12:45:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440065/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the dark of night, eight Korean teenagers raced for their lives, one by one, as their “friends” fell, taken down by the relentless pursuer. One of the girls, unable to bear the pace any longer, slowed to a stop. As she turned to face her fate, she saw the shadowy figure closing in on her, and with a wry smirk, whispered, &amp;ldquo;God, that was really rough.&amp;rdquo; Moments later, she was tackled to the ground.</description></item><item><title>#256: A Famous OnlyFans Model who became a Killer - Case of Courtney Clenney | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440066/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 12:34:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Courtney has over 2 million followers on Instagram. She has made over $3 million in the past 2 years on OnlyFans. In the beginning of 2022, it looked like the year couldn’t get any better for Courtney. She was bringing in a lot of money, living in a $ 10k-a-month apartment in Miami, and dating the love of her life. Till she stabbed him, just inches above his “Courtney” tattoo.</description></item><item><title>#255: She Found Nude Photos Of Herself On Her Stepdad’s Computer - So She Killed Him (Case of Jade Janks) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440067/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 21:55:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jade had always been a good stepdaughter. Ever since she was 12, she had respected, loved, and admired her stepfather. Even now, at 37 years old, she was his primary caretaker. Her stepdad struggled with his health and every time he was hospitalized, Jade wanted to do something nice for him. She would clean his entire house so that he wouldn’t have to come home to a messy place.</description></item><item><title>#254: Korea’s Biggest Sex Grooming Cult With Over 100k Members - The JMS Church | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440068/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 18:03:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kim had heard the rumors of Pastor Jeong raping his female followers but he knew the devil was working hard to take down their Messiah. But one day, while working in the JMS church post office - Kim stumbled upon a mysterious package. He opened it up to find a hard drive and hundreds of nude photos of women he recognized from the church. Photos of women in various stages of undress.</description></item><item><title>#253: Psychiatric Patient Burns Down Entire Clinic Killing 25 Other Patients &amp; Staff -2021 Osaka building fire | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440069/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 11:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440069/</guid><description>Podcast Description The hospital staff were frantic trying to save the 26 bodies that were being wheeled into the emergency room. A local psychiatric clinic had suspiciously burst into flames. Mental health professionals, doctors, and patients were being rushed into the hospital. The doctors focused on saving their lives. They started getting to work on a man that was wheeled in with the others. They gave him compressions, checked his vitals, and went to empty his pockets for safety reasons - and they found something odd.</description></item><item><title>#252: She Locked Her BF In A Suitcase During Sick Game of “Hide &amp; Seek” - Murder of Jorge Torres | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440070/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 11:18:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever played Hide &amp;amp; Seek? The game? Sarah and her boyfriend Jorge Torres decided to play one night. The best hiding spot they could find was inside a suitcase. Jorge crawled inside, and Sarah zipped it up. She waited a moment, then she watched as he pushed up against the suitcase trying to get out. He was struggling to get enough oxygen. He started begging her to let him out.</description></item><item><title>#251: Chinese Man Murdered His Mom’s Killers 22 Years Later - Hero or Villain? (Case of Zhang KouKou) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440071/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 11:44:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440071/</guid><description>Podcast Description He killed 3 people on Chinese New Year. He admitted to it, he turned himself in, and he said in court that he didn’t regret a single moment of it. He had waited 20 long years to finally do it and now he felt free. He confessed to a triple homicide so why was a whole country rooting for him?
Because he had gotten revenge on his mom’s killers.</description></item><item><title>#250: The Adopted Orphan Who Killed Her Siblings For Attention - The Real Life Case of the Movie “The Orphan” | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440072/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 22:06:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440072/</guid><description>Podcast Description 17-year-old Janice was hiding under the bed. There were 3 masked men that had broken into the family home. They were going from room to room attacking anyone they stumbled across. Janice managed to slide under her bed, but she had no idea if they would find her - if she were next. She couldn’t make a single noise. She tried to text her family to send help. She posted on Facebook, hoping someone would read it and call the police.</description></item><item><title>#249: The “K-Pop Serial Killer” - “Handsome” Killer Stirs Online Discourse &amp; Shocks South Korea | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440073/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 16:38:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lee’s girlfriend had just moved in with him. It was perfect; Christmas of 2022 was just around the corner, and he was the perfect gift to her life. Lee, was attentive, caring, compassionate, and the perfect boyfriend. He even had 3 adorable cats that she grew attached to. While Lee was out running errands, she started unpacking, and realized she needed to feed one of those cats. She searched everywhere for the bag of cat food, nowhere in the kitchen or pantry.</description></item><item><title>#248: Korean Female Air Force Sergeant Takes Her Own Life On Her Wedding Day - Case of Lee Yeram | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440074/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 21:40:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yeram’s wedding day was almost perfect. It was one of the happiest days of her life in a very long time. She spent the day grabbing fast food with her new husband, unpacking their newlywed house, and calling each other “wife” and “husband.” Later that night, on their wedding night, Lee Yeram would take her own life. Why? Why would she do this after one of the happiest moments of her life?</description></item><item><title>#247: The Cheongju 2006 Curling Iron Case - The Real Life Stories Behind K-Drama “The Glory” | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440075/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 13:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Her only mistake was picking up the phone. That’s it. She didn’t know it was the bully’s boyfriend calling her. This “mistake” almost cost her her life. She was dragged into a karaoke bar - beaten to an inch of her life. Then later, dragged into an alleyway near an abandoned factory where she was beaten by 5 bullies. They assaulted her for hours until she was drenched in blood, and the whole thing was caught on CCTV.</description></item><item><title>#246: The Disgusting Truth of a Wholesome Korean Pharmacist Who Spread Herpes To Fans | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440076/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 16:17:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440076/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you go to South Korea, there are a lot of fortune tellers. They have cafes, automated fortune dispensers, and palm readings; they have everything you need to figure out what’s in store for you in the future. They have all the answers. When SJ sat down in front of his fortune teller, she smiled. His future was clear as day. So easy to read. She told him - “You, my dear, will become famous.</description></item><item><title>#245: YouTuber Faked A LiveStream To Allegedly Create An Alibi For Murder  (Ongoing Case of Stephen McCullagh) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440077/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 20:29:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can you be at two places at once? Not in the metaverse, or in VR, but physically? Recently, a case has gone viral because it seemed a YouTuber was able to be at two very different places at the same time. December 18, 2022, Stephen was home live-streaming for his YouTube audience. His stream was titled “The Violent Night - Christmas Stream.” He was engaged in intense gameplay of Grand Theft Auto.</description></item><item><title>#244: 4 Women Brutally Beat In Public For Saying No To A Man (Case of Tangshan Restaurant Attack) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440078/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 17:22:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440078/</guid><description>Podcast Description There is something special about late night with friends. The 4 women sat in the corner of the packed BBQ restaurant and placed their order. Their lives felt perfect. When one friend walked out to take a phone call she heard her friends laughing and joking around. When she came back all she heard were their screams. Her friends were being brutally beaten by 9 strange men for the pure fact that they refused to sleep with them.</description></item><item><title>#243: Itaewon Halloween Tragedy - 159 Dead &amp; How The Police Tried To Cover It Up | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440079/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 13:11:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rotten Mango Visual: https://www.youtube.com/@rottenmangopod
On October 30th, a man walked out of his tiny little shop in Itaewon. He placed a pink blanket in the grim alleyway. He got on his knees in front of a tray of food he had prepared. Police immediately swarmed him, demanding he leave right away. Nobody was supposed to be in the alley, not after what had happened there. The man yelled at the police - “don’t you dare touch the food.</description></item><item><title>#242: The Dismemberment Case of Hong Kong Model- Abby Choi | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440080/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 17:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rotten Mango Visual: https://www.youtube.com/@rottenmangopod
The suburban house sat amongst the others that looked just like it. There was something different about this one. All the windows of the house were covered in dark cloth. Even the front door was covered by a giant black curtain. The neighbors wondered what secrets the new neighbors were hiding. Perhaps an illegal gambling ring? A brothel?
The world was shocked to see two stainless steel pots being carried out from that house with human remains found inside.</description></item><item><title>#241: The Most Evil Woman In Wisconsin - She Wanted To Be Female Jeffrey Dahmer? (Case of Taylor Schabusiness) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440081/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 19:15:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440081/</guid><description>Podcast Description He stomped the snow off his boots; the ice storm had no mercy on this town. It was nearly 3:30 in the morning, and the officer had somewhere important to be. He knocked on the woman’s door and followed her down into her basement. She didn’t even seem to notice the chill in the air. It seemed like she was distracted. Like she had seen something far more scarier than a relentless winter storm.</description></item><item><title>#240: The Cabo Six - Killing of Shanquella Robinson | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440082/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 19:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440082/</guid><description>Podcast Description RM VIDEO PODS HERE: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1XXanI2UPYY
She sat there listening to the man sitting in front of her. She had trusted him before all of this - but now, he was blubbering about what happened. All 6 of the vacationers would find their way to her house to tell her what happened on their Mexico trip. All of them had their own version of events, but it wasn’t adding up.</description></item><item><title>#239: The Whole High School Covered For A Killer For 20 Years- Case of Melanie Paquette | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440083/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 14:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440083/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 20 year high school reunion was a big deal for these friends. They had all grown up, started their own families, but one thing has always united them. Their oath of silence. Their oath of protection. Everyone sat down at their seats but their smiles quickly faded once they saw the empty chair next to them. They were reminded again of their friend who was not with them.</description></item><item><title>#238: The “Human Puzzle” In The Dublin Mountains (Case of the O’Connor Family) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440084/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 20:30:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440084/</guid><description>Podcast Description The person looked like they hadn’t slept in days. They were clearly agitated and nervous. Pacing. They flagged down a detective and told them “The stuff in the mountains. It was me. The body parts you’re finding. Scattered around the mountains. I cut them up and threw them all over the place. I blacked out, and I don’t know what happened. I just threw them all over the mountains.</description></item><item><title>#237: Vanished Man Came Back 6 Years Later With A CRAZY Secret (Case of John Darwin) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440085/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 17:18:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440085/</guid><description>Podcast Description It was a good day to look for a missing person. It sounds dark, but the conditions at sea were optimal for a search and rescue. But life is funny, it never works out the way you expect. They searched for days before they gave up. It’s like the man had vanished into thin air. For 6 years, his family mourned his disappearance. A husband, father, son, had been ripped from their lives.</description></item><item><title>#236: He Broke Up With Her - She Killed His Mom As Revenge (Part 2) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440086/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 13:32:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440086/</guid><description>Podcast Description They said she did it. They said they had all the evidence but the victim’s sisters weren’t so sure. Detective V picked up his phone at the sheriff’s department, there was a woman on the other line. She informed him that her sister had died mysteriously from ingesting a heavily regulated toxin and she was certain she knew who did it. It was her brother-in-law. She warned the detective - “And if he did it, you’re never going to catch him.</description></item><item><title>#235: She Was Brought Back To Life 6 Times In The Hospital - The Killer Witnessed It All | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440087/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 21:41:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mary died 6 times that day. Each time, a loud siren would blare through the hospital alerting the doctors. Her family rallied around her, praying, and hoping for a speedy recovery. There was her husband - he would soon enter into a romantic relationship with Mary’s sister. Then there was her son - he had already admitted to sleeping with a minor, what other atrocities could he have committed?</description></item><item><title>#234: 20 Year Old Girl Does Blackface To Commit Murder For The Most Bizarre Reason | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440088/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 20:24:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440088/</guid><description>Podcast Description The heat was suffocating. She was stuck in her car with no AC in the middle of the Florida summer heat. That’s comparable to being slow-cooked in an oven. She wiped the sweat off her forehead and left a smear of dark pigment on her hand. She was sweating her disguise off. She had to look as natural as possible. Not suspicious. But how could she? She was doing blackface in her car, wearing a giant hoodie, shoes that were 5 sizes too big, and a gun resting on her passenger seat.</description></item><item><title>#233: The Ugly Secrets of the Miss Universe Pageant - Allegations of Assault &amp; Rigging | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440089/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 21:09:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440089/</guid><description>Podcast Description There are experiences that only few will ever have the honor of feeling. Winning the World Cup, winning the presidency, maybe even winning an Oscar. It’s a feeling that feels unexplainable. The adrenaline, euphoria, joy, the release of tension when you realize you’re being rewarded for your work. The Miss USA pageant was one of those brain chemistry altering moments.The two women stood there, holding hands, waiting for the winner’s name to be called.</description></item><item><title>#232: The “Incel Hero” - Praised For Wanting Women To Become Breeding Machines (Case of Elliot Rodger) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440090/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 21:14:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440090/</guid><description>Podcast Description The University of Santa Barbara was a picturesque college town. Most days were filled with sun, surfs, and the smell of tanning lotions. But even the sunny town had sinister residents. Elliot sat in his math class as he wrote about the girl he had a crush on. It destroyed him to find out through social media that his crush, Brittany, already had a boyfriend. Elliot started fantasizing about kidnapping the couple and stripping Brittany’s boyfriend of all his skin.</description></item><item><title>#231: Explosive Updates On Idaho Murders Case- Did He Stalk Them On Instagram? | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440091/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 12:19:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Police had kept a tight lid on this ongoing case of the four University of Idaho students that were murdered in the middle of the night. But now bits and pieces of information have come to light. And while we have more answers, we have more questions now. Is it true that he visited the victims at the restaurant where they worked? Did he follow and message them on Instagram?</description></item><item><title>#230: The Resort Town Filled With Secret Swingers, “Hot” Firefighters, and Murder - What Could Go Wrong? | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440092/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 16:13:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440092/</guid><description>Podcast Description There’s never a great time to find out that your husband has nudes of other women on his phone. But this was probably the worst time. There were 30 of Sabrina’s closest friends gathered in her home when she found out about the pictures. The two men stood in front of her asking if she had any knowledge of her husband having an affair. Sabrina said it didn’t make any sense.</description></item><item><title>#229: The Vanishing School Bus - 26 Kids Went Missing Together | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440093/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 13:10:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440093/</guid><description>Podcast Description When someone goes missing without a trace, it’s enough to make the hair on our arms stand up. One second they are here; the next second, they are gone. When 26 kids vanish into thin air on their school bus… the whole nation loses their minds. Chaos. Parents calling authorities. People running up and down the streets calling the kids names. FBI booked out every single room in every hotel in the town.</description></item><item><title>#228: She Was Frozen Then Sadistically Lit On Fire While Alive by Evil Friends | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440094/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 18:38:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440094/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 3 men sat in front of the priestess. She was their spiritual godmother. The one that was to help them stay protected in life. She peered into a crystal bowl filled with water. Her wrinkled face changing rapidly, her eyes darting about, it was as if she was watching a silent movie in the bowl. She told them that bad bad things were happening around them. She saw a spirit.</description></item><item><title>#227: The Most Evil Child Star | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440095/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 19:53:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440095/</guid><description>Podcast Description The couple were in bed. The same one that they had slept in every single night for the past few years. Only, nothing about the day was normal. Jackie was inconsolable. She was sobbing, shaking, not understanding what was going on. Her husband, Tom, tried to comfort her. He told her everything was going to be alright. He was going to be with her. He tried to lean over and grab her hand so he could lovingly stroke it, giving her more reassurance.</description></item><item><title>#226: She Was Murdered For Wearing The Wrong Colored Shirt (Case of 14-Year-Old Brandy DuVall) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440096/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 12:40:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440096/</guid><description>Podcast Description It was her favorite outfit. A red Michael Jordan jersey, black shorts, and sneakers. She was hesitant about wearing it because, well, the color red meant something in the area, but her mom encouraged her to wear what she wanted. Besides, all she was doing was quietly waiting for the bus to take her back home to Grandma’s. As she stood there waiting, in red, a car drove past.</description></item><item><title>#225: The Idaho Murders - 4 College Students Murdered In Their Beds | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440097/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 17:27:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440097/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the ongoing case of the Idaho Murders. There were 6 roommates living in an off campus house when in the middle of the night, someone had entered the home, and left after taking 4 lives.
Since this is an ongoing case, there have been many speculations online of who it could have been. People were pointing fingers at just about anyone. But breaking news - a suspect has been taken into custody.</description></item><item><title>#224: Did Princess Diana Predict Her Own Death? - The Secrets Of Her Royal Marriage | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440098/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 18:25:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Diana’s note in her diary read - “I am sitting here at my desk today in October, longing for someone to hug me, and encourage me to keep strong and hold my head high.” “My husband is planning an ‘accident’ in my car, brake failure and serious head injury in order to make the path clear for Charles to marry.” Diana predicted that her husband wanted her dead in a car accident so he could marry the true love of his life.</description></item><item><title>#223: The “Blood Brothers” That Killed Their Father Because Their Hot New Boyfriend Told Them To | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440099/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 12:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440099/</guid><description>Podcast Description His two sons were out playing in the back while he supervised through the kitchen window. The boys were 13 and 12. What should have been a heartwarming moment, watching his two sons play and get along, was instead filled with anxiety. His friend asked, “what’s wrong?” “I don’t trust Derek.” His friend was confused. He peered at the window to see the boys playing on the swing set.</description></item><item><title>#222: The Survival Story of a Mute Boy Sold Into Pedophilia Organization | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440100/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 15:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joe’s mom had big big plans for him. She was one of those parents that liked to have high expectations for her children. She wanted Joe to accomplish things she never thought of doing when she was his age. She told him “you’re going to be a big big star in those films Joe.” He was confused. He was only 9. He didn’t know how to read, write, or even talk so how was he going to memorize a full script?</description></item><item><title>#221: He Plotted A Murder With His Therapist &amp; His Descent Into Madness | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440101/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 13:39:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440101/</guid><description>Podcast Description He was the college “simp.” His friends knew better than to ask him to go to a party with them. He would inevitably be too busy in his dorm room thinking about his girlfriend. Listening to audio clips of her telling her she loves him. But his best friend was the only one that knew the truth of what was going on. He had secretly recorded conversations he had with his dream girl on campus.</description></item><item><title>#220: A Group Of Friends Played Murder Games With One Rule - You Die In The Game, You Die In Real Life | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440102/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 19:09:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440102/</guid><description>Podcast Description The letters brought them together. Dean was sitting in his office when he got his letter. He could feel his pulse picking up. Someone knew what he did. Not too far away, Norman and Todd were shaking as they opened their letters. Inside Norman’s letter were a series of pictures of a woman. Norman understood the blackmailer wanted this woman killed or else he would die. Todd anxiously waited for his best friend Norman to tell him what was in his package.</description></item><item><title>#219: She Dated 3 Of Her Roommates Till One Ended Up Dead | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440103/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 12:00:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440103/</guid><description>Podcast Description They nicknamed her “mini Martha Stewart” because of how perfect she was. Her doctor husband adored her. She took care of their baby girl while still getting her master’s degree, cooking, cleaning, and even volunteering. Her life seemed so perfect till she was arrested and her secret life started to unravel. Years ago, before moving to the perfect suburban town, she lived with roommates. She dated 3 of them.</description></item><item><title>#218: He Made a DEAL WITH THE DEVIL - Sacrificed 80+ Children For Money &amp; Power (Serial Killer Gilles De Rais) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440104/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440104/</guid><description>Podcast Description There are a few things you should do before moving out of your house. Most people will make a short to-do list of sorts. Turn off the power, check all the closets for valuables, things like that. But even then you will always leave some part of yourself behind… maybe it’s a piece of mail, your welcome mat, or maybe even your scent. It’s inevitable. Understandable. You probably wouldn’t expect to find dead bodies though.</description></item><item><title>#217: The IHOP Murders - Waitress Willing To KILL To Keep Her Job | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440105/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440105/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Welcome to IHOP (International House of Pancakes), how many people in your party?” Dee had the routine down to a science. She knew what to say, when to smile, when to talk about her kids, when to flirt so she could keep the tips rolling in. Today was not her day though. She wanted to throw up. Her hands were shaking and she was messing up everyone’s orders. She ran to the bathroom to splash water on her face.</description></item><item><title>#216: The Locked House Mystery - Was The Killer Hiding Inside The House? | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440106/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 14:25:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440106/</guid><description>Podcast Description He was the type of psychiatrist that was to get to the bottom of someone’s underlying problem. What was the real reason she thought herself to be the devil’s child? What made her feel like she was so evil she could bring out the darkness in others? And what about those two guys? The ones she was so insistent that they were trying to seduce her? She claimed she just knew they were either going to seduce her or they would all commit some violent crimes together.</description></item><item><title>#215: The Mistress of Torture - She Chained Victims In Her Attic To Experiment On | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440107/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 17:49:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440107/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s said that there are a lot of dark spirits in New Orleans. It might be one of the most haunted cities in the entire world and one story that the city can’t seem to escape is that of Madame LaLaurie. The rumors go like this - she tortured her victims and experimented on them. It’s said she liked to drill skulls into victims’ heads and insert spoons inside so she could “stir their brains.</description></item><item><title>#214: The Rape &amp; Murder of a Transgender Man That Changed a Country (Case of Brandon Teena) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440108/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 15:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Becoming a mom is a dream for a lot of people. Especially Tom’s mom. She saw all the other moms and their deep connections with their beautiful children. So when Tom was born, she was ready for that. She would never get it. Her own son made her nervous. He made her feel unsettled. There was just something sinister about the way he did everything. He never cried, he would sit for hours in a cold bathtub, unmoving and staring at the wall.</description></item><item><title>#213: The Sound of Her Hypnotic Voice Turned Him Into a “Killer Wolf” | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440109/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440109/</guid><description>Podcast Description When you open the front door you might be expecting a package, the mailman, or even your Karen neighbor, but you wouldn’t expect Greg Marlow. I know you’re thinking the name doesn’t ring a bell. It didn’t either for Cyndi when she opened the door to see him. But there he was, in his tight shirt, handsome, smiling smoothly at her. There were a few things Cyndi would soon find out about this mysterious man on her doorstep.</description></item><item><title>#212: The Police Sex Cult That Sacrificed 25 Babies During Rituals | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440110/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 12:20:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440110/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Ingram house from the outside, would have presented itself as the dream life for a family. Situated on a beautiful ranch, with a vegetable garden out back, it was superbly normal. That is till Paul Ingram, the father and police officer, was accused of assaulting his two daughters since they were 5 years old. Not only that, but he would bring over cop buddies to assault not just his daughters but his young sons too.</description></item><item><title>#211: The Millionaire “Human Girl” Collector &amp; Sex Dungeons | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440111/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440111/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you walked into his house, you would be tempted to walk right back out. The smell alone could have knocked you back through the front door. Every surface, every wall, every square inch of the floor was littered with dust. He collected tens of thousands of bottles, empty cereal boxes, trash, magazines, everything. He kept it all. I don’t know how you would find anything, let alone anyone in a place like that.</description></item><item><title>#210: The Influencer Deepfake Sex Club - Blackmail &amp; Torture of Taiwanese YouTubers | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440112/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 12:39:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Zamy, a Taiwanese influencer, had worked hard to build up a wholesome reputable image. Yet, it was all going to come crashing down in the most nightmare-ish way possible. One day, she woke up to being flooded with messages with people asking her “what are you doing this for? Do you not make enough money on YouTube?” It was a “leaked” video of Zamy. She was engaging in sexual activity yet she didn’t remember anything about this encounter.</description></item><item><title>#209: Indonesia’s “Jeffrey Dahmer” - Serial Killer Very Idham Henyansyah | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440113/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 10:15:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440113/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the summer of 2009, there were whispers around South Korea. A Korean blogger had gone out to the woods and came back traumatized. They had seen something in the woods they shouldn’t have. They called it “The Mimic” and it is NOT human. It has no human emotions, no human empathy, but it sounds just like a human. It can mimic anyone’s voice to lure you into their web of death.</description></item><item><title>#208: The Killer On The Cruise | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440114/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 22:03:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440114/</guid><description>Podcast Description The cruise was absolutely stunning. The white sand beaches, the baby blue waters, the casinos inside the cruise, it was all incredible. The passengers were having the time of their life, including the married Nist couple. Mr. &amp;amp; Mrs. Nist had the perfect life - they were millionaires, with a beautiful child, friends who loved them, and they were in love. But on this cruise, Mrs. Nist would fall in love with a crew member.</description></item><item><title>#207: The Suicide Pact - Bizarre Suicide Or Perfectly Staged Murders? | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440115/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 13:43:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440115/</guid><description>Podcast Description They were meeting up again. They knew they should stop, it wasn’t doing any good for them, but how could they? They were the only ones that really understood each other. So the two of them would leave their spouses, their children, all at home to go be with one another. And I know what you’re thinking. Cheaters. Well, don’t judge a book by its cover. These two were not cheating on their spouses.</description></item><item><title>#206: “Hollywood’s Cannibal” - The Dark Empire of the Hammer Family | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440116/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 08:31:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440116/</guid><description>Podcast Description It all started with a Hollywood divorce. The joint statement released by both parties seemed amicable enough, but the public wanted more. They wanted to know the intimate details of the relationship’s downfall. They say 50% of marriages end in divorce, so the odds weren’t in their favor to begin with, but nobody expected it to go down like this. Very quickly, a public divorce turned into allegations of assault, abuse, and cannibalism.</description></item><item><title>#205: Incest Torture Van | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440117/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 17:46:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440117/</guid><description>Podcast Description They needed protection in order to go through with their big plans. She turned to black magic. Sure, it was risky to get dark magic and spirits involved, but their plans were more important. Their plans were to travel up and down the West Coast with their new van! It was a family van, one that could fit all their biological children in, one that you could sleep in, one that the children were supposed to feel safe in.</description></item><item><title>#204: The Man Who Eats Faces - Cannibal Frat Boy | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440118/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440118/</guid><description>Podcast Description The two police officers ran out of their car. They knew there was time was of the essence when they saw the stream of blood running down the residential driveway. They had their guns drawn and started making their way into the garage where they heard animalistic noises. A dog perhaps? They didn’t know what to expect but it wasn’t this. On the ground they found the victim laying flat on their back, arms spread, blood everywhere, looking up at them.</description></item><item><title>#203: The Carnival Boy - Serial Killer Pee Wee Gaskins | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440119/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 11:37:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440119/</guid><description>Podcast Description It was a bit gruesome even for a carnival act. The snake and the rat. A giant king cobra in the cage hissing about and an employee would throw rat after rat into the cage. No matter how full, bored, or even tired the snake was, it would kill each rat that entered the cage. Even most adults would grab their child’s arm and rush away. It was never a pretty sight to see death in action, but little Pee Wee Gaskins sat glued to the bars of the cage.</description></item><item><title>#202: The Rape of Nanking &amp; The Trafficking of Comfort Women | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440120/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 11:57:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440120/</guid><description>Podcast Description They were called “Comfort Women,” but their lives would not be in any sense comfortable. They were kidnapped, tortured, and held hostage to be assaulted by military officials. Soldiers had their own name for them; it was “public toilets.” Most of these women either died in captivity from murder, disease, or from the sheer violence of their assaults. But don’t be fooled by the name, sometimes comfort women were girls as young as 11 years old.</description></item><item><title>#201- High School Basement Torture - Gang Assault of Disabled Student | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440121/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 13:58:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Leslie only had Marie to lean on. They were best friends. Sure, they just started bonding, but Leslie really needed someone to count on. They spent countless hours on the phone, whispering, giggling, staying up, hoping their parents wouldn’t hear them. But it was a bit strange that she kept asking Leslie about what had happened in that basement. Leslie had been gang raped by some of the most popular kids in high school in the football captain’s basement.</description></item><item><title>#200: 13 Popular High School Football Players Gang Raped Their Disabled Classmate - “The Princes of Glen Ridge” | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440122/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 11:58:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440122/</guid><description>Podcast Description When I say “it was the town’s best-kept secret,” what do you imagine? Maybe an unknown hole-in-the-wall restaurant with the best milkshakes? Maybe a secret hangout spot near the river with the best city views. Not for the town of Glen Ridge; it was much darker than that. For them, their best-kept secret was their boys. The town’s group of star athletes - the football players, wrestlers, basketball players, and the most popular boys in class.</description></item><item><title>Wolves Among Us, Season 1, The Larry Lavin Story | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440123/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440123/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the surface, there was nothing remarkable about Larry Lavin. He lived in a quiet neighborhood with his wife and family, drove a Volvo, and practiced dentistry in Philadelphia. But, from 1978 to 1984, Dr. Lavin moonlighted as one of the largest cocaine kingpins on the Eastern Seaboard. Through the voices and perspectives of law enforcement, drug runners, friends, business associates and Larry Lavin himself, Wolves Among Us, Season One, The Larry Lavin Story, tells the story of Lavin’s dual life, his impact on Philadelphia culture in the late 70s and early 80s, and the stunning events that led to an intense manhunt for one of the FBI’s 10 most wanted fugitives.</description></item><item><title>#199: The Evil Twin - Her Twin Wanted Her Perfect Life + Husband &amp; Will Stop At Nothing To “Replace” Her | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440124/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 10:55:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440124/</guid><description>Podcast Description John was devastated when he got the call from his wife’s twin. His wife of two and a half years had just passed. Sure, he knew that she had been terminally ill for a while, but that didn’t ease the grief he felt. So when his wife’s twin sister showed up at his front door, he welcomed her in with open arms. She was the only one that understood his pain.</description></item><item><title>#198: The PTA Mom Turned Stalker - The Sinister Side of Rich Housewives, Obsession, and Conspiracies | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440125/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 14:07:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440125/</guid><description>Podcast Description They say when you seek revenge, you should dig two graves. One for yourself as well. The PTA moms didn’t think of that when they raged war. Jill was said to have gone up and down the hallways of the wealthy school to pass out flyers. Flyers that were printed with baseless accusations against another PTA mom. It’s said that she was jealous of the other mom. Some say it’s because she was trying to distract the community from the fact that she was cheating on her attorney husband with 4 firefighters - at the same time.</description></item><item><title>#197: The Chicago Ripper Crew - When 4 Serial Killers Decide To “Hunt” Together | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440126/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 17:07:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Edward’s new boss loved a good team-building event. Most companies would take their employees out for a fun night of bowling. But not Edward’s boss, Robin; he liked to have a more intimate setting. He gathered all 3 of his employees in the attic of his house and told them to follow after him. He started chanting random phrases while holding up an object into the air above them.</description></item><item><title>#196: The Mortuary’s Serial Killer | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440127/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 11:57:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Her boyfriend loved a good surprise. Surprise dates and gifts were kind of his specialty, but this one felt a bit different. She was blindfolded and taken into a building. He tied her to a chair in the middle of an empty room. She was getting giddy. He had been talking to her about buying a house for her soon. Maybe, he had finally done it! He ripped off her blindfold and got in her face to say, “welcome to my mortuary!</description></item><item><title>#195: The Little Red Mansion &amp; The Underground Egg Harvesting Case | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440128/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 15:14:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440128/</guid><description>Podcast Description You’ve heard of the red rooms - the alleged deep web livestreams of people being assaulted, tortured, and killed. The existence of red rooms is largely debated. But have you ever heard of the “Little Red Mansion?” Because this one is very real. The mansion itself was beautiful, filled with crystal chandeliers, gold crown moldings, and massive rooms filled with over-the-top furniture. It felt like an expensive boutique hotel.</description></item><item><title>#194: She Wanted To Make A Human SKIN SUIT - The Female Ed Gein &amp; The Welkom Graveyard Murder | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440129/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 11:09:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440129/</guid><description>Podcast Description Detective Nel was having a rough time falling asleep. She had a debilitating migraine and was throwing up all night long. Sure, her job as a detective wasn’t easy, but she almost always slept like a baby. The next day she went into work and was rushed to the cell of a young, doe-eyed girl that she personally arrested last night. It was a shocking case. The girl skinned someone’s entire face off.</description></item><item><title>#193: The Real Life “Parasite” Case - The Family In The Basement | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440130/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 11:41:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440130/</guid><description>Podcast Description It was going to be a long day - just like the movies. Each housewife was getting ready, staring into the mirror, clasping on their string of pearls. They hated these gatherings. All the other moms, bratty children, and don’t even get them started on the attorneys that shuffled into the room. Tensions were high. The 5 moms in total hated each other. Technically they should have a lot in common - being that they are all married to high-powered businessmen.</description></item><item><title>#192: Escaped Prisoner Holds Entire Family Hostage &amp; Plays Sick Mind Games | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440131/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440131/</guid><description>Podcast Description She wore a turtleneck out to the grocery store that day. Sure, a blizzard was coming down on them, but she did it to hide the bruises. She looked around at all the happy faces. The smiling couples. They were so in love. If only they could see what she was going through at home. She couldn’t tell them instead she suffered silently gathering up her groceries. Maybe she heard the other families talking about the winter storm or the news of the escaped prisoner.</description></item><item><title>#191: 12 Yr Old Held Captive For 181 Days In A Torture Chamber | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440132/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 17:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440132/</guid><description>Podcast Description It had been months since Abby had been held captive in the bucker/torture chamber. The cruelest torture had been carried out on her, every single day. She wanted it all to be over. It didn’t matter anymore that she would never graduate the 7th grade. Nothing mattered except making sure her kidnapper paid for this. Abby wrote a note, naming her kidnapper, and what he had done to her before slipping it into the lining of her shoe.</description></item><item><title>#190: How a High School Party Left 1 Murdered and 8 in Prison | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440133/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 13:05:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nicole’s phone had been ringing nonstop. It felt like the end of her 15-year-old life. Someone was going around calling Nicole’s friends to tell them nasty rumors about Nicole. How she had no eyebrows, she got ugly, she was talking bad about them, and how she had AIDs. It sounds ridiculous, but to Nicole this was her life. Someone was out there trying to take her down. Take her crown of being the most popular girl in school.</description></item><item><title>#189: How a Foster Care Home Created a Monster Predator | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440134/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 10:33:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440134/</guid><description>Podcast Description There were always 12. 10 foster kids in the house at all times, plus the two biological children of the Baker parents. 12 kids. All 12 kids would grow up to see some heinous things. It’s alleged that the Bakers would force the foster boys to molest the foster girls in their care. It’s said that the Bakers would even force brothers to inappropriately touch sisters under their direction.</description></item><item><title>#188: The Dark Life of a “Sex Trafficker/Pimp” | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440135/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 13:49:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440135/</guid><description>Podcast Description She never used to sleepwalk, but maybe that’s what happens when you hit your 30s? Her life was spiraling out of control because of it. She woke up one morning dangling off the side of 4th-floor balcony. She had no idea how she even got there. She could have seriously hurt herself or even died… she was just thankful he was there to save her. Or that time she woke up covered in blood.</description></item><item><title>#187: The Cartier Killer | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440136/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 13:37:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440136/</guid><description>Podcast Description It sounded like a new age of crime. We’ve all heard of jealousy being the motivation behind the murder, but this was a bit different. She was jealous that Naomi was a bigger “influencer” than she was. She hated that she was getting all the love, the likes, the follows. She was going to put a stop to it. Her brilliant plan? Have her boyfriend assault Naomi so that she would be too traumatized to work again.</description></item><item><title>#186: The Middle School Library Rapist | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440137/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 12:44:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440137/</guid><description>Podcast Description He called it the “bear cave.” He liked the sound of it. Bears were unassuming predators… that kind of sounded like him. Inside his “bear cave” there was a desk, an inviting yellow beanbag, and of course, it was filled with snacks and sodas. Don’t forget his hidden condom box, a stack of porn magazines, and pillows hidden in a box that said “Christmas decorations.” The only really odd thing about his “cave?</description></item><item><title>#185: The Mistress, The Killer &amp; The Hitlist | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440138/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 15:16:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440138/</guid><description>Podcast Description Both men were racing in their cars for different reasons. Peter was stepping on the pedal to his wife. She was sick, and he needed to get to her ASAP. He was worried for her. Larry was in his car - racing to his girlfriend, who wasn’t picking up his calls. He was worried for her. Both men were gripping their steering wheels till their knuckles turned white. They were both racing to the same woman.</description></item><item><title>#184: The Tiger Mom Killer (Case of Yuan Xi Tang) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440139/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 10:11:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tom was shaking after the call. A mysterious woman had called to tell him that she knew where his missing mother was. He didn’t know if it was a scam or a real lead. All he knew was that the police weren’t doing enough. So that’s how he found himself at a random Starbucks waiting for the mysterious caller. When she walked in, he knew that she had something up her sleeve.</description></item><item><title>#183: The Dark Web Human Auction + Kidnapping (Case of Chloe Ayling) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440140/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 14:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440140/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chloe was used to her pictures being posted on the internet. She was a model, after all. She posted on social media and updated her followers on her personal life. But she had never been posted on this type of website before in her life. It’s the type of website that you and I probably couldn’t access. You can’t just Google it. No. It exists only in the deep layers of the dark web.</description></item><item><title>#182: The People Who Spy On Us (KGB &amp; MI6 Spy Kidnapping) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440141/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 16:45:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440141/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the comfort of her own private living room, Rachel complained about her bad back to her husband. They needed to drive across the border to see a specialist. In Caroline’s place, Caroline argued with her husband about going on a double-date road trip for Rachel’s bad back. Her husband argued it was going to be boring, but he caved eventually. So it was settled the two couples would be road-tripping to Finland.</description></item><item><title>#181: Four Babies In The Bin &amp; The Sister’s Secrets | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440142/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 18:26:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440142/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joanne’s mom had always been a bit out there. Nobody could quite put her finger on it, but there were whispers that family members were witches. When Joanne’s mom sent her out in the middle of the night to dig up something in the woods for a spell… Joanne was confused. She was terrified of walking alone in the dark. What spell was her mom talking about? Joanne imagined she would be arrested that night.</description></item><item><title>#180: Robert’s “BDSM” Dungeon Parties &amp; Murder | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440143/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 13:24:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440143/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to the BDSM Dungeon party. If you’ve never been or if you’ve never heard of such a thing - you might think it sounds scary But it’s not scary at all. In fact, it can be very fun if that’s your thing. Bob’s favorite part of the dungeon party? Well, he couldn’t choose, was it the giant orgy room in the center of the building, or the crosses that you can tie people to, maybe it’s the playrooms where your deepest desires come true.</description></item><item><title>#179: Dismembered Into 2000 Pieces (Nanjing University Mutilation Case) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440144/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 16:53:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440144/</guid><description>Podcast Description Margaret was cooking up her favorite stew. She could use it. The temperature was below zero, the winter storms were approaching, and Margaret hoped the nutrients from the pork bones would give her energy. She would need the energy for her cleaning job. She took her pork bones, which were neatly pre-sliced, she took them out, washed them, and plopped them into her water. It was almost muscle memory - but when she stuck her hand in again she felt something strange.</description></item><item><title>#178: The Happy Face Serial Killer | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440145/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 16:03:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440145/</guid><description>Podcast Description The community was relieved. The killer couple was put behind bars and finally, they could relax. Thankfully the police were able to catch them after their first victim… the thought of having a serial killer on the loose was spine-chilling. They all felt safe. But many many miles away in a public restroom were the scribbles… “I killed Tanya. Yes, I’m sick, but I enjoyed myself. People took the blame and I’m free :)” A happy face.</description></item><item><title>#177: The LifeGuard Murder In Italy (Case of Marco Vannini) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440146/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440146/</guid><description>Podcast Description Summer in Italy - where else would you want to be? Marco was a lifeguard working at one of Italy’s beautiful seaside resorts. After his shift, he rushed over to his girlfriend’s house, and ate dinner with her entire family. They all got along. It’s like he was part of the family already. Even after dinner, Marco wanted to wash the scent of saltwater off his body and asked if he could take a bath.</description></item><item><title>#176: Torture Deaths of the “Ghost Girls” | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440147/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 13:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440147/</guid><description>Podcast Description The dead list - well, he called it the “List of the Doomed.” On there was a long meticulously written list of 50+ local young girls. In the years to come he would sit down, pull out his little dead list, and in a red pen, he would methodically write “D” next to a name. D for dead. Another one is dead. It didn’t matter if the girls on the list knew they were doomed.</description></item><item><title>#175: The Mind Games of The Pick-Me Girl Killer (Death of WePhone CEO) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440148/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 15:50:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440148/</guid><description>Podcast Description When he was found dead at the bottom of a building in Beijing - the police found two notes of interest. His suicide note where he named his killer. That seemed odd? And another note - a piece of paper that was handwritten. Where he had promised $2 million dollars to someone within the next 120 days. Could that even be a real contract? Would a handwritten random note be used in the court of law?</description></item><item><title>#174: Daddy’s Little Girl &amp; Her Murderous Secrets | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440149/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 12:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440149/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Theresa started dating David she had a gut feeling - that something was off about David’s ex-girlfriend. Sure, maybe Theresa was a little jealous? Cindy, his ex, was said to be beautiful, had an hourglass figure, and was wild in bed. But it wasn’t those things that made Theresa uneasy. It was the fact that David’s ex never showered. She doused herself in perfume hoping it would mask the scent.</description></item><item><title>#173: Miryang Middle School Girls Sexual Assault Case | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440150/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 01:41:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440150/</guid><description>Podcast Description Middle schooler Alice got off the train with excitement bubbling in her chest. She was meeting 17-year-old Peter for the first time. She had no idea that she would be ambushed by Peter and his friends, dragged to a local motel where she would be gang r*ped by more than 40 high school boys. They filmed the entire thing. Her torture would last a year. The boys blackmailed her into coming back for more assaults.</description></item><item><title>#172: The Cleveland Torso Butcher Serial Killer | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440151/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440151/</guid><description>Podcast Description They say Lake Erie is haunted. That’s where the “Lady of the Lake” lives. The bizarre pieces of the puzzle started to come together. A 14-year-old girl came out of the lake screaming, she claimed she saw a hand waving to her at the bottom of the lake. A few fishermen pulled up their line to find it tangled with a chunk of blonde hair. Human hair. A ferry operator claimed to see a suspicious bobbing object in the water.</description></item><item><title>#171: The Southern Belle Killer (Allanson Family Murders) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440152/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440152/</guid><description>Podcast Description Someone was out to get the Allanson family. That much was clear. Someone was targeting 3 generations of the family. But who? The Allanson’s started experiencing off-putting things as if they were being stalked. One family member was in her yard when she saw a man standing there. Watching her. Sleeves rolled up. Pants down - exposing his private parts. She ran inside. Another family member found sugar dumped into the gas tank of his car.</description></item><item><title>#170: The Virginity Pact Killers (Case of George &amp; Lucas) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440153/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 10:50:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440153/</guid><description>Podcast Description It was supposed to be a place of growth, learning, and happy laughter filling the yards. It was a place where people were supposed to feel safe. But in the parking lot of the elementary school, under a suspicious white van, there was a woman lying nude. Murdered. The police had the killers in the back of the cop car… they could see one of them looking at the victim.</description></item><item><title>#169: Project Taken (Abduction of Sherri Papini) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440154/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 10:18:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440154/</guid><description>Podcast Description He ran an anti-abduction training program called “Project Taken.” He would teach young girls how not to get kidnapped. He was not someone to mess around. Ex-military man. Specialist in kidnapping prevention. International hostage negotiator. He did it all. Well, nobody expected he would find himself wrapped up in one of the strangest, most bizarre kidnapping cases in all of true crime history. The kidnapping of Sherri Papini.</description></item><item><title>#168: The Real Handmaid’s Tale - 100 Teen Brides | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440155/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 13:32:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440155/</guid><description>Podcast Description The authorities burst into the room and their jaws dropped. The entire room was completely white. Even the books on the shelves were bound in white leather. But the most shocking was the pure white bed in the middle of the room surrounded by an arc of chairs. As if people sat around the bed like it was some sort of show. Which they did. Authorities found audio recordings of middle-aged men assaulting underage girls while their friends watched.</description></item><item><title>#167: The Deadly Housewives of Missouri (Case of Betsy Faria &amp; Pam Hupp) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440156/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 11:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440156/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pam was a normal housewife, she had a nice husband, and a job in the insurance industry. Everything about her was normal. Except, the dead body in her hallway. She had been ambushed in her own home and shot her attacker. When the police arrive they find the attacker had no ID, but a bizarre note in his pocket, it was detailed instructions on how to kidnap and murder Pam.</description></item><item><title>#166: The Korean Milk Princess &amp; Burning Sun Sex Scandal | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440157/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 19:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440157/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Burning Sun scandal exposed some of the most beloved K-pop idols to be depraved predators. The Burning Sun was a popular club. The type of club where rich men ruled. If you wanted a rare bottle of champagne. They would get it. If you wanted the club to stay open an extra hour. They would do it. If you wanted the bartenders to roofie a random girl’s drink so that you could have her escorted into your private room to assault… they would do it.</description></item><item><title>#165: The Taxi Driver &amp; The Missing Girls In Mexico (Case of Debanhi Escobar) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440158/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 11:33:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440158/</guid><description>Podcast Description The woman leaped to her death - plunging her body into the cold water of the river. She left a note that said “to my devil husband, I can only commit suicide to expose your crime and to tell the world about my helplessness.” It shocked the nation. She had been married to one of the richest, most powerful men in the nation. What did he do? And how does that connect to the haunting last picture of a woman that lives 7,168 miles away?</description></item><item><title>#164: The Conspiracy of The Mountain Devil (Case of Hiroo Onoda) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440159/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 19:55:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440159/</guid><description>Podcast Description He emerged from the thick jungle for the first time in a long time. He had been waiting for this moment for years. The day World War II would come to an end. He would be relieved from his duties and Japan glorious in their victory! Onoda held his breath while his commander read his release. Onoda waited for further orders but there were none. Just a tub of face cream.</description></item><item><title>#163: Horrors Inside Aston Hall Mental Hospital (Child Experiments) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440160/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 12:27:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440160/</guid><description>Podcast Description Truth serum. It has quite a dark history. The CIA tested the heavy sedative on suspected criminals, murderers, and terrorists. They hoped it would even the smartest spies to - well, tell the truth. It would be hard to imagine a world where truth serum was tested on children on a large scale. But it happened. In Aston Hall Mental Hospital a sick, twisted, depraved doctor hand-picked young girls to experiment on.</description></item><item><title>#162: Social Media Murder of Sisi Wu | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440161/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 13:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440161/</guid><description>Podcast Description The text messages were released. At first, it only circulated amongst smaller group chats - but like a fire, it spread. It was too good of a scandal. Two normal everyday people and the innermost private parts of their lives. Their affair. Wanda, the married woman, and mother, cheats on her husband with the mailman. Nude pictures and videos were circulating of the two. Wanda lost everything. She lost her job, her family, her friends, her reputation.</description></item><item><title>#161: The Styrofoam Head Killer (Serial Killer Ned Snelgrove) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440162/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440162/</guid><description>Podcast Description Everywhere he went, he was kind. He was kind to the woman he passed by in the produce aisle, the female cashier, and even the woman next to him at the red light. Maybe he was nice because he loved to picture all these women naked and in his bed. Sure, some would call it crass but was Ned’s favorite thing to do. Regardless, the women were nice back.</description></item><item><title>#160: Korean “Molar Daddy” Case (Lee Young-Hak) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440163/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440163/</guid><description>Podcast Description It all started when a woman jumped from her bathroom window. The police questioned whether or not it was a suicide. The whole nation did. Why did the seemingly happy wife and mother take her own life? Maybe someone pushed her? Why was her entire back filled with sexually derogatory tattoos? Just weeks later her father-in-law took his own life, and a 14-year-old girl’s body was found stuffed in a suitcase.</description></item><item><title>#159: The Therapist’s Deadly Double Life (Case of Dr. Al Canty) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440164/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 11:10:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440164/</guid><description>Podcast Description The four of them sat in the hospital room. The sound of rain pelted the windows. Al stood up and started shouting “They’re coming! They’re coming to take the wicked and the evil!” He fell to his knees in front of where the woman was sitting and started rubbing her with his palms. “MOMMY! DON’T LEAVE ME! PURE MOMMY. PURE AS SNOW.” The woman was shocked. The man was her husband, who was also a successful therapist.</description></item><item><title>#158: The Headless Bodies In The Bathtub (Killer Couple Erika &amp; BJ Sifrit Part 2) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440165/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 11:40:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440165/</guid><description>Podcast Description The couple’s vacation in Ocean City was supposed to help them fall in love again. Marriage is tough - they lost that spark. They were even staying in the penthouse of a beautiful oceanfront hotel. The penthouse bathroom had a hot tub that they were certain was going to help ignite their romance again. But the night ended with two headless bodies in the tub. They were dismembered. And honestly, it was exactly what the couple felt they needed.</description></item><item><title>#157: Hooters, Snakes, &amp; Navy SEALs (Killer Couple: Erika &amp; Benjamin Sifrit) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440166/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 11:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440166/</guid><description>Podcast Description Being a marriage counselor is a tough job. I imagine the married couple Erika &amp;amp; BJ would tell very different stories about their couples vacation. BJ would say that he fell asleep in the car while his wife went into a hotel room with a couple they just met. He was heartbroken and devastated when he found out what she had done. Erika would argue that BJ was there the whole time - in fact, he wanted her to take pictures of him with the couple’s decapitated heads.</description></item><item><title>#156: Murder Of The Coors Beer Heir (Case of Adolf Coors) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440167/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440167/</guid><description>Podcast Description He knew this was going to happen sooner or later. The FBI had already stopped by twice to let him know that he was on a criminal’s “kidnap wish list.” He just didn’t know - that the one being kidnapped wouldn’t be him. It would be his very own son. The heir to the Coors Beer Dynasty. He felt confident he could deal with this. It’s like a business transaction.</description></item><item><title>#155: How He Got Away With Murder But Was Killed By Karma (Case of Mel Ignatow) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440168/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 11:53:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440168/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Watkin’s family moved into their new home and their first project was ripping out the old, brown, ugly carpet. Rip. Rip. Wait, what is that? They found a hole in the ground. Strange. Inside that hole is a little treasure. Jewelry and a roll of undeveloped film. They had it developed and it showed 112 pictures. A series of photo sequences leading up to the gruesome torture and murder of a young woman.</description></item><item><title>#154: The Rapist That Came Back Alive After Death Sentence (Case of Sun Xiaoguo) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440169/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 19:04:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440169/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you heard of the Chinese urban legend? It’s about the most famous thief in history. He was able to steal entire train cabins from moving trains. When he was finally caught - the thief was sentenced to death. He said his very last wish in life was to be breastfed one last time. The mom pitied her full-grown son and laid her chest bare. One last time. He lifted his mouth up, and with the most force he could summon, he ripped off her nipple.</description></item><item><title>#153: The Unicorn Killer (Case of Ira Einhorn) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440170/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440170/</guid><description>Podcast Description Unicorns are mystical creatures. They are so rare that most of us wouldn’t know what to do if we came across one. When the inmates heard that the Unicorn Killer was joining them - they were terrified. Most of them had heard of the Unicorn, heard the whispers. How even the CIA was terrified of the Unicorn. How the Unicorn evaded capture for 20 years. But nobody could answer the one pressing question the inmates had - what happens when you come face to face with a real-life Unicorn?</description></item><item><title>#152: Secrets On The Boat (Case of Thai Actress Tangmo Nida) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440171/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440171/</guid><description>Podcast Description There were 6 people on the boat that night. A-list actress, Tangmo Nida, her manager and lifelong friend, as well as 4 very wealthy socialites were on the boat. A lot of rumors currently surround the six. There are whispers of affairs, inheritances, and wills. But the most sinister rumor? That they were trying to sell Tangmo Nida, the A-list actress, to a high-powered Thai businessman/ government official. But when only 5 make it back alive - it seems like the questions are never ending, and the secrets are only getting darker.</description></item><item><title>#151: “The Bad Vegan” (Case of Sarma Melngailis) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440172/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440172/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you heard about how to boil a frog? They say if you throw a frog into a pot of boiling water - it will jump out. But if you throw a frog in a pot of cool water… and you slowly start turning up the heat. Slowly but surely. So slow that it’s just incremental changes in heat. It’s said the frog will sit there, completely unaware of its impending doom, and it will be cooked to death.</description></item><item><title>#150: The Chinese Corpse Dungeon (Serial Killer Jia Wenge) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440173/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440173/</guid><description>Podcast Description She woke up disoriented in the dark. She didn’t know where she was… oh god, what’s that awful smell? Her hand was touching something sticky on the ground. When her eyes slowly adjusted to the dark she saw - bodies. Dead bodies. Stacked on top of each other. Some of their faces were frozen still as if they were still screaming. The stickiness on her hand? The bodies coming together and forming a sticky sludge filled with maggots.</description></item><item><title>#149: The Baton Rouge Cannibal (Serial Killer Sean Gillis) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440174/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 18:06:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440174/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sean hopped into his car to pick up his girlfriend. He was always so happy to see her. He couldn’t get enough of her. “Honey bunny” I’m over here! Sean’s girlfriend slid into the passenger side and he leaned in for a kiss. He couldn’t help but pull back with a giant grin. He wondered if she could taste it. He could… The taste of human flesh always lingered in his mouth.</description></item><item><title>#148: The Mysterious Vidocq Society | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440175/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440175/</guid><description>Podcast Description The FBI agent walked into the warehouse. It was exactly what he expected… A concrete fortress, barely any natural light, and then he saw it. The walls. The walls were filled with rows and rows of decapitated heads, skulls, and bones. Some still had rotting flesh on them - others were completely skeletonized. When the FBI agent made it to the back he came face to face with the man.</description></item><item><title>#147: The Bodies In The Abandoned Mine (Case of Alice &amp; Gerald Uden) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440176/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 13:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440176/</guid><description>Podcast Description The gas station attendant was helping him fill up his car. What timing. It was a hot summer’s day, the sweat trickled down his forehead, and he was anxious to get going. The two of them stood awkwardly at the back of his truck waiting for his tank to get full. Drip. Drip. Drip. “Sir, I think your car is leaking.” They both looked down to see a red liquid drip down onto the pavement.</description></item><item><title>#146: The Pathological Liar &amp; The Corpse (Case of Casey Anthony) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440177/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 16:24:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440177/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s said that some pathological liars are even considered functionally delusional. They can even pass a lie detector test. They believe their own lies. Sometimes they re-write their lies and memories on the spot. You can see their eyes flutter, a shift in attitude, and boom. They are living a new reality and you almost feel like you’re the one going crazy. But as humans, we can detect lies, right?</description></item><item><title>#145: He Was Shot Then He Fought To Save His Attacker’s Life (Terrorist Mark Stroman) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440178/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440178/</guid><description>Podcast Description The public was split. Most wanted him dead. He didn’t deserve to live, he killed 2 people, and shot another in the face. Another group of people, a smaller group, fought to save his life. Activists, professors, and lawyers fought hard. They knew he was guilty but they fought. One man fought the hardest. He traveled the world campaigning for his release. The world was shocked. They asked him: are you sure you want him to be free?</description></item><item><title>#144: The Lake Waco Murders (Case of David “Chili” Spence) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440179/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 23:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440179/</guid><description>Podcast Description Think about your dog, cat, or any beloved pet. If you don’t have one - imagine one. Would you ever chain your dog up to your chair all day long while you and your buddies watched TV? Would you make the dog beg you on all fours to use the restroom? And if the dog did something you didn’t like - would you ever dream of chaining up outside to a tree in the cold winter night?</description></item><item><title>#143: The Temple Of DOOM (Case of Belinda Lucas) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440180/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 19:52:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Children say the scariest things. Sometimes you can’t help but feel like they know something you don’t. One daycare worker vividly remembers a moment that sent shivers traveling down her spine. A little boy was playing with a little girl. House. Innocent right? Out of nowhere, the little boy started to scream and smash mommy doll up against the wall. It was so unlike him. The alarming part? The little boy’s mom had recently been murdered and everyone suspected someone close to her.</description></item><item><title>#142: The Mama’s Boy Night Stalker (Case of Fred Coe) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440181/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 17:06:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440181/</guid><description>Podcast Description The only thing he loved in life was his mom. She was his everything. He couldn’t bear to be fighting with his “Mama Bear.” He was worried that South Hill Rapist would come for his mom. I mean why wouldn’t he? He was terrorizing the entire neighborhood - no woman was safe. The rapist would drag women into the bushes, assault them, threaten them, and then whisper in their ears.</description></item><item><title>#141: The Cleveland Strangler (Serial Killer Anthony Sowell) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440182/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 19:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440182/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Cleveland Health Department had been flooded by calls from residents on Imperial Avenue. The residents complained of an inescapable, pungent, thick stench that was so strong that it made their eyes sting. After years of calls, the inspectors went out to investigate. The source was clear. Ray’s Sausage Shop! That made perfect sense, fresh meat being ground daily into sausages has to produce some stench right? No matter what the residents tried - the smell never went away.</description></item><item><title>#140: Murder On The Deserted Island (Case of Palmyra Island) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440183/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 01:58:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440183/</guid><description>Podcast Description What would scare you the most about being on a deserted island? The sharks? The thick jungle that is so thick and humid you have no idea what animals are lurking beyond? Or maybe it’s basic survival - finding out how to get water, food, and shelter. The last thing on your mind would be murder right? That’s what the Graham couple thought when they docked on the deserted isolated island of Palmyra.</description></item><item><title>#139: The “World Health Organization” Killer (Case of Jean-Claude Romand) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440184/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 22:48:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440184/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jean was a successful doctor working as a researcher at the well-respected World Health Organization. His wife was a pharmacist and they had 2 beautiful children. Ah yes, it’s another perfect family. But we both know that there’s no such thing. Jean was cheating on his wife with a mutual friend - a child psychologist. But the affair does something mysterious to Jean. He starts blacking out, has holes in his memory, but most alarming of all - he wakes up one day to find himself hovering over his wife’s dead body&amp;hellip; What really happened here?</description></item><item><title>#138: The Sunset Killer (Serial Killer Douglas Clark) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440185/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440185/</guid><description>Podcast Description Carol demanded to see what Doug had been doing with his other women. Recently their relationship had changed - all Doug cared about was cheating with other women and threesomes. He warned her. This would scare her away. She couldn’t handle the truth. Doug was smug. He walked over and he plopped down into the sink… A severed head. Carol didn’t scream, she didn’t run, instead, she sat down and started applying makeup on the severed head.</description></item><item><title>#137: Chinese Student Murdered In Japan &amp; Exposed The Darkest Side Of Humanity (Case of Jiang Ge) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440186/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 17:11:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440186/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s a tale as old as time. A farmer was walking his fields one cold winter when he spotted a snake. The snake was frozen stiff from the cold. The farmer knew the snake to be deadly but he couldn’t help himself. He scooped it up and put it in his jacket to warm it up. Slowly the snake woke up and gathered enough strength to look up at the kind man who saved him… and bit him.</description></item><item><title>#136: “She Saved Him, Can You Save Her?” (The Case of Rebecca Zahau) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440187/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 20:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440187/</guid><description>Podcast Description You might think her life is perfect. Millionaire boyfriend, $13million dollar mansion, and a cute dog. But behind closed doors it was rough - her boyfriend’s ex-wives hated her, she fought with his teenage kids all the time and spent a lot of her time babysitting his youngest child. One day under her care - the little boy ends up unconscious and is rushed to the hospital. Nobody blames her though - or do they?</description></item><item><title>#135: “Wanna kill grandma? lol” (Case of Wendy Gardner) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440188/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 17:06:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440188/</guid><description>Podcast Description 15 year old James gathered all his friends at the bowling alley and dragged them outside. He wanted to show off his 13 yr old girlfriend and his brand new car! The kids were shocked - how did James get a new car? He doesn’t even have a license but they were too excited to care. They all packed in the car. Windows down. Music on. Speeding on the streets.</description></item><item><title>#134: The Real Lolita &amp; The Fake FBI (Case of Sally Horner) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440189/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440189/</guid><description>Podcast Description The FBI agent watched her across the store. He was seasoned enough to know what that little girl was trying to do. He watched her steal a notebook and make a run for the door. Not today. The agent grabbed her arm and stopped her. She was under arrest. “I’m an FBI agent and you just committed a crime, little girl. I need to take you to my boss.</description></item><item><title>#133: The 12 Year Old “Temptress” | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440190/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440190/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is a nymphet? It’s a seductress of course. She knows what she’s doing. She finds men that are alone, vulnerable, and she tempts them. She will walk by and by using her superpower seduction she doesn’t even need to talk to them. She doesn’t touch them. She simply exists and that is enough. The men then drop to their knees and forget to think straight. They are willing to risk it all for her.</description></item><item><title>#132: The Sisters of Terror (Case of The Price Sisters) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440191/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 18:19:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440191/</guid><description>Podcast Description The sisters were arrested - they went with the plan. Stare at a fixed object to the point of looking hypnotized. The police were getting fed up “YOU&amp;rsquo;RE AN EVIL LITTLE MANIAC TELL US WHERE THE BOMBS ARE.” The sisters remained “hypnotized” till at exactly 3 PM they looked at their wristwatch and let out a big sinister smile. BOOM. The bomb went off in the busy streets of London injuring hundreds.</description></item><item><title>#131: Pretty Little Liars Killers (Case of Skylar Neese) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440192/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440192/</guid><description>Podcast Description The three girls never went anywhere without each other. They were besties. Well, except Biology Class - the one class that only Rachel and Sheila were in. Maybe that’s why during biology Sheila would ask a lot of strange questions. “Excuse me, what kind of acid would you dispose of a body in?” “I don’t know… why?” “Oh, we’re trying to figure out what to do with Skylar.” Rachel would be off on the side giggling.</description></item><item><title>#130: The Murder Planned In The Psychiatric Ward (Case of Celeste Beard) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440193/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440193/</guid><description>Podcast Description The two women met in the psychiatric ward and instantly sparks were flying. Their hair was wild, they were heavily drugged up but they knew that it was only a matter of time before they had s*x. They were so different but it worked. One woman - the wife of a millionaire. The other woman - was struggling with life and addiction. But they just knew that they would be together.</description></item><item><title>#129: High School Boys Kill Hot Teacher’s Husband (Case of Pamela Smart Part 2) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440194/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440194/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 16-year-old girl couldn’t stop ranting at work. Life is so short - her high school teacher’s husband had just been viscously murdered. Can you believe it? Her teacher is now a sad widow. During her rant, one of her coworkers cut her off. Wait- didn’t you tell me a few weeks ago that your 15-year-old friend was planning on murdering him? So that he could be with his teacher?</description></item><item><title>#128: “Hot Teacher” Teaches Boys To Kill (Case of Pamela Smart) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440195/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 16:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440195/</guid><description>Podcast Description They were just like any other couple. They went on dates on the beach, went shopping for lingerie together, and they had “fun” wherever they could. In cars. At their houses. In the park. Everywhere. Sure, they were plotting a murder but does that really mean much in the grand scheme of their all-encompassing love? By night - they were plotting the perfect murder. By day - he was a 15-year-old high school student and she… Well, she was his high school teacher of course.</description></item><item><title>#127: The Hammer Man Strangler (Case of Harvey Carignan) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440196/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 16:32:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440196/</guid><description>Podcast Description The wife of high-powered influential Harry Piper was kidnapped. A random note was left - “We want $1 million dollars to be paid in 50,000 unmarked $20 bills.” The family paid it. It would be two full days till Virginia was found chained up to a tree. Alive. She never saw the kidnapper’s face. After three long years, the police presented her with a few audio clips. She perked up.</description></item><item><title>#126: Mom “Cures” Son With Incest (Murder of Barbara Baekeland) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440197/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440197/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tony was getting fed up. His friend wasn’t listening to him. “No no no you don’t get it! I’m f***ing my mother!” - he screamed. The restaurant went quiet. Tony came from a strange family, to say the least. His great-grandparents were the creators of plastic. Yes, plastic. His mom was an eccentric aspiring author working on her debut novel about a mom who seduces her son on a yacht - that everyone believed to be more of an autobiography.</description></item><item><title>#125: The “Angel Face Killer With Demon Eyes” (Case of Amanda Knox Part 2) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440198/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440198/</guid><description>Podcast Description The stories were becoming wilder. Did you know that right after killing her roommate with her boyfriend - she took a shower in the blood-soaked bathroom? She killed her roommate over a threesome gone wrong! She even did cartwheels, backflips, and splits in the police station. If this were true she just might be the evilest woman in all of Italy. But what if it wasn’t? What if this was an innocent woman spending 5 years in prison for a murder that she did not commit?</description></item><item><title>#124: The Bizarre Case of Amanda Knox | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440199/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 21:38:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440199/</guid><description>Podcast Description The American exchange student skipped home - her life in Italy was perfect. She had great roommates and a new Italian boyfriend. Nothing could ruin her time abroad. That is - till she finds the door to her apartment wide open, blood smeared all over her bathroom, and one of her roommates dead in her room. Her “strange behavior” makes her a target for the police. I mean would an innocent person do yoga in the police station, journal about pizza during an interrogation, and “make-out” with her boyfriend while police are around?</description></item><item><title>#123: The Murdaugh Family Murders | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440200/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440200/</guid><description>Podcast Description They say family secrets are like vampires - they never really die. The Murdaugh family knows this better than anyone. For generations, they were one of the most powerful, wealthiest, families in South Carolina. But when those around them start mysteriously dying… and even two of their own end up dead. You have to wonder - is someone finally getting their revenge on the untouchable family? An eye for an eye?</description></item><item><title>#122: The Billionaire Inside 3 Suitcases (Case of Elize Matsunaga) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440201/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440201/</guid><description>Podcast Description He was about to sell his family company and become a billionaire. But then he went missing. In order to find him, the police had to dig into his personal life. Why was a private detective following him? Who hired them? What’s on the videos the PI took of him? Why was he visiting a very shady chat forum every single day - what kind of information was he looking for on there?</description></item><item><title>#121: The House of Gucci Murder (Case of Maurizio Gucci) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440202/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440202/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Welcome to the House of Gucci.” You’re instantly hit with the smell of leather and well - money. This is what Gucci is all about - wealth, excess, and opulence. It’s a household name. But have you heard of the Gucci killer? The one fueled by lust, greed, and counterfeit bags. The one that would kill in the name of Gucci. They say money can’t buy happiness - but it’ll get you a whole lot of Gucci.</description></item><item><title>C13Features Presents: Ghostwriter, Starring Kate Mara and Adam Scott | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440203/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440203/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to Ghostwriter, a new gripping and suspenseful podcast movie listening experience from C13Features. In Ghostwriter, Kate Mara and Adam Scott star in a psychological thriller about a former journalist who reluctantly accepts a job ghostwriting a new murder mystery novel for an eccentric billionaire. Kate Michaels has been living a solitary life after a traumatic experience, but after pressure from her rational agent and candid best friend, she begrudgingly concedes that she needs the work.</description></item><item><title>#120: The Olympian Mommy Killer (Case of Keli Lane &amp; Her Secret Kids) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440204/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440204/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bbzzz - when the buzzer goes off they know it’s game time. The high contact sport of water polo begins. For the next few hours - they attack, get dragged underwater, and they try to win at all costs. And then afterward the team will reward themselves with shots at the bars. Keli was nervous. She didn’t know how to sneak out of the party early without anyone knowing.</description></item><item><title>#119: The Death List - The Scorecard Serial Killer (Case of Randy Kraft) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440205/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440205/</guid><description>Podcast Description The highway patrol officers turned on their sirens. 2nd drunk driver of the night. This guy was worse than the first. He had a friend in the passenger seat - drunk, passed out, and he didn’t even realize they had been pulled over. He sat there sleeping while the driver was being arrested. “Come on bud time to find a new ride” - the officer tapped the window. That’s when he realized - the passenger wasn’t drunk.</description></item><item><title>#118: 5 Teens Went Into The Woods - Only 1 Walked Out (Case of “Gitchie Girl”) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440206/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440206/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the halls of their high school - nobody dared to walk near her. Most of the students pretended they didn’t see her, hear her, or know her. If you were new there you might ask - “What did she do?” “Oh, you don’t know? That’s Gitchie Girl. She went into the woods with 4 of her friends and she’s the only one that came out alive. And we all know that Gitchie Girl is hiding something.</description></item><item><title>#117: The Monster of Italy And His Sick “Trophies” (Serial Killer) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440207/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440207/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Florence, Italy - it’s said that 1/3 of people are conceived in cars. Young couples would drive up the isolated hills to have some fun - and creepers would flock to watch them. They would watch, record, “enjoy” themselves, and then go home. Except for one creeper - he wanted more. He would ambush the couple right after they were done - and drag the woman out of the car to take something for himself.</description></item><item><title>#116: Eaten by Alligators or Murdered at Lake Seminole (Case of Mike Williams) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440208/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440208/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alligators are one of the world’s oldest predators. Their bite is 3x stronger than that of a lion. So it was a no-brainer to police when they were told Mike Williams went missing at Lake Seminole. “He was eaten alive - maybe they took his body to their dens for later food.” - they thought. But when pieces of clothes that presumably belonged to Mike surfaced - people were confused.</description></item><item><title>#115: The Crime Show Copycat Killer (Case of Jason Bautista) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440209/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440209/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jason was a straight A college student, with 2 jobs, and his favorite show was “The Sopranos.” He was a nice kid with a bright future ahead of him. One day police found Jason’s mom had gone missing. Jason was worried. He had thrown her headless body off a cliff - just like what he learned from his favorite show. But he had been so busy - that he hadn’t gotten around to burning her head and her hands.</description></item><item><title>#114: The Creepy Father In Law Diaries (Case of Susan &amp; Josh Powell) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440210/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440210/</guid><description>Podcast Description He wrote in his diary everyday about his love and desire for Susan. He took hundreds of pictures of Susan - of her getting dressed, eating cereal, using the restroom, even shopping at Costco. Her husband was no good for her. They were not in love. Not like the way he and Susan were in love. You probably guessed it but Susan had no idea that he was in love with her.</description></item><item><title>#113: The Pharmacy Killer (Twisted Case of Sheila Davalloo) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440211/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440211/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s healthy for couples to talk to each other. That’s exactly what Mrs. C was trying to do to keep her marriage alive. She would come home to tell her husband about the love triangle at work. “Melissa loves Jack but Jack is seeing Anna” can you believe it? At first, it seemed like innocent coworker drama but slowly it got sinister. Mrs. C wanted to help Melissa spy on the couple, hack into voicemails, and even break into apartments.</description></item><item><title>#112: The Hillside Stranglers Part 2 (Case of Angelo Buono Jr &amp; Kenneth Bianchi) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440212/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440212/</guid><description>Podcast Description Family should always be close. The two cousins did everything together. They slept with their son&amp;rsquo;s underage girlfriends together, started a business, and even lived together. They wanted to experience life’s greatest pleasures - together, as a family. The rush of injecting a woman with Windex (the window cleaner) to see how they would convulse. The rush of hooking up a woman to electrical wires from an auto shop.</description></item><item><title>#111: The Hillside Stranglers (Case of Angelo Buono Jr &amp; Kenneth Bianchi) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440213/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440213/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kenny was ecstatic - he was finally moving to LA where he would chase his dreams. To make things better his older cousin was letting him stay at his house. He would also teach him a few lessons on how to be successful. “Lesson #1: You gotta hit the bullseye. Make it your target. Right between the legs. Always use a wet towel. It doesn’t leave bruise marks. Oh, and Kenny?</description></item><item><title>#110: The Alcàsser Girls (Case of Toñi, Desirée, &amp; Miriam) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440214/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440214/</guid><description>Podcast Description The beekeeper called for his friend - “Jose you need to come now!” He had found something near the abandoned house. They rushed over to a small pit on the ground covered with branches. They bent down - used an old spatula to move around the dirt. It was a watch. They screamed…the watch was still attached to its owner. The two men unknowingly discovered the bodies of 3 missing girls, that would lead the whole country down a rabbit hole of conspiracies, scandal, and a man on Interpol’s most-wanted list.</description></item><item><title>#109: The Vampire of Düsseldorf (Case of Peter Kürten) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440215/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440215/</guid><description>Podcast Description This night was special from the rest - he felt his stomach rumble violently. Oh no. He bent over and threw up everything… What was the problem? He was used to drinking all night - in fact, it was his only true joy. Maybe it was her fault. He looked down at the girl laying on the ground covered in her own blood. Maybe her blood just didn’t sit right in his stomach.</description></item><item><title>C13Features Presents: Treat, Starring Kiernan Shipka | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440216/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440216/</guid><description>Podcast Description A perfect town comes with a terrifying price. From C13Features comes Treat, a podcast movie starring Kiernan Shipka as Allie West, an unpopular teenager who is dealing with issues beyond her years while struggling to fit in with her seemingly perfect small town. But, on one Halloween night, everything changes, and she discovers that her town’s idyllic image comes at a deadly cost. As she learns about the mysterious Piper’s powerful hold on the town, she, along with her younger brother, realize they are the only ones who can save their community before it’s too late.</description></item><item><title>#108: The Angel of Death (Serial Killer Jane Toppan) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440217/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440217/</guid><description>Podcast Description You look around - you’re in the hospital but you feel trapped. Why can’t you talk? Why can’t you move? You start to feel your body involuntarily shake… The nurse noticed and rushed to your bedside. Good, someone is coming to help. She pulls back your covers and crawls into the bed with you. She’s stroking your hair, kissing your face, and wants to look you directly in the eye as your pupils dilate, violently convulse, and you take your last breath.</description></item><item><title>#107: The Barbie Doll Kidnapper (Case of Katie Beers) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440218/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440218/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Big John” loved his little apartment. It wasn’t nice but it was his. He was in his 40’s and he wanted to decorate it with whatever style he pleased. His bedroom was more of a game room with a mattress on the ground. The walk-in closet was wall-to-wall with the newest and latest games. Nintendo games, board games, barbies, you name it. His drawers were stuffed full with candy and his mini-fridge only had soda in it.</description></item><item><title>#106: The Haunting of Corpsewood Manor (Case of Dr. Charles Scudder) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440219/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440219/</guid><description>Podcast Description Charles took a step back from his self-portrait. He was just adding his finishing touches of paint. “Are you sure this is what you saw? This is how I’m going to die?” “Yes” the voice said. The painting showed Charles with a gag in his mouth and 5 bullet wounds on his forehead. It was a gruesome piece of art but everyone that knew Charles said he was just “eccentric.</description></item><item><title>#105: The Ripper of China (Serial Killer Gao Chengyong) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440220/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 16:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440220/</guid><description>Podcast Description They sat around the dinner table - whispering. As if the man the town called “The Ripper” could hear them. “Don’t wear red shoes - he will kill all girls wearing red shoes.”
“I thought it was red clothes?”
“I heard it was girls with long hair - because it’s easier to grab when they try to run away.”
Whatever it is - we have to try it all.</description></item><item><title>#104: The Strangler Tree Deaths (Case of Bhatia Family Deaths) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440221/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 15:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440221/</guid><description>Podcast Description The banyan tree is a terrifyingly beautiful sight. It looks like it&amp;rsquo;s draped in a shredded cloak… with its long roots suspended from the branches - hanging eerily straight towards the ground. That’s the first thing the officer thought of when he walked into the family home. 11 people dead. 10 hanging. Together, perfectly spaced out, 10 family members were suspended from the ceiling like the roots of a banyan tree.</description></item><item><title>#103: The Nurse Killer From Hell (Case of Richard Speck) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440222/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 14:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440222/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 7 nursing students were huddled in their dorm room bunk beds - panicking about what to do next. They had been tied up by an intruder.
They waited till he came back into the room and he pointed at a nurse “you.” He escorted her out and tortured her for 30 minutes. She would never return. One by one - like a ritual the killer escorted out nurses to their death.</description></item><item><title>#102: The Werewolf of Russia (Serial Killer Mikhail Popkov) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440223/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 16:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440223/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 17 year old girl woke up in a panic. Where was she? It was so bright and cold - a hospital? She turned her head to the left - a pale dead body. She tried to scream but her voice wouldn’t work. She looked to her right - a dead body. She wanted to jump up and run out of there but half of her body was now paralyzed.</description></item><item><title>#101: The Chicken Coop Serial Killers (Case of Gordon Northcott) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440224/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440224/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Ooooh Sanford get out here! I have a present for you - it’s in the bucket!” Sanford didn’t understand why his uncle was so giddy to be back to the chicken farm but he rushed outside.
He peered into the bucket for his surprise. Immediately he wanted to gag. Why did his uncle bring home roadkill? Why did it look like the animal had a wig on?
“Look closer Sanford.</description></item><item><title>#100: Body In The High School Gym (Case of Kendrick Johnson) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440225/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 15:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440225/</guid><description>Podcast Description All morning there had been whispers at LHS - they found a student’s body in the old gym. The body of 17 year old KJ had been found rolled up into a giant gym mat about 6ft tall. When the police arrive they rule out foul play - they believe KJ willingly went into the mat where he would later suffocate to death. But what about all the other strange evidence?</description></item><item><title>#99: The Case of Gabby Petito &amp; Jelani Day | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440226/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 17:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440226/</guid><description>Podcast Description The couple embarked on a cross country trip in their converted van to experience the beauty of the national parks. They documented their trip, posted on Instagram, YouTube, they were in the process of starting their blog. But only one came back. How is that possible? Where did Gabby go? Why did Brian - her fiance - come back with the van without her?
And now with Gabby’s body found and Brian is now missing - the ongoing investigation is only getting muddier.</description></item><item><title>#98: Mom &amp; Son Incest Killers (Case of Sante Kimes) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440227/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 17:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440227/</guid><description>Podcast Description When you walked by her house in the exclusively rich part of Newport Beach California you would never think it holds such sinister secrets.
She was holding young women captive in her house and would be arrested for slavery charges. After escaping from prison - she went on to brutally murder and scam her way into millions of dollars with her boyfriend.
Who is her boyfriend you ask? Well, none other than her very own son.</description></item><item><title>#97: The Kindergarten Teacher Killer (Case of Angila Wilder) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440228/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440228/</guid><description>Podcast Description First day of Kindergarten is always a nerve-racking time for parents. But when they meet Mrs. W their tensions are probably eased. She has a soft face with a dirty blonde bob and she’s a mom of three! She seems like the perfect teacher - kind, nurturing, sweet. But when she’s with the police she’s a totally different person. “I want to see where it stabbed her.” “I want to see a video of them having s** with my husband!</description></item><item><title>#96: Kidnapped By North Korea Part 2 (Case of Choi Eun-hee) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440229/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440229/</guid><description>Podcast Description You want us to do what? - the couple had been kidnapped and forced to live in North Korea for years before they found out the truth. The wife was a former beloved movie actress. The husband was an award-winning film director. And now North Korea had kidnapped them to make movies for Kim Jong Il. It sounds like a fictional story - but it was very much real.</description></item><item><title>#95: Kidnapped By North Korea Part 1 (Case of Choi Eun-hee) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440230/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 20:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440230/</guid><description>Podcast Description She couldn’t believe it. They wanted her to write a letter to her kidnappers thanking them for all that they have done for her. Are these people out of their minds? She missed her old life in South Korea - she had been a famous movie actress, her children, freedom, she missed it all. Now she was kidnapped in a foreign country forced to write letters of love to the men who ordered it.</description></item><item><title>#94: The Baby Faced Killer (Case of Gonzales Family Murders) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440231/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440231/</guid><description>Podcast Description The goal was simple. Break into the house - sneak into the upstairs room and murder the 18 year old high school girl. Now comes the hard part - the wait. Waiting in an eerily silent house near the body of the young girl till her parents come home. They too have to be murdered. Now for the finishing touches. Write on the walls in big blue spray paint “f**k off Asians KKK.</description></item><item><title>#93: The Mommy Blogger Killer (Case of Lacey Spears) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440232/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 15:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440232/</guid><description>Podcast Description She was rushing to the emergency room - her 5-year-old son was in the back. Every minute could mean life or death. He had been having seizures all day. But before entering the hospital she stood over her suffering son and took a picture.
What would she caption this one? Maybe she would mention how this was going to be his 13th surgery. Yeah, that would be good. The followers would eat that up.</description></item><item><title>#92: The Hair Fetish Serial Killer (Case of Danilo Restivo) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440233/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 15:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440233/</guid><description>Podcast Description Her body was found by her own children. When the police rushed to the scene they were shocked. She had been brutally mutilated - but something curious was in her hands. They were the keys to solving the case.
A clump of hair was found in each hand - when they ran the DNA… One locket of hair belonged to her - the other an unidentifiable woman.
A ritualistic killing with an emphasis on women’s long hair.</description></item><item><title>#91: Teacher Stalked By Student For 15 Years (Case of Mary &amp; Beth Stauffer) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440234/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 17:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440234/</guid><description>Podcast Description He wasn’t like the other boyfriends and husbands. He treasured every single moment that he spent with her. When they went grocery shopping he studied her favorite foods and brands.
When they went shopping he admired all the clothes that she picked out and watched her try them on. Sure - she was married but that can’t stop true love. And what if she doesn’t know him yet? Once he kidnaps her - she will fall in love.</description></item><item><title>#90: Trapped For 70 Days (Case of the Tininenkos &amp; James Fisher) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440235/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 16:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440235/</guid><description>Podcast Description 3 people stranded on a boat in the middle of the ocean. 1 of them has lied to the others. The truth will have deadly consequences. 1 of them is hiding a big secret from the others. A secret she doesn’t want to get out. And only 1 will survive the 70 day ordeal. Book Rec: “Lost” - by Thomas Thompson (one of my fave authors) it’s so good you’ll read it all in one sitting especially if it’s a rainy day.</description></item><item><title>#89: The Butcher Of Kansas Serial Killer (Case of Bob Berdella) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440236/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440236/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Welcome to Bob’s Bazaar Bizarre” - the small shop for oddities from around the world. May Bob interest you in some genuine human skulls? Perhaps a shrunken head in a jar?
When you leave the shop’s bizarre environment you can’t help but wonder… that Bob guy is so strange…
And how does he even collect so many real human skulls? You can’t help but wonder what Bob does in his free time to enlarge his collection.</description></item><item><title>#88: The Girl Under The Mattress (Kidnapping of Shannon Matthews) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440237/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 14:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440237/</guid><description>Podcast Description The police had been searching for Shannon for 24 days - a search that would cost taxpayers over $3.2 million. The police were doing yet another routine search of a house they heard a tiny voice call out “stop it you’re scaring me.” Shivers went down their spine.
Where is that coming from? Inside the bed? They looked closer and realized the 9-year-old was underneath the mattress… They asked her “well where is the man that took you?</description></item><item><title>#87: The Devil’s Pass Killers (Case of Elizabeth Peña &amp; Jennifer Ertman) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440238/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 17:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440238/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joe wasn’t your average Joe - he wanted to be someone spectacular. Someone to be feared. He skipped class, stole cars, carried guns, and even managed to get a girlfriend named Esther. So when he saw the “E” ring he knew he had to have it - to give to his girlfriend. He leaned over and pulled it off the girl’s lifeless hand. The girl that he and his friends had just murdered.</description></item><item><title>#86: The Mysterious Disappearance of Kristin Smart | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440239/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440239/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a rough start, Kristin was adjusting well at Cal Poly. She made friends and even took a lifeguard position that required her to get up by 4:20 AM.
And then she disappeared. Nearby, Mary had just rented a new house but the problem was that dang alarm. It would go off every day at 4:20 AM and she didn’t know where it was. But strangely it wasn’t coming inside the house.</description></item><item><title>#85: The Rockefeller Murder (Case of Clark Rockefeller) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440240/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 19:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440240/</guid><description>Podcast Description Did you hear? The upper elite of New York City had a new resident - Clark Rockefeller. You know - from the billionaire Rockefeller family. He swooped in with his impeccable designer suits, tens of millions worth of art, and his old beat down car. Some might think that to be strange. But you know what they say - old money never flaunts. But why did he kidnap his 7-year-old daughter in the middle of the street?</description></item><item><title>#84: The Girl In The Doghouse (Case of Cinnamon Brown) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440241/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 18:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440241/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you saw Patti &amp;amp; David walk down the street they look like the perfect couple. But those who knew them looked like they had seen a ghost. The whispers - but David’s wife was only recently murdered. What about the girl that the police found in his doghouse? And why is the younger sister of his dead wife wearing all of her clothes and jewelry? Strange things happen in perfect towns.</description></item><item><title>#83: The Tooth Fairy Serial Killer (Case of Snowtown Murders) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440242/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 19:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440242/</guid><description>Podcast Description You walk into an empty abandoned bank. You walk straight for the vault. Sure, you know there won’t be anything of value left but you can’t help but try. In there you see a strange sight. 6 giant barrels lined up against the wall. Maybe they’re filled with money?
Or maybe it contains the tortured, dismembered, and cannibalized remains of 8 people. Well, go on - open it. Source Notes: rottenmangopodcast.</description></item><item><title>#82: The Ballroom Murders (Case of John List) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440243/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2021 17:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440243/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wanda was reading a tabloid of “The Perfect Crime.” She couldn’t believe it - how does a family man just viciously murder his entire family in their 19 bedroom mansion?
And the worst part is he got away with it and has been on the run for 18 years.
At that moment she looked up and saw the killer. Staring back at her. Only it wasn’t John List. It was her new neighbor… or was it?</description></item><item><title>#81: Friday The 13th Axe Killer (Case of Candy Montgomery) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440244/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 18:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440244/</guid><description>Podcast Description The investigators arrived at the scene - it was Friday the 13th and the victim had been brutally killed with an axe. The victim suffered over 40 stabs with a 3ft long axe and half of her face was missing. Was it a gang? A serial killer? It definitely wasn’t the cute little housewife that makes taco salad, takes painting classes, and was headed for church that day - because that would be crazy.</description></item><item><title>#80: The 10 Year Old Killers (Case of James Bulger) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440245/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2021 18:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440245/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 2-year-old James goes missing at the mall his mom is quick to start her frantic search. Within seconds he had disappeared into the crowd. When the police arrive and show her the CCTV footage everyone is relieved. James had been lured out of the mall by two 10-year-old boys. Thank god it’s not some creepy old man. Nobody had any clue that these 10-year-olds were planning a murder.</description></item><item><title>#79: The FaceBook Killers (Case of The Potter Family) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440246/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 19:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440246/</guid><description>Podcast Description What would you do if someone unfriended you on Facebook?
You probably wouldn’t even notice. Maybe you confront them. Or maybe you sneak into their house and brutally murder them and their significant other… How dare they unfriend you on Facebook? This case is filled with twists, delusions, social media drama, and so much cat-fishing that you start to believe there’s no way this is real. But you know what they say - social media can be deadly</description></item><item><title>#78: Isolated For 27 Years (Case of Christopher Knight) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440247/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jul 2021 18:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440247/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 27 years he only spoke one word. “Hi.”
For decades he lived without a mirror - he had forgotten what he had looked like. He had no friends, no family, no pets, no emotional attachments - those were all cut off the day he disappeared. When he is finally arrested after 27 years - the questions remain. Why did a 20-year-old walk into the woods and decide to disappear?</description></item><item><title>#77: A High Schooler, A Stripper &amp; A Suspicious Mom (Case of Franklin Floyd) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440248/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 19:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440248/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sharon - the high school student with straight A’s. She seemed perfect - but why does a 14-year-old have a closet full of lingerie and provocative clothes?
Tonya - the mom who took a job as a dancer at a club. She was found dead on the side of the road. But why is her husband acting so strange?
Sandra - the mom whose baby was kidnapped. But why are there rumors that Sandra sold her child?</description></item><item><title>#76: The Baskin Robbins Killer (Unsolved Case of Amy Mihaljevic) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440249/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 18:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440249/</guid><description>Podcast Description The rookie police officer was sent to the local middle school to give a lecture on how to be safe. Stranger Danger! But this town had nothing to worry about - it was a safe small town.
The officer left happy with his work - he had no idea that one of the very kids sitting in his lecture would be kidnapped and murdered right after school.
This case was unsolved in the FBI files for over 30 years… but would a woman’s phone call in 2020 finally catch the child killer?</description></item><item><title>#75: The Mean Girls Killers (Case of Shanda Sharer) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440250/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 19:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440250/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 4 teenage girls decided they wanted McDonald&amp;rsquo;s for breakfast after their all-nighter. They carefully reverse parked into the lot so that all the bloody handprints on the back of their trunk would be hidden.
They ordered a full breakfast - and one of the girls lifted up the sausage patty and giggled “doesn’t this look like Shanda?”
The 12-year-old girl that they kidnapped? The one they tortured in unspeakable ways for the past 8 hours?</description></item><item><title>#74: The Party Monster Murder (Case of Michael Alig) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440251/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 17:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440251/</guid><description>Podcast Description The hottest clubs in New York City were run by Michael. He knew how to throw a party - serving cat food as appetizers, performances of women pulling Christmas lights out of - well, you know where. A rotating wheel of 6 cow tongues for anyone to “rub” up against. This was the place to be. But when rumors started circling that Michael had injected one of his friends with Drano and dismembered him in his bathtub… nobody believed it.</description></item><item><title>#73: Hotel Of Horrors (Serial Killer - H. H. Holmes) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440252/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 18:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440252/</guid><description>Podcast Description You’ve booked a room in a nice hotel that everyone calls “The Castle.” You quickly realize things are not what it seems here. Doors with spikes attached. Vaults filled with acid. Secret peepholes in the rooms. Staircases that start and stop out of nowhere. You see the “elasticity machine” it’s supposed to stretch your body so you can be taller. The owner wants to create a new race of giants… Everything feels so strange.</description></item><item><title>#72: The Body In The FBI Agent’s Trunk (Case of Mark Putnam &amp; Susan Smith) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440253/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 20:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440253/</guid><description>Podcast Description The hardworking FBI agent was on his way to a meeting when he noticed the large crack on the passenger window of his car. How is he going to explain that?
He had a lie for the large wound on his hand. What about the deep scratches all over his neck? Surely he could come up with something. Now the only thing left to take care of - was the decomposing body in his trunk.</description></item><item><title>#71: Cannibal Mountain (Case - Uruguayan Rugby Team) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440254/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 20:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440254/</guid><description>Podcast Description “What’s the last thing you ate?” the doctor asked. All 16 of them responded the same - “human flesh.”
A plane of 45 passengers had crashed into the side of a snow covered mountain in the Andes. Yes, it’s freezing, they were only wearing t-shirts, and many were wounded if not dead - but, they will be rescued soon. That was what they put their faith in. But they were wrong.</description></item><item><title>#70: The Snuff Film Killers (Serial Killers Leonard Lake &amp; Charles Ng) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440255/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 18:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440255/</guid><description>Podcast Description Most people collect ordinary things - paintings, books, baseball cards. But what if you could collect your darkest desires? Two men decide they will collect women to be held captive in their torture bunker. The men started gathering all their weapons of torture - power drills, clamps, gags, and pliers… the last thing they needed was a video camera. Because they were going to film it all. The snuff film director, the collector, and the serial killer.</description></item><item><title>#69: The Walgreens Killers (Case of Patricia Columbo &amp; Frank Deluca) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440256/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 17:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440256/</guid><description>Podcast Description When you step into this Walgreens it feels like any other - aisles filled with cosmetics, household goods, and a pharmacy. The employees are kind but they’re harboring their own dark secrets. The woman in cosmetics had inappropriate relations with a German Shepherd and her ex boyfriend refuses to get rid of the incriminating pictures.
The store manager has a deadly liking for underage girls. Another employee is plotting the murder of 3 people.</description></item><item><title>#68: The Girl Who Died Twice (Case of Becky Brown &amp; Amy Burridge) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440257/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 17:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440257/</guid><description>Podcast Description She died twice on that 12 story bridge. The first time - she was thrown off the bridge by two men in hopes of killing her. This would be the only way their night of sick torture would stay secret. The second time - 19 years later. The same bridge. The same spot. The same 120 feet fall. Are the events connected? How does someone die twice?
Source Notes: rottenmangopodcast.</description></item><item><title>#67: 105 Hostages - The Hijacking of Flight 701 (Case of Roger Holder &amp; Cathy Kerkow) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440258/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 18:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440258/</guid><description>Podcast Description A man with a briefcase entered the cockpit of Western Flight 701. The man tells the pilots there are 2 bombs on the plane and a grenade in his suitcase. For 20 hours - a couple terrorized the entire flight in hopes of having their demands met. They wanted $3 million dollars in cash, 5 parachutes, a woman on trial for murder to be handed over to them, and a flight to Vietnam.</description></item><item><title>#66: Burned Alive - 7 Hours of Torture (Cheshire Home Invasion Murders) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440259/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 19:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440259/</guid><description>Podcast Description A family of 4 is startled awake by two masked men - they tell them that everything is going to be okay. We just want money - that’s all. Slowly for the next 7 hours - it becomes clear that’s not all they want. The 11yr old daughter was assaulted. The mother was assaulted and strangled. The house engulfed in flames - all while the police were standing outside.</description></item><item><title>#65: The Sisterhood Of Torture (Case of Michelle Knotek) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440260/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 18:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440260/</guid><description>Podcast Description They knew something was different about their family. The sisters saw it. They had guests doing chores - completely nude - in the house. Guests being duct-taped to the walls.
They had a man jumping from their roof onto his bare feet over and over again. Until his legs broke. Even all this pain - was nothing compared to the humiliation and psychological torture taking place… what was really going on here?</description></item><item><title>#64: The “666” Death (The Man Who Wrote Letters To Serial Killers) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440261/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2021 19:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440261/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dear Mr. John Wayne Gacy… That’s how it all started… One letter to the “Clown Killer” who was responsible for 33 murders of young boys - and Jason was hooked. For months he developed relationships and even visited with John Wayne Gacy, Jeffrey Dahmer, Richard Ramirez, and Charles Manson. He wanted to get inside their heads - but what happens if they get inside his first?
Source Notes: rottenmangopodcast.</description></item><item><title>#63: Yosemite National Park Serial Killer (Case - Steven &amp; Cary Stayner) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440262/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 20:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440262/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why do so many people go missing in National Parks? Alien conspiracy theory? Government experiments? Or just lost in nature? In this case - it’s none of the above. It’s a serial killer that leaves a trail of bloodshed and a decapitated head bobbing in a stream in Yosemite. Once they catch the killer that’s when the real mystery begins - wasn’t his little brother a national hero? Didn’t they make TV shows about this family?</description></item><item><title>#62: Vanished In Tokyo Part 2 (Case Lucie Blackman / Joji Obara) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440263/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 18:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440263/</guid><description>Podcast Description There is international panic on the fate of the missing British Airways flight attendant… and the crazy leads don’t make it any easier for police. She was sold to the Yakuza (Japanese Mafia). An adult film producer claims his colleague kidnapped her for producing a snuff film. The police finally get their first good lead - they knock on the suspect’s door and open up a can of worms.</description></item><item><title>#61: Vanished In Tokyo (Case Lucie Blackman / Joji Obara) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440264/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 19:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440264/</guid><description>Podcast Description A Japanese Hostess Club - purchase a table by the hour - female hostesses will come and sit with you the entire time. They pour your drinks, light your cigarette, flirt with you, and stroke your ego. There’s an unspoken law that all the flirting - was nothing but a fantasy. But when a British Airways flight attendant disappears while working at a hostess club - a question arises… Was her abduction someone’s fantasy?</description></item><item><title>#60: The Death Room Murders (Serial Killer - Dorothea Puente) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440265/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 00:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440265/</guid><description>Podcast Description You look out your window - the landlord has dug up another large hole in the backyard… they’re always doing strange gardening projects late at night. You walk into the kitchen - there’s that smell again… the landlord says it’s new fertilizer but the smell is distinct. There are usually 8 tenants but once in a while, one will disappear without notice… what really is going on in this house?</description></item><item><title>#59: The Pig Farm Serial Killer (Case - Robert Pickton) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440266/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 18:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440266/</guid><description>Podcast Description Did you know pigs will eat anything?
The Pickton Pig Farm - was isolated, private, had its own slaughterhouse equipped with commercial freezers, and hundreds of very hungry pigs. The farm was well known by locals for many things - mainly the smell that radiated from it… but soon it would be known by the whole world. For where 49 women get murdered… Source Notes: rottenmangopodcast.com
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#58: Dr. Starvation The Serial Killer (Linda Hazzard &amp; Belle Gunness) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440267/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440267/</guid><description>Podcast Description A massive 3 story sanatorium in the isolated woods of Washington. The whispers about what goes on in there - I heard she buries another patient every single day. If you walk past it the scary doctor might snatch you, lock you in a room, and starve you to death. Sounds like campfire scary stories? But what if it’s not. What if this is one of America’s worst female serial killers?</description></item><item><title>#57: The Kidnap Kit (Case of Becky Watts) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440268/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 19:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440268/</guid><description>Podcast Description A family begged their community to help find their missing 16 year old daughter. #FindBecky started trending on social media. Nobody was prepared to find out that - A 16 year old schoolgirl had been brutally murdered in her own room, decapitated, dismembered, and placed into suitcases. Not long after 6 people were arrested - 2 of them are family members. Source Notes: rottenmangopodcast.com
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#56: Mommy Needs Money Murders (Case of Ellen Boehm) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440269/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 19:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440269/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ellen could hear her 8-year-old daughter splashing around in the bath with her barbies. Thankfully her son was fast asleep - another long exhausting day as a single mom. But what if things didn’t have to be this way? Ellen calmly walked over to the bathroom, plugged in her hairdryer… and threw it in the bathtub where Stacy was playing&amp;hellip; Plop.
Source Notes: rottenmangopodcast.com
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#55: The Killer Kitty (Richardson Family Murders) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440270/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 18:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440270/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Richardson family was found viciously murdered in the middle of the night… The police are gathering clues when they realize that a family member is missing.
The 12-year-old daughter… where is she? Has she been abducted? Did she escape? Was she killed? Is her body somewhere else? Time is ticking&amp;hellip;
Source Notes: rottenmangopodcast.com
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>#54: Abducted, Tortured, Left For Dead (Case of Alison Botha) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440271/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 19:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440271/</guid><description>Podcast Description She was driven off the main road where she was assaulted, disemboweled, and left for dead. Against all odds, she managed to survive this attack. But that was just the beginning of a diabolical crime&amp;hellip;
Source Notes: rottenmangopodcast.com
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#53: Captive For 24 Years/ Girl In The Basement (Case-Elizabeth Fritzl) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440272/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 19:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440272/</guid><description>Podcast Description She was held captive for 24 years in the secret basement of the house that she grew up in. During her captivity she gave birth to 7 children - all in the dark with nothing but a pack of diapers and a pair of scissors. For 24 years there were two families residing in one house. The “family above” lived a normal life. Celebrating holidays. Taking pictures. The “family below” lived a life with no sunlight, mold on the walls, and torment beyond imagine.</description></item><item><title>#52: Giggling Granny Serial Killer (Nannie Doss) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440273/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 19:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440273/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who would ever suspect a sweet little grandma with the best-baked goods in town of having a sinister past?
She was a doting grandmother, wife, daughter, and a “domestic goddess.” But once in a while, she would add a special ingredient to her baked goods resulting in the death of her loved ones. After 11 funerals - nobody suspected the grieving grandma. Do you trust your grandma?
Source Notes: rottenmangopodcast.</description></item><item><title>#51: The Architect’s Almost Perfect Murder (Case Elaine O'Hara) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440274/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 19:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440274/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two friends go fishing - instead of fish they catch:
BDSM leather masks, ropes, handcuffs, knives, and bondage equipment. Could this be the aftermath of a really crazy party?
OR was it something more sinister? A case filled with intimate text messages between the killer and victim, bloodlust, and a raging psychopath.
Source Notes: rottenmangopodcast.com
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>#50: The Most Psychopathic Woman in Korea (Case Angela Simpson &amp; Lady Eom) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440275/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 20:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440275/</guid><description>Podcast Description The press claimed she had a “perfect score” on the Psychopath Test - making her the most psychopathic woman in South Korea. Why did all her loved ones go blind? Why did all her husbands end up dead? And why did she try to burn down an entire hospital? How much is too much coincidence?
Source Notes: rottenmangopodcast.com
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#49: Tokyo Subway Killers (Case of Shoko Asahara) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440276/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 22:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440276/</guid><description>Podcast Description 5 men board 5 different Tokyo subway trains at the same time. Each of them are carrying plastic bags filled with poison.
At exactly 8 AM - peak rush hour - they will release the poison to thousands of passengers who are stuck in the trains breathing in the lethal gas.
Source Notes: rottenmangopodcast.com
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>#48: The "Best Friends Forever" Murder (Case: Christine Paolilla &amp; Vera Jo Reigle) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440277/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 18:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440277/</guid><description>Podcast Description They met in High School and became popular and inseparable. One of them was even voted “Miss Irresistible.” Best friends forever &amp;amp; ever they said - but when four of them are found brutally murdered you have to wonder if someone close to them was involved…
Secrets between friends are sometimes the darkest ones. One of them is a Pretty Little Liar.
Source Notes: rottenmangopodcast.com
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#47- Willy Wonka Killer Part 2 (Serial Killer Dean Corll) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440278/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 19:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440278/</guid><description>Podcast Description The CandyMan and his 2 assistant killers are ramping up their serial murders&amp;hellip;
29 boys go missing from the same small town. Where are the police? And who finally takes down Willy Wonka? It all ends with one last party.
Source Notes: rottenmangopodcast.com
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#46: The Candy Man Part 1 (Serial Killer Dean Corll) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440279/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 22:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440279/</guid><description>Podcast Description The “CandyMan” is what all the little boys called him. He was a candy factory owner who passed out free candy to all the kids. In the same small town of Houston Heights 29 boys go missing in the span of a few years… At a time where it felt like nobody could be trusted - the CandyMan seemed like a wholesome adult figure. But you know where this story goes.</description></item><item><title>#45- Korean Manson Cult (Case Jijonpa Family Cult) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440280/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 21:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440280/</guid><description>Podcast Description A cult in Korea heard the saying “eat the rich” and they decided to do just that. Literally. They turned their victims into side dishes for their Korean BBQ.
Is this about the ever-growing wealth gap or are they just a sinister cult looking for blood? Source Notes: rottenmangopodcast.com
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>#44- The Sinister Staircase (Case of Michael &amp; Kathleen Peterson) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440281/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 21:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440281/</guid><description>Podcast Description From the outside - they’re perfect. Wealthy, educated, compassionate, veteran, with 5 children in a blended marriage. When Kathleen is found dead at the bottom of the staircase - all of the Petersons&amp;rsquo; family secrets come to light. We have more questions than ever…
IF she fell (like Michael Peterson claims) why was there blood soaking the floor &amp;amp; walls? Why did Michael delete personal emails right after he found out his wife died?</description></item><item><title>#43- The Vienna Strangler (Serial Killer Jack Unterweger) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440282/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 19:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440282/</guid><description>Podcast Description A convicted murderer - sentenced to life in prison - decides to start publishing children’s books, short stories, and even a memoir. The elite literary community soaks in every word and praises him for becoming a reformed man in prison. They even start a petition to the President of Austria to let this reformed man out and walk the streets amongst us! Once released - it’s his second chance to do the things he’s always wanted to do!</description></item><item><title>#42- Mysterious Death of Elisa Lam | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440283/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440283/</guid><description>Podcast Description Guests of the Cecil Hotel started complaining about water quality issues - their tap water was brown and had a strange taste to it&amp;hellip; They sent a maintenance man to go check on the water tanks on the roof that only staff had a key to - as it was a restricted access area and armed. There he found the body of Elis Lam in one of the water tanks.</description></item><item><title>#41: The Law School Murder (Case of Lauren Giddings) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440284/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 22:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440284/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a law student goes missing - you can’t help but suspect everyone in her class. Was this law school jealousy, a love triangle, or a random crime?
What if one of these very law students wrote about how to commit the perfect crime? Is this a situation of How To Get Away With Murder?
Source notes on rottenmangopodcast.com
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#40- The Trash Chute Murder (Mysterious Death of Phoebe Handsjuk) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440285/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 20:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440285/</guid><description>Podcast Description A woman falls feet first down a 12 story trash chute to her death. The police are quick to determine it&amp;rsquo;s a suicide or accidental death. But there are still more questions than answers:
How did she fit herself into a garbage chute that has an opening the size of a laptop? Why were her jeans pulled down below her knees? Who is her boyfriend and why are people suspicious of him?</description></item><item><title>#39- She Made SOAP From Her Victim's Bodies (Serial Killer Leonarda Cianciulli) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440286/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440286/</guid><description>Podcast Description The famous soap maker was giving away free soaps &amp;amp; tea cakes from her beloved soap shop. The neighbors were ecstatic to take home their luxurious bars of soap that they got for free and couldn&amp;rsquo;t wait to test them out&amp;hellip; They wouldn&amp;rsquo;t know till it was too late that the Soapmakers recipe included the bodies of her victims. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#38- Ted Bundy 2.0 (Serial Killers Danny Rowling &amp; Charlie Brandt) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440287/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 21:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440287/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two serial killers operating in the same state with the same goal - to be the next Ted Bundy. &amp;ldquo;A superstar&amp;rdquo; one says. They both have a thing for beheading women and staging the crime scene to look as if the victim&amp;rsquo;s head is staring at her own headless body. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>#37- The Waterbed Murder (Case of Maddie Clifton &amp; Josh Phillips) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440288/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440288/</guid><description>Podcast Description Melissa was sick of telling her teenage son to clean his room. For the past week, there had been a disgusting stench coming from it. She had a theory - his waterbed was leaking and was causing the smell. She lifted it up hoping to find the source. But instead, she found a dead little girl. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy</description></item><item><title>#36- Sexton Family Cult Murders (Case of Eddie Sexton &amp; His Incestuous Family) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440289/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 21:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440289/</guid><description>Podcast Description They saw their dad as a &amp;ldquo;Half God&amp;rdquo; - the product of Lucifer mating with humans. They followed his every command whether it was - marrying him, fathering children with his daughter, having sexual relations with their own siblings, or even killing people who learned of his secrets. He led the FBI on a massive manhunt that would ultimately lead to the unraveling of his secret cult. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#35- The Bizarre Kidnapping of an Unborn Child (Case of Lisa Montgomery) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440290/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 20:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440290/</guid><description>Podcast Description She told all of her friends that she was pregnant. People started getting suspicious when they realized she was so close to her due date but hadn&amp;rsquo;t even started showing yet. But Lisa had a plan. She would go visit an unsuspecting pregnant friend and cut the unborn baby from her womb. Welcome to the first-ever minisode! We will have long episodes, as usual, every Wednesday + the new additional mini-episodes on Sundays!</description></item><item><title>#34- The Dance Moms Murder | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440291/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440291/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cheerleading tryouts at this junior high school become deadly once a mom hires a hitman to literally &amp;ldquo;knock out&amp;rdquo; the competition. What&amp;rsquo;s a couple of dead people when your daughter has the chance to be a cheerleader? We also cover the story of the Blood Countess. One of the most prolific female serial killers who has claimed the lives of over 600 victims. She believed the secret to youth was to take baths&amp;hellip; full of blood.</description></item><item><title>#33- India's Daughter - New Delhi Bus Rape and Murder Case | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440292/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440292/</guid><description>Podcast Description A 15-year-old hitchhiker catches a ride with a sweet &amp;ldquo;grandpa looking man.&amp;rdquo; She was excited to go home but he had plans of his own. His plans resulted in her with both her arms amputated and thrown off a cliff. On the other side of the world, another girl got on a bus after visiting the movies with a friend. She would be found tossed off the bus clinging on for her life.</description></item><item><title>Kidnapped Victim Forced To "Fall In Love" With Her Captor | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440293/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 01:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440293/</guid><description>Podcast Description She wakes up in a room with no memory of where she is and even who she is&amp;hellip; What&amp;rsquo;s even more alarming is that her kidnapper tells her that she will only survive this if she falls in love with him. Anytime the kidnapper believes it isn&amp;rsquo;t going as expected he drugs up the victim and resets her memory once more&amp;hellip;
Today&amp;rsquo;s episode is a Baking A Mystery which is a completely fictional story!</description></item><item><title>#32- The British Jeffrey Dahmer - He Keeps Corpses As Roommates (Serial Killer Dennis Nilsen) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440294/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 20:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440294/</guid><description>Podcast Description Police are called out about clogged drains underneath a house in London&amp;hellip; doesn&amp;rsquo;t really sound like detective work. BUT it soon becomes apparent that the drains have been clogged with human remains. Someone inside the house has been flushing human remains down the toilet. (Remember Jeffrey Dahmer?)
The police think they&amp;rsquo;re about to arrest a murderer but little do they know they&amp;rsquo;ve got a serial killer on their hands.</description></item><item><title>Deaf Author Gets Stalked By Serial Killer In The Woods (BAM) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440295/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 03:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440295/</guid><description>Podcast Description A deaf &amp;amp; mute horror writer is staying isolated in the cabin so that she can focus on her manuscript. A serial killer happens upon her house and decides to make her his next victim. Can she outsmart him? How will she escape? After all, he has the advantage. He can hear her. Today&amp;rsquo;s episode is part of the Baking A Mystery series and is a completely fictional story!</description></item><item><title>The Missing Korean YouTubers (BAM) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440296/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 01:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440296/</guid><description>Podcast Description Korean YouTubers decide to explore the most haunted place in South Korea&amp;hellip; Gonjiam - an abandoned mental asylum where there are rumors of patients who were driven to madness and eventually murdered by the evil hospital director. The YouTubers are live-streaming their entire experience inside the haunted place and slowly&amp;hellip; one by one&amp;hellip; they go missing.
Today&amp;rsquo;s podcast episode is a Baking A Mystery! It is a completely fictional story!</description></item><item><title>#31- The Mysterious Slumber Party Death - Death of Tamla Horsford | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440297/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 20:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440297/</guid><description>Podcast Description A slumber party filled with responsible football moms whose kids all play football together&amp;hellip; when they wake up one of them is dead in the backyard. When the police start investigating things start getting weirder&amp;hellip; A woman tries to bribe the police with Dunkin Donuts gift cards (yes, you read that right). A boyfriend in law enforcement kept accessing Tamla&amp;rsquo;s investigation file unlawfully. And that&amp;rsquo;s just the tip of this murky, confusing, mysterious iceberg of a case.</description></item><item><title>I Killed My Wife And Her Body Disappeared (BAM) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440298/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 01:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440298/</guid><description>Podcast Description The body of a deceased CEO of a major pharmaceuticals company goes missing from the morgue before it can be autopsied. The police find mounting evidence that the husband has a lot of motive to murder his wife and then steal her corpse so all evidence of the murder will be gone. The husband also finds mounting evidence that his wife is not dead at all&amp;hellip; and maybe she walked out of the morgue?</description></item><item><title>#30- The Real Life "Dexter" Serial Killer (Case of Pedrinho Matador) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440299/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 19:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440299/</guid><description>Podcast Description A serial killer who only kills other murderers. He has killed over 60 drug dealers, murderers, molesters, and fellow serial killers in some of the most brutal ways. Fun Fact: He&amp;rsquo;s a free man today. Is he the real-life Dexter? Is this vigilante justice? Or is he just as sick and twisted as all the other serial killers out there? To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#29- The Bleach Torture Killer (Case of Kelly Anne Bates &amp; Suzanne Capper) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440300/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 20:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440300/</guid><description>Podcast Description She was tortured with bleach till her skin fell off - and then her friends lit her on fire. Another girl had her knees crushed by her boyfriend so she could never run away. Frequently spoken about alongside Junko Furuta&amp;rsquo;s case&amp;hellip; these two cases are some of the vilest cases of torture we&amp;rsquo;ve researched. We also do a quick dive into where torture even started (the CIA gets involved).</description></item><item><title>#28- The McDonald's Killer | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440301/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 21:43:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440301/</guid><description>Podcast Description 77 minutes of absolute psychological torture, murder, and loss. His youngest victim was 8 months old. This might be one of the saddest cases we cover. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#27- The Foot Fetish Killer (Serial Killer Jerry Brudos) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440302/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 20:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440302/</guid><description>Podcast Description He took something from his first victim - one of her feet. He kept it in the freezer and used it to model his collection of high heels. A collector of sorts - feet, breast, high heels, and underwear from unsuspecting women for over a decade but his dream was to have a collection of women in his freezer. Did he make his dream come true?
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>She Moved Into A Serial Killers House And Now They Won't Stop Calling (BAM) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440303/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 01:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440303/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Korean movie &amp;ldquo;The Call&amp;rdquo; that has been highly requested is finally here! This is what happens when a serial killer keeps calling you asking for favors. It&amp;rsquo;s a really intense one so buckle up! Today&amp;rsquo;s episode is a Baking A Mystery! This is a fictional story and did not happen in real life. If you are only interested in true crime (don&amp;rsquo;t worry) we have episodes every single Wednesday and I&amp;rsquo;ll see you then!</description></item><item><title>#26- Daisy's Destruction - Dark Web "Pedo-Empire" | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440304/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 20:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440304/</guid><description>Podcast Description Daisy&amp;rsquo;s Destruction - the 1-hour long video with 3 adults torturing an infant (18-month-old Daisy) was released onto the dark web in 2012. To most of us, it sounded like an urban legend, but to a lot of twisted people in the world, it was worth the $10,000 viewing price. Today&amp;rsquo;s episode enters the world of the dark web &amp;ldquo;Pedo-Empire&amp;rdquo; and you would never believe who&amp;rsquo;s behind the screen.</description></item><item><title>#25- The Baby Farm Killer (Case of Gary Heidnik) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440305/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440305/</guid><description>Podcast Description A millionaire who dreams of having dozens of women to all get pregnant with his children at the same time. He will do whatever it takes&amp;hellip; There&amp;rsquo;s electrocution, a Cuisnart blender, and a freezer full of meat, even stomping screwdrivers into women&amp;rsquo;s ear holes..
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#24- The Chessboard Killer (Serial Killer Alexander Pichushkin) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440306/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 21:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440306/</guid><description>Podcast Description 64 squares on a chessboard. And each represented a victim he viciously murdered. His trademark? Shoving a vodka bottle into the cracks of the skull he just split. The victims were almost always still alive during this. Obsessed with the Queen&amp;rsquo;s Gamebit? Got a new fascination with chess? He was obsessed too. Meet the chessboard killer. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy</description></item><item><title>#23- The Girl In The Box | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440307/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 20:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440307/</guid><description>Podcast Description She was kidnapped and placed in a coffin-like box for 23 hours a day for 7 years. The kidnappers placed her under their water bed all day and only brought her out at night to torture her. They made a sensory deprivation box outfitted for her head that they forced her to wear. It prevented light, sound, smell, and fresh air from entering. This episode is about couples who kidnap young women to fulfill their sick fantasies.</description></item><item><title>#22- The Lululemon Murder | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440308/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440308/</guid><description>Podcast Description 2 women were terrorized in the back of a yoga store at the time of closing. 2 men in black caught on security cameras. The investigation comes to a sudden halt when the investigators realize nothing is as it seems. All for some yoga pants. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>No Doctor Has Ever Survived Treating This Mental Asylum Patient (BAM Halloween Special) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440309/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 02:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440309/</guid><description>Podcast Description An undiagnosable patient at a mental asylum has driven every single one of his doctors into madness and often times&amp;hellip; to their mysterious death. Is there something sinisterly wrong with him or is it a contagious madness? Welcome to the Halloween special of Baking A Mystery! This is a fictional story and isn&amp;rsquo;t true. As always, the video version is up on the YouTube channel &amp;ldquo;MissMangoButt&amp;rdquo; If you are exclusively into true crime there will always be a new episode every Wednesday!</description></item><item><title>#21- 120 Days Of Murder (Serial Killers Ian Brady &amp; Myra Hindley) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440310/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440310/</guid><description>Podcast Description 4 wealthy men isolate themselves on an island with 40 victims and spend 4 months torturing them with the most vile, sick torture. This is the inspiration behind the prolific serial killer couple from the UK.
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Gardener And His "Butterflies" (Kidnapped Women He's Desperate To Preserve) BAM EPISODE | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440311/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 01:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440311/</guid><description>Podcast Description In an isolated mansion, a &amp;ldquo;gardener&amp;rdquo; is obsessed with his &amp;ldquo;butterfly&amp;rdquo; collection. His kidnapped victims must play into his sick fantasy or risk being killed.
Welcome to another Baking A Mystery (BAM) series! Today&amp;rsquo;s video is a fictional story and is NOT a true crime story. If you guys are only interested in true crime stay tuned every Wednesday! The visual version of this is up on YouTube under &amp;ldquo;MissMangoButt Baking A Mystery&amp;rdquo;</description></item><item><title>#20- The Hunger Games Serial Killer (Case of Robert Hansen) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440312/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 19:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440312/</guid><description>Podcast Description He blindfolds his victims, releases them out into the wilderness, gives them a head start&amp;hellip; then he hunts them down with his hunting rifle. Hunting is his favorite game and human are his favorite prey. This is the story of the real-life Hunger Games serial killer.
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#19- The Werewolf Of New York (Case of Katherine Knight &amp; Albert Fish) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440313/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440313/</guid><description>Podcast Description She killed her husband then tried to feed his children dinner&amp;hellip; that she cooked with his body parts. He likes to cover people in bacon before roasting them. In honor of Spooktober, today&amp;rsquo;s episode is a long juicy one with two different killers who have completely different methods + motives&amp;hellip; but a strange fascination with the forbidden meat. Whatever you do &amp;hellip; don&amp;rsquo;t look in their oven.
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#18- The Real House Of Horrors (Serial Killers Rosemary &amp; Fred West) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440314/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 20:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440314/</guid><description>Podcast Description Peepholes installed for his viewing pleasure. Chains from the ceiling to suspend the victims. Baby monitors placed strategically so he could hear her from anywhere. Shallow graves in the basement, garage, and backyard. We are starting off Spooktober with the Real House of Horrors. This is one house you would never want to step foot in. Nobody is safe. Especially the children. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Snowed In With 4 Strangers - 1 Of Them Is A Murderer (BAM #3) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440315/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 19:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440315/</guid><description>Podcast Description And she only has 15 hours to figure out which one of them is the killer. It&amp;rsquo;s only a matter of time before the killer realizes that she&amp;rsquo;s onto them. Baking A Mystery #3! This is a fictional story (if you are only into true crime please come back for our scheduled Wednesday postings!) *If you would like to see the video version of this it is up on YouTube &amp;ldquo;MissMangoButt Baking A Mystery&amp;rdquo; there is a playlist where all of the visuals get posted!</description></item><item><title>#17- The Alice in Wonderland Murders | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440316/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440316/</guid><description>Podcast Description A quadruple homicide An adult film star (known for his spectacularly large &amp;ldquo;asset&amp;rdquo;) at the center of the murder investigation
The police compared the brutality of the crime with that of the Manson murders&amp;hellip; and it left everyone wondering&amp;hellip; What actually happens in Wonderland? To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#16- The Twisted Life of Jeffrey Dahmer *He Wanted to Create Living Zombies | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440317/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 22:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440317/</guid><description>Podcast Description He injected his victims in the skull with hydrochloric acid and sometimes boiling water - all because he wanted to create living zombies. Jeffrey Dahmer is one of the most twisted serial killers in history. It&amp;rsquo;s a real life nightmare guys. Get ready.
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#15- The REAL Silence of the Lambs Killer *he wears skin (seriously) Case of Serial Killer Ed Gein | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440318/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440318/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;rsquo;ve seen the movies Silence of the Lambs + Texas Chainsaw Massacre and went to bed thinking &amp;ldquo;at least it&amp;rsquo;s just a movie.&amp;rdquo; But what if it wasn&amp;rsquo;t? What if the person the movies were inspired by was darker, more sinister, and scarier than the movies themselves? This is the real life story those movies are inspired by. He wears dead people&amp;rsquo;s skin. Seriously. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#14- The Dairy Farm Serial Killer | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440319/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 21:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440319/</guid><description>Podcast Description 3 girls from a dairy farm in Ohio go to Florida for their first ever vacation. It was going to be the trip of their dreams. Disney World. Beaches. Boat Rides. They documented everything on their camera. Then they were found floating attached to concrete blocks in Tampa Bay. They had been dead for days. The investigators follow their entire itinerary to catch a potential serial killer on the loose.</description></item><item><title>#13- The Vampire Serial Killer (Case of Tsutomu Miyazaki) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440320/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440320/</guid><description>Podcast Description He was a product of incest, born with &amp;ldquo;Dracula hands&amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip; He would then grow up to murder 4-year-old girls Drink their blood And take their hands home to roast and to consume..
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>She saw her neighbor's murder but everyone tells her the neighbor never even existed (BAM #2) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440321/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 20:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440321/</guid><description>Podcast Description She&amp;rsquo;s an Agoraphobe that never leaves her house Agoraphobic - an extreme/irrational fear of the outside Through her window she witnesses her neighbor being murdered. But everyone around her including the police, her own family, and the neighbor&amp;rsquo;s family all tell her that the neighbor she saw die NEVER even existed&amp;hellip; BAKING A MYSTERY #2 is a fictional minisode on the Rotten Mango If you guys are just interested in true crime please watch out for a crazy story coming to you on Wednesday!</description></item><item><title>#12- The Butcher of Russia (Serial Killer Andrei Chikatilo) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440322/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440322/</guid><description>Podcast Description One of Russia&amp;rsquo;s most infamous serial killers ever&amp;hellip; He has killed over 53 women and children&amp;hellip; and it all started because he couldn&amp;rsquo;t get a boner. You read that right. His erectile dysfunction led him down a dark sinister path of murder. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#11- Sex with Severed Heads (Serial Killer Ed Kemper) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440323/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440323/</guid><description>Podcast Description The title is NOT a lie. This serial killer is into having sex with severed heads. For some reason he doesn&amp;rsquo;t like it when the head is attached to the body. One of the nastiest necrophiliacs I&amp;rsquo;ve researched. *Necrophilia [noun] sexual intercourse with or attraction towards dead bodies
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description></item><item><title>Everyone Goes Missing In This Apartment Building (BAM #1) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440324/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440324/</guid><description>Podcast Description She gets a job at an apartment building. Her boss gives her a list of strange rules to follow. DON&amp;rsquo;T BE NOSY is one of them. But she can&amp;rsquo;t help but notice that everyone is going missing in this building. Welcome to Baking A Mystery where I tell you guys the story of a mystery (fictional usually) that I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking heavily about. This series started on my YouTube channel (MissMangoButt) and will be released here for the audio listeners!</description></item><item><title>#10- The Dildo Submarine Murder | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440325/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440325/</guid><description>Podcast Description Remote-controlled dildos Russian mafia Columbian drug cartels A strip club named Porky&amp;rsquo;s and The $35 million Russian military submarine that was about to be sold to transport 40 tons of cocaine right under the nose of the FBI. I can&amp;rsquo;t make this shit up.
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#9- Incest Murder Party | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440326/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440326/</guid><description>Podcast Description A 19 year old girl goes missing Two days later her abusive uncle “commits suicide” Then police arrest 11 family members
Coincidence? Or was the family hiding something as dark as an incestuous sex ring run by an uncle who wanted everyone to “swap children.” Warning - this story is really dark and triggering.
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>#8- The Coca-Cola Torture Murder (Case of Sylvia Likens) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440327/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440327/</guid><description>Podcast Description On her stomach, she was branded with the words &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m a prostitute and proud of it&amp;rdquo; She was tortured by Coca-Cola bottles and knives for months..
This might ruin soda for you forever
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#7- The Japanese Cannibal Murderer | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440328/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440328/</guid><description>Podcast Description He murdered a woman because he wanted to eat her bottom, breasts, and thighs. The police caught him but set him free. The free man who happens to be a cannibal + murderer then turns in an ADULT FILM ACTOR. THIS IS A WILD STORY. I can&amp;rsquo;t even write a summary without wanting to pull out my hair in confusion. And guess what? He&amp;rsquo;s a free man today. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>#6- The Killer Clown - Serial Killer (Case of John Wayne Gacy) | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440329/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440329/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you afraid of clowns? Most clowns when they take off their makeup and costumes they&amp;rsquo;re just normal people. But today&amp;rsquo;s case is about a clown&amp;hellip; when he took off his makeup he was something scarier&amp;hellip; a serial killer. &amp;ldquo;Do you want to see a magic trick?&amp;rdquo; - it&amp;rsquo;s about to get really creepy. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>#5- The Hello Kitty Murder | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440330/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440330/</guid><description>Podcast Description The decapitated head of a woman was found sewn into a giant Hello Kitty doll&amp;hellip; The rest of her body was missing. A 14 year old girl claims to have been haunted by her ghost. BUT IT GETS WEIRDER&amp;hellip; If you love Hello Kitty - this one might give you some nightmares. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>#4- The Unabomber - Genius Serial Killer or Harvard Experiment Gone Wrong? | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440331/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440331/</guid><description>Podcast Description Not your typical serial killer case&amp;hellip; you have a genius Harvard graduated mathematician inside a tiny wooden shed in Montana making 16 different bombs to ship across the nation. He terrorized America for almost 20 years and caused one of the largest manhunts in FBI history&amp;hellip;.
Honestly the scary thing is he might have gotten away with it if it weren&amp;rsquo;t for&amp;hellip; biss you better listen I&amp;rsquo;m not going to tell you in this box</description></item><item><title>#3- Cannibalism- The Forbidden Meat | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440332/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440332/</guid><description>Podcast Description One man wants to eat human flesh with a glass of wine. One man wants to have his &amp;ldquo;eggplant&amp;rdquo; bitten off and grilled. They end up going on a deadly date and filming the 4 hour long deed. They called it the &amp;ldquo;slaughtering.&amp;rdquo;
Is it murder if the victim got off to it and wanted it? Grab a plate of sausages and eggs and let&amp;rsquo;s get cooking. I&amp;rsquo;m kidding.</description></item><item><title>#2- 44 Days Of Hell – The Murder of Junko Furuta | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440333/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440333/</guid><description>Podcast Description The darkest case I have ever covered 44 days of the sickest torture&amp;hellip; there&amp;rsquo;s burning alive&amp;hellip; and fireworks involved? It get&amp;rsquo;s really dark. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#1- Toy Box Killer | Rotten Mango</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4471440334/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4471440334/</guid><description>Podcast Description To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>