<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence! on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/real-english-conversations-podcast-learn-to-speak-understand-real-english-with-confidence/</link><description>Recent content in Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence! on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 19:45:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/real-english-conversations-podcast-learn-to-speak-understand-real-english-with-confidence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Part 2: Things We Miss about Canada | Advanced English Conversation | English Stories | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590045/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 19:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ever find yourself daydreaming about the good old days and the things that make home feel like, well, home? In our latest podcast episode, Amy and Curtis take a trip down memory lane, sharing heartfelt stories about the things they miss most about Canada while savoring their new life in Mexico. From dinghy floats on Canadian lakes to the joy of snowboarding, they spill the beans on the unique Canadian dishes that still make their mouths water.</description></item><item><title>Part 1: Things We Miss about Canada | Advanced English Conversation | English Stories | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590044/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ever find yourself daydreaming about the good old days and the things that make home feel like, well, home? In our latest podcast episode, Amy and Curtis take a trip down memory lane, sharing heartfelt stories about the things they miss most about Canada while savoring their new life in Mexico. From dinghy floats on Canadian lakes to the joy of snowboarding, they spill the beans on the unique Canadian dishes that still make their mouths water.</description></item><item><title>Cabin Getaways | English Listening Practice | conversação em inglês | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590043/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 16:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Getting away from the city to spend a few days relaxing in a cabin surrounded by nature is a great way to wind down. Amy &amp; Curtis LOVE to stay in cabins when they explore different areas so they can enjoy time by the campfire, relax while listening to the sounds of nature, and sometimes, do activities like kayaking or hiking. Hear about their most memorable cabin getaways in this episode!</description></item><item><title>Interesting Small Talk Conversations #2 | American Conversation | 英語のポッドキャスト | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 18:16:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Small talk goes beyond talking about the weather! Being able to strike up an interesting conversation and talk about stories or recent events can lead to very interesting conversations that are memorable. In this conversation, you'll hear and example of small talk as Amy and Curtis chat about what's they've been up to, what's new, and some interesting things that have happened recently. Do you love our podcast</description></item><item><title>Find a Focus &amp; Start Seeing Real Results | Learn Real English | 英语对话 | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590002/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's time to get focused and see faster results with your English learning. In this episode, you will learn a simple 2-step process that can help you identify the skills you should be focusing on right now and how to create an action plan to see noticeable progress in as little as 2 weeks! Do you love our podcast conversations? Get full access to ALL of our conversations</description></item><item><title>[Part 2] Job Interviews: Be the Dream Candidate with All Ears English (with Lindsay McMahon) | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590003/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590003/</guid><description>Podcast Description In your next job interview, we want you to stand out from the crowd and be the dream job interview candidate! We've invited special guest Lindsay McMahon from the All Ears English podcast to share her top tips to help you understand what employers are looking for, trick questions to watch out for, how to talk about your strengths, and also how to ask smart questions about the company.</description></item><item><title>[Part 1] Job Interviews: Be the Dream Candidate with All Ears English (with Lindsay McMahon) | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 21:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590004/</guid><description>Podcast Description In your next job interview, we want you to stand out from the crowd and be the dream job interview candidate! We've invited special guest Lindsay McMahon from the All Ears English podcast to share her top tips to help you understand what employers are looking for, trick questions to watch out for, how to talk about your strengths, and also how to ask smart questions about the company.</description></item><item><title>Camping | English podcast with Transcript | Conversación en inglés | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590005/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 00:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Camping is all about being able to spend a few days exploring and enjoying the great outdoors. In this podcast episode, Amy and Curtis share their experiences with camping, traditional 'campfire' snacks, and the different styles of camping. And what about the wild animals? Isn´t it dangerous to sleep in a tent with bears roaming around? We've got a story to tell you about some hair-raising adventrures as well!</description></item><item><title>Favorite Apps &amp; Software Programs | Real English | 英会話 | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590006/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 00:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Apps are so common in our day-to-day lives that we don't even think twice about using them. Google Maps, Spotify, Gmail, banking, the list goes on and on. In this episode, we thought it would be interesting to talk about the top apps and explain why we find them so useful! Do you love our podcast conversations? Get full access to ALL of our conversations lesson including the</description></item><item><title>Ferry Boat Rides in Canada | Real Canadian English Conversations | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Discover Canada's beautiful lakes and its unique ferry boat rides with Curtis and Amy on The Real English Conversations Podcast. As part of their summer visits, they share the history and reasons behind their love for this transportation mode, as well as their personal experiences.
😍 Send Our Podcast Some Love with a Review! If you have 2 minutes to leave the Real English Conversations Podcast a 5-star review on your favorite podcast app that would be incredibly helpful to us!</description></item><item><title>Living Abroad in Mexico | Real English Conversations Podcast | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 20:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590008/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a Real English Conversation, Amy and Curtis share their experience of what it’s like immigrating to and living in Mexico. They will share the top reasons why they have chosen Mexico as their home while they discuss the people, the amazing landscapes, and the geographic diversity!
😍 Send Our Podcast Some Love with a Review!
If you have 2 minutes to leave the Real English Conversations Podcast a 5-star review on your favorite podcast app that would be incredibly helpful to us!</description></item><item><title>Canadian Style Weddings | Conversations In English | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 15:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to The Real English Conversations Podcast! In this episode, we'll delve into the fascinating world of Canadian weddings.
Weddings are special celebrations of love and unity, and Canada offers a rich tapestry of wedding traditions and customs. Join us as we explore the unique elements that make Canadian weddings memorable.
In this episode, we'll discuss the different wedding ceremonies and rituals observed in Canada. From traditional church weddings to outdoor ceremonies in scenic locations, we'll uncover the diverse ways Canadians say "</description></item><item><title>Unexpected Adventures of Real English Conversations | English Listening Podcast | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590010/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 19:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590010/</guid><description>Podcast Description The best stories that come out of a trip usually come from an unexpected surprise or adventure. In this episode of The Real English Conversations Podcast, you will hear about Amy and Curtis' latest road trip that leads to a great way of connecting with the local people in a small village. Unlock your fluency with TEACHER CURTIS. Take the 90-Day Next Level English Challenge. Listen to The Phrasal Verb Podcast 😍 Send Our Podcast Some Love with a Review!</description></item><item><title>Interview with Luke's English Podcast | Is Grammar Important? | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590011/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The Real English Conversations Podcast, Amy has an interview with a special guest, Luke Thompson, from Luke's English Podcast where they share some tips on learning English. They share their thoughts on whether or not it's important to focus on grammar or if it’s possible to learn a language without looking at any grammar at all. This a great English lesson and discussion for our intermediate to advanced learners who aren't sure how much time or attention to put into grammar studies versus learning in more organic ways or practicing what you already know!</description></item><item><title>Cell Phones &amp; Technology Podcast | Everyday English Communication | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590012/</guid><description>Podcast Description In only 20 years, cell phones have gone from being an item only a few 'cool people' had to an item nearly everyone has (and can't imagine leaving the house without it)! In this Real English Conversations Podcast episode, Curtis and Amy talk about their first cell phones, and share some funny stories to show how important cell phones are and how they can be used to save the day!</description></item><item><title>Taking Breaks &amp; Avoiding Language Loss | Staying Motivated to Learn English | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590013/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 16:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590013/</guid><description>Podcast Description On The Real English Conversations Podcast, Amy and Curtis share their expert advice and strategies to help you identify different types of breaks and get motivated to resume your studies as soon as possible.
If you're feeling stuck and not making progress in your English language learning journey, we're here to help with the 90-Day Next Level English Challenge. At Real English Conversations, we specialize in helping our students focus on the right things, identify effective learning activities, and provide direct access to a teacher who can answer their questions, give them corrections, and help them practice.</description></item><item><title>Small Talk | Real English Conversations | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to The Real English Conversations Podcast! In this episode, we'll explore the art of small talk in English.
Small talk is a casual conversation that helps us connect with others. Join us as we provide tips and phrases for engaging in enjoyable small talk.
We'll cover common topics like weather, hobbies, and current events. You'll learn how to start conversations, keep them going, and polite ways to end them.</description></item><item><title>Curtis Get's Caught In The Rain | A Real English Story | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 17:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to "The Real English Conversations Podcast!" In this episode, Curtis has a funny story to tell about a time he didn't bring an umbrella with him. Get ready to laugh as Curtis talks about the embarrasing moment on his way to get a haircut, when he got caught in the rain without an umbrella. If you've wanted to learn how to tell an English story, or you just like to listen to funny English stories, you'll LOVE this episode!</description></item><item><title>Amy Interviews Jessica Beck IELTS Specialist Pt. 2 | Real English Conversations | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 17:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Whether you need to prove your English level for your job or to immigrate abroad, you might need to reach a certain score on the IELTS exam. In this episode of The Real English Conversations Podcast, Amy continues her interview a special guest, Jessica Beck, one of the co-hosts of the All Ears English Podcast and who is also a former IELTS examiner, to talk about all about the IELTS exam and to give us some of her insider tips.</description></item><item><title>Amy Interviews Jessica Beck IELTS Specialist Pt.1 | Real English Conversations | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Whether you need to prove your English level for your job or to immigrate abroad, you might need to reach a certain score on the IELTS exam. In this episode of The Real English Conversations Podcast, Amy interviews a special guest, Jessica Beck, one of the co-hosts of the All Ears English Podcast and who is also a former IELTS examiner, to talk about all about the IELTS exam and to give us some of her insider tips.</description></item><item><title>Forest Fires In Canada | Intermediate English Conversations | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 16:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to The Real English Conversations Podcast! In this episode, we'll discuss forest fires.
Forest fires have a significant impact on the environment and communities. Join us as we explore their causes, effects, and management.
Subscribe now to join us on this informative journey. Tune in to understand more about forest fires. Let's protect our forests and communities together. Don't miss out—tune in today!
😍 Send Our Podcast Some Love with a Review!</description></item><item><title>Interview: Hadar Shemesh talks about English Pronunciation | Real English Conversations | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 19:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Let me introduce Hadar Shemesh. an accent coach specializing in American English, she has helped thousands of students to reduce their accents, speak with better fluency, and most importantly, build confidence to speak in English. Listen to this interesting Interview with Amy &amp; Hadar Shemesh about Learning Mindset &amp; Pronunciation. Ready to take your English conversation skills to the next level? Why not join "The Real English Conversations Podcast Course"</description></item><item><title>Bike Riding Adventures | English Story Conversation | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590020/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590020/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Curtis and Amy discuss their memories of riding their bikes as kids and teenagers, and also, some experiences they've had as adults riding around some of their favorite places in Canada. This conversation is packed with tons of interesting expressions, phrasal verbs, and very descriptive dialogue.
🎧 Ready to take your English conversation skills to the next level? Why not join "The Real English Conversations Podcast Course"</description></item><item><title>Chores &amp; Responsibilities | Intermediate English Conversations | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590021/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to The Real English Conversations Podcast!, In this episode Curtis and Amy discuss how they divide up the responsibilities around the house to keep things tidy and clean. This conversation has lots of great English phrases and vocabulary terms related to everyday living! Subscribe now Let's explore the topic of household chores together. Don't miss out—tune in today!
😍 Send Our Podcast Some Love with a Review!</description></item><item><title>Recycling &amp; Why it's Important | Intermediate English Conversations | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to The Real English Conversations Podcast! In this informative episode, we'll explore recycling in Canada and its role in protecting the environment.
Recycling is when we take things like bottles, cans, and paper we don't need anymore and turn them into new items instead of throwing them away. It's an important way to reduce waste and care for our planet.
Subscribe now to embark on this educational journey.</description></item><item><title>Funerals and Loss | Polite English Conversation | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 16:45:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to The Real English Conversations Podcast! In this heartfelt episode, we'll explore polite English for funerals and coping with the loss of a loved one.
For many of our students at first, learning how to express our emotions and feelings in English so they can offer support can be challenging, especially in a language that isn't our first.
Join us as we provide essential English vocabulary, phrases, and cultural insights to help you use polite English for these difficult situations with respect.</description></item><item><title>Applying For Jobs In English | Business English Conversation | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 15:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to The Real English Conversations Podcast! Get ready to excel in applying for jobs and winning job interviews in English. In this episode, we'll train you with essential skills to win the job application process with confidence.
But that's not all! We'll also give you all the English interview strategies, helping you handle common questions and communicate confidently during English Job interviews.
Subscribe now and boost your job search, and unlock the secrets of successful fluent English for job applications and interviews Don't miss out—tune in today and conquer the English job market!</description></item><item><title>English Language Immersion | English Advice Podcast | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590025/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 22:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to The Real English Conversations Podcast! Join your hosts Amy and Curtis as they share practical strategies that will help you surround yourself with English in your daily life, creating an immersive language-learning experience. They discuss the benefits of language immersion, such as improved fluency, cultural understanding, and increased confidence in real-world communication. By tuning in to this episode, you'll gain the tools and inspiration to take your English to the next level through language immersion.</description></item><item><title>Resumes For Jobs In English | Business English Conversation | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590026/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to The Real English Conversations Podcast! Get ready to unlock the secrets of crafting impactful resumes for jobs in English. In this episode, we're here to guide you through the exciting world of resume creation, giving you valuable tips and strategies to help you shine in the English-speaking job market.
Whether you're an experienced professional or just starting your career, this episode is filled with essentials that will take your resume skills to the next level.</description></item><item><title>Canadian Family Vacations | English Speaking Podcast | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590027/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 17:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to The Real English Conversations Podcast! Join us on an exciting journey through the world of Canadian family vacations. In this episode, we'll share our personal vacation stories and experiences that will inspire and teach English language learners like you how to talk about this topic in English just like a native English speaker would.
Whether you're a long-time listener or new to our podcast, this episode is packed with the most common English vocabulary, expressions, and phrasal verbs.</description></item><item><title>The First Podcast Episode From 2015 | Real English Conversations | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590028/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 00:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to The Real English Conversations Podcast, where we take you on a captivating journey through the English language. In this special episode, we're rewinding the clock back to our very first recording, introducing the world to the nostalgia and excitement of our podcast's beginnings. Tune In!! to hear the initial nerves and how easy it was to find our teaching and podcasting rhythm, we'll take you behind the scenes of creating engaging and informative content for language learners like you.</description></item><item><title>Strategies for Building English Vocabulary | Real English Conversation | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590029/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 15:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590029/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of The Real English Conversations Podcast, Amy and Curtis provide expert guidance on effective strategies to enhance your English vocabulary-building process. Learn simple yet efficient methods to expand your vocabulary faster and improve word retention. Tune in now to start improving your English vocabulary today!
😍 Send Our Podcast Some Love with a Review! If you have 2 minutes to leave the Real English Conversations Podcast a 5-star review on your favorite podcast app that would be incredibly helpful to us!</description></item><item><title>Moving to Mexico - Selling Everything and Starting Fresh | Listening English Conversations | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590030/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 19:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Discover the challenges of moving to Mexico in our latest episode of The Real English Conversations Podcast. Join us as we share our experience of selling everything we owned, including our house, and letting go of cherished collections. From garage sales to sorting methods, we discuss the process of starting anew. Whether you're an English language learner or simply looking for an engaging conversation, our podcast offers an immersive and informative experience.</description></item><item><title>Making Smaller Commitments | Studying English Conversations | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590031/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 21:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to The Real English Conversations Podcast, your go-to resource for mastering the English language. In this episode, our host Amy shares valuable insights on how to make smaller commitments to improve your English skills every day. With her expert guidance, you'll discover actionable tips to develop a consistent practice routine and adopt the right mindset to achieve your language goals.
In today's fast-paced world, finding time for language practice can be challenging.</description></item><item><title>Mother Nature and Our Environment | Real English Discussion | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590032/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 23:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to The Real English Conversations podcast! In this episode, we explore the awe-inspiring power of Mother Nature, including earthquakes, hurricanes, floods, and droughts. We discuss the science behind these natural phenomena and ways to protect ourselves and the planet. Improve your English and learn about environmental science and geography by tuning in. Share this episode with friends and family to spread awareness and inspire action. Subscribe to The Real English Conversations podcast for more exciting content on language learning.</description></item><item><title>Snowboarding &amp; Making Movies: Interview with Moreno Pt.2 | Canadian English Conversation | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590033/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 20:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to Part 2 of our interview with Moreno on The Real English Conversations podcast. In this episode, we delve into Moreno's interests in snowboarding, filmmaking, and the Canadian sport of hockey. If you enjoyed our previous conversation on space exploration, you don't want to miss this one! Tune in to improve your English language skills and learn about these fascinating topics, this episode is perfect for ESL learners interested in Canadian culture and sports.</description></item><item><title>Space Exploration: Interview with Moreno | Advanced English Conversation | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590034/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 21:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Looking for an interesting podcast to improve your English language skills? Check out the two-part interview series with Amy and her friend Moreno. In Part 1, they look into the exciting topic of space exploration, while Part 2 covers Moreno's passions for filming and snowboarding. Don't miss out on this opportunity to learn more about these fascinating topics and enhance your English abilities. Subscribe now to The Real English Conversations podcast for more engaging content on language learning.</description></item><item><title>Carnival! Adventures in Colombia | Listening English Conversation | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590035/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Looking for a rich cultural experience? Carnival is celebrated all over the world with music, dancing, and delicious food. In Colombia, we had the adventure of a lifetime experiencing the second-largest carnival in the world. Tune in to our podcast to hear all about it. Enhance your English language skills while learning about different cultures and traditions. Subscribe now to The Real English Conversations podcast for more exciting content on language learning.</description></item><item><title>Predicting The Future In English | Intermediate &amp; Advanced English Listening | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590036/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Enhance your English language skills with The Real English Conversations podcast. In this episode, Amy and Curtis explore the different methods people in North America use to predict the future, including horoscopes and historical practices like reading animal poop and roosters pecking grain. Tune in to learn more about these fascinating topics and improve your language abilities. Subscribe now to The Real English Conversations podcast for more engaging content on language learning.</description></item><item><title>(Part 4) Supercharge Your Motivation! | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590037/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to the final episode of The Real English Conversations podcast series on supercharging your motivation. In this episode, we'll share tips on how to achieve incredible results with your studying and practice, leaving you full of energy and ready to conquer the next level of English. Don't miss out on this impactful podcast that will boost your motivation and leave you feeling inspired. Subscribe to The Real English Conversations podcast for more engaging content on language learning.</description></item><item><title>(Part 3) Creating Unstoppable Consistency | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590038/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Looking to make easy progress in learning a new language? Consistency is key, but staying motivated and consistent can be a challenge over time. In this episode, learn a trick that can help you stay on track with your language learning even when life gets busy. Tune in to The Real English Conversations podcast to discover this helpful tip and improve your language abilities. Don't forget to subscribe for more engaging content on language learning.</description></item><item><title>(Part 2) Navigating the Difficult Path to Fluency | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590039/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 15:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tune in to Part 2 of The Real English Conversations podcast, where we discuss the challenges of learning a language at the intermediate to advanced level. With so much bad advice out there, it's easy to get stuck at your current level. But don't worry, we've got you covered. In this episode, we provide tips on how to navigate this stage and achieve faster results while focusing on your specific areas for improvement.</description></item><item><title>(Part 1) Kickstart Your Motivation with English! | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590040/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Looking to supercharge your motivation and achieve your English language goals this year? Tune into this 4-part podcast series, where we share insights and tips to help you succeed. In the first episode, we'll help you get clear on your goals and create a powerful motive for your English language learning journey. This motive will guide you in creating a solid plan, which we'll discuss in Episode 2. Don't miss out on this opportunity to improve your English and achieve your goals.</description></item><item><title>Spooky Stories: Haunted Houses &amp; UFO’s | English Stories with Transcripts | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590041/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 02:05:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get ready for some spine-tingling tales! Join Amy and Curtis on The Real English Conversations Podcast as they share their creepiest stories about ghosts, haunted houses, and even UFO sightings.
Not only will you get a good scare, but you'll also pick up some great English vocabulary and expressions along the way. Tune in to our English education podcast to expand your language skills and connect with the spooky side of English-speaking culture.</description></item><item><title>English Conversation about Driving | Real English Conversations Podcast | Real English Conversations Podcast - Learn to Speak &amp; Understand Real English with Confidence!</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9678590042/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 07:01:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9678590042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Another new Real English Conversations Podcast episode is ready! In this one, we tell you all about our experiences driving in Canada. You will hear us mention our experiences behind the wheel of a car and about everything from what you have to do to get your driver's license in Canada to following the rules of the road if you don't want a ticket from the police. Subscribe now and join the conversation as we dive into the fascinating world of storytelling together.</description></item></channel></rss>