<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Morning Brew Daily on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/morning-brew-daily/</link><description>Recent content in Morning Brew Daily on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 12:05:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/morning-brew-daily/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why Ketamine Startups are Struggling &amp; Travis Kelce is King of Game-Day Ads | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310216/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 12:05:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310216/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 215: Neal and Toby discuss what Uber joining the S&amp;amp;P 500 means and how seven tech companies are carrying the stock market right now. Plus, Ketamine startups are struggling in the wake of Matthew Perry&amp;rsquo;s death and how Costco banked almost $100 million off gold bars. Plus, Travis Kelce runs game day advertising and Weight Watchers markets to ozempic users. Finally, Netflix may be getting your favorite show back and here is what we are watching for this week.</description></item><item><title>Why Companies Do Layoffs Before the Holidays &amp; Disney's Board Battle | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310001/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 12:06:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 214: Neal and Toby look at the recent layoffs from Cruise, Hasbro and Etsy and explain why companies announce layoffs just before the holidays. Plus, there&amp;rsquo;s a board battle brewing at Disney and Starbucks doesn&amp;rsquo;t run the coffee show in China anymore. The guys share their stocks of the week and why the rental market in the US may finally be favoring tenants. Finally, what business lessons can we learn from Willy Wonka?</description></item><item><title>The Pro Sports Move Costing DC Billions &amp; 'Nerds' Candy Sweet $500M Business | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 12:07:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 213: Neal and Toby explain why Washington DC&amp;rsquo;s pro sports teams are moving to Northern Virginia and the financial implications it will have on both regional economies. Plus, Tesla recalls 2 million vehicles and access to a key abortion drug heads to the Supreme Court. Neal shares his favorite numbers and ChatGPT is paying a mass media company to use it&amp;rsquo;s content. Finally, Nerds Candy has exploded from being worth $50 million to $500 million.</description></item><item><title>Your Wages Are Catching Up to Inflation &amp; Why Tesla Could Sue Cyber Truck Owners | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 11:51:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 212: Neal and Toby discuss how gas prices and wage rates have impacted the latest inflation report. Plus, Netflix posts viewer data from every show for the first time ever and Tesla says they have the right to sue anyone who attempts to re-sell a Cyber Truck. Next the guys get into Choice Hotels&amp;rsquo; hostile takeover of Wyndham, and what is the latest with Adam Neumann&amp;rsquo;s latest &amp;lsquo;utopian&amp;rsquo; apartment project.</description></item><item><title>Google Takes a Big L &amp; YouTube Soars Past TikTok | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 11:55:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 211: Neal and Toby talk about Epic Games latest victory against Google that could shift the app market. Next, the economy’s biggest threat doesn’t come from financial institutions, but our geopolitics. Then, will a buyout of Macy’s ultimately mean its demise? Meanwhile, teens spend more time on YouTube than TikTok. Lastly, Apple tries to shut down Android’s only hope for iMessage and Google releases its top trending searches of 2023.</description></item><item><title>Elon Musk Unbans Alex Jones &amp; SmileDirectClub Files for Bankruptcy | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 12:01:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 210: Neal and Kyle recap the weekend with major leadership changes in Argentina and the University of Pennsylvania, both in economical turmoil. Then, Elon Musk brings back Alex Jones on X while SmileDirectClub closes up shop and files for bankruptcy. Next, LA scores BIG with Ohtani’s massive deal with the Dodgers and Lakers winning the In-Season chip. Meanwhile, SantaCon season is here but maybe those charitable dollars aren’t that…charitable.</description></item><item><title>Cameos as Propaganda? &amp; Tech Startups Are Out of Money | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310006/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 11:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 209: Neal and Toby preview what to expect from today&amp;rsquo;s jobs report. Plus, Russia was using celebrity cameos as propaganda and are tech startups really running out of money? The guys share their stock and dog of the week and Krispy Kreme is heading to Paris. And finally, why Pantone says &amp;ldquo;Peach Fuzz&amp;rdquo; is the color of the year for 2024. Listen to Morning Brew Daily Here: https://link.</description></item><item><title>Google's AI Redo to Challenge ChatGPT &amp; The Year of T-Swift | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 11:55:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 208: Neal and Toby explain if Google&amp;rsquo;s new AI &amp;lsquo;Gemini&amp;rsquo; will be able to compete with ChatGPT. Plus McDonald&amp;rsquo;s is making big waves; bringing back the snack wrap and planning to open over 9,000 stores in the coming years. Neal shares his favorite numbers including why Taylor Swift was TIME&amp;rsquo;s person of the year and why Tom Petty&amp;rsquo;s streams are up thanks to GTA 6. Also, women&amp;rsquo;s sports have never been bigger and what are the biggest foods supposed to be for 2024?</description></item><item><title>The NCAA Trust Fund? &amp; Couples Without Kids Are Making Bank | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 11:55:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 207: Neal and Toby explain the letter that NCAA President Charlie Baker sent to schools proposing that a trust fund be established to compensate college athletes. Plus, couples with no kids are raking it in and Israeli regulators did not find trade abnormalities before the Hamas attack on October 7th. CVS is planning to overhaul how much prescription drugs cost and Godzilla is back on the big screen.</description></item><item><title>Spotify Laying Off 17% of Staff &amp; Tesla Losing Their Tax Credits? | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310009/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 11:49:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 206: Neal and Toby explain why Spotify is planning to lay off 17% of their staff following the successful release of Spotify Wrapped. Plus, Bitcoin has never been hotter and why Tesla&amp;rsquo;s cheapest model might be losing its tax credit. Also, Venezuela has approved a referendum to claim territory in oil-rich Guyana and Toby shares his favorite trends. Finally, why newspaper puzzle games might be the new million dollar investment.</description></item><item><title>How the Supreme Court Could Impact Your Taxes &amp; Another Billion $$$ Airline Merger | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 11:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 205: Happy Monday! Neal and Toby are back in the saddle and are explaining how a massive Supreme Court case around the opioid epidemic could change bankruptcy court rulings forever. Plus, why another court case could impact your taxes and Alaska Air has dolled out almost $2 billion to purchase Hawaiian Airlines. The guys share their winners of the weekend and is ChatGPT more efficient if you tip a few dollars?</description></item><item><title>One Year of ChatGPT &amp; Why Most Billionaires Are Now... Nepo Babies | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310011/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 11:50:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 204: Neal and Kyle discuss why the stock market is hotter than ever. Plus, it&amp;rsquo;s the one-year anniversary of ChatGPT and why we are in the era of nepo baby billionaires. Also, a recap of the Cop28 Climate Summit and how much money did Red Lobster lose on their endless shrimp deal? And finally, Forbes shares their Hall of Shame 30 Under 30 list. Listen to Morning Brew Daily Here: https://link.</description></item><item><title>The Cybertruck Is Finally Here &amp; The Marketing Genius of Spotify Wrapped | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 11:46:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 203: Neal and Toby preview Thursday&amp;rsquo;s launch of Tesla&amp;rsquo;s Cybertruck and why it comes at an interesting time for electric vehicles. Plus, why Wall Street is getting behind Nikki Haley and the marketing genius of Spotify Wrapped. Neal shares his favorite numbers and Google is ready to delete the account you haven&amp;rsquo;t touched in years. And, London&amp;rsquo;s Black Cabs are finally available on the Uber app. Listen to Morning Brew Daily Here: https://link.</description></item><item><title>Remembering Berkshire Hathaway's Charlie Munger &amp; The $16 McDonald's Inflation Burger | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310013/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 11:49:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 202: Neal and Toby discuss the death of Charlie Munger and his legacy at Berkshire Hathaway. The guys also get into Mark Cuban&amp;rsquo;s recent moves involving selling the majority of his shares in the Dallas Mavericks and leaving the show &amp;ldquo;Shark Tank&amp;rdquo;. Plus, the $16 McDonald&amp;rsquo;s meal that is sending Americans over the inflationary edge and airlines are looking into sustainable aviation fuel. And finally, Sports Illustrated is accused of using AI writers and the drug that could extend your dog&amp;rsquo;s life.</description></item><item><title>Oil Deals at the Climate Summit? &amp; Finding Love on Duolingo | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310014/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 11:53:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 201: Neal and Toby explain the reports that officials from the UAE are looking to cut oil deals at the COP28 Climate Summit. Plus, Young Thug&amp;rsquo;s racketeering case and Shein files for a US IPO. Toby shares how you can find love on Duolingo or Strava, and why Amazon is becoming the biggest package delivery service in America. And finally, what is the word of the year. Listen to Morning Brew Daily Here: https://link.</description></item><item><title>Online Retail Rakes in Nearly $10B &amp; 3-Year Cruise Called Off Abruptly | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 11:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 200: Neal and Toby go through the winners and losers of the holiday weekend. Online retailers raked in almost $10 billion on Black Friday and United Airlines might be using customer data to create targeted ads. Plus, why US oil production is on fire and college football hasn&amp;rsquo;t been this popular in a long time. Why advertisers are leaving &amp;lsquo;X&amp;rsquo; in droves and the story behind the 3-year long cruise that was abruptly cancelled two weeks before departure.</description></item><item><title>Special Mailbag Episode with Neal and Toby | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 199: Neal and Toby gather questions listeners submitted over the last two weeks. Topics they discuss include the process behind making an episode of Morning Brew Daily, what Neal thinks of American transportation and Toby even shares some relationship advice. Listen to Morning Brew Daily Here: https://link.chtbl.com/MBD Watch Morning Brew Daily Here: https://www.youtube.com/@MorningBrewDailyShow The 2024 Money with Katie Wealth Planner is now live—grab yours at moneywithkatie.com/wealthplanner. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Ex-NFL Star Donovan McNabb Talks the Big Business of Thanksgiving Football | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 198: Former NFL quarterback Donovan McNabb joins Neal and Kyle to discuss why Thanksgiving is such a significant day for football. Donovan reflects on what it was like to play on the holiday as well as his iconic Campbell&amp;rsquo;s Chunky Soup brand deal featuring his mom. Watch out Kelces! He also shares his thoughts on current players building out their own brands with podcasts, and what the international expansion of the National Football League could look like.</description></item><item><title>OpenAI Saga Ends with Sam Altman Returning &amp; Binance Pays Billions in Crypto Plea Deal | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 11:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 197: Neal and Toby break down the timeline of events that led Sam Altman to return to OpenAI as the company&amp;rsquo;s CEO. Plus, why Binance is paying billions in a Crypto plea deal and Kim Kardashian invests in truffle sauce. The guys also preview the NFL and Amazon game on Black Friday and everything else coming up over the long Thanksgiving weekend. Listen to Morning Brew Daily Here: https://link.</description></item><item><title>OpenAI Chaos Continues as Most of Staff Threatens to Quit | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 11:50:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 196: Neal and Toby discuss the latest drama surrounding Sam Altman&amp;rsquo;s departure from OpenAI and why employees are threatening to leave the AI giant if he isn&amp;rsquo;t reinstated as CEO. Plus why the Cruise CEO stepped down and what are the benefits of Argentina adopting the dollar? Toby shares his favorite trends and a clay shortage may be impacting movie productions. And finally, where the Turkeys that are pardoned end up.</description></item><item><title>Microsoft Hires Ousted OpenAI CEO &amp; SpaceX Loses Most Powerful Rocket Ever | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 11:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 195: Neal and Toby break down the weekend drama where OpenAI ousted Sam Altman and then Microsoft swooped in and hired the former CEO in the early hours of Monday morning. Plus, how will Argentina&amp;rsquo;s Presidential election impact the economy and what happened with SpaceX&amp;rsquo;s Starship launch? Formula 1 takes Las Vegas and who were the winners of the weekend. And finally aside from Thanksgiving, here is what we are watching for this week.</description></item><item><title>You Can Buy a Car on Amazon? &amp; SpaceX’s Most Powerful Rocket Ready to Launch | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310021/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 12:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 194: Neal and Kyle break down Hyundai&amp;rsquo;s deal with Amazon to sell cars directly to consumers. Plus, F1 head to Vegas for a pricey race and SpaceX&amp;rsquo;s Starship is ready to launch. The guys share why Boeing is outselling Airbus for the first time since 2017 and how can the USPS stop losing money? George Santos won&amp;rsquo;t seek re-election after being accused of falsely spending campaign money. And finally, why Spotify tattoos may not be worth the investment.</description></item><item><title>TikTok Gets Banned Again &amp; What Are the Best Airports in America? | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 11:54:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 193: Neal and Toby discuss Starbucks workers striking on Red Cup Day and why the UAW deal with GM may be in peril. Plus, Nepal bans TikTok and Warner Bros. may be in trouble with the FTC thanks to Wile E. Coyote. Neal shares his favorite numbers and what are the best airports in America? Finally, how John Oliver influenced the best bird in New Zealand. Listen to Morning Brew Daily Here: https://link.</description></item><item><title>Economic Implications of US-China Meeting &amp; Climate Change Costs $150B a Year | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 11:55:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 192: Neal and Toby discuss the historic meeting between President Biden and Chinese President Xi Jinping in San Francisco and how it will impact the global economy. Plus, inflation is finally cooling and the $150 billion a year cost of climate change. Also, Wall Street bankers&amp;rsquo; bonuses won&amp;rsquo;t be as big and the phone trying to bring iMessage to Android. Finally, the Maine soccer team that won the state title for Lewiston.</description></item><item><title>ESPN Gambles On A Sportsbook &amp; You Need to Earn How Much to Buy a House? | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310024/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 12:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 191: Neal and Toby break down ESPN&amp;rsquo;s launch into the wagering space with ESPN Bet on Tuesday. Plus, a new study was released revealing who is buying homes and how much the typical buyer is making. Also, why there is a shift in international students flocking the US for college and Exxon goes all in on Lithium. Toby shares his favorite trends and how much would you pay for a pet psychic?</description></item><item><title>The Stock Market is on Fire &amp; Marvel is in Crisis | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 11:52:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 190: Neal and Toby explain why the stock market has been on fire lately and what investors are thinking. Plus, the AI pin you can wear that is trying to replace smart phones and why Marvel Studios could be in trouble. The guys share their winners of the weekend (imagine being fired and still getting $77 million) and also why tipflation may be at a tipping point. Finally, what we are watching for this week.</description></item><item><title>We Rated Your Craziest Business Ideas | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310026/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 11:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Neal and Toby pitch the craziest business ideas submitted by listeners to Money With Katie and Tara Reed from &amp;lsquo;BOSSY&amp;rsquo;, and the girls share if they would be IN, or OUT. Listen to BOSSY on Spotify, Apple, watch on YouTube or find it wherever you get your podcasts Listen to Morning Brew Daily Here: https://link.chtbl.com/MBD Watch Morning Brew Daily Here: https://www.youtube.com/@MorningBrewDailyShow Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.</description></item><item><title>Streaming Saves Disney &amp; Video Games Keep Crushing It | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310027/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 11:53:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 188: Neal and Toby discuss why WeWork&amp;rsquo;s bankruptcy could majorly disrupt the commercial real estate market. Plus, the guys share the biggest takeaways from entertainment and video games earnings reports and why Disney may be leaning on streaming to bring in cash. Neal shares his favorite numbers and Google&amp;rsquo;s co-founder&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Airship&amp;rsquo; is ready to take flight. And finally, why the Washington DC Pandas leave the Capitol on a first class flight back to China.</description></item><item><title>Elon is Ready to Put a Chip in Your Brain &amp; YouTube Hates Ad Blockers | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 11:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 187: Neal and Toby explain why Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s brain implant startup was approved to start surgical trials. Plus, how YouTube&amp;rsquo;s problem with ad blockers may violate the EU Law and the spicy book that came out on Ray Dalio&amp;rsquo;s hedge fund &amp;lsquo;Bridgewater&amp;rsquo;. Also why Ram is rolling out a hybrid EV truck and Americans really do love drive-throughs. Finally where in the US is the best place to retire?</description></item><item><title>WeWork Goes Bankrupt &amp; Trump Takes the Stand | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310029/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 11:56:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 186: Neal and Toby discuss the Donald Trump civil fraud case involving his business and property valuations. Plus, WeWork finally files for bankruptcy and Google takes on Epic Games in a second anti-trust lawsuit. Toby shares his favorite trends of the week and Bumble gets a new CEO. Finally, why are there so many celebrity memoirs and what made Barbara Streisand call Tim Cook? Listen to Morning Brew Daily Here: https://link.</description></item><item><title>Elon Musk’s ChatGPT Rival &amp; The Washington Post's $100M Problem | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310030/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 12:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 185: Neal and Toby discuss Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s new AI chatbot, &amp;lsquo;Grok&amp;rsquo; which he says is set to rival ChatGPT and &amp;ldquo;loves sarcasm&amp;rdquo;. Plus, can the Washington Post&amp;rsquo;s new CEO fix the media company&amp;rsquo;s $100 million problem and how teenagers are being deepfaked by AI. The guys share who they think won the weekend and which budgeting app is ending business? Finally, what we are watching for this week.</description></item><item><title>Disgraced Crypto King SBF Convicted of Fraud &amp; $2B Theme Park Merger | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310031/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 10:54:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 184: Neal and Toby discuss disgraced FTX founder Sam Bankman-Fried&amp;rsquo;s conviction that could land him up to 110 years in prison. Plus, the guys share their biggest takeaways from a week of market movement and earnings reports. Who won the stock of the week and who fell to dog of the week? Also, the $2 billion merger bringing two massive theme parks together. And finally, what is the deal with daylight savings time?</description></item><item><title>Microsoft's AI Writes Your Emails &amp; Don't Be Cheap with DoorDash Drivers | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310032/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 10:57:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 183: Neal and Toby discuss the launch of Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s AI program Copilot, and how it can help you write emails. Plus, why Americans aren&amp;rsquo;t confident in the economy despite high employment rates and why offshore wind farms could be in trouble. Neal shares his favorite numbers and if you want your food on time, you better tip your DoorDash driver properly. And finally, why it is Mariah Carey&amp;rsquo;s time to shine.</description></item><item><title>Home Schooling is Big Business &amp; The Perks of Being a Hollywood CEO | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310033/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 10:53:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 182: Neal and Toby explain why home schooling has gotten so big and why millions of dollars have been poured into it. Plus, some fairly big stock movement already this week, who are the biggest risers and fallers? Also, Tesla resolves a lengthy lawsuit and global companies are finding it hard to leave Russia. Finally, what is the true cost of being a Hollywood CEO? Listen to Morning Brew Daily Here: https://link.</description></item><item><title>US Gov't Comes for AI &amp; $18 For A Big Mac? | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310034/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 11:02:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 181: Neal and Toby recap the first-of-its-kind Executive Order by President Biden to create safeguards on AI. Then, McDonald&amp;rsquo;s may have jacked up its prices but their recent earnings show customers are still lovin&amp;rsquo; it. And, the auto industry is back on the road with the latest deal between automakers and the UAW. Next, recent numbers may show that &amp;ldquo;pandemic-era&amp;rdquo; trends are drifting back into pre-pandemic life. Lastly, would you buy a haunted house if it had everything you were looking for?</description></item><item><title>Automakers Are Out on EVs &amp; Kim K Bets on Menswear | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310035/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 180: Neal and Toby recap why the auto industry is becoming less bullish on the EVs and why driverless cars have hit a bump in the road. Then, the latest impacts from the Israel/Hamas war and UAW labor strikes that aren&amp;rsquo;t done. Next, people are packing up and getting out of California and New York, and Boomers are living their best life. Finally, Kim Kardashian is looking to takeover menswear.</description></item><item><title>US Economy Is Exploding &amp; X's Turbulent First Year Under Elon | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310036/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 11:13:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 179: Neal and Toby break down the US Economy&amp;rsquo;s explosive growth in the third quarter and what that could mean moving forward. Plus, Sam Bankman-Fried takes the stand and it&amp;rsquo;s been one year since Elon Musk purchased &amp;lsquo;X&amp;rsquo;, formerly Twitter. What has the last year looked like at the social media company? The guys share the dogs of the week and explain why scientists misjudged Hurricane Otis. Finally, what does the way you sign off a Zoom call say about you?</description></item><item><title>The Auto Strike Is Over? &amp; Boeing's Billion $$$ Air Force One Problem | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310037/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 178: Neal and Toby have the latest on talks between the United Auto Workers Union and Ford that would send employees back to work. Plus, why Boeing has lost billions on Air Force One and Meta&amp;rsquo;s latest earnings. They also run through why AppleTV is raising its prices, SBF getting set to testify and Bud Light striking a deal with UFC. Neal shares his favorite numbers and the guys explain the lawsuit against Panera&amp;rsquo;s caffeinated lemonade.</description></item><item><title>States Go After Meta for Addictive Features &amp; Is Bitcoin Back? | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310038/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 10:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 177: Neal and Toby discuss the lawsuit against Meta where dozens of states are suing the tech company for it&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;addictive features&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;mental harm&amp;rsquo; it has caused children. Plus, Bitcoin is on fire and we are in the full swing of earnings season with reports from Microsoft, Alphabet and Spotify. Hear what Jamie Dimon said about banks and the unrest in the Middle East and why Excel may no longer botch scientific data.</description></item><item><title>Auto Strike Gets Even Bigger &amp; Tinder Lets Your Friends Play Matchmaker | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310039/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 10:54:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 176: Neal and Toby have the latest news surrounding the UAW strike and why workers walked out of a Ram 1500 truck plant. Plus, Bill Ackman doesn&amp;rsquo;t want to bet on bonds and Chevron spends billions in another oil mega deal. The guys also recap stories including the off-duty pilot who tried to take over an Alaska Airlines flight, what happened at a Chinese beer company and the latest lawsuit against Tesla.</description></item><item><title>US Budget Deficit Skyrockets &amp; Amazon Replacing Employees with Robots? | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310040/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 10:53:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 175: Neal and Toby explain how the US budget deficit hit $1.7 trillion as Congress ends their fiscal year. Plus, the guys wrap up the biggest headlines of the weekend, including the fallout between Jon Stewart and Apple and Taylor Swift at the box office. Also, how one museum is connecting Van Gogh and Pokemon cards, and why orange juice is out and apple juice is in. Finally, is the actors strike nearing a breaking point?</description></item><item><title>Americans Are All-In on Owning Stocks &amp; China Concerns Ground Canada Goose | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310041/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 11:09:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 174: Neal and Toby discuss how CEOs and companies are responding to the Israel-Hamas War. Plus, why over half of American households own stock now and how net neutrality may soon be revived. The guys share their stock and dog of the week and also Costco&amp;rsquo;s long-time CEO is stepping down. And finally, what&amp;rsquo;s the deal with GeoGuessr? Listen to Morning Brew Daily Here: https://link.chtbl.com/MBD Watch Morning Brew Daily Here: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Netflix Cashes In on Ads and Password-Sharing Crackdown &amp; AI Lawyer Fail | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310042/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 173: Toby and Neal share their biggest takeaways from Netflix and Tesla earnings. Turns our password sharing restrictions work! Plus, premiums for health insurance have never been higher and why one high profile court case was lost because of an AI lawyer. Neal gets to share his favorite numbers and Toby might even get in on the action. And finally, Meta&amp;rsquo;s new headset hits the streets of San Francisco.</description></item><item><title>Americans LOVE to Spend &amp; Why Broker's Fees Are Going On Trial | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310043/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 10:54:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 172: Neal and Toby explain the significance of President Biden visiting Israel today and what the implications are of the House attempting to elect a speaker. Plus retail rates are up as Americans love to spend and why real estate brokers may be heading to trial for broker&amp;rsquo;s fees. The guys also take a look at Marc Andreessen&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Techno Optimist Manifesto&amp;rdquo; and what is United&amp;rsquo;s new boarding protocol?</description></item><item><title>Home Sales Have Never Been Slower &amp; No One Wants to be an Accountant | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310044/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 10:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 171: Neal and Toby discuss why home sales haven&amp;rsquo;t been this low in a long time. Plus, LinkedIn is cutting more jobs in the latest wave of tech layoffs and why no one wants to be an accountant these days! Toby wants you to get ready with him and how robots might be making your next sweetgreen bowl. And finally which sports are coming to the Olympics. Listen to Our Future Podcast Here: https://link.</description></item><item><title>Why War in Middle East Could Lead To A Global Recession &amp; Rite Aid Goes Bankrupt | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310045/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 12:10:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 170: Neal and Toby discuss how global markets are bracing for impact as tensions rise in the Middle East. Plus, Rite Aid files for bankruptcy in the latest chapter of the drug store crisis and Netflix is pursuing retail. The guys share their winners of the weekend and why are influencers and YouTube stars really into boxing? Finally, a preview of the week ahead. Listen to Morning Brew Daily Here: https://link.</description></item><item><title>Inflation Needs to Chill &amp; How Fake Parts Got In Airplanes | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310046/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 11:19:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 169: Neal and Toby discuss the latest inflation report and how it has impacted markets and mortgage rates. Plus, why the US and Qatar have agreed to stop Iran from accessing $6 billion and how one company was making fake parts that infiltrated airplane fleets. The guys share their stock and dog of the week and TikTok fights a ban in Montana. Finally, what is the Vesuvius Challenge?</description></item><item><title>The $60B Deal Crowning Exxon US Oil King &amp; Birkenstock IPO Flop | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310047/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 10:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 168: Neal and Toby discuss Exxon&amp;rsquo;s $60 billion purchase of Pioneer to become the top oil dog in the US. Plus, why some companies want to blacklist certain college students for hire in the fallout of the Israel-Hamas war and why Birkenstock&amp;rsquo;s stock price tanked after going public. Neal shares his favorite numbers and what brands does Gen Z love the most? And finally, Alaska Airlines is coming out with their own coffee that tastes better in the sky.</description></item><item><title>SBF's Ex-Girlfriend Takes the Stand &amp; California Coming For Your Skittles? | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310048/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 10:54:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 167: Neal and Toby explain how Hamas raised millions in crypto and the role crypto has played in terrorism fundraising. Plus, former Co-CEO of Alameda and Sam Bankman-Fried&amp;rsquo;s ex girlfriend Caroline Ellison takes the stand in the FTX fraud trial. Also, California looks to ban certain food additives and why Ireland is swimming in money. And Home Depot has it&amp;rsquo;s own crime tracker and finally, the billionaire who gave away all his wealth passes away.</description></item><item><title>The Global and Economic Fallout from the Israel-Hamas War &amp; 23andMe Data Breach | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310049/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 10:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 166: Neal and Toby explain what is happening in the war between Israel and Hamas and how the world is reacting to it. Plus, retailers say holiday shopping is already underway and what happened with the 23andMe data breach? Walgreen pharmacists stage a walkout and the men&amp;rsquo;s marathon world record was shattered over the weekend in Chicago. Also, the winner for the Nobel Prize in Economics was announced and Toby explains what &amp;ldquo;coffee badging&amp;rdquo; is and how it is impacting return to office.</description></item><item><title>Bullish or Bearish: The Great Debate | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310050/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 165: Neal and Toby get bullish or bearish on a range of topics, including; is a 4-day work week feasible? What about the future of plant-based meat, and is the global population decline a real problem to be concerned about? Will we see a trillionaire in our lifetime and is higher education worth the cost anymore? Plus, where will San Francisco be in the next 10 years and is AI worth the help in your dating apps.</description></item><item><title>Elon Musk Keeps Getting Sued &amp; How Shrek's Music Can Make You $$$ | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310051/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 10:56:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 164: Toby and Neal explain the lawsuits that Elon Musk has found himself in this week, including ones about his Twitter acquisition and a self-driving car incident. Plus, why almost 20 million cars are being recalled and nearly every Alaskan is getting a $1300 check for oil. The guys also share their stock and dog of the week and Michelin will now be ranking hotels. And finally why this billion $$$ Powerball prize isn&amp;rsquo;t as much as you think.</description></item><item><title>Snacks Are Out, Ozempic is in &amp; Wearable AI | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310052/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 10:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 163: Neal and Toby discuss why investors are shorting snack stocks as Ozempic usage explodes. Plus the guys circle back on a couple of stories that have evolved over the last week, including the biggest healthcare strike in US history and why Maui is welcoming tourists again. The guys also share some startup companies they are keeping an eye on - some even focusing on AI you can wear.</description></item><item><title>MrBeast, Tom Hanks Warn of AI Deepfakes &amp; Why Mortgage Rates Keep Soaring | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310053/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 10:53:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 162: Neal and Toby discuss how record bond sales are the biggest factor in the market right now and are a huge reason mortgage rates have skyrocketed. Plus, celebrities like Tom Hanks and MrBeast are warning people of AI deepfakes as technology advances and why Chicago might do away with tipping. And narrative violation! Millennials are actually financially better off than we would have thought. Oh, and bedbugs are stronger than ever before.</description></item><item><title>The $32B Downfall of FTX &amp; Can Paris Hilton Save 'X'? | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310054/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 10:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 161: Neal and Toby break down the Sam Bankman-Fried and FTX fraud trial that is set to get underway today. How did we get here and what could be in store for the former king of crypto? Plus, the Nobel Prize was awarded to the creators of the mRNA vaccine and &amp;lsquo;X&amp;rsquo; inks a deal with Paris Hilton. Toby shares his favorite trends and why ads on Walgreens coolers ended up in court.</description></item><item><title>Government Avoids a Shutdown &amp; The Largest Healthcare Worker Strike in History | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310055/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 10:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 160: Neal and Toby explain how the government avoided a shut down over the weekend. Plus, a round up of the latest strike news and why we could see the largest healthcare strike in history begin this week. The guys share their winners of the weekend, including a sea lion at the central park zoo and the impact BTS has on the South Korean economy. Finally, the Las Vegas sphere has officially opened and what we are watching this week.</description></item><item><title>Netflix Sends Its Last DVDs &amp; Building The "iPhone of AI" | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310056/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 10:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 159: Happy Friday! Neal and Toby discuss the end of and era, Netflix discontinued its DVD delivery service today. Plus, OpenAI is exploring building the &amp;ldquo;iPhone of artificial intelligence&amp;rsquo;. The guys explain why Costco is the stock of the week (thank you gold bar sales) and why Ryan Cohen can&amp;rsquo;t save GameStop from being the dog of the week. Also, how the global coffee shortage could impact you and the creator of the nutrition label passed away.</description></item><item><title>The Billion $$$ Impact of a Government Shutdown &amp; AI in Your IG and FB Feeds | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310057/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 10:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 158: Neal and Toby discuss how contract workers would be impacted by a possible government shutdown. Plus, Meta brings AI photo editing and chatbots to their social media apps and struggling Peloton strikes a deal with Lululemon. Neal shares his favorite numbers and why are brands so&amp;hellip; online? And how are they trying to make money off of it? And finally why one Vermont town has banned tourists from taking picture of it&amp;rsquo;s foliage.</description></item><item><title>Amazon Sued in Massive Monopoly Case &amp; Victoria's Secret Fashion Hits Streaming | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310058/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 10:58:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 157: Neal and Toby discuss the massive lawsuit where the US government and 17 states are suing Amazon for being too large of a monopoly. Also, a judge rules that Donald Trump defrauded banks and insurers while building out his real estate empire and why New Orleans could enter a drinker water emergency. Also, the guys discuss the rise and fall of Victoria&amp;rsquo;s Secret and why tax payers are shelling out thousands to maintain Russian billionaires&amp;rsquo; yachts.</description></item><item><title>ChatGPT Finds Its Voice While Amazon Invests Billions in AI Rival | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310059/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 10:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 155: Neal and Toby break down the biggest AI news at the top of the show, including; ChatGPT developing the ability to speak and analyze images, Amazon investing $4 billion into Anthropic and Spotify using OpenAI to release podcasts in alternate languages. Plus, how much are auto CEOs making compared to their striking workers? Then Toby shares his favorite trends and the Air Force gets into the taxi biz.</description></item><item><title>How The Writers and Studios Finally Struck A Deal &amp; Tinder Goes Bougie | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310060/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 10:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 154: Kyle Hagge joins the show! Toby and Kyle get into how the Hollywood writers and studios struck a tentative deal over the weekend to end the strike that lasted over 140 days. Plus, why Tinder is offering some users a $499 a month subscription tier, and why Lego is ditching their sustainability promise. The guys also share their winners of the weekend and explain how NASA brought asteroids to Earth.</description></item><item><title>Murdoch 'Succession' Drama's Grand Finale &amp; Florida's Train of the Future? | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310061/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 10:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 153: Neal and Toby discuss Rupert Murdoch stepping down as chair at Fox and handing over power to his son Lachlan. Talk about &amp;lsquo;Succession&amp;rsquo; lore. Plus, they get into the biggest business headlines from a week filled with geopolitical news. And also Florida&amp;rsquo;s new high speed passenger rail line debuts after 11 years in the making. The guys share their stock and dog of the week, and how AI is creating images out of thing air.</description></item><item><title>What Happens If the Government Shuts Down? &amp; Amazon's AI Author Crackdown | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310062/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 11:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 152: Neal and Toby discuss why the government could shut down and what it means for you. Plus the guys discuss Fortnite&amp;rsquo;s $245 million settlement with the FTC and how Amazon is cracking down on AI authors. Neal shares his favorite numbers from the week and here is why celebrities are spending thousands on a full body MRIs. And finally, would you pay $10 million for a Bob Ross painting?</description></item><item><title>Disney's $60B Park Investment &amp; Amazon Bulks Up for the Holidays | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310063/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 11:12:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 151: Neal and Toby discuss why Disney is investing $60 billion over the next ten years into their theme parks. Plus, Amazon and other major retailers are bulking up on staff before the holidays. The guys also explain the latest trend of entrepreneurship through acquisition and how the Senate&amp;rsquo;s new dress code reflects the biggest changes in office culture. And finally, the reason an artist had to repay a museum for his work.</description></item><item><title>The Missing $100M Fighter Jet &amp; College Rankings' Massive Shake Up | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310064/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 12:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 150: Neal and Toby discuss Instacart&amp;rsquo;s IPO on Tuesday at $30 a share which values the company at a cool $10 billion. Plus, the $100 million fighter jet that was temporarily missing and the massive overhaul of the US News &amp;amp; World Report rankings of colleges. Toby explains the trendiest features of iOS17 and the guys get into which streaming service cancels the most shows. Finally, the brand new hotel in Las Vegas that cost almost $4 billion.</description></item><item><title>Why Elon Musk is Winning the UAW Strike &amp; Oil Hits Highest Price In 2023 | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310065/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 149: Toby and Neal have the latest details on the United Auto Workers strike and why it has Elon Musk raking in cash off. Plus, the latest news on talkshows planning to return this fall as the writers&amp;rsquo; and actors&amp;rsquo; strikes continue to freeze Hollywood and why oil is the priciest it has been this year. Also, Deion Sanders and NYC pay transparency have won the weekend. Speaking of winners, who took home the who took home the Ig Nobel Prize Awards?</description></item><item><title>Why Car Buying is About to Get Harder &amp; Delta Loyalty is for the Rich | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310066/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 148: Neal and Toby discuss the UAW strike and its effects across the auto industry and US economy. It looks like Hot Labor Summer goes into the Fall. Next, another big splash in the IPO market that has Wall Street buzzin&amp;rsquo;. Then, a look into why decades of maintenance deferments to Libya&amp;rsquo;s dam could&amp;rsquo;ve prevented one of the most devastating floods in history. Plus, big corporations giveth and taketh: Delta raises the bar for its Sky Lounge and McDonalds says goodbye to soda fountains.</description></item><item><title>Casinos Losing Millions in Minutes &amp; Tech Titans Hit Capitol Hill | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310067/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 147: Neal and Toby chat about the big hack that hit Las Vegas casinos causing millions of loss revenue for multiple days. Then, the Monday Night Letdown for the NY Jets has sparked the debate of whether the NFL should invest in grass fields instead of astroturf to protect their players and the game. Plus, a momentous meeting in Congress between lawmakers and tech leaders to talk about AI and the standards to be set moving forward.</description></item><item><title>iPhone Charging Gets a Makeover &amp; Why Cold Medicines are Useless | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310068/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 11:01:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 146: Neal and Toby list off all the exciting tidbits from Apple&amp;rsquo;s big product event, including the iPhone 15 reveal. Next, how a covid-era government program is affecting poverty rates in America. Plus, quick relief from a cold may be gone as FDA declares a key ingredient in cold medicines ineffective. Then, the UFC &amp;amp; WWE merger debuts at the NYSE and promotions are doing the opposite of what employers want.</description></item><item><title>The Mega Deal Changing Snacking &amp; Elon Musk's 'Demons' | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310069/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 145: Neal and Toby discuss the huge shifts in the packaged foods industry with the latest Smucker&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of Hostess Brands. Will this mean a PB&amp;amp;J Twinkie?? Next, the juiciest parts of Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s biography that paint a more complicated person than we thought. Plus, North Korea&amp;rsquo;s Kim Jong Un&amp;rsquo;s obsession with an armor-plated bulletproof train that has an interior of a cruise ship. Then, a &amp;lsquo;budget Ozempic&amp;rsquo; that might not be as miraculous as the real one.</description></item><item><title>Why the DOJ is Suing Google &amp; IRS Coming For Millionaires | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310070/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 144: Neal and Toby preview a potential hallmark case between Google and the US Justice Department on whether Google&amp;rsquo;s search business empire violates antitrust laws. Then, an unlikely partnership between the US and Vietnam to ween off manufacturing in China. Plus, water is essential to human life&amp;hellip;and artificial intelligence. The guys talk about the environmental impact of hundreds of data centers needed to keep ChatGPT going. Lastly, the biggest winners of the weekend, a US Open recap, and what to watch for this week.</description></item><item><title>Why Apple's Stock Just Tanked &amp; Workers Are Unhappier Than Ever | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310071/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 143: Neal and Toby discuss the reported iPhone ban in China and how it it has plummeted Apple&amp;rsquo;s stock over the last week. Plus, why workers are unhappier than ever and Elon Musk reportedly ordered Starlink to be turned off during the Ukrainian War. The guys also share their stock and dog of the week and how Drake&amp;rsquo;s AI ghost writer is chasing a grammy. Finally, what are the most photographed restaurants on yelp.</description></item><item><title>Are Cars Sharing Your Data? &amp; ABBA's Virtual Avatar Concert Worth Millions | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310072/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 142: Neal and Toby share why experts say cars are the worst at keeping your private data secure. Plus, the Pentagon has plans for AI drones to keep up with China&amp;rsquo;s rapidly expanding military. And the Rolling Stones keep on working and how is ABBA making millions off avatar concerts? Neal shares his favorite numbers and the guys explain why Olive Oil is hard to come by these days.</description></item><item><title>Millions Lose ESPN and ABC In Disney-Spectrum Beef &amp; NYC's Airbnb Crackdown | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310073/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 141: Neal and Toby discuss the fight between Disney and cable provider Charter Spectrum and why ESPN and ABC has been blacked out for millions of people, and what does it mean for the future of cable? Plus, NYC cracks down on Airbnb and video game &amp;lsquo;Starfield&amp;rsquo; finally hits the market after years in the making. Also the guys break down why the German economy is struggling and what CEO makes $379 million a year.</description></item><item><title>Thousands Stranded in the Desert at 'Burning Man' &amp; Jimmy Buffett's 'Margaritaville' Empire | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310074/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 140: Neal and Toby discuss &amp;lsquo;Burning Man&amp;rsquo;, a festival in the Nevada desert beloved by the nation&amp;rsquo;s tech bros and billionaires, and how heavy rains left thousands stranded over the weekend. Plus, why invasive species cost humans over $400 billion a year and the guys take a look at the &amp;lsquo;Margaritaville&amp;rsquo; empire Jimmy Buffett built over the course of his life. Also, the winners of the weekend, the popularity of lab-grown diamonds explodes and what we are watching this week.</description></item><item><title>The Summer of Spending Thanks to Taylor Swift, Beyonce &amp; Barbenheimer | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310075/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 139: Happy Labor Day! Neal and Toby recap the biggest stories of the summer, including how the economy was impacted by Taylor Swift, Beyonce and Barbenheimer. They also explain how the past couple months of extreme weather altered the national and global markets. Plus, the guys quiz each other on which companies did the best and worst, and who said what? Finally predictions for the rest of the year.</description></item><item><title>Inflation Just Won't Quit &amp; Taylor Swift Coming to the Big Screen | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310076/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 11:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 138: Happy almost Labor Day Weekend! Toby and Neal discuss how the Fed is grappling with rising inflation and give a preview of Friday&amp;rsquo;s jobs report. Also, a technology company wants to fix McDonald&amp;rsquo;s ice cream machines and Apple wants customers to fix their own iphones. Plus, Taylor Swift is bringing her Eras Tour to a big screen near you. The guys share their stock and dog of the week and also get into why the US isn&amp;rsquo;t the corn exporting powerhouse it used to be.</description></item><item><title>Hurricane Idalia’s Multibillion $$$ Impact &amp; Narcan Goes Over-The-Counter | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310077/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 137: Neal and Toby explain how Floridians are planning to recover from the multibillion $$$ cost of Hurricane Idalia. Plus, how easing marijuana restrictions would impact the cannabis market and Narcan becomes the first overdose treatment to be sold on drug store shelves. Neal shares his favorite numbers from the week Amazon and Google pair up in a JBL speaker collab. And finally, why people who live in &amp;lsquo;Blue Zones&amp;rsquo; have the highest life expectancy.</description></item><item><title>The 10 Drugs Getting Medicare Price Cuts &amp; Bitcoin's Big Win Over the SEC | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310078/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 136: Neal and Toby discuss which 10 drugs President Biden is looking to slash prices of with his Medicare cost cuts. Plus, Bitcoin is up after a court ruling that sides with Grayscale over the SEC and 3M reaches a $6 billion settlement over earplugs. Also, Eminem takes legal action over Vivek Ramaswamy rapping his music and AI written sports articles about high school football are not nearly as accurate as you think.</description></item><item><title>Are Silicon Valley Elite Building a Utopia? &amp; China's Deal-Making Card Game | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310079/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 135: Neal and Toby discuss the Silicon Valley investors that are putting hundreds of millions of dollars into developing an urban utopia for tech&amp;rsquo;s brightest minds in California. Plus, the World Cup kiss that is turning the Spanish soccer world upside down and the Chinese card game that is beloved by their bankers. Toby shares his favorite trends and Google unveils a new feature that will get you the best deal on your holiday flights.</description></item><item><title>Instacart Checks Out the IPO Market &amp; Why Everyone is Leaving Scooter Braun | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310080/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 134: Neal and Toby discuss why Instacart is filing for an IPO after raking in more than $240 million in the first half of 2023. Plus, UAW workers have authorized a strike at GM, Ford and Stellantis and why are music&amp;rsquo;s biggest stars parting ways with manager Scooter Braun? Also, why has the dwindling demand for French wine cost millions. Finally, the guys share their winners of the weekend and what we are watching this week.</description></item><item><title>Mug Shot Merch Takes Over the Internet &amp; SpaceX Sued by the DOJ | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310081/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 133: Neal and Toby discuss how former President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s mug shot took over the internet on Thursday evening and how Etsy sellers are making money off of the merch. They also explain why the DOJ is suing SpaceX over discriminatory hiring practices and what a weekend in Jackson Hole looks like for the Federal Reserve. Plus, Subway sells to a private equity firm and which companies are the stock and dog of the week.</description></item><item><title>Nvidia Rides AI Boom to Massive Quarter &amp; India's Lunar Landing | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310082/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 132: Neal and Toby start Thursday with a deep dive into Nvidia&amp;rsquo;s earnings report where they raked in billions in the second quarter thanks to their focus on artificial intelligence. They also discuss India&amp;rsquo;s historic moon landing and why Starbucks is betting your next Pumpkin Spice Latte will be iced. Neal shares his favorite numbers and Bored Ape investors sue NFT companies. Finally, Fyre Festival 2 tickets went on sale and almost immediately sold out.</description></item><item><title>Biden's Plan to Help With Student Loans Launches &amp; US Homes are Shrinking | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310083/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 131: Neal and Toby circle back and update some stories Morning Brew Daily has been following the last couple of weeks. Including Biden&amp;rsquo;s plan to help student loan borrowers, Meta is launching &amp;lsquo;Threads&amp;rsquo; on desktop, teamsters ratifying their new deal with UPS, and a South Korea power plant releasing radioactive water. Plus, Ikea goes all in on San Francisco and why America&amp;rsquo;s homes are shrinking despite getting pricer.</description></item><item><title>US Malls Aren't Dead Yet &amp; Americans Want $80k for a New Job | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310084/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 130: Neal and Toby explain why malls in the United States may not be going completely under just yet. Plus, why there is only one car left that costs under $20k and what is the average salary Americans are asking for when applying for new jobs? Also, Toby gets trendy and explains why Gen Z loves pickles and Ozempic is controlling the economy in Denmark. And finally the voice of Mario has called it a career.</description></item><item><title>The Race to the Moon is Back On &amp; Why SF is Slowing It's Roll on Robotaxis | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310085/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 129: Happy Birthday Neal! The guys jump into Monday and discuss the international space race to get back to the moon. They also explain how Meta&amp;rsquo;s news ban in Canada is impacting how people are sharing information on wildfires. Plus, Robotaxis in San Francisco have been getting in too many accidents and the guys get into their winners of the weekend. Finally super market sushi has never been bigger and a preview of the week ahead.</description></item><item><title>Mortgage Rates Skyrocket to 20-Year High &amp; Is Tourism Helping or Hurting Maui? | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310086/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 128: Neal and Toby dive right in and discuss what has sent mortgage rates to the highest they have been in over 20 years and how US Treasury Yields are closing in on a 16-year high. They also discuss the debate in Hawaii of whether tourism could help or hurt Maui as the island recovers from devastating wild fires. Also, if you&amp;rsquo;re investing your 401k properly you could be a millionaire by the time retirement comes around.</description></item><item><title>Target Struggles To Recover from Pride Backlash &amp; Is Food Delivery Dead? | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310087/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 127: Neal and Toby discuss Target&amp;rsquo;s latest earnings report and explain why the retailer struggled last quarter. Also, record labels are not producing pop stars like they used to and people are heading to restaurants more and more to pick up their own food. Neal shares his favorite numbers and global wealth rises while inequality falls. And would you buy a&amp;hellip; pink pineapple? Listen to Morning Brew Daily Here: https://link.</description></item><item><title>Is the Inflation Reduction Act Working? &amp; Why Warren Buffett is All In On the US Housing Market | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310088/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 126: It&amp;rsquo;s been a year since the Inflation Reduction Act has passed, and Neal and Toby discuss exactly what the bill has done with billions of investments into clean energy and jobs, and and what it is still expected to do. Plus, Argentina&amp;rsquo;s insane interest rates and why Warren Buffett is going all in on the US housing market. Also, the makers of Bazooka bubblegum and the underwear brand &amp;lsquo;Parade&amp;rsquo; were purchased for hundreds of millions of dollars.</description></item><item><title>Trump Indicted for 4th Time &amp; 'Blind Side' Star Says Story Was a Lie | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310089/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 125: Neal and Toby break down the details of former President Donald Trump being indicted for the fourth time in Georgia on Monday night. The guys also discuss Michael Oher&amp;rsquo;s petition that he was not compensated for his life story that was portrayed in the movie &amp;lsquo;The Blind Side&amp;rsquo;. Plus, the historic climate case win for kids in Montana and children in Illinois can now make money off influencer deals.</description></item><item><title>Hawaiian Wildfires Could Cost $10 Billion &amp; Does America Have Bad Sunscreen? | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310090/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 124: Neal and Toby discuss the Hawaiian wildfires and the billions of dollars it will cost the economy to recover from the disaster. They also explain why America has poor quality sunscreen compared to the rest of the world and a how a totaled Tesla came back online in&amp;hellip; the Ukraine? Plus, the winners of the weekend and a deep dive into the Iowa State Fair. And finally, a look ahead at what we are watching this week.</description></item><item><title>The iPhone Feature Saving Lives in Maui Wildfires &amp; Coach Owner buys Versace Parent Company for $8.5B | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310091/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 123: Kyle Hagge joins the show! Kyle and Toby discuss the wildfires in Maui and how an iPhone feature has been saving the lives of people without cell phone service. Plus, the parent company Coach strikes a deal to purchase Michael Kors and Versace for $8.5 billion. And surprise, Manhattan rent has hit a new record&amp;hellip; again. The guys also get into the latest inflation report and stock and dog of the week.</description></item><item><title>Disney Hikes Streaming Prices 27% &amp; Why Jeopardy Is Recycling Answers | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310092/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 122: Neal and Toby discuss the writer&amp;rsquo;s strike hitting 100 days and why Jeopardy is recycling answers. Plus, Bob Iger tries to right the Disney ship by increasing streaming prices and hinting at a password crackdown in the company&amp;rsquo;s latest earnings call. Also, what China slipping into deflation could mean for the global economy and Neal shares his favorite numbers from the week. Finally, the first mother and daughter duo are set to launch into space.</description></item><item><title>Penn and ESPN Gamble on New Partnership &amp; Credit Card Debt Soars Over $1 Trillion | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310093/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 121: Neal and Toby discuss ESPN&amp;rsquo;s $2 billion deal with Penn Entertainment to launch a betting app. The guys also get into why Penn sold Barstool Sports back to Dave Portnoy and just exactly what the details of that agreement look like. Plus, for the first time ever credit card debt in the US tops $1 trillion and the weight-loss drug that can also stop heart attacks. Also, how one Jersey show town is fighting back against wind turbines and what the future of WeWork looks like.</description></item><item><title>PayPal Enters Crypto Game with New Stablecoin &amp; Warren Buffett is Crushing It Right Now | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310094/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 120: Neal and Toby explain why Paypal is entering the Stablecoin game and what that could mean for their crypto business. Plus, Berkshire Hathaway shares have never been higher and LA workers are preparing for a strike that could highly impact the city. Also, Campbell&amp;rsquo;s Soup acquires Rao&amp;rsquo;s for $2.7 billion and Paramount sells Simon &amp;amp; Schuster to a private equity firm. Toby shares his favorite trends and why big oil having trouble attracting young talent.</description></item><item><title>The Billion $$$ NCAA Shakeup &amp; Zoom Says Remote Work is Dead | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310095/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 119: Neal and Toby are back from the weekend and are breaking down the college conference realignment that is costing millions in television deals. Plus, remote work is officially dead as Zoom wants workers to return to office. &amp;lsquo;X&amp;rsquo; is once again making headlines commandeering account handles and Mark Zuckerberg has his doubts on whether the platform can handle the stream of a cage match against Elon Musk.</description></item><item><title>Apple Sales in a Major Slump &amp; Your AI Dating Wingman | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310096/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 118: Neal and Toby celebrate Friday by diving into Apple and Amazon earnings reports, including Amazon&amp;rsquo;s blowout profit and why Apple is struggling with sales&amp;hellip; But customers have over $10 billion deposited in their savings accounts. Plus, why gas prices are the highest they have been this year and why Airlines want you to travel domestically. Also the guys share their stock and dog of the week and how AI can help you write your dating profile.</description></item><item><title>Economists Scrap Recession Forecasts &amp; Amazon's Grocery Store Overhaul | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310097/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 117: Neal and Toby discuss Bank of America economists scrapping their recession forecast and what it could mean on a larger scale. The guys also get into why Amazon is overhauling their grocery stores and how drug makers are navigating the Adderall and Penicillin shortage. Neal shares his favorite numbers, including statistics that explain why married people are happier. Plus, the billion dollar sports memorabilia business and how NASA lost a space craft almost 13 billion lightyears away.</description></item><item><title>US Debt Rating Gets Downgraded &amp; How Uber Is Finally Making Money | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310098/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 116: Neal and Toby discuss Fitch downgrading the US debt rating from AAA to AA+, citing how close Congress was to defaulting on the debt ceiling as well as the insurrection. The guys also go through their biggest takeaways from yesterday&amp;rsquo;s earnings reports and get into how Uber is finally making money. Plus, which independent film has raked in more money than Mission Impossible and MrBeast is taking legal action against the company making his burgers.</description></item><item><title>Biden's Plan for $0 Student Loan Payments &amp; How A.I. is Shaping the Future of Warfare | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310099/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 115: Neal and Toby discuss President Biden&amp;rsquo;s new student loan plan that could cost borrowers&amp;hellip; $0 a month? Plus, the first ever Nuclear reactor that was built from scratch and how it went $31 billion over budget. And Palantir stock has never been hotter and the guys get into how the AI company is shaping the warfare landscape. Also, Birkenstocks plan for IPO and Toby explains how to play Pokemon Sleep.</description></item><item><title>Facebook's $20 Million Algorithm Study &amp; Why Some Credit Card Companies Hate Marijuana | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310100/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 114: Neal and Kyle discuss the research published over the weekend that says Facebook algorithms are not responsible for political polarization. which comes on the tails of Meta&amp;rsquo;s strong earnings report last week. Also, Mastercard says you can&amp;rsquo;t use their debit cards to make cannabis purchases. And why even a $700 million bailout could not save the trucking giant &amp;lsquo;Yellow&amp;rsquo;. The guys also share their winners and losers of the weekend and explain why the &amp;lsquo;X&amp;rsquo; logo in San Francisco may be in line with some permit violations.</description></item><item><title>July Set to be the Hottest Month Ever, Grimace Helps McDonald's Soar &amp; What's a 'Lazy Girl Job'? | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310101/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 113: Neal and Kyle explain why this July is set to be the hottest month in Earth&amp;rsquo;s history and what the economic fallout is from the sky high temperatures. Plus, McDonald&amp;rsquo;s Grimace campaign sends the company to new heights, and what is the stock and dog of the week? Also why are adults in China being paid to be &amp;lsquo;full-time&amp;rsquo; children and what is a &amp;rsquo;lazy girl job?</description></item><item><title>Fed Hikes Interest Rates to 22-Year High &amp; Automakers Unite To Build EV Charging Network | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310102/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 112: Neal and Toby discuss the Federal Reserve&amp;rsquo;s decision to approve a hike in interest rates to combat inflation that brought them to 5.25-5.5%, which is the highest in 22 years. The guys also recap the Congressional UFO hearing and explain why automakers are banning together to build a electric vehicle charging network to compete with Tesla&amp;rsquo;s. Plus, why one British billionaire was charged with insider trading and Neal shares his favorite numbers.</description></item><item><title>Microsoft and Alphabet Ready to Spend Big on AI &amp; Parents Dropping $4k on Sorority Consultants? | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310103/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 111: Neal and Toby dive into the earnings reports from Microsoft and Alphabet and explain why big tech is ready to spend big on AI. Also, UPS Workers agree on a deal worth $30 billion to avoid a strike. And why did Twitter&amp;rsquo;s rebrand to &amp;lsquo;X&amp;rsquo; cost the company almost $20 billion in brand value? And how the UN is stepping in to stop a massive oil spill from a decaying tanker.</description></item><item><title>Sam Altman Launches 'Worldcoin', Who College Admissions Are Snubbing &amp; Neopets' New Era | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310104/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 110: Neal and Toby discuss Sam Altman&amp;rsquo;s newest crypto project that requires users to verify their identity by scanning their eyeballs. Plus, the guys break down new research that shows why the wealthiest are much more likely to be admitted to the nation&amp;rsquo;s top colleges. Also, an update on the strikes going on in Israel and why Neopets are finally making a comeback. Finally, why Spotify is upping their price and which soccer superstar is being offered a 1-year deal for&amp;hellip; a billion dollars.</description></item><item><title>Twitter Rebrands to 'X' and 'Barbenheimer' Makes $230+ Million On Opening Weekend | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310105/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 109: Neal and Toby explain why Elon Musk has decided to rebrand Twitter as, &amp;lsquo;X&amp;rsquo;. Plus it looks like &amp;lsquo;Barbenheimer&amp;rsquo; surpassed expectations after making history at the box office, raking in over $230 million. Also, how power grids across the country are holding up against record hot temperatures and who won the weekend? Finally, what to expect from the Nasdaq rebalance and what Neal and Toby are watching this week.</description></item><item><title>How 'Barbenheimer' Can Save The Box Office &amp; Kim Kardashian's 'Skims' Worth $4 Billion | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310106/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 108: Kelsey Sutton joins the show! Kelsey is the Deputy Editor of Marketing Brew and lends her expertise as she and Neal break down all of the hype surrounding the opening weekend for blockbusters &amp;lsquo;Barbie&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Oppenheimer&amp;rsquo;. Plus, Kim Kardashian&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Skims&amp;rsquo; valued at a whopping $4 billion, stocks of the week, and how one family won a $800,000 lawsuit over&amp;hellip; chicken nuggets? Listen to Morning Brew Daily Here: https://link.</description></item><item><title>Tesla Posts Record Q2 Revenue, Goldman Sachs Struggles &amp; Wesleyan Ends Legacy Admissions | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310107/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 107: Neal and Toby discuss the biggest earnings reports from Wednesday, including Tesla&amp;rsquo;s record Q2 revenue, Netflix&amp;rsquo;s major growth in subscribers and Goldman Sachs drop in profits. Also the guys explain why the President of FIFA is asking people in New Zealand to buy tickets to the World Cup. Neal shares his favorite numbers and Wesleyan University has stopped accepting legacy admissions. Finally the latest TikTok trend that is making some creators almost $7,000 a day.</description></item><item><title>Record Heat Hits Europe, SAG-AFTRA Takes on Influencers &amp; Apple Maps is Good Now? | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310108/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 106: Toby and Neal discuss the record temperatures over in Europe during peak travel season. Plus, how could influencers take advantage of the SAG-AFTRA strike in Hollywood and Meta introduces Llama 2 for commercial use while Microsoft is offering a $30 subscription to incorporate AI into Microsoft 365. And why SHEIN is in the midst of a Rico lawsuit and what parallels that has with&amp;hellip; the mafia? Finally what is the workday dead zone and apparently Apple Maps is the new wave.</description></item><item><title>Americans Finally Have Money in the Bank &amp; Promising New Alzheimer's Drug | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310109/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 105: Neal and Toby explain why Americans currently have the most cash in the bank since before the pandemic. Plus, why wages are finally starting to outpace inflation but for Europeans, the story isn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily the same. Meanwhile Eli Lilly&amp;rsquo;s Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s drug that could change the game waits for FDA approval and why a typo sent millions of US Military emails to the wrong country. Toby explains why an aging filter on TikTok is going viral, and also, how passengers are &amp;lsquo;skiplagging&amp;rsquo; to take advantage of airlines pricey travel.</description></item><item><title>DeSantis Burning Through Cash, Actor and UPS Strikes Could Cost Billions, &amp; Tesla Cybertruck is Here | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310110/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 11:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 104: Neal and Toby explain how Ron DeSantis spend $7.9 million in his first six weeks of his Presidential campaign and how other candidates are spending and fundraising comparatively. Plus, why the actor and UPS strikes could cost billions, and after two long years Tesla&amp;rsquo;s Cybertruck is finally here. Also, United pilots get paid and Lionel Messi loves Publix. The guys also want to wish a happy &amp;lsquo;World Emoji Day&amp;rsquo; to you and yours and they take a look ahead to what we are watching this week.</description></item><item><title>FTC Investigates OpenAI, Birth Control Finally Available Over The Counter &amp; Bob Iger Goes Off | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310111/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 103: Kyle Hagge joins the show! Kyle and Toby discuss all of the headlines swirling around the FTC right now; including their investigation of OpenAI, the clash between Chair Lina Khan and Congress and why Twitter is asking a federal court to drop a settlement from 2022. Plus, for the first time birth control will be available over the counter - what does this mean for insurance companies?</description></item><item><title>Hollywood Actors Set To Strike &amp; Good Inflation News Sends Markets Soaring | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310112/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 102: Neal and Toby discuss why writers and actors in Hollywood could be striking at the same time for the first time in over 60 years. Plus wages are finally rising faster than inflation as it falls to 3%, and Domino&amp;rsquo;s and Uber Eats are partnering to change the pizza game. Then Neal shares his favorite numbers, which includes Burger King Thailand&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Real Cheeseburger&amp;rsquo; which is just&amp;hellip; 20 slices of cheese.</description></item><item><title>Microsoft-Activision Deal Complete &amp; Bank of America Opens Fake Accounts | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310113/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 101: Neal and Toby discuss a judge ruling that Microsoft can complete its $69 billion deal to purchase Activision Blizzard despite an injunction from the FTC. Plus, historic flooding in the Northeast that is costing billions and Bank of America is on the hook for $250 million after opening fake accounts and charging customers illegal junk fees. And what is Anthropocene? And why can we only talk about it every 13,000 years?</description></item><item><title>Fed Rolls Out Instant Payment System &amp; The Battle for Aretha's $18M Estate | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310114/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 100: Happy 100th episode! Neal and Toby celebrate by explaining what the Federal Reserve&amp;rsquo;s new instant payment service is and how it could impact you. Plus, why there is a sea salt shortage in South Korea as people are preparing for Japan&amp;rsquo;s release of treated radioactive water. The guys also discuss the drama surrounding Aretha Franklin&amp;rsquo;s handwritten wills and why her sons are heading to court. And Disney hasn&amp;rsquo;t been this empty in a long time - the guys explain why executives aren&amp;rsquo;t surprised the Mouse isn&amp;rsquo;t pulling in visitors this summer.</description></item><item><title>San Francisco's Robotaxi Problem &amp; The FDA vs. Logan Paul's Prime Energy | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310115/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 11:16:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 99: Neal and Toby explain why safe street activists in San Francisco are disabling robotaxis with traffic cones. Plus, the telecom companies that have left behind a network of toxic lead cables strewn across America and Senators call for the FDA to investigate Logan Paul&amp;rsquo;s Prime Energy Drink because it has the caffeine equivalent of&amp;hellip; Eight Coca-Colas!? Then the guys share their winners of the weekend and explain why the NBA is adopting a midseason tournament.</description></item><item><title>Twitter Fires Back at Meta &amp; US Labor Market is Sizzling | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310116/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 98: It seems like everywhere you look, people are talking about Threads. Luckily, Neal and Toby are here to break it all down and talk about the biggest moments since its launch. Plus, early data shows the US labor market is strong and thriving. So then why is Wall Street backing away? Then, Las Vegas unveils its roundest entertainment center — a 366-foot-tall LED sphere. Meanwhile, the heat is getting turned up on the celebrities tied up in the FTX collapse saga.</description></item><item><title>Regulating AI Hiring &amp; Auto Sales Make A Comeback | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310117/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 97: Neal and Toby discuss the latest legal troubles for AI and whether ChatGPT&amp;rsquo;s first decline in growth is a telling sign. Plus, the US auto industry is alive &amp;amp; well with soaring sales from major automakers, which could be a turning point for the economy. Then, a look at why retirees are investing into the stock market as if they&amp;rsquo;re millennials, why Gen-Z is taking over golf, and what 3 straight record-breaking hot days could mean for the Winter.</description></item><item><title>Meta Launching Twitter Rival Threads &amp; US and China’s Semiconductor War | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310118/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310118/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 96: Neal and Toby are back after a refreshing long weekend with lots of news to get to! Meta is coming for Twitter as it&amp;rsquo;s set to launch Threads on Thursday but is it innovative enough to take down the already struggling social outlet? Plus, a judge ordered President Biden and his administration to limit contact with social media companies as the US is wrapped up in a tit-for-tat battle with China over semiconductors and solar panels.</description></item><item><title>Business Building with Alex Lieberman | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310119/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 95: On this special holiday edition of Morning Brew Daily, Neal and Toby sit down with Morning Brew Co-Founder Alex Lieberman. The guys discuss Alex&amp;rsquo;s journey in building the Brew with now CEO Austin Rief while they were both in college at Michigan and why Alex almost didn&amp;rsquo;t hire Neal as MB&amp;rsquo;s third ever full-time employee. Alex also explains how his mental health took a hit when he shifted from CEO to Executive Chairman in 2021 and how he has navigated a shift in responsibilities over the last few years.</description></item><item><title>Get to Know Good Work's Dan Toomey | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310120/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310120/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 94: Neal and Toby chat with the face of Morning Brew&amp;rsquo;s social media, Dan Toomey, on this special Holiday edition of Morning Brew Daily. Dan recently launched his own franchise called &amp;lsquo;Good Work&amp;rsquo; after having been with Morning Brew for the past few years. Dan discusses how how he arrived at MB, how he manages his mental health as a creator, his future aspirations and even what his go-to Dunkin Donuts order is.</description></item><item><title>Is Diet Coke Dangerous? &amp; US Supreme Court Bans Affirmative Action | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310121/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 93: Neal and Toby unpack the momentous Supreme Court decision to reject the consideration of race in university admissions. Then, a leaked report shows a common artificial sweetener used in sugar-free products could be carcinogenic to humans. Plus, Virgin Galactic launches it&amp;rsquo;s first commercial flight into space while the spotlight is on extreme tourism. Also, the 80s are cool again. Not the decade, but the age. Why 80 year olds are choosing to work vs.</description></item><item><title>Shein Influencers Catch Backlash &amp; Why Air Travel Is So Bad | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310122/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310122/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 92: Neal and Toby cover the multiple reasons why air travel this Summer is in shambles and continues to struggle. Plus, a trip to China goes horribly wrong as social media unleashes its fury towards the traveling Shein influencers. Also, Costco takes a page out of Netflix&amp;rsquo;s playbook and starts cracking down on shoppers sharing membership cards, and is Airbnb on its way towards a collapse? The numbers may surprise you.</description></item><item><title>Lordstown Motors Goes Bankrupt &amp; Why is 'Barbie' Everywhere Right Now?! | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310123/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310123/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 91: Neal and Toby explain why Lordstown Motors has filed for bankruptcy and is suing Foxconn for $170 million. Plus, how the &amp;lsquo;Barbie&amp;rsquo; marketing team has taken over the world with a sea of pink and product collabs. Also, Ryan Seacrest is your new host of &amp;lsquo;Wheel of Fortune&amp;rsquo; after Pat Sajack steps down following more than four decades on the show, and which company is offering interns $120 an hour.</description></item><item><title>Cities Charging for Traffic &amp; Wall Street Loves Weight Loss | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310124/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 90: Neal and Toby break down New York City&amp;rsquo;s adoption of a congestion toll that would charge vehicles for driving in Manhattan, and why it could be setting a precedent for other cities around the country. They also explain why a possible weight-loss pill from Eli Lily has investors on Wall Street salivating. Plus, SCOTUS hears a case that could block plans to tax the rich. Toby gets trendy and explains why Gen-Z loves cottage cheese and why insurance companies are not pickleball fans.</description></item><item><title>Russian Turmoil's Impact On The Global Economy &amp; The Fruit States Crop Crisis | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310125/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 89: Neal and Toby explain what is going on in Russia; who is the Wagner Group and how has the civil unrest in Moscow impacted the global economy? They also break down the not-so-peachy crop crisis happening in Florida and Georgia and why wild weather is to blame and did you know that Elton John has the highest-grossing tour of all-time!? Plus, Congress is proposing a decrease in training hours for commercial pilots to combat the national pilot shortage.</description></item><item><title>'Catastrophic Implosion' Destroys Titanic Sub &amp; Why Global Inflation Keeps Rising | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310126/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 88: Neal and Toby have the latest on the &amp;lsquo;catastrophic implosion&amp;rsquo; that destroyed the Titan submersible. They also explain why inflation rates continue to rise around the world and how Overstock.com would find any value in purchasing Bed Bath &amp;amp; Beyond&amp;rsquo;s IP for over $20 million. Plus, why Dominoes is up and Disney is down. And following last night&amp;rsquo;s NBA Draft, European athletes are having their moment in major American sports.</description></item><item><title>Zuck and Elon Want to Brawl? &amp; Amazon Sued for Duping Prime Customers | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310127/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 87: Did you hear? Mark Zuckerberg has challenged Elon Musk to a cage match brawl. Neal and Toby place their bets. Plus, the FTC sues Amazon over tricking millions of customers into subscribing to Prime. Also, the Prime Minister of India, Narendra Modi, visits the US and meets with President Biden and other top business leaders. And finally why Lab-Grown meat is now FDA approved and how DC bars got approval to stay open for 24 hours this summer.</description></item><item><title>The Missing Titanic Sub Latest, Homebuilding Soars, Student Loan Payments Resume | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310128/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310128/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 86: Toby is back! The guys dive into the search for the missing submersible en route to explore the Titanic shipwreck. They have the latest on &amp;lsquo;banging&amp;rsquo; heard in the ocean and discuss a 2018 lawsuit against the company OceanGate Expeditions. Plus, why there is a boom in homebuilding and how it has impacted the housing nation-wide shortage. Oh, and if you haven&amp;rsquo;t heard - student loan payments are officially set to restart in the fall.</description></item><item><title>Canada's Population Advantage, UPS Workers Authorize Strike &amp; Missing Titanic Submersible | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310129/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310129/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 85: Neal and Kyle get right back into the swing of things after the long weekend and discuss how Canada&amp;rsquo;s population explosion has kept them in the race for labor. Plus, why UPS workers have voted to strike and how could it impact your packages. Also, a submersible on an expedition to see the Titanic shipwreck has gone missing in a remote part of the Atlantic Ocean, and rescuers are on a time crunch to help the five people aboard.</description></item><item><title>'Money With Katie' Gives Personal Finance Tips | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310130/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310130/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 84: On this episode of Morning Brew Daily, Katie Gatti Tassin from &amp;lsquo;Money With Katie&amp;rsquo; joins the show and reflects on her journey as a personal finance creator. She also shares her best personal finance advice with Neal and Toby. Her wisdom includes:
How to pick a high-yield savings account
Is it possible to be saving too much?
What is the best credit card for you?
Is it more important to invest or save?</description></item><item><title>Cava Crushes In IPO, Has Pixar Lost It's Fastball? &amp; Ticketmaster Gets Honest | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310131/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 83: Not Toby set his alarm extra early and has made his return. Welcome back Kyle Hagge! He and Neal get into Cava&amp;rsquo;s monstrous IPO debut after their stock doubled on Thursday. Plus, with Pixar&amp;rsquo;s newest movie &amp;ldquo;Elemental&amp;rdquo; coming out, can the studio recover from some of their recent struggles? And President Biden makes Ticketmaster get honest with fees and the guys share their stock and dog of the week.</description></item><item><title>Fed Finally Pauses Rate Hikes &amp; AI is Coming for Doctors and Lawyers | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310132/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310132/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 82: Toby got up extra early in the Pacific North West coast to join us this morning! We are bi-coastal baby. The guys break down the Federal Reserve finally pausing rate hikes and what it could mean for you. Plus, there&amp;rsquo;s a new top beer in the US and which labor sector will be most impacted by AI in the year 2027? Senators are probing the deal between LIV and the PGA and Neal shares his favorite numbers.</description></item><item><title>Inflation Rate At Two-Year Low, San Francisco's Retail Exodus &amp; Instant Pot Goes Bankrupt | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310133/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 81: Neal and Toby take a look at the CPI Data and explain why the inflation rate is at the lowest it&amp;rsquo;s been in two years and what that means for you, and eggs. Plus, the retail exodus from San Francisco and the maker of Instant Pot has filed for Chapter 11. Also, how one four week old AI startup raised over $110 million and Paul McCartney explains why AI could give us one more never before heard Beatles song.</description></item><item><title>S&amp;P 500 Hits New Highs &amp; Gig Workers Get a Raise | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310134/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 80: Neal and Toby explain why the S&amp;amp;P 500 is absolutely ripping, as it jumps to it&amp;rsquo;s highest level in over a year. Plus, how the youths in Montana are taking charge in the climate change crisis and food delivery workers in New York City just got a raise. Is London the new crypto hub? And finally the pasta protests that have Italy sauced up. Listen Here: https://link.</description></item><item><title>Reddit Goes Dark &amp; Netflix Password Sharing Lockdown Skyrockets Subscribers | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310135/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 79: Neal and Toby explain the drama that has led thousands of Subreddits to go dark on Monday. Plus, how the collapse of a portion of 95 in Philadelphia impacts travel and business and how Netflix subscriber numbers have skyrocketed after their password sharing lockdown. Also, which billionaire has handed over his empire to his son? Finally, why this person spent 100 days under water and what we are watching for this week.</description></item><item><title>GM Joins Tesla's Charging Network &amp; It Costs How Much to Climb Everest?! | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310136/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310136/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 78: Neal and Toby discuss why GM is adapting their electric vehicles to be able to use Tesla Superchargers and what it means for EV industry standards. Plus N95 masks are in everyone&amp;rsquo;s Amazon carts and why Carvana shares are up and Gamestop fired their CEO. They also get into the money required to climb Mt. Everest and why one man is under fire for thanking his sponsors and not the sherpa who saves his life.</description></item><item><title>Wildfire Smoke Stuns Northeast &amp; Apple and Adidas Bring Messi to MLS | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310137/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 77: Neal and Toby discuss the economic fallout from the Canadian wildfire smoke that has stunted the Northeast the past two days. They also break down soccer superstar Lionel Messi&amp;rsquo;s historic deal with MLS team Inter Miami how Apple and Adidas share deals factored into his arrival to the US. Plus, why Martha Stewart says everyone should return to the office. Neal shares his favorite numbers from the week and there&amp;rsquo;s a mystery person in Ohio who has found themselves in a sh**** situation.</description></item><item><title>Stunning Billion $$$ Golf Merger, Alien Whistleblower &amp; Obsession with Succession | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310138/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310138/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 76: Neal and Toby discuss the historic billion dollar golf merger between LIV and the PGA that seemingly came out of nowhere on Thursday. How did it happen and what does it mean for the sport and Saudi Arabia&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;sportswashing&amp;rsquo;? Also, they rip through headlines you should know including why 100 million people were impacted by poor air quality along the east coast and why the SEC is going after Coinbase.</description></item><item><title>Apple Unveils 'Vision Pro' Headset &amp; Twitter's New CEO Takes Over | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310139/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 75: Neal and Toby take a look at Apple&amp;rsquo;s new &amp;lsquo;Vision Pro&amp;rsquo; mixed reality headset and explain why the product is so significant for the company. They also dive into the SEC&amp;rsquo;s lawsuit against Binance and what to expect from Linda Yaccarino as she takes over Twitter CEO from Elon Musk. Plus, Toby attempts to explain to Neal why &amp;lsquo;beige flags&amp;rsquo; are trending on TikTok and would you spend $43k on a tiny home from Home Depot?</description></item><item><title>Oil Prices Rise On Saudi Cuts &amp; 'Barbie' Movie Global Pink Shortage | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310140/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310140/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 74: Neal and Toby explain why Saudi Arabia is cutting 1 million barrels of oil a day in a deal with OPEC and what it could mean for gas prices for this summer travel season. They delve into a Hollywood business news roundup from the weekend; including a new deal between directors and and studios and Christopher Nolan&amp;rsquo;s case for seeing &amp;lsquo;Oppenheimer&amp;rsquo; in IMAX. Plus the &amp;lsquo;Barbie&amp;rsquo; movie was so pink, it caused an international paint shortage.</description></item><item><title>Is The Great Resignation Over?, Meta's New VR Headset, &amp; The War on Big Dairy | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310141/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 73: Neal and Toby discuss why the latest labor data indicates that &amp;lsquo;The Great Resignation&amp;rsquo; might be over. They also break down Meta&amp;rsquo;s new VR headset and why the company is using all their firepower to take on Apple in the race to be top dog in the virtual reality space. Plus did Aubrey Plaza&amp;rsquo;s ad for big dairy violate a federal law? And what stock absolutely collapsed this week vs why big tech is dominating the market right now.</description></item><item><title>Bud Light Out as Top US Beer? &amp; How The Debt Ceiling Deal Impacts You | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310142/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310142/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 72: Neal and Toby discuss how a almost 30% drop in Bud Light sales revenue may dethrone the beer as the US&amp;rsquo;s top brew. Who is hot on their heels? Plus, what is actually in the Debt Ceiling Deal and how will it impact you and the economy. Also, why the National Eating Disorder Association phased out their chatbot and which airline is weighing passengers before getting on planes.</description></item><item><title>Nvidia Joins The Trillion $$$ Club &amp; AI Researchers Warn Against 'Risk of Extinction' | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310143/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 12:32:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310143/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 71: Neal and Toby are up to break down the biggest headlines ahead of your morning commute! They discuss tech company Nvidia becoming a part of the exclusive trillion dollar market cap club. They also get into why AI researchers are warning against a &amp;lsquo;risk of extinction&amp;rsquo;. Plus Theranos founder Elizabeth Holmes finally reports to prison and Toby explains why smelling good is trendy. And have you ever thought about renting someone&amp;rsquo;s backyard pool for a little summer soiree?</description></item><item><title>Debt Ceiling Deal, Losing $1B in Blackjack &amp; The Biz of TSwift | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310144/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310144/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 70: Toby and Neal break down the Debt Ceiling Deal that came together over the weekend. They also take a look at a lawyer who had to apologize for using ChatGPT in a lawsuit and why State Farm won&amp;rsquo;t insure homes in California anymore. Plus, how blackjack players lost $1 billion in Vegas last year. And Neal and Toby are Swifties? They give a full recap of their experience at The Eras Tour.</description></item><item><title>Memorial Day Special: Get to Know Toby and Neal | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310145/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310145/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 69: On this Memorial Day Special episode of Morning Brew Daily, Toby and Neal take a moment to get to interview one another about their pasts. They discuss where they went to college and their Morning Brew origin stories. Did you know that Toby was the captain of the soccer team at Brown and almost went pro? And that Neal almost wasn&amp;rsquo;t hired by Morning Brew? The discuss all of that and more.</description></item><item><title>Neuralink Approved for Human Trials, A Game of Shaq &amp; Mouse, &amp; Starbucks' Cold War | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310146/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310146/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 68: Neal &amp;amp; Toby chat about Elon Musk’s brain implant company receiving FDA approval for human trials. Would you volunteer to go under the knife for Neuralink? Then, after eluding process servers for months, Shaq gets served during an NBA game at the former FTX arena&amp;hellip;ironic isn’t it? Next, Starbucks switches its ice cubes and stirs up a debate online. Finally, Memorial Day weekend is here! Neal &amp;amp; Toby have some interesting stats that might help your wallet for the upcoming weekend.</description></item><item><title>#DeSaster on Twitter, NVIDIA’s Potential Stock Market Record, &amp; A $22.5 Million Ghost Town?! | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310147/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310147/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 67: Neal and Toby recap the fiasco that was Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis&amp;rsquo; official presidential bid on Twitter Spaces. They go over what happened, what were they thinking, and what this could mean for the 2024 election. Then they talk NVIDIA’s track to breaking a stock market record. Meanwhile, Fitch put the US&amp;rsquo; credit rating on watch for a possible downgrade. Whoa. Finally, a mysterious buyer purchases a ghost town in CA for $22.</description></item><item><title>Anthropic vs. OpenAI, Netflix Password Crackdown, &amp; Teen Mental Health Crisis | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310148/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310148/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 66: Neal and Toby dive into potential game changers in AI: Ex-OpenAI execs receive the largest funding to-date and Adobe&amp;rsquo;s AI-enhanced Photoshop. Then, Netflix&amp;rsquo;s crackdown on password sharing has arrived in the US. Meanwhile, teen mental health reaches emergency situation&amp;hellip;a report says social media is to blame. Lastly, a look at the top 100 most reputable brands &amp;ndash; can you guess where Twitter lands? Hint: It&amp;rsquo;s not very high.</description></item><item><title>Ozempic the Anti-Addiction Drug, Age of Streaming Mergers, &amp; Bezos's Boat | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310149/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310149/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 65: Neal and Toby discuss the increasing buzz around potent weight loss drugs with Pfizer&amp;rsquo;s oral version and Ozempic&amp;rsquo;s anti-addiction side effects. Then, Showtime merges with Paramount+, Max absorbs Discovery+, and Disney+ wants to include Hulu. Are we entering the age of streaming mergers? Meanwhile, Western states reach a deal that might stop its main water source from completely drying up. Lastly, Jeff Bezos just popped the question to his girlfriend but why are people only talking about who the figurehead on his yacht looks like.</description></item><item><title>What if the US Defaults?, Instagram vs. Twitter &amp; Game Over for E-Sports? | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310150/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310150/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 64: Neal and Toby break down what would happen if the US defaults. Plus the guys talk about Instagram throwing its hat in the battle of text-based platforms. Then, is the allure of E-Sports starting to fade? A look into the stagnant industry and if it&amp;rsquo;s time to give up on its future. Lastly, Cava gets ready for IPO, debt ceiling update, and a whale problem that is wreaking havoc in Europe that may be a sign of a killer whale revolution.</description></item><item><title>Disney Drops $1B FL Project, Working with Weed &amp; Best US Beaches | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310151/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310151/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 63: Neal and Toby get you ready for the weekend as they dive into the latest rift between Disney &amp;amp; DeSantis and why this one is costing the state nearly 2,000 jobs. Plus if ESPN moves to streaming does that mean cable is officially dead? Meanwhile more people than ever are smoking weed while they work and why does Congress care so much about AM Radio? Finally the guys break down the best beaches in America and even read some amazing listener emails.</description></item><item><title>Montana Bans TikTok, Miami's Bitcoin Buyer's Remorse, &amp; Uber for Teens | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310152/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310152/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 62: Neal and Toby give the latest update on government news with the debt ceiling crisis and Montana&amp;rsquo;s bold ban on TikTok on all devices. Then, Bitcoin 2023 is here! Except&amp;hellip;Miami isn&amp;rsquo;t all that excited about it anymore. What can happen in a year, amirite? Meanwhile, Uber reaches out to teenagers and soccer moms. Heinz makes all your sauce dreams come true with over 200 sauce combos. Maybe you can pour it over your CRISPR salad.</description></item><item><title>ChatGPT Goes to Congress, Tesla Ads Coming, &amp; Liberating Taco Tuesdays | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310153/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310153/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 61: Dynamic duo Neal and Toby recap OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s CEO Sam Altman&amp;rsquo;s trip to Congress, asking for AI to be regulated. They&amp;rsquo;ll also cover Tesla&amp;rsquo;s annual shareholder meetings where Elon made some big announcements, including advertising for the first time. Then, Taco Bell&amp;rsquo;s crusade to free &amp;ldquo;Taco Tuesday&amp;rdquo; and available to all. Lastly, the latest jewelry heist that rocked Europe comes to a close.
Learn more about our sponsor, Brex: brex.</description></item><item><title>Americans $17 Trillion in Debt, Free TVs... Kinda &amp; Martha's Still Got It | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310154/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310154/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 60: The prodigal son returns&amp;hellip;Toby is back! Neal and Toby reunite to talk about the record-high consumer debt hurting Americans. Plus, this company wants to give you a free TV in exchange for constant ads. The question is: would you take the deal? Then, the IRS is testing out its own e-filing system. Finally, Martha Stewart gracing the cover of Sports Illustrated at 81 years old and Netflix&amp;rsquo;s biggest flop to-date.</description></item><item><title>Vice Media Bankruptcy, Meet the New AI Datebot &amp; Eurovision is Big Business | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310155/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310155/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 59: Kyle is back for one more round! Neal and Kyle dive into why Vice Media became the latest major media flameout and what it means for the news industry. Plus the guys wrap up some big headlines around the world from Turkey&amp;rsquo;s Presidential election to why Eurovision is big business. Meanwhile we&amp;rsquo;ll get introduced to a new AI datebot, CarynAI and they&amp;rsquo;ll also preview a huge week ahead filled with earnings and film festivals.</description></item><item><title>Twitter's New CEO, Peloton Recalls 2 Million Bikes &amp; Workers Are Happier Than Ever | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310156/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310156/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 58: We kick off Friday with Kyle Hagge! Neal and Kyle discuss Elon Musk&amp;rsquo;s announcement that Twitter has found a new CEO. They also dive into the latest Peloton drama where the company has recalled over 2 million bikes; not good if you&amp;rsquo;re a stockholder! Plus, why workers are happier than ever and who will make more money on tour: Taylor Swift or Beyonce? Learn more about our sponsor, Fidelity: https://fidelity.</description></item><item><title>Googling with AI, Topgolf Off its Game, sweetgreen Goes Robotic | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310157/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310157/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 57: Welcome back Kyle Hagge! Neal and Kyle dive into Google&amp;rsquo;s I/O presentation yesterday, and of course the tech giant is very high on AI. Plus, are the guys bullish on an $1,800 foldable phone? They also break down the latest earnings including losses from Disney and&amp;hellip; Topgolf? Plus Wendy&amp;rsquo;s introduces an AI drive-thru and sweetgreen goes robotic. Neal shares his favorite numbers and the hit show entering it&amp;rsquo;s 7th season&amp;hellip;.</description></item><item><title>Inflation Keeps Going Down (Whew) &amp; Tucker Carlson's Twitter Show | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310158/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310158/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 56: Kelsey Sutton has returned! She and Neal get into the latest news out of DC, including the inflation report that fell below expectations and why McCarthy and Biden couldn&amp;rsquo;t agree on a Debt Ceiling deal. Plus, Tucker Carlson is launch a new show on twitter; will this be good or bad for the social media platform? Also, the stock market loves AI and the billion dollar mattress deal.</description></item><item><title>Airlines Could Pay You For Cancellations, America's Most Trustworthy News &amp; Quiet Luxury is Trendy | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310159/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310159/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 55: Kyle returns as Toby continues his European adventure! Kyle and Neal explain why Airlines may be on the hook for compensating you for delays and cancellations. Plus, why the Weather Channel is America&amp;rsquo;s most trusted media outlet and why iPad tipping culture is causing quite the stir. Neal and Kyle also debate if they could wear or afford &amp;ldquo;quiet luxury&amp;rdquo; and how one woman survived for five days on just&amp;hellip; wine and lollipops.</description></item><item><title>Buffett's Bank Warning, Own a Share of a Derby Horse &amp; Zuck is a Jiu-Jitsu Champ | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310160/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310160/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 54: Kyle Hagge is here! Kyle and Neal break down Warren Buffett&amp;rsquo;s comments at the annual Berkshire Hathaway shareholders meeting; including his thoughts on the regional bank crisis and why Apple is the perfect company. Oh to be in Omaha. Plus, the controversy at the Kentucky Derby this past weekend and why a certain app lets you buy shares of racehorses. And Mark Zuckerberg is a Jiu-Jitsu champion and Kyle makes a pitch for the royal family to hire him and Neal and consultants.</description></item><item><title>Labor Market is on Fire, Americans Nervous About Banks, UK Economy-Saving Coronation | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310161/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310161/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 53: Kelsey Sutton is here! Kelsey and Neal break down the latest jobs report which was stellar, and they explain why Americans are nervous about keeping their money in banks. The economy has never been more confusing. Plus, this week&amp;rsquo;s earnings roundup and if King Charle&amp;rsquo;s coronation will be good or bad for the British economy. And Snoop Dogg may be all in on the NHL while Ed Sheeran made music lawsuit history.</description></item><item><title>Fed Hikes Rates Despite Banking Woes, AirBnB Room Rentals &amp; NY Out On Gas Stoves | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310162/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310162/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 52: Neal and Toby discuss the Federal Reserves decision to raise interest rates by a quarter point and what it could mean for the future of the banking sector. Plus, AirBNB goes all-in on single room rentals and New York is out on gas stoves. Neal gets into the spirit of May the 4th with some Star Wars themed numbers and&amp;hellip; astronomers saw a star swallow a planet?</description></item><item><title>Regional Bank Stocks in Free Fall, Hindenburg Targets Icahn &amp; Pornhub Blocks Utah | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310163/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310163/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 52: Neal and Toby discuss the future of regional banks amidst the failure of First Republic and stock free fall of Western Alliance and PacWest. They also breakdown the Hindenburg report on Icahn Enterprises that erased a fifth of the company&amp;rsquo;s value. Plus, why Pornhub blocked access to it&amp;rsquo;s site in Utah and why the US Surgeon General is declaring loneliness the new epidemic. And finally, Forbes released the list of the highest paid athletes in 2023, why a surprising number of them have a connection with&amp;hellip; the Middle East.</description></item><item><title>SpaceX Explosion Lawsuit, Hollywood Writers' Strike &amp; 'Godfather of AI' Quits | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310164/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310164/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 51: Neal and Toby discuss the impact the Hollywood writers strike will have on the movie, television and streaming industries. They also explain why environmental groups are suing the FAA over the failed SpaceX Starship launch. And why is the &amp;lsquo;Godfather&amp;rsquo; of AI is leaving Google? Plus, the NYPD is telling people to put Apple AirTags in their cars&amp;hellip; Good idea? Toby shares a new cinematic trend that may or may not be illegal and here&amp;rsquo;s what Uber&amp;rsquo;s lost and found looks like.</description></item><item><title>JPMorgan Buys First Republic Bank, What is Bluesky? &amp; ChatGPT Negotiations | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310165/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310165/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 50: Neal and Toby dive into JPMorgan&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of First Republic Bank and what it means for the banking crisis. Plus I bet you randomly heard about an app called Bluesky this weekend, but what is it and why is it feel kinda like Twitter? Meanwhile ChatGPT is invading the workplace from boosting employee productivity to even helping you negotiate salaries. And the Met Gala kicks off Monday night, the guys dig into the numbers into why this event could actually be big business.</description></item><item><title>Fastest Earnings Recap in Biz, GDP Slowdown &amp; Jerry Springer Renaissance Man | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310166/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310166/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 49: Neal and Toby are looking to break their own world record for fastest earnings coverage. This time they&amp;rsquo;re hitting Amazon all the way to Crocs. Also its a &amp;lsquo;worst of both worlds&amp;rsquo; scenario as the US economy is seeing high inflation and a GDP slowdown. Meanwhile Eli Lilly is about to throw their hat in the highly coveted weight-loss drug ring and the guys breakdown why Chipotle is sizzling and First Republic Bank is fizzling.</description></item><item><title>AI Helps Meta Surge, Disney Sues DeSantis &amp; Hawks Delay Janet Concert | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310167/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310167/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 48: Neal and Toby dive deep into Meta&amp;rsquo;s strong sales quarter and break down why Zuck thinks AI deserves some of the credit. Meanwhile Disney is suing DeSantis claiming his political antics are bad for business. The guys also break down what Congress&amp;rsquo;s latest bill means for the Debt Ceiling battle with President Biden and why you can finally iMessage from your PC! Plus Neal dazzles us with his crazy stats and why Janet Jackson may be beefing with Trae Young.</description></item><item><title>Need to Know Earnings Roundup &amp; UK blocks $69B Microsoft-Activision Deal | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310168/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310168/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 47: Neal and Toby rip through a huge week so far in earnings reports. Microsoft, Alphabet, McDonalds, Spotify; who isn&amp;rsquo;t reporting? They share their biggest takeaways and what it could mean for you. Plus the UK blocked the $75 billion deal between Microsoft and Activision Blizzard. Also why Millennials are just too tired to get into the stock market before it bounces back. And gone are the days of free labor - we wrap up with the highest paying internships of 2023.</description></item><item><title>Carlson Wipes $500M+ from Fox Stock, LVMH passes $500B, Snap's Hated AI | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310169/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310169/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 46: Toby and Neal discuss how Tucker Carlson&amp;rsquo;s departure from Fox led to over a $500 million stock loss. They also discuss LVMH&amp;rsquo;s rise to a $500 billion valuation and how the family behind the company may reflect one of the top shows on television right now. Plus, First Republic bank lost over $100 billion in deposits and why we hate Snapchat&amp;rsquo;s new AI. Toby shares why the kids are loving chess and we break down the lawsuit between&amp;hellip; Ed Sheeran and Marvin Gaye?</description></item><item><title>Bed Bath &amp; Beyond Bankruptcy, Twitter verifies dead celebs &amp; Bud Light Ad Drama | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310170/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 14:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310170/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 45: Neal and Toby explore the painful path that led to retail giant Bed Bath &amp;amp; Beyond to file for bankruptcy protection this past weekend. They also take a look at Twitter&amp;rsquo;s verification process and why some celebrities are verified without even subscribing to Twitter Blue. Plus, Bud Light places two execs on leave and Toby and Neal share their weekend winners and loser. And here is what we are watching for the week ahead.</description></item><item><title>Buzzfeed News Shuts Down, SpaceX Rocket Explosion, Ikea's $2-Billion US Investment | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310171/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310171/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 44: Neal and Toby explore the path that led Buzzfeed to make the decision to shut down their news division. And on Thursday SpaceX launched their Starship rocket, and even though it exploded about 4 minutes into it&amp;rsquo;s flight path the mission was still considered a success. Plus, Ikea&amp;rsquo;s $2 billion American Investment. And finally how one woman accidentally found herself on the verge of winning $250k by playing&amp;hellip; Candy Crush?</description></item><item><title>Tesla Earnings Dive, Facebook could owe you money?, &amp; TSwift shut down FTX | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310172/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310172/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 43: Neal and Toby break down the latest earnings from Tesla and explain what they mean for the company moving forward. Also, Facebook might actually owe you money. Here&amp;rsquo;s how to make your claim in the $725 million lawsuit. Plus, the CEO that told her employees to leave &amp;lsquo;pity city&amp;rsquo; and why Taylor Swift shut down FTX. Learn more about our sponsor, Fidelity: https://fidelity.com/stocksbytheslice Listen Here: https://link.chtbl.com/MBD Watch Here: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Historic $787M Fox-Dominion Settlement and India's Business Renaissance | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310173/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 14:06:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310173/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 42: Neal and Toby discuss the winners and losers of the historic $787.5 million settlement between Fox and Dominion over election fraud claims. Also, Apple opens their first store in India and Netflix reports less than impressive earnings. Linktree takes on Instagram and what EV can you buy to qualify for a tax credit? (Hint: there aren&amp;rsquo;t as many as you think). Plus why a man was arrested after applying for a job on rentahitman.</description></item><item><title>Apple Wants to be Your Bank, $776M for Angry Birds?!, Hamburglar Returns | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310174/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 14:03:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310174/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 41: Neal and Toby discuss Apples brand new savings account and delve into the tech giants partnership with Goldman Sachs. Speaking of Goldman Sachs, we delve into the earnings reports of them and Bank of America from Tuesday morning. Plus, writers in Hollywood are preparing to strike and the maker of Angry Birds is over $770 million richer. Toby breaks down the latest TikTok trend and the Hamburglar has made his return.</description></item><item><title>SpaceX attempts history, Schwab's $41B deposit loss, Netflix's live fail | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310175/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310175/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 40: Neal and Toby break down how SpaceX will attempt to launch Starship, the most powerful rocket ever built. They also discuss Charles Schwab&amp;rsquo;s latest earning reports and how they lost $41 billion in deposits over the first 3 months of 2023. They also break down Google&amp;rsquo;s race to beat Microsoft in AI after Samsung ponders a change in search engines. Plus, Netflix&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Love is Blind&amp;rsquo; live streaming fail on Sunday night and what we are looking forward to this week.</description></item><item><title>Banks Thriving Despite Crisis, Magic's $6B NFL Deal, Meet the NYC Rat Czar | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310176/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310176/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 39: Neal and Toby take a look at all of the bank earning reports that came out on Friday morning, and it looks like they are doing just fine. Plus, Josh Harris and Magic Johnson put a team together to buy the NFL&amp;rsquo;s Washington Commanders for a record $6 billion. And what is Auto-GPT? They also share their stock of the week and dog of the week. And rats beware, New York City introduces the newest government official, the Rat Czar.</description></item><item><title>EPA says EVs are the Future, NPR leaves Twitter, Walmart is over Chicago | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310177/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 14:05:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310177/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 38: Neal and Toby discuss the EPA&amp;rsquo;s latest emission rules and why the agency is pushing hard for electric vehicles to hit the road. Plus, why NPR is leaving twitter. And jury selection is set to begin in the Fox-Dominion billion dollar lawsuit. HBO Max is just max now, and Walmart hates Chicago? Also, how the new pitch clock at MLB games is impacting beer sales. Learn more about our sponsor, TaxAct: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Inflation Cooling, Buffett weighs in on Banking Crisis, Twitter &amp; X Corp. | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310178/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310178/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 37: Neal and Toby break down the latest CPI Data released on Wednesday Morning. Also, Elon has revealed his latest plan for Twitter - which might be an entire new company? And Warren Buffett explains why bank depositors should relax. Oh, and pack your bags because travel to Europe is the new wave. Plus, million dollar vanity plate business and why this billionaire is donating $300 million to Harvard.</description></item><item><title>Pharma CEOs Condemn TX ruling, Tupperware tumbles, Reformation rewear trend | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310179/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310179/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 36: Neal and Toby discuss hundreds of pharmaceutical CEOs signing a letter calling for a reversal of the abortion pill ban ruling made by a Texas judge. They also explain why Tupperware may be in trouble as their stock takes a tumble. Plus, how FTX completely mismanaged funds and why Bitcoin is over $30k for the first time since last summer. Toby discusses why Reformation is subtly taking advantage of TikTok virality.</description></item><item><title>Classified Doc Leak, Tesla Shanghai battery factory, Can AI defame you? | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310180/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 35: Neal and Toby take a look at the leaked US classified documents that hit social media over the weekend. They also discuss the opposing rulings from two judges over the weekend on the FDA approval of an abortion pill. Plus, Tesla is opening a mega-pack battery factory in Shanghai, and can ChatGPT be sued for libel? And of course Neal and Toby share their winners of the weekend and what we are watching this upcoming week.</description></item><item><title>Job Market Slowing, WWE stock soars, A day in the life of Tim Cook | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310181/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310181/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 34: Neal and Toby breakdown the latest Jobs report data released on Friday morning. What does it mean and how will the markets react when they open on Monday? Plus, the latest on the lawsuit saga between Chipotle and Sweetgreen. And Why Vince McMahon has never been better and Snoop Dogg might be&amp;hellip;. the dog of the week. We wrap Friday with National Beer Day, which state has the most affordable brews?</description></item><item><title>Twitter vs NPR, McDonalds layoffs, Chipotle files lawsuit against Sweet Green | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310182/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310182/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 33: Neal and Toby dive into the latest Twitter naming NPR a state-affiliated media source. They also discuss McDonald&amp;rsquo;s layoffs and why Chipotle filed a lawsuit against Sweetgreen in a battle of burrito bowls. Plus, Neal&amp;rsquo;s Numbers - which if you have any fancy kitchen appliances, you may wanna take a look at your real estate value. And a full preview of the new Barbie Movie and why the food prices at The Masters are inflation-proof.</description></item><item><title>Big day for business fraud, Jamie Dimon's bank warning, Billionaire Trivia | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310183/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310183/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 32: Neal and Toby explain the business fraud charges against Donald Trump, and why they are felonies. They also discuss a former startup founder of a college financial planning site being charged with&amp;hellip; Fraud. Plus, Jamie Dimon&amp;rsquo;s warning of a possible banking crisis and if we should take those words to heart. And Google is eliminating some of their employee perks. Meanwhile a professional women&amp;rsquo;s soccer team is coming to San Fran!</description></item><item><title>Trump’s arraignment, NASA's Lunar Mission, and Virtual Boyfriend craze!? | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310184/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310184/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 31: Neal and Toby discuss Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s historic arraignment in Manhattan on Tuesday. They also break down NASA&amp;rsquo;s announcement of the astronauts that will participate in the Artemis 2 mission around the moon. Plus, Paris bans e-scooters and Dodgecoin investors are coming after Elon Musk. And have you heard of dating a virtual boyfriend&amp;hellip; IRL? Well Toby is here to tell you about it. And quite possibly, a Harry Potter series coming to a streaming service near you.</description></item><item><title>WWE &amp; UFC Billion $$ Merger, Journalist arrested in Russia, Weekend Winners | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310185/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310185/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 30: Neal and Toby discuss the billion dollar merger bringing UFC and WWE together under one company and one awesome ticker symbol $TKO, because of course. They also discuss the latest details around the detainment of the WSJ Journalist that was arrested in Russia. Plus the latest drama around paid twitter verification. And Duolingo pulls an epic April Fools joke. Plus Apple Music is helping classical make a comeback.</description></item><item><title>Trump's Historic Indictment, Disney curbs DeSantis, LA Taxing the rich | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310186/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310186/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 29: Neal and Toby break down the historic indictment against former President Donald Trump. They explain what it means, and what could come next in his arraignment. They also discuss how Disney restructured their district before Ron Desantis had authorities come in and take over power. Plus - why are millionaires in LA in a rush to sell their mansions? And Neal has been talking about the new Tetris movie all week.</description></item><item><title>Musk's AI Warning, Bernie Sanders grills Starbucks &amp; Metaverse is meh? | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310187/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310187/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 28: Neal and Toby discuss the letter penned by Elon Musk and other tech giants calling for a pause on AI developments and experiments. They also breakdown why things got spicy between Sen. Bernie Sanders and the Starbucks CEO. Plus Disney and Microsoft are out on the Metaverse, what does that mean? Neal shares his favorite numbers from this past week and also&amp;hellip; How does a billionaire die without anyone knowing?</description></item><item><title>Congress grills SVB regulators, Apple buy now pay later, Mammoth Meatballs!? | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310188/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310188/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 27: Neal and Toby recap the Congressional hearings of SVB and Signature Bank on Capitol Hill on Tuesday and how it will impact the banking sector moving forward. Plus, Apple is finally letting you pay late. And which jobs are most prone to AI taking over? And if you&amp;rsquo;re hungry - there&amp;rsquo;s a startup company in Australia serving up&amp;hellip; Woolly Mammoth meatballs. Learn more about our sponsor, Grasshopper: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Stylin' Pope is actually AI?, TikTok debuts new app, Crypto war hits Binance | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310189/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310189/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 26: Neal and Toby discuss the drippy Pope image that has taken the internet by storm&amp;hellip; but it&amp;rsquo;s actually just AI. And the guy who made it was on shrooms? Plus the war on crypto continues as Binance faces a lawsuit from the CTFC. Uber Eats cracks down on virtual restaurants. And TikTok is rolling out a new app amidst rumors of it being banned - what&amp;rsquo;s the deal?</description></item><item><title>SVB finally acquired, Twitter $20B valuation &amp; ChatGPT dinner reservations | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310190/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310190/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 25: Neal and Toby break down First Citizen&amp;rsquo;s acquisition of a large chunk of Silicon Valley Bank and what it means for the banking ecosystem. They also discuss the political crisis and protests in Israel and what it means for the economy. And twitter is now less than half of what Elon purchased it for? Plus, ChatGPT has plugins now for your favorite apps! No excuse to not make a dinner reservation now.</description></item><item><title>TikTok CEO can't sway congress, CashApp Fraud?, Apple at the movies | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310191/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310191/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 24: Neal and Toby take a look at TikTok CEO&amp;rsquo;s Shou Chew&amp;rsquo;s testimony before Congress yesterday and why lawmakers still have major concerns over the app&amp;rsquo;s security. Also, Hindenberg&amp;rsquo;s report on Block and CashApp has sent the company into a tailspin. And why is Apple investing billions in movies? Plus the stock of the week is giving&amp;hellip;. &amp;lsquo;The Last of Us&amp;rsquo; vibes. Learn more about our sponsor, TaxAct: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Fed rate hikes ending?, TikTok on the Hill, SCOTUS Poop Case | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310192/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310192/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 23: Neal and Toby discuss the Fed raising interest rates but signaling it could be stopping soon. Plus TikTok’s CEO heads to Capitol Hill and why SCOTUS is hearing a Jack Daniel’s poop case. And the latest celebrity crypto settlement and why Taylor Swift is…. even richer. Learn more about our sponsor, Fidelity: https://fidelity.com/stocksbytheslice Learn more about our sponsor, TaxAct: https://www.taxact.com Listen Here: https://www.mbdailyshow.com/ Watch Here: https://www.youtube.com/@MorningBrewDailyShow Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Google rolls out BARD, Banks on edge ahead of Fed meeting &amp; White Claw Vodka | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310193/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310193/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 22: Neal and Toby discuss Google&amp;rsquo;s rollout of &amp;lsquo;Bard&amp;rsquo;, the AI software set to compete with Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s ChatGPT. They also preview the pivotal Fed meeting as banks look to stabilize. Also, hosing prices fall for first time in 11 years. And get ready, White Claw is getting into the liquor business. By the way, if you have ever wanted a new Dodge Challenger, you only have one more chance.</description></item><item><title>Biden's first veto, Climate 'Survival Guide' &amp; ChatGPT Hustle Culture | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310194/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310194/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 21: Neal and Toby discuss why President Biden vetoed a retirement investment resolution bill. They also dive into Amazon&amp;rsquo;s latest round of layoffs and what the UN is saying about the latest climate change report. Plus what is HustleGPT and how can it help you become the next great entrepreneur. And let&amp;rsquo;s debate; would you rather make less money and be happy, or more money and be miserable?</description></item><item><title>UBS $3B Credit Suisse rescue, U.S. Banking Latest, Seaweed to invade FL | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310195/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310195/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 20: Neal and Toby explain the deal that led to UBS taking over Credit Suisse for over $3 billion. Calm down global markets! They also take a look at the latest banking news in the U.S. including First Republic&amp;rsquo;s stock struggles, and why Warren Buffett may be getting involved. Also a bed of seaweed twice the size of America is heading to Florida. Plus, what we are keeping an eye on this week.</description></item><item><title>French retirement protests, Youtube TV $$$ Increase, Octopus Farm Outcry | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310196/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 14:41:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310196/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 19: Marketing Brew senior reporter Kelsey Sutton is in for Toby! Kelsey and Neal discuss the protests in France over President Macron&amp;rsquo;s efforts to raise the retirement age and take a look at what OpenAI can do for Microsoft Word and Excel. They also share their stock of the week and dog of the week (watch out banks). Plus, the Octopus farm controversy you need to know about.</description></item><item><title>Credit Suisse Rebounds, Ryan Reynolds is super rich &amp; TikTok Sale? | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310197/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310197/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 18: Neal and Toby break down why Credit Suisse is on the rebound. They also discuss why the U.S. is advocating for the sale of TikTok and why Ryan Reynolds is one of the most successful celebrity entrepreneurs. Plus, the economics of March Madness, and NASA&amp;rsquo;s nifty new spacesuits. Oh also they reveal the Greatest Logo of All Time bracket - head to our social channels to sound off!</description></item><item><title>OpenAI can take your SATs, Meta Layoffs, Boneless Wing Controversy | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310198/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310198/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 17: Neal and Toby explain why ChatGPT may soon be a better test-taker than the average human. Also Meta is laying off another 10,000 people - how did they get there? Plus the latest on the SVB fallout, tumultuous train situations across the country, and why a man is suing Buffalo Wild Wings over&amp;hellip; boneless wings? Learn more about our sponsor, Grasshopper: https://www.grasshopper.bank/thedailyshow Learn more about our sponsor, TaxAct: https://www.</description></item><item><title>SVB &amp; the future of Crypto, Biden approves Alaska drilling, Meta out on NFTs | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310199/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310199/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 16: Neal and Toby explain how the Silicon Valley Bank disaster is impacting regional banks, and what it could mean for the future of Crypto. Plus, President Biden approves a controversial Alaska oil drilling project. The guys also break down the latest inflation data and why Meta is out on NFTs. Plus, is Samsung taking fake pictures of the moon? And remembering the man who took 7-Eleven global.</description></item><item><title>The Silicon Valley Bank implosion and what's next for you &amp; investors | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310200/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310200/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 15: Neal and Toby take a deep dive into what happened with Silicon Valley Bank over the weekend. They dissect the timeline, the discourse around it and what this could mean for the future of the financial system and other Banks. Plus, Oscars recap and what we are watching for this week. Learn more about our sponsor, TaxAct: https://www.taxact.com Listen Here: https://www.mbdailyshow.com/ Watch Here: https://www.youtube.com/@MorningBrewDailyShow Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Banks losing billions, Biden's budget and Czech Baseball Team side hustles | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310201/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310201/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 14: Neal and Toby explain why banks are losing billions after the stumble of SVB financial group. They also take a look at President Biden&amp;rsquo;s budget proposal and what it could mean for the wealthy and corporations. And the Czech baseball team shares how they are preparing for the World Baseball Classic while also holding full day-time jobs. Learn more about our sponsor, TaxAct: https://www.taxact.com Listen Here: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Yeezy's push Adidas losses, Betting on the WWE?, LA Clippers love toilets | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310202/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310202/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 13: Neal and Toby take a look at why Adidas is warning of their first annual loss in over 30 years after their billion dollar fallout with Yeezy. They also discuss why the WWE is looking to legalize gambling on scripted matches. Plus, what&amp;rsquo;s the breakdown of the Fox News and Dominion lawsuit. And Neal shares his favorite numbers - turns out Clippers&amp;rsquo; owner Steve Ballmer is really excited about toilets.</description></item><item><title>Mexican Medical Tourism, DOJ vs JetBlue &amp; Spirit, ChatGPT meets Slack | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310203/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310203/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 12: Neal and Toby take a look at the economics behind Mexican medical tourism after two Americans were killed in a Cartel mix up after traveling to the country for a plastic surgery procedure. Also they breakdown why the DOJ wants to block JetBlue&amp;rsquo;s takeover of Spirit airlines. And, hate talking to your co-workers? Well Slack wants ChatGPT to do it for you. Plus, why everything is awesome for Legos right now.</description></item><item><title>California to cut ties with Walgreens, EV Bike Fires, Swiss Chocolate Drama | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310204/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 15:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310204/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 11: Neal and Toby discuss California cutting ties with Walgreens over the pharmacy&amp;rsquo;s position on abortion pills. They also get into the implications of EV bike fires and why the Swiss are putting their foot down on what can be considered their native chocolate. And what is &amp;ldquo;body doubling&amp;rdquo; and why it could help people with ADHD work remotely. Oh, and if you could name a snowplow - what would that name be?</description></item><item><title>Companies push 'premium' products, Amazon HQ2 delay, ChatGPT student survey | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310205/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 15:06:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310205/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 10: Neal and Toby discuss the economic strategy that companies are taking pushing higher end products to maintain profits. They also dig into Amazon pausing construction on their new headquarters in Virginia, and why college students aren&amp;rsquo;t completely sold on ChatGPT just yet. Also what happened with HQ Trivia? Learn more about our sponsor, Huel: https://huel.com/dailyshow Listen Here: https://www.mbdailyshow.com/ Watch Here: https://www.youtube.com/@MorningBrewDailyShow Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Can Only the Rich Buy A House? Whiskey Fungus, Glassdoor for NFL Teams | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310206/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310206/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 9: Neal and Toby break down why you have to make more money than ever to own a home. Good luck millennials! Also what The Last of Us and Jack Daniel&amp;rsquo;s have in common. Plus the NFLPA released report cards for every single team. And yes, F- is a real grade. And why Salesforce and Rivian stocks are going in opposite directions. Learn more about our sponsor, TaxAct: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Tesla Investor Day Underwhelms, TikTok Time Limit, Tequila &amp; High Noons? | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310207/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310207/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 8: Neal and Toby discuss why Elon&amp;rsquo;s Master plan fell flat at Investor Day. They&amp;rsquo;ll examine TikTok&amp;rsquo;s new time limit for teens and why Eli Lilly is slashing insulin prices. Neal tells us why stick-shift is back and in the canned cocktail world - a merging of powers; Tequila and High Noons. Learn more about our sponsor, Huel: https://huel.com/dailyshow Listen Here: https://www.mbdailyshow.com/ Watch Here: https://www.youtube.com/@MorningBrewDailyShow Sources: Tesla Investor Day Underwhelms: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Goldman Sachs CEO On Hot Seat?, High Cost of Vaping, Biden Chip Plan | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310208/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310208/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 7: Neal and Toby discuss the consumer product drama surrounding Goldman Sachs CEO David Solomon. Also why vapes might be getting more expensive, and how President Biden is taking some excess profits from chipmakers in the US. Plus the case for a lunar timezone, and who would ever order the same thing as your partner at dinner? Listen Here: https://www.mbdailyshow.com/ Watch Here: https://www.youtube.com/@MorningBrewDailyShow
Sources: Goldman Sachs CEO on the hot seat: https://www.</description></item><item><title>SCOTUS Takes On Student Debt, Rise of Part-Time Work, AI Beauty Filter | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310209/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310209/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 6: Toby and Neal break down the Supreme Court hearing arguments over Biden&amp;rsquo;s Student Loan Forgiveness plan on Tuesday. They also explain why burnout is causing millions of Americans to turn to part-time work. And what is happening to the Disney District? Plus, Toby explains the latest TikTok trend to Neal and why he’s never looked better - well, maybe. Listen Here: https://www.mbdailyshow.com/ Watch Here: https://www.youtube.com/@MorningBrewDailyShow Sources: SCOTUS Student Loan Forgiveness: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Covid Lab Leak?, Buffett Defends Buybacks, More Twitter Layoffs | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310210/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310210/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 5: Neal and Toby explain the report that the Covid-19 outbreak may have been caused by lab leak in China. Warren Buffett released his annual shareholder letter over the weekend and defended stock buybacks. While over in the tech world Elon Musk lays off at least 200 Twitter employees and Nokia announces a logo redesign. And it&amp;rsquo;s Monday! We take look ahead as to what&amp;rsquo;s on the docket for this week as we turn the calendar to March.</description></item><item><title>One year of war in Ukraine, Bezos the NFL owner?, Cocaine Bear hits theaters | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310211/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310211/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 4: On the one year anniversary of the war in Ukraine Neal and Toby take a look back at the most staggering moments and global economic impact. Also, Jeff Bezos has hired a firm to explore a possible bid for the Commanders. The guys also share their winning stock and dog of the week, and preview the movie of the century that hits theaters this weekend - Cocaine Bear.</description></item><item><title>Diabetic drug diet craze, Mormon church pays SEC $5M &amp; Bill Gates' beer run | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310212/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310212/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 3: Neal and Toby discuss the Ozempic shortage - the drug that diabetics need, but dieters are using. Also blizzard warnings in LA and record heat in DC, what is happening??? The guys also dive into Spotify&amp;rsquo;s new AI DJ, and why Bill Gates is investing over $900 million in beer. Plus why is the Mormon Church paying fines to the SEC? Listen Here: https://www.mbdailyshow.com/ Watch Here: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Will SCOTUS change the internet? 4-day workweek &amp; ChatGPT writes books now | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310213/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310213/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode 2: Neal and Toby take a look at the Supreme Court&amp;rsquo;s case that could change the future of the internet. We&amp;rsquo;ll also dive into a study on why 4-day workweeks actually work. Plus ChatGPT can write books now? And Neal even surprises Toby with some of his favorite numbers from his ridiculous consumption of news. Listen Here: https://www.podpage.com/dashboard/morningbrewdaily/ Watch Here: https://www.youtube.com/@MorningBrewDailyShow Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.</description></item><item><title>Biden's Kyiv Trip, Social media pay-to-play, Cocaine Bear hits theaters | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310214/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310214/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this episode of Morning Brew Daily, Neal and Toby discuss Putins&amp;rsquo;s nuclear announcement and President Biden’s surprise trip to Kyiv. They also dive into Home Depot spending over $1 billion to raise wages for workers and why Meta is joining Twitter in paid verification. Also what is going on with the ice coverage in the Great Lakes? That and Cocaine Bear hits theaters this Friday. Listen Here: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Introducing Morning Brew Daily | Morning Brew Daily</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8915310215/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8915310215/</guid><description>Podcast Description Morning Brew Daily is a talk show that covers the latest news on business, the economy, and everything else that you need to know more about, with Neal Freyman and Toby Howell. The show is a smart, witty and informative way to to start your day. Catch us every weekday on all podcasting platforms and Youtube starting on February 21st. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices</description></item></channel></rss>