<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/nothing-much-happens-bedtime-stories-to-help-you-sleep/</link><description>Recent content in Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/nothing-much-happens-bedtime-stories-to-help-you-sleep/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Tree Farm | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540229/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540229/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called The Tree Farm, and it’s a story about one of the last trees of the season, finding its home. It’s also about steam from a thermos rising into the evening air, memories tied to the fresh scent of pine, a good deed passed to a stranger, and the reminder that we are made of stars.
We give to a different charity each week and this week we are giving to Gleaners Community Food bank.</description></item><item><title>Under the Tree (Encore) | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Under the Tree and it’s a story about a day of decorating around the house. It’s also about a bowl of oatmeal with cinnamon and apples, a box of ornaments wrapped in paper and the things that connect us to where we come from.
Purchase Our Book: https://bit.ly/Nothing-Much-Happens
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mistletoe and Marmalade | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Mistletoe and Marmalade, and it’s a story about decorating for the holidays with the whole family. It’s also about birds at the feeder, ornaments made in kindergarten that still make it onto the tree, the ways that love can surprise you, and a greyhound in a Christmas sweater.
We donate to a different charity each week, and this week, we are giving to The Good Food Institute.</description></item><item><title>Fresh Snow (Encore) | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Fresh Snow, and it’s a story about time spent outside as the flakes fall. It’s also about a late-night bath, a peppermint stick in a cup of hot chocolate, and the easy comfort of long-held friends.
Purchase Our Book: https://bit.ly/Nothing-Much-Happens
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Snow and Street Lights | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540004/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Snow and Streetlights, and it’s a story about an afternoon at the bookshop on the edge of winter. It’s also about a bell jingling on a dog’s collar, the soft buffer of the first snowfall, a door held open by a stranger, and a pack of paper stars.
We donate to a different charity each week, and this week, we are giving to Brother Wolf.</description></item><item><title>Lost &amp; Found (Encore) | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Lost and Found, and it’s a story about the first snowfall of the year. It’s also about firewood stacked high beside the hearth, paw prints in the snow, and the magic of two paths crossing at just the right moment.
Subscribe for ad-free, bonus, and extra-long episodes now! https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/premium-subscription
Purchase Our Book: https://bit.ly/Nothing-Much-Happens
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Winter Evening Yoga | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Winter Evening Yoga, and it’s a story about stepping into a safe, soothing space after a long day. It’s also about bolsters and blankets, love notes sent to yourself, low lights and soft music, and feeling completely at ease.
At NMH, we give to a different charity each week, and this week, we are giving to Pups Without Borders working to rescue pups of all ages.</description></item><item><title>Over the River and Through the Woods (Encore) | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540007/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Over the River and Through the Woods, and it’s a story about going home for Thanksgiving. It’s also about fresh rolls from the bakery, late-night card games, and sitting at a long kitchen table with people who know you well.
Subscribe for ad-free, bonus, and extra-long episodes now! https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/premium-subscription
Purchase Our Book: https://bit.ly/Nothing-Much-Happens
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Thanksgiving at Weathervane Farm | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Thanksgiving at Weathervane Farm, and it's a story about coming together to celebrate on a cool day out in the country. It’s also about a busy kitchen crowded with friends, donkeys lined up along the split rail fence, music played in the open air, and building a family of our friends, furry and otherwise.
Subscribe for ad-free, bonus, and extra-long episodes now!
→ nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>At The Parade (Encore) | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “At the Parade” and it’s a story about a tradition to start off Thanksgiving morning. It’s also about the sky at dawn, streaked with pink, noticing small things that make life sweet and a marching band coming down Main Street.
Subscribe for ad-free, bonus and extra long episodes now! https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/premium-subscription
Purchase Our Book: https://bit.ly/Nothing-Much-Happens
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Joy of Missing Out | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called The Joy of Missing Out, and it’s a story about recharging your body when your battery has run down. It’s also about frost on the windows, reading a favorite book snuggled deep under the covers, being honest about what you need, and giving others permission to do the same.
Subscribe for ad-free, bonus and extra long episodes now! nothingmuchhappens.com/premium-subscription
At NMH, we give to a different charity each week, and this week we are giving to Greyhound Rescue.</description></item><item><title>Sunday Reset (Encore) | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Sunday Reset and it’s a story about a day set aside to plan for a good week ahead. It’s also about sheets hung on the line, drying in the last warm rays of the autumn, a record spinning on the turntable and a changed outlook after advice from a friend.
Subscribe for ad-free, bonus and extra long episodes now! https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/premium-subscription
Purchase Our Book: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>The Middle Path | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called The Middle Path, and it’s a story about a trek down an unknown trail at the park. It’s also about red berries on a vine, the fog of your breath in the late autumn air, geese crossing the sky, and making space for the beauty that lives all around you.
Our Premium Plus Feed has over 30 exclusive bonus episodes. I’ve just written a really nice story called Afternoon Tea that lives on that feed.</description></item><item><title>Bells and Whistles (Encore) | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Bells and Whistles, and it’s a story about being in the right place at the right time to hear something special. It’s also about seashells on a shelf, stacks of pumpkins on storefront stoops, and the trips we take to bring each other back home. It was inspired by a conversation I had with our pre-order winner, a lovely lady named Ginger. Her memories set my imagination spinning, and this is where it landed.</description></item><item><title>Sycamore &amp; the Gravestones, Part 3 | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Sycamore and The Gravestones, Part 3, and is the finale of this year's Halloween special. It’s a story about a good deed undertaken in a forgotten corner of the village. It’s also about train tracks and moss, mending something that was long broken, and being seen for who you are.
We give to a different charity each week, and this week we are giving to a charity founded in my own neighborhood.</description></item><item><title>Sycamore &amp; the Gravestones, Part 2 | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Sycamore and The Gravestones Part 2, and it is a story about a tall tree at the edge of the Inn and the secret it holds in one of its dark knots. It’s also about cornstalks and strings of purple and orange lights, crochet hooks and ink pens, and a new friendship that will make the coming winter so sweet. Purchase Our Book: https://bit.</description></item><item><title>Sycamore &amp; the Gravestones, Part 1 | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Sycamore and the Gravestones (Part 1), and apart from that being the best band name I’ve ever heard in my life, it is the first of our three-part Halloween special. It’s a story about a trip back to the Curios Shop and plans for one of the best times of year. It’s also about words written in blue chalk on a board, a dream about a familiar tree, and a way to remember others with kindness and care.</description></item><item><title>Fall Fair (Encore) | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story this week is called Fall Fair and it’s a story about a day with loved ones out where the blue ribbons are handed out and the cider is being served. It’s also about a scarf wrapped twice around your shoulders, horses grazing in an open field, and the way simple good feelings show up when you’re paying attention.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Buy the book</description></item><item><title>The Corn Maze or The Say Yes Club | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called The Corn Maze, or The Say Yes Club and it’s a story about a trip out into the country as the leaves fall. It’s also about the smell of dried corn stalks, kettle corn, and wood chips and finding a group of friends to have adventures with.
We give to a different charity each week and this week we are giving to Lonely Whale who's work to prevent plastic waste from entering the ocean.</description></item><item><title>The Crow's Nest (Encore) | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “The Crow’s Nest” and it’s about a hike to a high spot when the trees are turning in the Autumn. It’s also about the generosity of a stranger, a bowl of granola, and a chance meeting where the forest thins and the view is best.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Buy the book
Get beautiful NMH merch
Get autographed copies
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes</description></item><item><title>Fallen Trees &amp; Firewood | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Fallen Trees and Firewood, and it’s a story about a day spent in a meadow beside a cabin in the woods. It’s also about a task made easier by a neighbor, dogs running together through dry leaves, the glory of the mountains and the generosity of trees.
We give to a different charity each week, and this week we are giving to the Nature Conservancy, whose purpose is to tackle the dual threats of accelerated climate change and unprecedented biodiversity loss.</description></item><item><title>Rosemary For Remembrance (Encore) | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540021/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Rosemary, for Remembrance and it’s a story about preparing a garden for the coming frost. It’s also about a row of pumpkins waiting to be claimed, what the poets have to say about herbs, and the unending generosity of nature.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Subscribe to our bonus and ad-free episodes, request a cameo from Kathryn, and learn more about the village of Nothing Much at www.</description></item><item><title>The Porch Steps | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called The Porch Steps, and it’s a story about tending to a satisfying chore on a cool day. It’s also about acorns falling on the sidewalk, the scent of a wood fire on a cool night, a daydream about the wind, and stepping back to take in a job well done.
We give to a different charity each week, and this week we are giving to the Sierra Club.</description></item><item><title>Fall Foraging | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Fall Foraging and it’s a story about the first signs of the changing seasons and foods that go along with them. It’s also about a tart lemony spice harvested from a plant growing freely along the road, crabapples, and the bounty of autumn when you know where to look.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Buy the book
Get beautiful NMH merch</description></item><item><title>The Big Day | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called The Big Day, and it’s a story about a ceremony held beside the lake on a soft September day. It’s also about piano music drifting through the air, champagne corks popping, catching ahold of moments as they pass, both big and small, and the whole village of Nothing Much coming together to celebrate love.
We give to a different charity each week and this week we are giving to The International Committee of the Red Cross.</description></item><item><title>Something Blue | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Something Blue, and it brings us a little closer to a much-anticipated event in the village of Nothing Much. It’s a story about autumn skies and turning leaves. It’s also about a kitten wrapped in a shawl, star anise and peppermint, and letting yourself love again after loss.
We give to a different charity each week, and this week we are giving to the World Central Kitchen.</description></item><item><title>Something Borrowed | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540026/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Something Borrowed, and it’s the next installment in our series leading up to a special day here in the Village of Nothing Much. It’s a story about early morning at the Inn. It’s also about pretty plates brought out of the pantry cupboards... cardamom and cinnamon... and remembering that you don’t have to do everything on your own.
We give to a different charity each week and this week we are giving to the GoFundMe Education Fund.</description></item><item><title>Something New | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540027/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Something New and it’s a story about stumbling upon a
beautiful place on a late summer bike ride. It’s also about lily pads, an X marked on a
map and the joy of watching a friend step into a new season of their life.
We give to a different charity each week and this week we are giving to the Fruit
Tree Planting Foundation, Working to alleviate world hunger, combat climate change,</description></item><item><title>Something Old | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540028/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Something Old and it’s a story about a gift found on a treasure hunt. It’s also about taking the time to do something well, an embroidery hoop and an orange ribbon and seeing magic in every day objects that can tell stories from the past.
Our charity this week is Sea Shepherd They work to conserve and protect wildlife in the world’s oceans and ecosystems.</description></item><item><title>Retreat | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540029/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Retreat and it’s a story about some time spent somewhere quiet and calm. It’s also about paths through a pine forest, the soft experience of living moment to moment and a butterfly finding jasmine as she flits among plants deep in the woods.
We give to a different charity each week and this week we are giving to The Maui Strong Fund. The fund is providing financial resources that can be deployed quickly, with a focus on rapid response and recovery for the devastating wildfires on Maui.</description></item><item><title>Camping Out | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540030/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Camping Out and it’s a story about a tent set up in the backyard on a summer night. It’s also about fireflies blinking from between the trees, a pep talk that helps you forget your worries and a snoring dog, stretched out between the sleeping bags.
We give to a different charity each week and this week we are giving to Whaley Children’s Center in my hometown of Flint Michigan.</description></item><item><title>Special Delivery at Weathervane Farm | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540031/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Special Delivery at Weathervane Farm and it’s a story about getting chores done in the farmyard on a summer afternoon. It’s also about the animals having their say, a rest with the cows in their pasture, and an invitation stuck to the fridge with a heart-shaped magnet.
We give to a different charity each week and this week we are giving to NAMI, the National Association for Mental Illness www.</description></item><item><title>Stone Fruit | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540032/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Stone Fruit and it’s a story about a sweet part of the summer season. It’s also about how many pecks make a bushel, lovely silly kid logic, apple blossoms, and vanilla, and picking the best peach with your own two hands.
We give to a different charity each week and this week we are giving to the National Audubon Society https://www.audubon.org/ “We protect birds and the places they need.</description></item><item><title>The Boathouse | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540033/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called The Boathouse and it’s a story about an escape down to the end of the dock on a hot day. It’s also about a drawer full of old maps with dotted lines to mark journeys taken, the scent of lavender on your skin, and enjoying the pockets of ordinary magic wherever they can be found.
This week we are giving to Ferst Readers (ferstreaders.</description></item><item><title>Summer Storm (Encore) | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540034/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Summer Storm and it’s a story about a cool cloudy day enjoyed from a favorite spot. It’s also about a simmering pot of soup on the stove, taking a day for pure rest, and an old friend to learn lessons with.
Purchase Our Book: https://bit.ly/Nothing-Much-Happens
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Heirloom | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540035/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Heirloom and it’s a story about a garden in the middle of summer. It’s also about things handed down through generations, making and keeping friends of all ages, and a stack of farmer’s almanacs in the quiet corner of a shed.
We give to a different charity each week and this week we are giving to https://www.guidingeyes.org/ They provide guide dogs to people with vision loss.</description></item><item><title>RSVP | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540036/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called RSVP and it’s a story about a stack of envelopes on their way to being delivered. It’s also about a day many have suspected was on its way, the view from the front porch swing and how good it is to have something to look forward to.
This week we are giving to monafoundation.org. They work to support grassroots initiatives around the world that educate all children, empower women and girls, and enable them to transform their own communities.</description></item><item><title>Joyride | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540037/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Joyride and it’s a story about a spontaneous trip for two friends on a summer day. It’s also about music coming from the records shop’s door, a new book in a beloved series and riding off into the sunset with the windows rolled down. We give to a different charity each week and this week we are giving to The Dougy Center www.dougy.org The Dougy Center provides grief support in a safe place for children, teens, young adults, and their families.</description></item><item><title>Magic Words | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540038/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Magic Words and it’s a story about a trip into town on summer morning. It’s also about the scent of fresh-cut lumber, a dog biscuit buried in the flower beds, how a moment at the start of the day can alter your path, and something in a shop window that catches your eye. We give to a different charity each week and this week we are giving to Alliance for the Great Lakes at greatlakes.</description></item><item><title>The Waves at Night | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540039/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called The Waves at Night and it’s a continuation of last week’s story, still set at the cottage on a warm day. It’s also about poppies blooming by the roadside, a journal waiting beside the glider on the porch, and sleeping with the windows open as the waves roll in on the beach. We give to a different charity each week and this week we are giving to Outright International.</description></item><item><title>A Day at the Cottage | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540040/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 09:26:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called A Day at the Cottage and it’s a story about settling back into a beloved place as the weather warms up. It’s also about a cupboard full of old dishes that have served meals for decades, a stack of magazines to flip through from the lounge chair, and a love for hand-me-downs and the memories they carry.
We give to a different charity each week and this week we are giving to Alliance for the Great Lakes at greatlakes.</description></item><item><title>Strawberry Moon | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540041/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Strawberry Moon and it’s a story about dusk on the porch on one of the first warm evenings of summer. It’s also about the lit window of a neighbor’s house, the quiet tick of clock in the hall and a good book before bed. This week we are giving to International Rescue Committee whose purpose is to help people whose lives and livelihoods are shattered by conflict and disaster, including the climate crisis, to survive, recover and gain control over their future.</description></item><item><title>The Bookfair | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540042/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called The Bookfair and it’s a story about a love of reading and the creativity that inspires. It’s also about the last days of school before summer vacation, taking class outside into the open air and the feeling of watching little ones grow up and expand their worlds.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Piano | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540043/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called The Piano and it’s a story about an out-of-tune instrument ready for a new owner. It’s also about birds with glimmering feathers, an old Victorian house full of treasures, and a friendship formed from an act of generosity.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Lilac Grower | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540044/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called The Lilac Grower and it’s a story about a beloved flower that blooms briefly in the spring. It’s also about a clothesline strung with a new cord, a serendipitous meeting on a dirt road, and a reminder of how to be a good and gentle neighbor.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dandelions and Mayapples | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540045/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Dandelions and Mayapples and it’s a story about a trip down to the creek on a spring afternoon. It’s also about a bench on the bank where the sound of the water echoes, rhododendrons, and stone steps, and giving yourself the grace to ebb and flow.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>At the Tower Mill | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540046/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called At the Tower Mill and it’s a story about the sails of a windmill turning in the Spring breeze. It’s also about a warm morning and breakfast in the open air, cherry trees, carved burstone, and the things that bring neighbors together.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Five Year Anniversary Special! | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540047/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Let&amp;rsquo;s celebrate five years of bedtime stories and sweet dreams together with this special Q &amp;amp; A episode with Kathryn and Bob! While still relaxing and calm, this episode is best saved for a time other than bedtime.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Old Houses (Reprise) | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540048/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “Old Houses” and it’s a story about a wandering amble through an unknown neighborhood. It’s also about a forgotten piece of music in an old piano bench, a penny pressed into a sidewalk, and the stories we tell about the places we live.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Back Home Again | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540049/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Back Home Again and it is the final chapter (for now) in the great saga of Marmalade the cat and her dog friends, Crumb and Birdy. It’s about the end of a trip away and the memories that are carried home after. It’s also about a sunny plaza and cups of lemonade, falling in love, and a tea party that serves catnip and biscuits.</description></item><item><title>Marmalade at the Inn Part 3 | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540050/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Marmalade at the Inn Part Three because I just have too much to tell you about Marmalade the cat, and her dog friends Crumb and Birdy. It’s a story about a bit of the Inn’s history. It’s also about fresh sheets, a package waiting at the front door, and the sweet sound of ringing bells.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Marmalade at the Inn Part 2 | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540051/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Marmalade at the Inn Part Two and if you didn’t hear part one, it couldn’t matter less. It’s a story about the beautiful old Inn that sits on the edge of the lake and the Innkeeper who takes care of all who stay there. It’s also about enjoying a new routine, the healing result of a bit of affection, and a bright morning at the end of a long winter.</description></item><item><title>Sticks and Stones (Special Bonus) | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540052/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “Sticks and Stones” and it’s a story about solitude and slowing down for a long walk. It’s also about a stream full of colored rocks, one man’s treasure, and a spot in the forest for admiring beautiful things.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Marmalade at the Inn | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540053/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Marmalade at the Inn and it’s a story about a few days at the Inn on the Lake. It’s also about dog beds laid out in front of the fire, three cups of coffee poured in the library, and a small adventure for three of our favorite souls in the village of Nothing Much.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Catnap | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540054/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Catnap and it’s a story about Marmalade the cat and Crumb the dog as they find ways to play through the winter. It’s also about a spark of something sweet that begins to grow between friends, a pup cup enjoyed on a heated patio, and a suitcase ready to be packed.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Snowfall at the Bakery Part 3 | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540055/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Snowfall at the Bakery Part Three and it’s a story about the snowmen in the park and the sledding hill beside them. It’s also about a memory of a grandfather in front of the fire, a pocketful of dog treats, and the simple joy of playing in the snow. This week we are giving to the Turkish Red Crescent http://www.kizilay.org.tr/ https://linktr.ee/nothingmuchhappens
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Snowfall at the Bakery Part 2 | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540056/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Snowfall at the Bakery Part Two and it’s a story about closing up shop and stepping out into falling flakes. It’s also about a bag full of wrapped treats, knowing today that you’ll be snowed in tomorrow, and a lost glove on its way back to its owner.
We give to charitable organizations each week and this week we are giving to Syrian American Medical Society (SAMS) https://www.</description></item><item><title>Snowfall at the Bakery | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540057/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Snowfall at the Bakery and it’s a story about the reappearance of winter after a few weeks of mild weather. It’s also about hot chocolate made with care, schoolchildren let out early and the prospect of snowmen in the park.
We give to a different charity each week and this week we are giving to National Alliance to End Homelessness at endhomelessness.org They are committed to preventing and ending homelessness in the United States.</description></item><item><title>Quiet Celebration | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540058/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Quiet Celebration and it’s a story about softly stepping into the next year of your life. It’s also about a good dream that lingers after waking, a glass raised with best wishes and a cake decorated with orange slices and rosettes.
This week we are giving to The Arc of the United States thearc.org Their Purpose is &amp;ldquo;to promote and protect the human rights of people with intellectual and developmental disabilities and actively support their full inclusion and participation in the community throughout their lifetimes.</description></item><item><title>Winter Views | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540059/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Winter Views and it’s a story about some different things to enjoy or look forward to in the winter. It’s also about a cardinal singing from the branches, a jar of huckleberry jam and the extra minutes of light that come with each day after the solstice.
Thanks to your support, we give to a different charity each week. This week we are giving to International Justice Mission https://ijm.</description></item><item><title>The Innkeeper's Blanket | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540060/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 11:34:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called The Innkeeper’s Blanket and it’s a story about a favorite hobby, rediscovered in the quiet of winter. It’s also about a simmering pot in the kitchen, geese gathering before they fly and making something by hand that is perfectly imperfect.
This week we are giving to the Fred Rogers Institute, at fredrogersinstitute.org. Their purpose is to advance the legacy of Fred Rogers by investing in the strengths of families and caring adults to support the healthy development of children.</description></item><item><title>Winter Getaway Part 3, Chef's Kitchen | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540061/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Winter Getaway Part Three or Chef’s kitchen and it’s a story about a humble meal cooked for a friend. It’s also about hand written notes in the margins of a cookbook, a gift wrapped in brown paper and the steam rising up off of a bowl of soup.
Thanks to your support we donate to a new charity every week and this week we are sending some help to World Central Kitchen at wck.</description></item><item><title>Winter Getaway Part Two or The Chalet | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540062/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Winter Getaway Part Two or The Chalet and it’s a story about an abundance of time to do nothing with. It’s also about a steaming bathtub, catching a moment with all of your senses, and a way to say I love you. https://linktr.ee/nothingmuchhappens
Our charitable donation this week goes to https://bookaid.org.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Winter Getaway | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540063/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Winter Getaway and it’s a story about an invitation that arrives on the back of a postcard. It’s also about glittering snow and a cabin tucked into a mountain side, a stack of new books and deep deep rest. https://linktr.ee/nothingmuchhappens
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Shooting Stars | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540064/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Shooting Stars and it’s a story about a wish made in the quiet of the new year. It’s also about shaking off the chill of winter, a soft towel fresh from the laundry and the deep peace of being at home with yourself. https://linktr.ee/nothingmuchhappens
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Comfort and Joy | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540065/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Comfort and Joy and it’s a story about adding light to the dark evenings of winter. It’s also about bringing back a sweet neighborhood tradition, a rowen tree laced with lights and a paper chain to count down the days. https://linktr.ee/nothingmuchhappens
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Holiday at Weathervane Farm | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540066/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “Holiday at Weathervane Farm” and it’s a story about lighting up the farm for some winter guests. It’s also about hay rides through snowy fields, the ducks waddling back from a day at the pond, and a new calf born who will only ever know kindness. https://linktr.ee/nothingmuchhappens
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Model Trains and Make-Believe | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540067/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Model Trains and Make Believe and it’s a story about a tiny world full of bustling streets and railroad tracks. It’s also about a red and white box of popcorn, a dining car with white table clothes and being never too old to imagine. https://linktr.ee/nothingmuchhappens
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Heavy Snow at the Cabin | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540068/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Heavy Snow at the Cabin and it’s a story about a morning spent watching the winter arrive. It’s also about taking your time to make something delicious, woodsmoke rising from chimneys and the contagious simple joy of dogs. https://linktr.ee/nothingmuchhappens
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Friendsgiving, Again | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540069/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Friendsgiving, Again and it’s a story about a growing tradition and the new people and places folded into it with each year. It’s also about rosemary trees, a Christmas village laid out on a piano lid, and a big old building made merry for the holiday. https://linktr.ee/nothingmuchhappens
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ship in a Bottle | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540070/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Ship in a Bottle and it’s a story about a crate of bequests ready to be unwrapped. It’s also about the dark bark of oak trees after a storm, garden benches waiting to be sat on and the ordinary magic of handmade things. https://linktr.ee/nothingmuchhappens
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sunday Reset | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540071/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Sunday Reset and it’s a story about a day set aside to plan for a good week ahead. It’s also about sheets hung on the line, drying in the last warm rays of the autumn, a record spinning on the turntable and a changed outlook after advice from a friend. https://linktr.ee/nothingmuchhappens
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Behind the Curtain (Halloween Special Part 2) | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540072/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Behind the Curtain and it’s the second part of our Halloween special this season. It’s a story about two friends meeting for the first time. It’s also about a copper kettle simmering on the stove, a gentle approach to tip people toward kindness and cinnamon sticks and sliced apples. https://linktr.ee/nothingmuchhappens
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Curios Shop (Halloween Special pt. 1) | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540073/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called The Curios Shop and it’s the first in our two part Halloween special this year. It’s a story about a little shop in downtown Nothing Much, that takes the right set of circumstances to be found. It’s also about creaky wood floors, an old book covered in velvet and a small grey cat with yellow eyes. https://linktr.ee/nothingmuchhappens
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Lookout | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540074/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called The Lookout and it’s a story about a hidden place deep in the woods with a very special view. It’s also about all the different names for Juneberries, a maple leaf and green stone, and enjoying your time when you’re alone. https://linktr.ee/nothingmuchhappens
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Autumn Ride | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540075/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Autumn Ride and it’s about pedaling with friends under falling leaves. It’s also about treats from bakery, wrapped up and ready to share, rediscovering a pure feeling of joy out on the road and a hoodie zipped up to your chin. https://linktr.ee/nothingmuchhappens
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Field Trip Part Two | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540076/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “Field Trip, Part Two” and it’s a story about a bus ride out to the pumpkin patch. It’s also about a cold glass of cider enjoyed in the autumn air, a pumpkin with a curly green stem and making a memory that will last. Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens https://linktr.ee/nothingmuchhappens Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Field Trip | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540077/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Field Trip and it’s a story about a rite of passage for lots of second graders and the people in their lives who get to go along for the ride. It’s also about a bus waiting by the playground, learning to be a better listener, and a form stuck to the front of the fridge. Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens https://linktr.ee/nothingmuchhappens Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>The Pecan Tree | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540078/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called The Pecan Tree and it’s a story about having just the right tool for the right moment. It’s also about a piano playing in a neighbor’s house, gravel paths in a garden and an afternoon visit from a few friends at the split rail fence.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens https://linktr.ee/nothingmuchhappens Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Sleeping Weather | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540079/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “Sleeping Weather” and it’s a story about a break from the heat and humidity. It’s also about the view from the porch swing at night, deer walking quietly through the corn fields and clearing your mind with paper and pen and end of the day. Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens https://linktr.ee/nothingmuchhappens Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Librarian | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540080/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “The Librarian” and it’s a story about the quiet of the closed up library at the end of the day. It’s also about the books that sometimes get overlooked on the top shelf, a string of lights over an outdoor table, and knowing what your next book will be. Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens https://linktr.ee/nothingmuchhappens Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm</description></item><item><title>The Corner Store | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540081/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called The Corner Store and it’s a story about the aisles of the neighborhood grocery where there are always interesting things to discover. It’s also about a display of school supplies, a recipe from a neighbor and the feeling of belonging in a particular place. Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens https://linktr.ee/nothingmuchhappens Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Old Friends | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540082/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Old Friends and it’s a story about plans falling apart so that something even better can fall together. It’s also about a spoonful of sugar stirred into a cup of hot coffee, the ease of being with those who know you best, and a movie marathon watched from the couch while the rain comes down. Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens https://linktr.ee/nothingmuchhappens Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Raining Cats and Dogs | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540083/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Raining Cats and Dogs and it’s a story about a playdate for a few furry friends. It’s also about someone’s first trip to the groomers, lightning flashing through the curtains, and looking out at the rain as a kitty purrs in your arms. Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens https://linktr.ee/nothingmuchhappens Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Yard Sale OR Another Man's Treasure | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540084/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Yard Sale or Another Man’s Treasure and it’s a story about a neighborhood event on a summer day. It’s also about sidewalk chalk art, a collection of salt and pepper shakers and red petunias growing in a flower box. Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens https://linktr.ee/nothingmuchhappens Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Potter's Wheel | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540085/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called The Potter’s Wheel and it’s a story about the pleasures of making something with your own two hands. It’s also about laundry drying on the line, a little room that is just for you, and initials etched into the bottom of a vase. Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens https://linktr.ee/nothingmuchhappens Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Beach Walk | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540086/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Beach Walk, and it’s a story about meeting the morning light where the water meets the land. It’s also about the first step into the cool water, a dog chasing a stick into the waves, and a beach towel laid out neatly in the sand. Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens https://linktr.ee/nothingmuchhappens Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Fireflies on a Summer Night ENCORE | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540087/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “Fireflies on a summer night” and it’s a story about the magic language of lighting bugs. It’s also about the cool quiet feeling of being all by yourself in the moonlight, words that start with the letter G, and a persistent enduring belief in magic. Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens https://linktr.ee/nothingmuchhappens Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Summer at the Inn Part 3 | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540088/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is the last installment in our Summer at the Inn series, at least for now. It’s a story about a book waiting to be picked up and read. It’s also about a cool sleeping porch, empty and quiet in the afternoon, a cup of sweet espresso and having a bit of time all to yourself. Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens https://linktr.ee/nothingmuchhappens Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Summer at the Inn Part 2 | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540089/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is taking us back to the Inn for part 2 in this series. It’s a story about a busy afternoon for the innkeeper. It’s also about watermelons, ripe and ready to cut, a dinner bell ringing on the porch, and how good it feel to care for and be cared for. So get cozy and ready to sleep. Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens https://linktr.ee/nothingmuchhappens Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Summer at the Inn | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540090/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Summer at the Inn and it’s a story about a morning by the lake at the great old house. It’s also about setting a table with care, a blue jay sitting at a feeder and how to borrow someone’s else’s joy and wear it as your own. So get cozy and ready to sleep. Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens https://linktr.ee/nothingmuchhappens Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Hummingbird | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540091/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Hummingbird and it’s a story about the calm after the storm. It’s also about a cool glass of iced coffee drunk on the front steps, a visitor to the helenium flowers and making a habit out of noticing when things are good. So get cozy and ready to sleep. Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rain and Shine | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540092/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “Rain and Shine” and it’s a story about a solid day’s effort in the garden followed by a long shower and dinner as the storm clouds roll in. It’s also about the way the rain sounds falling on the roof, walnuts and pumpkin seeds and a night of excellent sleeping weather. So get cozy and ready to sleep. Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens</description></item><item><title>At the Drive-in | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540093/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called At the Drive-In and it’s a story about a chance meeting on a summer evening. It’s also about bubbles and whirligigs, stretching out on a blanket as the screen flickers to life and the fun that can come when you stop overthinking and just say yes. So get cozy and ready to sleep. Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>The Canoe | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540094/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called the The Canoe and it’s a story about sunny days spent near and on the water. It’s also about a journal to write about the best parts of the day in, falling asleep in crisp cool sheets, and the way sunlight reflects on water. https://linktr.ee/nothingmuchhappens
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Road Trip | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540095/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Road Trip and it’s a story about riding down the interstate with the windows down on a sunny day. It’s also about a little town down the road to explore, a plaque on a park bench, and the first of the summer strawberries.
https://linktr.ee/nothingmuchhappens
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Petrichor | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540096/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Petrichor and it’s story about things getting greener as the spring rain falls. It’s also about a record player with a favorite album on the turntable, deer dozing in the grass and making a habit out of enjoying yourself. Listen to Kathryn&amp;rsquo;s new mediation podcast through one of the links below: Apple:https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1621073052?app=podcast&amp;amp;at=1000lHKX&amp;amp;ct=linktree_http&amp;amp;itscg=30200&amp;amp;itsct=lt_p&amp;amp;ls=1&amp;amp;mt=2
Spotify: https://open.spotify.com/show/3FXqLRuKTFbNStskj7xJGZ
Google Podcasts: https://podcasts.google.com/?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9mZWVkcy5zaW1wbGVjYXN0LmNvbS9JcHplRWw4VQ
Castbox: https://castbox.fm/vic/1621073052
Or listen here: https://feeds.simplecast.com/IpzeEl8U</description></item><item><title>First This, Episode one | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540097/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 13:31:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Let Kathryn lead your through a short meditation and learn a very useful mantra along the way. If you are overwhelmed, have a lot on your plate, this is the episode you need right now. Listen to Kathryn&amp;rsquo;s new mediation podcast through one of the links below: Apple:https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1621073052?app=podcast&amp;amp;at=1000lHKX&amp;amp;ct=linktree_http&amp;amp;itscg=30200&amp;amp;itsct=lt_p&amp;amp;ls=1&amp;amp;mt=2
Spotify: https://open.spotify.com/show/3FXqLRuKTFbNStskj7xJGZ
Google Podcasts: https://podcasts.google.com/?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9mZWVkcy5zaW1wbGVjYXN0LmNvbS9JcHplRWw4VQ
Castbox: https://castbox.fm/vic/1621073052
Or listen here: https://feeds.simplecast.com/IpzeEl8U
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Flower Day at the Market | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540098/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Flower Day at the Market and it’s a story about the signs of summer showing up in parks and gardens and the market. It’s also about sidewalk sales, a guitar being tuned and fresh growing things as far as the eye can see. Listen to Kathryn&amp;rsquo;s new mediation podcast through one of the links below: Apple:https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1621073052?app=podcast&amp;amp;at=1000lHKX&amp;amp;ct=linktree_http&amp;amp;itscg=30200&amp;amp;itsct=lt_p&amp;amp;ls=1&amp;amp;mt=2
Spotify: https://open.spotify.com/show/3FXqLRuKTFbNStskj7xJGZ
Google Podcasts: https://podcasts.google.com/?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9mZWVkcy5zaW1wbGVjYXN0LmNvbS9JcHplRWw4VQ
Castbox: https://castbox.fm/vic/1621073052</description></item><item><title>The Bicycle Shop | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540099/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called The Bicycle Shop and it’s a story about a dream that finds its time and place to come true. It’s also about shiny chrome bumpers, a mug of coffee drunk in the quiet of the shop in the morning and what can happen when you stop waiting to feel ready. Listen to Kathryn&amp;rsquo;s new mediation podcast through one of the links below: Apple:https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1621073052?app=podcast&amp;amp;at=1000lHKX&amp;amp;ct=linktree_http&amp;amp;itscg=30200&amp;amp;itsct=lt_p&amp;amp;ls=1&amp;amp;mt=2</description></item><item><title>The Front Door and the Back Door | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540100/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called The Front Door and the Back Door and it’s a story about a bit of Spring Cleaning inside and outside the house. It’s also about butterflies drawn in chalk on the sidewalk, a message arriving at the just the right moment, and seedlings waiting for their chance to grow. So get cozy and ready to sleep. Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>The Weathervane | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540101/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called The Weathervane and it’s a story about a few acres out in the country. It’s also about the smell of fresh hay on a warm morning, mud boots for getting chores done and a pocketful of carrots for the donkeys in the last stall of the barn. So get cozy and ready to sleep. Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Dog Walk | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540102/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Dog Walk and it’s a story about a daily excursion out into the neighborhood streets. It’s also about games played through the fence, walking with a spring in your step and a window seat where you can watch the street. So get cozy and ready to sleep. Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Spring Cleanup | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540103/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Spring Cleanup and it’s a story about one of the first warm sunny days of the year. It’s also about bird feeders full of seed hanging in the branches, a vintage Tupperware box full of treats, and the simple idea that many hands make light work. So get cozy and ready to sleep. Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>The Pantry | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540104/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “The Pantry” and it’s a story about a chore that becomes a sort of meditation. It’s also about neat rows of cans with their labels all turned the same way, the satisfaction of a job well done and taking care of little you, even once you’re all grown up. So get cozy and ready to sleep. Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Begin Again | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540105/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Begin Again and it’s a story about about a reset scheduled for the equinox. It’s also about sunrise watched from an open hatch back on a road outside of town, birds and squirrels ringing in the spring and making your own rituals to mark a moment. So get cozy and ready to sleep. Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Pillow Forts and Treehouses | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540106/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 10:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Pillow Forts and Treehouses and it’s a story about a rainy afternoon tucked into a hideaway. It’s also about the big ideas of children, a bowl of pretzels and apple slices, and remembering that you are never too old to enjoy a fort. So get cozy and ready to sleep. Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm</description></item><item><title>Hyacinths | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540107/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Hyacinths and it’s a story about a sneak peak at Spring from the tail end of Winter. It’s also about sweet potatoes and shelves full of sauces and spices, a gift given while a back is turned and the patience that comes with a bit of hope and fresh air. So get cozy and ready to sleep. Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Opening Night | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540108/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540108/</guid><description>Podcast Description So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Our story tonight is called Opening Night and it’s a story about the moments before the curtain rises. It’s also about flowers in the green room, the electric feeling of stepping out from the wings and an armful of programs waiting to be passed out. Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Dog Days of Summer | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540109/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “The Dog Days of Summer” and it’s a story about the a day with a best friend. It’s also about a cucumber picked from the garden, meeting friends in the park the most important lessons we learn from the animals we share our lives with.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Supper Club | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540110/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Supper Club and it’s a story about adventures in cooking and friendship. It’s also about less being more, a bubbling pandowdy and patience it takes to carefully fold a dumpling.
Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens Get beautiful NMH merch: https://www.podswag.com/collections/nothing-much-happens Get an autographed copies: https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/nmh-stuff Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mixtape | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540111/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Mixtape and it’s a story about a box of memories tangled up with songs. It’s also about the messages we send with the tracks we pick out, new batteries in an old walkman and finding the music that helps you find yourself. Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens Get beautiful NMH merch: https://www.podswag.com/collections/nothing-much-happens Get an autographed copies: https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/nmh-stuff Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm</description></item><item><title>Breathe in, Breathe out | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540112/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “Breathe in, Breathe out” and it’s a story about setting aside some time to just be in a special place. It’s also about a cup of green tea, learning to hop away a little less, and the goodness of knowing you are welcome. Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens Get beautiful NMH merch: https://www.podswag.com/collections/nothing-much-happens Get an autographed copies: https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/nmh-stuff Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Cold Snap and Crosswords | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540113/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Cold Snap and Crosswords and it’s a story about a midwinter morning, when you’ve got no plans to leave the house. It’s also about feeling snug and tucked well away from the winter wind, books of puzzles and the view from the top floor. Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens Get beautiful NMH merch: https://www.podswag.com/collections/nothing-much-happens Get an autographed copies: https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/nmh-stuff Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Crumb Comes Home | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540114/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Crumb Comes Home and it’s a story about a little dog and his first few months with his new family. It’s also about learning new things, Christmas sweaters and taking long naps when you know you’re home for good. Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens Get beautiful NMH merch: https://www.podswag.com/collections/nothing-much-happens Get an autographed copies: https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/nmh-stuff Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Solarium | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540115/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called The Solarium and it’s a story about a sunny break in a cold month. It’s also about sweet-smelling citrus, a warm bright place to read a book and taking the time to charge your battery all the way up. Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens Get beautiful NMH merch: https://www.podswag.com/collections/nothing-much-happens Get an autographed copies: https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/nmh-stuff Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Auld Lang Syne | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540116/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Auld Lang Syne, and it’s a story about daybreak on a new year. It’s also about a little book with a page missing, what we let go of and what we keep and the scent of woodsmoke on a January morning. Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens Get beautiful NMH merch: https://www.podswag.com/collections/nothing-much-happens Get an autographed copies: https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/nmh-stuff Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Over the Fence | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540117/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Over the Fence and it’s a story about two friends and their plans for the New Year. It’s also about shooting stars seen from the beach, letting go of things that no longer serve, and a bag of pastries passed over the fence. Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens Get beautiful NMH merch: https://www.podswag.com/collections/nothing-much-happens Get an autographed copies: https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/nmh-stuff Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>The Innkeeper's Holiday | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540118/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540118/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called The Innkeeper’s Holiday and it’s a story about a favorite time of year celebrated at the Inn by the lake. It’s also about glass ornaments and pinecones, twinkle lights on the water and caring for a place where cheer and merriment can live. Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens Get beautiful NMH merch: https://www.podswag.com/collections/nothing-much-happens Get an autographed copies: https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/nmh-stuff Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>The Holly and The Ivy | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540119/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called The Holly and the Ivy and it’s a story about a trip into the woods on the first snowy day of winter. It’s also about handmade gifts given in friendship, refreshing your perspective and snowy owls hidden in plain sight. So get cozy and ready to sleep. Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens Get beautiful NMH merch: https://www.podswag.com/collections/nothing-much-happens Get an autographed copies: https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/nmh-stuff Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Winter Market | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540120/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540120/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Winter Market, and it’s a story about a bustling marketplace on a bright December morning. It’s also about cups made on a spinning pottery wheel, pride in the skills and talent of one’s community, and hot chai and chestnuts from a street cart. So get cozy and ready to sleep. Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens Get beautiful NMH merch: https://www.podswag.com/collections/nothing-much-happens Get an autographed copies: https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/nmh-stuff Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Light a Candle | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540121/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Light a Candle and it’s a story about reminding each other about the light that lasts through the long nights of winter. It’s also about a busy kitchen full of family, cinnamon and walnuts, and a memory of something shared that felt very special. So get cozy and ready to sleep. Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens Get beautiful NMH merch: https://www.podswag.com/collections/nothing-much-happens Get an autographed copies: https://www.</description></item><item><title>At the Parade | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540122/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540122/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “At the Parade” and it’s a story about a tradition to start off Thanksgiving morning. It’s also about the sky at dawn, streaked with pink, noticing small things that make life sweet and a marching band coming down Main Street. So get cozy and ready to sleep. Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens Get an autographed copy and other merch here: https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/nmh-stuff Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>First Frost | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540123/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540123/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called First Frost and it’s a story about enjoying the sparkle of the first signs of winter. It’s also about a kitty watching the birds on a cold morning, pinecones scented with cinnamon and something precious waiting to be found. So get cozy and ready to sleep. Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens Get an autographed copy and other merch here: https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/nmh-stuff Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Autumn at the Cabin | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540124/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Autumn at the Cabin and it’s a story about some time away to rest and restore. It’s also about a stack of books waiting to be read, popcorn and apples and the feeling of having truly nothing to do but enjoy the passing days. So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get an autographed copy and other merch here: https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/nmh-stuff Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Table for One | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540125/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Table for one and its a story about a rainy afternoon watched from a favorite place. It’s also about an old radiator that hisses and bangs under the window, a meal that feels like love and enjoying the pleasure of your own company.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get an autographed copy and other merch here: https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/nmh-stuff Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Trick or Treat | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540126/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Trick or Treat and it’s a story about a roaming the streets on All Hallow’s Eve. It’s also about a gust of wind that turns you around, lit porch lights and making memories with the people you love. So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get an autographed copy and other merch here: https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/nmh-stuff Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Fall Fair | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540127/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story this week is called “Fall Fair” and it’s a story about a day with loved ones out where the blue ribbons are handed out and the cider is being served. It’s also about a scarf wrapped twice around your shoulders, horses grazing in an open field, and the way simple good feelings show up when you’re paying attention. So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Buy the book:http://hyperurl.</description></item><item><title>The Pumpkin Farmer | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540128/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540128/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “The Pumpkin Farmer” and it’s a story about a family tradition and the harvest that comes after a season of careful tending. It’s also about a long table set out beside the barn with every chair taken, a flannel shirt with the sleeves rolled up and living in step with the seasons. So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get an autographed copy and other merch here: https://www.</description></item><item><title>The Crow's Nest | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540129/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540129/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “The Crow’s Nest” and it’s about a hike to a high spot when the trees are turning in the Autumn. It’s also about the generosity of a stranger, a bowl of granola and a chance meeting where the forest thins and the view is best. So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get an autographed copy and other merch here: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Fall Foraging | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540130/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540130/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Fall Foraging and it’s a story about the first signs of the changing seasons and foods that go along with them. It’s also about a tart lemony spice harvested from a plant growing freely along the road, crabapples and the bounty of autumn when you know where to look. So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get an autographed copy and other merch here: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Harvest Moon | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540131/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “Harvest Moon” and it’s a story about a night around the bonfire under the full moon. It’s also about resetting when your mind gets jumbled up with details, the best way to cut chives and the closing in of the welcome autumn. So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get an autographed copy and other merch here: https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/nmh-stuff Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Marmalade and Crumb | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540132/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 13:10:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540132/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “Marmalade and Crumb” and it’s a story about a face looking up at you from a newspaper, its also about a new collar and leash, a first meeting that feels like a reunion and trusting your heart when it steers you in a direction you didn’t expect.
Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get an autographed copy and other merch here: https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/nmh-stuff
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>At the Diamond | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540133/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called At the Diamond and it’s a story about a warm day, stretched out on a blanket under a tree. It’s also about jumping through a sprinkler on soft green grass, a dried flower with blue petals and a home run hit out past center field. So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get an autographed copy and other merch here: https://www.</description></item><item><title>The Main Sail | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540134/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called The Main Sail and it’s a story about the end of the summer traditions up at the cottage on the river. It’s also about penny candy in a brown paper bag, the sun just before it sets and the ways we mark the time we spend with people we love.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get an autographed copy and other merch here: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Summer Storm | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540135/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Summer Storm and it’s a story about a cool cloudy day enjoyed from a favorite spot. It’s also about a simmering pot of soup on the stove, taking a day for pure rest and an old friend to learn lessons with.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get an autographed copy and other merch here: https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/nmh-stuff Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>The Phone Booth | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540136/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540136/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called The Phone Booth and it’s a story about a trip downtown with a forgotten envelope in hand. It’s also about a table of books for sale at the library, music coming from an open window in an alley and a message delivered years ago that becomes a way to live day to day.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens</description></item><item><title>Back To The Bakery | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540137/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Back to the Bakery and it’s a story about the early morning preparations made in the kitchen before the Village of Nothing Much wakes. It’s also about a kitty with a crooked tail, hot donuts set out on a tray and summer pick me up made with love.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get an autographed copy and other merch here: https://www.</description></item><item><title>From the Hammock | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540138/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540138/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called the From the Hammock and it’s a story about naps, and where and when and under what circumstances we take them. It’s also about a slow walk through the garden, jars of pickles put up in the cellar and knowing that what you seek is seeking you.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get an autographed copy and other merch here: https://www.</description></item><item><title>The Lake at the Inn | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540139/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called the Lake at the Inn and it’s a story about a misty summer morning on the water. It’s also about a mug of coffee poured by a friend, the sounds you hear when you truly stop to listen and a row boat just waiting to be pushed out away from shore.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get an autographed copy and other merch here: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Housewarming Part 2 | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540140/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540140/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Housewarming, part two and it’s the first time we’ve had a to be continued sort of story. It’s about a slow hunt for a gift for a friend. It’s also about freshly sharpened pencils, the stamp inside library books, and a daydream that connects the dots.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get an autographed copy and other merch here: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Housewarming | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540141/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Housewarming and it’s a story about an event marked on the calendar to look forward to. It’s also about a window seat full of houseplants, an invitation in a red envelope and a memory of a perfectly wrapped present.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get an autographed copy and other merch here: https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/nmh-stuff Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Daydreamer | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540142/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540142/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Daydreamer and it’s a story about drifting from one thought to the next, giving into a bit of nostalgia and imagining what might be. It’s also about help from a stranger, the sound of the school bus coming down the street and an open window on a spring morning.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get an autographed copy and other merch here: https://www.</description></item><item><title>The Tulip Farm | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540143/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540143/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called The Tulip Farm and it’s a story about a bright spring day among beds of flowers. It’s also about a gift left at dawn, redwing blackbirds, and soft moments that take your breath away.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get an autographed copy and other merch here: https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/nmh-stuff Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Toast and Marmalade | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540144/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540144/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Toast and Marmalade and it’s a story about the first few months of a lifelong friendship. It’s also about a collar with a bell on it, letting go of what ifs, and the joy of watching someone discover a year of firsts.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get an autographed copy and other merch here: https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/nmh-stuff Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Sugar Snow | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540145/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540145/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Sugar Snow and it’s a story about shifting seasons. It’s also about pots of pansies, breakfast for dinner and the people and places that teach us to play.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get an autographed copy and other merch here: https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/nmh-stuff Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Touchstone | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540146/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540146/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Touchstone and it’s a story about finding something unexpected along one’s path. It’s also about the way we think as children, thunder and lighting and the things we find when we keep our eyes open.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get an autographed copy and other merch here: https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/nmh-stuff Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.</description></item><item><title>People Watching and The Coffee Shop | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540147/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540147/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called People Watching and the Coffee Shop and it’s a story about the view from a table in the back corner, it’s also about found family, a neatly shoveled sidewalk and simple ways to feel connected. So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get an autographed copy and other merch here: https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/nmh-stuff Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.</description></item><item><title>Keepsake | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540148/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540148/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Keepsake and it’s a story about stepping back through time to remember a particular rainy day. It’s also about sunflowers, the things our younger selves can teach us and a scrap of something saved for years in a box.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get an autographed copy and other merch here: https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/nmh-stuff Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Clean Slate | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540149/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540149/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “Clean Slate” and it’s a story about a room of one’s own. It’s also about a jade plant on a window sill, a bit of still useful old technology, and figuring out what’s worth keeping and what’s not.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get an autographed copy and other merch here: https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/nmh-stuff Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>All The Way Around The Lake | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540150/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540150/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called All the way around the Lake and it’s a story about a slow walk on a cold day. It’s also about crossing bridges, a paper birch tree on an island and remembering things that were forgotten. So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get an autographed copy and other merch here: https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/nmh-stuff Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm</description></item><item><title>Game Night | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540151/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540151/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Game Night, and it’s a story about ringing in the new year with friends around the kitchen table. It’s also about a memory of card games with aunts and uncles, a secret ingredient and the importance of good old fashioned fun.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get an autographed copy and other merch here: https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/nmh-stuff This episode mentions alcohol.</description></item><item><title>City Sidewalks | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540152/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540152/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called City Sidewalks, and it’s a story about an evening looking into shop windows filled with Holiday displays. It’s also about miracles made in gingerbread, realizing when something is good, and the hushed excitement in a theater as the movie is about to begin.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get an autographed copy and other perch here: https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/nmh-stuff Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Lost &amp; Found | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540153/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540153/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Lost and Found and it’s a story about the first snowfall of the year. It’s also about firewood stacked high beside the hearth, paw prints in the snow and the magic of two paths crossing at just the right moment.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get an autographed copy here: https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/nmh-stuff (US only)
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Friendsgiving | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540154/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540154/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Friendsgiving and it’s a story about a meal shared on mismatched dishes across an old table. It’s also about a gate connecting two yards, the way crabapple trees grow, and making new traditions when things change.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get an autographed copy here: https://www.nothingmuchhappens.com/nmh-stuff (US only)
This episode mentions alcohol.
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Bells and Whistles | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540155/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540155/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Bells and Whistles and it’s a story about being in the right place at the right time to hear something special. It’s also about seashells on a shelf, stacks of pumpkins on storefront stoops and the trips we take to bring each other back home. It was inspired by a conversation I had with our pre-order winner, a lovely lady named Ginger. Her memories set my imagination spinning and this is where it landed.</description></item><item><title>The Other Innkeeper | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540156/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540156/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called The Other Innkeeper and it’s a story about a memory and the path it lays out. It’s also about a card waiting to fall into the right hands, creaking hallway floors and the end of something that may actually be a beginning.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Buy the book now yperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
For a spookified version of this episode go to https://www.</description></item><item><title>The Leaf House | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540157/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540157/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called The Leaf House and it’s a story about an autumn day spent working in the yard. It’s also a game remembered from childhood, a spider’s web spun on a chrysanthemum, and different ways to think about home.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Buy the book:http://hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>In The Bleachers | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540158/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540158/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called In the Bleachers, and it’s a story about a game watched on a crisp fall evening. It’s also about pumpkins on doorsteps, flannel shirts and remembering that there are lots of ways to grow.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonfire | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540159/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540159/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Bonfire and it’s a story about an evening on the beach toward the end of the summer. It’s also about bare feet in the sand, kite tails flapping in the air, and the subtle signs of the shifting season.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Summer Feast | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540160/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540160/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Summer Feast, and it’s a story about a meal eaten on a blanket spread over the grass. It’s also about shapes spotted in the clouds, whistle weeds and taking the time to savor some favorite flavors.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Labyrinth | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540161/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540161/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called The Labyrinth and it’s a story about a slow walk on a gravel path in mid-summer. It’s also about hidden places, unseen acts of kindness, the way cats sit in their windows and always always looking for magic.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>The Turnaround | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540162/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540162/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “The Turnaround” and it’s a story about a trip down a gravel road on a summer day. It’s also about bulrushes and bonfires, family stories and coming back to a place you know well.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>In the Map Room | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540163/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540163/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called In the Map Room and it’s a story about the pleasures of looking at the world drawn out on paper. It’s also about a gasp of koi fish in a pond, a bike ride that leads somewhere surprising and the view from the upper room of an old house.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Wind and Wildflowers | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540164/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540164/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Wind and Wildflowers and it’s a story about a summer afternoon walk in the woods. It’s also about the moments before the rain rolls in, the secret life of trees and a glass of iced tea drunk from a back porch glider.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.</description></item><item><title>The Inn Keeper | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540165/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540165/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called The Inn Keeper and it’s a story about a morning in early summer on the lake. It’s also about taking the time to do something well, a porch swing that faces the water and a slice of coffee cake on thin china plate.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm</description></item><item><title>The Hardware Store | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540166/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540166/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story this week is called The Hardware Store and it&amp;rsquo;s a story about finding all the right things for a few projects at home. It’s also about stacks of fresh sawn wood, a packet of peanut butter cups and the ride home, with the window down.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.</description></item><item><title>A Dance In The Park | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540167/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540167/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called A Dance in the Park and it’s a story about coming back into the world after a bit of time spent alone. It’s also about a glass of pink hibiscus tea, window shopping on a downtown street and moving to the music on a sunny day.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Old Houses | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540168/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540168/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “Old Houses” and it’s a story about a wandering amble through an unknown neighborhood. It’s also about a forgotten piece of music in an old piano bench, a penny pressed into a sidewalk and the stories we tell about the places we live.
So let&amp;rsquo;s get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>The Front Door and The Back Door | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540169/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540169/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called The Front Door and the Back Door and it’s a story about a bit of Spring Cleaning inside and outside the house. It’s also about butterflies drawn in chalk on the sidewalk, a message arriving at the just the right moment, and seedlings waiting for their chance to grow.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>At the Hideaway | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540170/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540170/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “At the Hideaway” and it’s a story about getting away to a tiny cabin in the woods. It’s also about seeing signs of Spring, a long walk and finding a way to feel connected even when we’re far apart.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
This episode mentions alcohol.
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Jewelry Box | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540171/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540171/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called The Jewelry Box and it’s a story about a an heirloom handed down through a family. It’s also about a jeweled broach pinned on the lapel of a jacket, Spring sunlight and some good advice for when things break.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Tea Shop | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540172/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540172/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called The Tea shop and it’s a story about a carefully prepared cup of tea drunk on a cool morning. It’s also about a cat with a crooked tail, a memory of belonging and the days on the edge of a new season.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.</description></item><item><title>Nothing Much Happens - Trailer | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540173/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 15:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540173/</guid><description>Podcast Description Having trouble sleeping? Join Yoga and meditation teacher Kathryn Nicolai for bedtime stories where nothing much happens to help you relax and sleep peacefully. The stories are a soft landing spot for your mind. Rather than letting your brain race through the same thoughts you’ve been chasing all day, we are taking a detour to a calm and comfy place. We tell the story twice and go a bit slower the second time.</description></item><item><title>All Day, At Home | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540174/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540174/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called All day, At home and it’s a story about tucking yourself away from the world for a bit. It’s also about watching winter from a window seat, red pepper flakes from the Italian coast and the joy of minding one’s own business.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.</description></item><item><title>Hearts &amp; Flowers | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540175/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540175/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Hearts and Flowers and it’s a story about showing someone what’s in your heart. It’s also about a Valentine’s Day card signed with a flourish, a shop full of flowers and the moment that you decide to to take a risk.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Fresh Snow | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540176/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540176/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Fresh Snow and it’s a story about time spent outside as the flakes fall. It’s also about a late night bath, a peppermint stick in a cup of hot chocolate and the easy comfort of long held friends.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
This episode mentions alcohol.
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.</description></item><item><title>A Break In The Weather | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540177/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540177/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called A Break in the Weather and it’s a story about a day in the sun. It’s also about a heart drawn on a window pane, dripping icicles and that fresh open feeling that comes with a little bit of change.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Little Rituals | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540178/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 13:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540178/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “Little Rituals” and its a story about a simple way to shift into a calmer place. It’s also about tiny cups and saucers, a memory from a favorite place and lessons learned from mom.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Under the Tree | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540179/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540179/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Under the Tree and it’s a story about a day of decorating around the house. It’s also about a bowl of oatmeal with cinnamon and apples, a box of ornaments wrapped in paper and the things that connect us to the past.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.</description></item><item><title>Skating In The Park | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540180/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “Skating in the Park” and it’s a story about revisiting a yearly tradition. It’s also about a thermos of coffee waiting to warm you up, thick socks and the kind of friends who even after a while apart, can pick right back up where they left off.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Over the River and Through the Woods | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540181/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540181/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Over the River and through the Woods and it’s a story about going home for Thanksgiving. It’s also about fresh rolls from the bakery, late night card games and sitting at at a long kitchen table with people who know you well.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
This story mentions alcohol.
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>The Cabin in the Woods | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540182/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540182/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “The Cabin in the Woods” and it’s a story about a trip along winding roads and a special place at the end of them. It’s also about pine cones high in their branches, a jigsaw puzzle spread out on the kitchen table and calm quiet feeling that comes from being far away from everything.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now!</description></item><item><title>Grandmother's Grimoire | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540183/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540183/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Grandmother’s Grimoire and it’s a story about a family heirloom that arrives in the crispy cool days of October. It’s also about an afternoon in the attic with old trunks and photographs, a cup of sugar from the pantry and the return of an old friend.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Rosemary For Remembrance | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540184/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540184/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “Rosemary, for Remembrance” and it’s a story about preparing a garden for the coming frost. It’s also about a row of pumpkins waiting to be claimed, what the poets have to say about herbs, and the unending generosity of nature.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>The First Cool Days | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540185/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540185/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called The First Cool Days and it&amp;rsquo;s a story about that pivotal time between seasons and how lovely it can be to go from the heat of the lakeside to the cool shadowy days of September. It’s also about being allowed some time to be alone and quiet, a candle burning on a kitchen windowsill and the best bite of watermelon.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.</description></item><item><title>Back to School | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540186/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540186/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “Back to School” and it’s a story about the tingling anticipation of a new school year. It’s also about freshly sharpened pencils neatly tucked into a case, Halloween candy eaten a bit early and the thrill of learning something new.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Summer Harvest | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540187/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540187/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “Summer Harvest” and it’s a story about the result of a season’s worth of hard work and planning. It’s also about telling time like a farmer would, a red popsicle eaten under a maple tree, and rows of canned tomatoes neatly lined up in the pantry.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>The Dog Days Of Summer | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540188/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540188/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “The Dog Days of Summer” and it’s a story about the a day with a best friend. It’s also about a cucumber picked from the garden, meeting friends in the park the most important lessons we learn from the animals we share our lives with.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>A Letter In An Envelope | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540189/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540189/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “A Letter in an Envelope” and it’s a story about the everyday magic of messages sent between friends. It’s also about peanut butter spread on toast, a favorite spot on the back porch, and a lifelong habit of saving stories.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>At The Summer Fair | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540190/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540190/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “At the Summer Fair” and it’s a story about a yearly tradition and how it changes in the different summers of your life. It’s also about plums taken from the icebox, a handmade cup wrapped in paper and strolling along the river as the streetlights blink on above you.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Someplace Only We Know | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540191/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540191/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “Someplace only we know” and it’s a story about being drawn out on a summer night to explore and feel the evening air on your face. It’s also about a cup of lemon ice, riding down a hill on your bicycle and remembering something sweet that you’d long ago forgotten.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Fireflies On A Summer Night | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540192/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540192/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “Fireflies on a summer night” and it’s a story about the magic language of lighting bugs. It’s also about the cool quiet feeling of being all by yourself in the moonlight, words that start with the letter G, and a persistent enduring belief in magic.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Coffee On The Stoop or How to Have a Better Day | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540193/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540193/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “Coffee on the stoop, or how to have a better day” and it’s a story about a day devoted to small acts of kindness. It’s also about a kitty sleeping in a window, paints and brushes and flower seeds and the awe we feel when a stranger reaches out to do us a good turn.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now!</description></item><item><title>Opening Up The Cottage | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540194/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540194/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “Opening the cottage” and it’s a story about the first day back in a well loved familiar place. It’s also about the little traditions that make up the history of a family, a sandwich eaten on the end of a dock and the soft happy feeling of summer arriving.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>The Lilac Thief | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540195/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540195/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called The Lilac Thief and it’s a story about finding the forgotten places where one can, in secret acquire some spring blooms. It’s also about the curiosity we feel when we look into the windows of an old house, a cup of iced coffee drunk at a sidewalk cafe and the secret code of thieves.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now!</description></item><item><title>Spring at the Allotment | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540196/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540196/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called Spring at the allotment and it’s a story about setting up a garden of herbs and vegetables with a friend. It’s also about a picnic basket full of sandwiches, turning over the soil with your hands and the pleasure of sewing seeds in neat rows on a bright sunny day.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>In The Bakery | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540197/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540197/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “In the Bakery” and it’s a story about a weekend morning among bagels and breads. It’s also about old cookbooks full of notes, being proud of what you do, and a secret ingredient handed down from baker to baker.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>First This, Then That | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540198/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540198/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called First This, Then That and it’s a story about a bit of Spring cleaning on a sunny day. It’s also about watching birds at their feeder, sharing things with your neighbors and the joy of finding something forgotten in old coat pocket.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.</description></item><item><title>Getaway | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540199/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540199/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “Getaway” and it’s a story about taking a break from the cold and ice. It’s also about the feeling of falling asleep in the sun with a paperback book in your hand, the sound of the waves at night and the pleasant longing for your own bed at the end of time away.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now!</description></item><item><title>Fog and Light | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540200/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540200/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “Fog and Light” and it’s a story about a day of simple pleasures meant to clear out the winter blues. It’s also about a little girl in a red hat, the Latin names for rare flowers and good advice from an old friend.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm</description></item><item><title>A Little Romance | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540201/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540201/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “A little romance” and it’s a story about the beginnings of Spring in the city. It’s also about fond memories of young love, a picture tucked into the back of a wallet and and the sweet realization that someone somewhere is thinking of you.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Winter Walk | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540202/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540202/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “Winter Walk” and it’s a story about stepping through crisp layers of deep snow on a sunny cold day. It’s also about a well made bed, a sleeping kitty and the welcome way that nature can take your breath away.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>A New Leaf | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540203/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540203/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “A New Leaf” and it’s a story about starting off the new year with a fresh book to write your plans in. It’s also about a memory of something magical, a cup of coffee on a cold day and the pleasure of a freshly sharpened pencil.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Christmas Eve | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540204/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2018 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540204/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called &amp;ldquo;Christmas Eve&amp;rdquo; and it’s a story about being with the ones you love at a special time of year. It’s also about plates of home baked treats, thinking back to the holidays of childhood and the everyday miracle that is dogs.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
This episode mentions alcohol.
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Snowed In | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540205/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540205/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called &amp;ldquo;Snowed In&amp;rdquo; and it’s a story about watching the snow come down from the cozy warmth of home. It’s also about treating yourself to things you usually don’t have time for, a memory of kindness and the quiet hush of deep snow.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.</description></item><item><title>Getting The Tree | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540206/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540206/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “Getting the Tree” and it’s a story about a Holiday tradition that’s been updated from childhood, it’s also about a champagne toast, sharing a quiet moment and the kindness of a stranger.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
This episode mentions alcohol.
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bustle in the City | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540207/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540207/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “Bustle in the City” and it’s a story about watching the streets of a downtown come to life on a dark December night. It’s also about the merriness of seeing friends at the height of the holiday season, the quiet refuge of a room of one’s own and sending your love in a letter to someone far far away.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.</description></item><item><title>The Day after Thanksgiving | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540208/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540208/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “The day after Thanksgiving” and it’s a story about enjoying the quiet after a big day, and looking forward to the season to come. It’s also about being in your pajamas for as long as you like, the best way to pop popcorn and some happy traditions.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
This episode mentions alcohol.</description></item><item><title>A rainy day, making soup | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540209/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540209/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “A rainy day, making soup” and it’s a story about feeling lit up from the inside when it gets dark and gloomy out. It’s also about a drink of something special, a welcome home kiss and falling asleep on the sofa while dinner is being made.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
This episode mentions alcohol.
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>A Cool Walk and a Hot Bath | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540210/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540210/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called &amp;ldquo;A cool walk and a hot a bath&amp;rdquo; and it’s a story about those particular days right on the edge of Autumn and Winter when the wind is changing and there are pleasures to be found in being outside and in being in. It’s also about saying hello to a friend, the joy of unwrapping a gift and watching the seasons change.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.</description></item><item><title>Ducks in a Row | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540211/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540211/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “Ducks in a row” and it’s a story about a slow paced Sunday, several cups of tea, and having the time to do the things you need to. It’s also about a shared loaf of banana bread, watching a cold wind blow through the last leaves of autumn, and feeling cared for and ready for a new week.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.</description></item><item><title>Halloween, in an Old House | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540212/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540212/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called &amp;ldquo;Halloween, in an old house&amp;rdquo; and it’s a story about making friends with whoever you share your space with. It’s also about getting to be someone else for a bit and the contagious excitement of children on one of their favorite nights of the year.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>At the Mill, with Pumpkins and Cider | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540213/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540213/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “At the mill, with pumpkins and cider” and it’s a story about an afternoon in the cool autumn air doing some favorite things. It’s also about taking the time to let a moment unfold, a childhood memory and a shared cup of cider.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm</description></item><item><title>At the Farmers Market, on a Fall Morning | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540214/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540214/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “At the Farmer’s Market, on a Fall Morning and it’s a story about the abundance of autumn and the bustle of a busy neighborhood market. It’s also about the feeling of looking forward to the winter and of looking back to being a child.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>In the Library | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540215/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540215/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “In the Library” and it’s a story about a day spent in the cool quiet company of books. It’s also about an early morning cup of coffee, the first cool days of Autumn and the excitement of a new book.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>The Last Warm Days | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540216/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 18:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540216/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “The Last Warm Days” and it’s a story about enjoying the heat of summer before the Autumn comes to take it’s place. It’s also about sheets dried in the sun, the smell of tomato plants and taking time to do as one likes.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm</description></item><item><title>In the Kitchen, During a Storm | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540217/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540217/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “In the kitchen, during a storm” and it’s a story about doing something simple with great care. It’s also about the cool breeze that comes with a storm, remembering a sweet time in your past and listening to records on a summer night.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
This episode mentions alcohol.
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>A Walk in the Woods | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540218/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540218/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called &amp;ldquo;A walk in the woods&amp;rdquo; and it’s a story about getting far out into nature and trading in your usual cares for the sights and sounds of the countryside. It’s also about the pleasures of wandering, whirlybirds falling to the forest floor and being alone.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Summer Vacation | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540219/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540219/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called &amp;ldquo;Summer Vacation&amp;rdquo; and it’s a story about the feeling of freedom and having lots of time ahead of you to do what you like. It’s also about planning sweet things with someone special, the fresh harvest of the late summer and enjoying the sights along the way.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
This episode mentions alcohol.</description></item><item><title>Summer Nights | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540220/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540220/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “Summer Nights” and it’s a story about a day at the lake with friends, a huge summer feast and sweet night air. It’s also about the feeling of realizing when something is good and being happy about it.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
This episode mentions alcohol.
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.</description></item><item><title>Afternoon Nap | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540221/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540221/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “Afternoon nap” and it’s a story about the best kind of nap, the one you didn’t think you had time for. It’s also about enjoying small luxuries and the serendipity of unexpected free time.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Early to Yoga | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540222/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540222/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “Early to Yoga” and it’s a story about the comfort of a quiet safe place. It’s also about the feeling of privacy and the ease and serenity that come from someone showing you a little tenderness and affection.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Three Good Things | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540223/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 May 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540223/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called &amp;ldquo;Three Good Things&amp;rdquo; and it’s about reminding yourself of some of the simple happy moments that happen during the day. Sometimes good stuff slips through our brains without leaving much of a trace, while scary upsetting stuff gets stuck in there. So it helps to notice and highlight sweetness when it shows up, even if that just amounts to us saying to ourselves, “Oh that’s nice.</description></item><item><title>The Windows Were Open | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540224/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540224/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “The windows were open” and it’s a story about a sunny summer day by the lake, solitude, and strawberries. It’s also about the feeling of being free from a schedule and deadlines, and about doing some favorite things.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.</description></item><item><title>Some Days | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540225/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540225/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called &amp;ldquo;Some days&amp;rdquo; and is short, and not so much a story as just some reminders for when you’ve had a crummy day, so we’re releasing it as a bonus episode.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
This episode mentions alcohol.
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Spring in the Yard | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540226/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2018 11:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540226/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “Spring in the Yard” and it’s a story about getting outside at the end of a long winter, being in the fresh air and tidying things up. It’s also about quiet companionship, dogs, and the last fire of the season.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
This episode mentions alcohol.
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.</description></item><item><title>Closing Up Shop | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540227/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540227/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our story tonight is called “Closing up shop” and it’s a story about a book shop at the end of the day. Lev Grossman wrote in The Magician’s Land “It didn’t matter where you were, if you were in a room full of books you were at least halfway home.” If that feels true to you, then this story is for you. Beyond the friendliness of the company of books, this story is also about being in a safe place and looking out from it at one’s leisure, and about the lovely feeling of anticipating something nice.</description></item><item><title>A Block From Home | Nothing much happens: bedtime stories to help you sleep</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2173540228/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2173540228/</guid><description>Podcast Description Turn off the light, get comfortable and let us tell you a story. These are bedtime stories for grownups, in which nothing much happens, you feel good and then you fall asleep.
So get cozy and ready to sleep.
Order the book now! hyperurl.co/NothingMuchHappens
Get our ad-free and bonus episodes here: https://nothingmuchhappens.supportingcast.fm
See omnystudio.com/listener for privacy information.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>