<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Ezra Klein Show on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/the-ezra-klein-show/</link><description>Recent content in The Ezra Klein Show on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/the-ezra-klein-show/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>India Is Transforming. But Into What? | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360282/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360282/</guid><description>Podcast Description India is known as a country of paradoxes, and a new one has recently emerged. At the same time that the country is poised to become a major global player — with a booming economy and a population that recently surpassed China’s — its democracy is showing signs of decay.
Prime Minister Narendra Modi and his administration have silenced critics and independent institutions. India’s social media discourse has turned increasingly right wing and hostile to Muslims.</description></item><item><title>The Paradox of India’s Rise | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360281/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360281/</guid><description>Podcast Description India is known as a country of paradoxes, and a new one has recently emerged. At the same time that the country is poised to become a major global player — with a booming economy and a population that recently surpassed China’s — its democracy is showing signs of decay.
Prime Minister Narendra Modi and his administration have silenced critics and independent institutions. India’s social media discourse has turned increasingly right wing and hostile to Muslims.</description></item><item><title>A Different Path Israel Could Have Taken — and Maybe Still Can | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360280/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360280/</guid><description>Podcast Description Before Oct. 7, Israel appeared to many to be sliding into a “one-state reality,” where it had functional control over Gaza and the West Bank, but the Palestinians who lived there were denied full rights. In 2021, a group of hundreds of former senior defense and diplomatic officials in Israel published a report warning that this was a catastrophe — for Israel’s security, its democratic values, its international standing, and its very soul.</description></item><item><title>‘This Is How Hamas Is Seeing This’ | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360279/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360279/</guid><description>Podcast Description Here are two thoughts I believe need to be held at once: Hamas’s attack on Oct. 7 was heinous, murderous and unforgivable, and that makes it more, not less, important to try to understand what Hamas is, how it sees itself and how it presents itself to Palestinians.
Tareq Baconi is the author of “Hamas Contained: The Rise and Pacification of Palestinian Resistance,” one of the best books on Hamas’s rise and recent history.</description></item><item><title>A Lot Has Happened in A.I. Let’s Catch Up. | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360278/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360278/</guid><description>Podcast Description Thursday marked the one-year anniversary of the release of ChatGPT. A lot has happened since. OpenAI, the makers of ChatGPT, recently dominated headlines again after the nonprofit board of directors fired C.E.O. Sam Altman, only for him to return several days later.
But that drama isn’t actually the most important thing going on in the A.I. world, which hasn’t slowed down over the past year, even as people are still discovering ChatGPT for the first time and reckoning with all of its implications.</description></item><item><title>Best Of: This Is Your Brain on Deep Reading. It’s Pretty Magnificent. | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360277/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360277/</guid><description>Podcast Description Every day, we consume a mind-boggling amount of information. We scan online news articles, sift through text messages and emails, scroll through our social-media feeds — and that’s usually before we even get out of bed in the morning. In 2009, a team of researchers found that the average American consumed about 34 gigabytes of information a day. Undoubtedly, that number would be even higher today.
But what are we actually getting from this huge influx of information?</description></item><item><title>The Best Primer I’ve Heard on Israeli-Palestinian Peace Efforts | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360276/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360276/</guid><description>Podcast Description It is too early to talk about a peace deal between Israel and the Palestinians. With the trauma of Oct. 7 still fresh for the Israeli public and with the ongoing devastation in Gaza, any talk of conflict-ending solutions is cruel fantasy.
But it wasn’t always. Peace efforts in the Middle East have been tried over and over again. It is not a history without breakthroughs. There was a time when a peace treaty between Israel and Egypt would have been unthinkable.</description></item><item><title>The Sermons I Needed to Hear Right Now | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360001/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360001/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a conversation about the relationship between Jewishness and the Jewish State. About believing some aspects of Israel have become indefensible and also believing that Israel itself must be defended. About what it means when a religion built on the lessons of exile creates a state that inflicts exile on others. About the ugly, recurrent reality of antisemitism.
You know, the easy stuff.
In these past few months, I’ve been moved by the sermons of Rabbi Sharon Brous, which have managed to hold these paradoxes with more grace and prophetic wisdom than most.</description></item><item><title>Are Democrats Whistling Past the Graveyard? | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360002/</guid><description>Podcast Description A New York Times and Siena College poll released Nov. 5 showed Donald Trump leading Joe Biden in five of the six key swing states, with a notable jump in support among nonwhite and young voters. In response, Democrats freaked out.
But then two days later, voters across the country actually went to the polls, and Democrats and Democratic-associated policy did pretty well. In Kentucky, Andy Beshear held the governorship.</description></item><item><title>What Israelis Fear the World Does Not Understand | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360003/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Earlier this week, we heard a Palestinian perspective on the conflict. Today, I wanted to have on an Israeli perspective.
Yossi Klein Halevi is a senior fellow at the Shalom Hartman Institute in Jerusalem and the author, most recently, of “Letters to My Palestinian Neighbor.”
In this episode, we discuss Halevi’s unusual education as an Israeli Defense Forces soldier in Gaza during the first intifada, the “seminal disconnect” between how Israel is viewed from the inside versus from the outside, Halevi’s view that a Palestinian state is both an “existential need” and an “existential threat” for Israel, the failures of the Oslo peace process and how the second intifada hardened Israeli attitudes toward peace, what Oct.</description></item><item><title>An Intense, Searching Conversation With Amjad Iraqi | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Before there can be any kind of stable coexistence of people in Israel and Palestine, there will have to be a stable coexistence of narratives. And that’s what we’ll be attempting this week on the show: to look at both the present and the past through Israeli and Palestinian perspectives. The point is not to choose between them. The point is to really listen to them. Even — especially — when what’s being said is hard for us to hear.</description></item><item><title>She Polled Gazans on Oct. 6. Here’s What She Found. | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360005/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360005/</guid><description>Podcast Description The day before Hamas’s horrific attacks in Israel, the Arab Barometer, one of the leading polling operations in the Arab world, was finishing up a survey of public opinion in Gaza.
The result is a remarkable snapshot of how Gazans felt about Hamas and hoped the conflict with Israel would end. And what Gazans were thinking on Oct. 6 matters, now that they’re all living with the brutal consequences of what Hamas did on Oct.</description></item><item><title>If Not This, Then What Should Israel Do? | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360006/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360006/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Two things are true: Israel must do something, and what it’s doing now is indefensible.” So writes Zack Beauchamp, a senior correspondent at Vox.
Almost a month has passed since Hamas fighters slaughtered over 1,400 people in Israel and the state mounted its furious response. For weeks, Israel has laid siege to Gaza, cutting off water and electricity to the tiny strip of land and carrying out airstrikes that have reportedly killed over 8,000 Palestinians.</description></item><item><title>The Conflicted Legacy of Mitt Romney | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360007/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360007/</guid><description>Podcast Description After factional infighting dominated the G.O.P.’s struggle to elect a House speaker, it feels weirdly quaint to revisit Mitt Romney’s career. He’s served as governor, U.S. senator and presidential nominee for a Republican Party now nearly unrecognizable from what it was when he started out. At the end of his time in public office, Romney has found a new clarity in his identity as the consummate institutionalist in an increasingly anti-constitutionalist party.</description></item><item><title>The Jewish Left Is Trying to Hold Two Thoughts at Once | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360008/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Grief moves slowly and war moves quickly. After Hamas assailants killed at least 1,400 Israelis and took hundreds more hostage, Israel dropped more than 6,000 bombs on Gaza in the first week of a conflict that is still ongoing. So far, more than 5,000 Palestinians are reported dead and many more injured. There’s no one way to cover this that reconciles all that is happening and all that needs to be felt.</description></item><item><title>Israel Is Giving Hamas What It Wants | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Oct. 7 was Israel’s Sept. 11. That’s been the refrain. I fear that analogy carries so much more truth than the people making it intend.
Thoughts? Guest suggestions? Email us at ezrakleinshow@nytimes.com.
You can find transcripts (posted midday) and more episodes of “The Ezra Klein Show” at nytimes.com/ezra-klein-podcast, and you can find Ezra on Twitter @ezraklein. Book recommendations from all our guests are listed at https://www.nytimes.com/article/ezra-klein-show-book-recs.
This audio essay for “The Ezra Klein Show” was fact-checked by Michelle Harris, with Mary-Marge Locker.</description></item><item><title>We Need Better Narratives About Gender | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360010/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360010/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s a time of contrast and contradiction for gender queerness in America: At the same time that about 5 percent of Americans under 30 identify as transgender or nonbinary, over 20 states have passed some sort of restriction on gender-affirming care for children. In 2023 alone, over 550 anti-trans bills have been introduced across the country.
The political push and pull can overshadow a broad spectrum of rich questions and possibilities that queer culture opens up — about how we think about identity and social categories, how we structure our communities and support networks, our anxieties about having children who are different from ourselves, how gender norms shape all bodies and how difficult it can be to make big life decisions.</description></item><item><title>Meet the ‘Angry, Aggrieved’ New Right | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360011/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360011/</guid><description>Podcast Description The New Right has been associated with everyone from Senator Josh Hawley of Missouri to right-wing influencers and Catholic integralists. The breadth of the term can make it hard to define: Is the New Right a budding ideological movement or a toxic online subculture? What does it mean if it’s both?
Stephanie Slade is a senior editor at the magazine Reason, and has covered the New Right extensively. She argues that the New Right subverts the conventional left/right political binary and is better understood as the illiberal backlash to classical liberalism.</description></item><item><title>Two Attorneys Rank the Severity of Trump’s Indictments | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360012/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360012/</guid><description>Podcast Description With four ongoing criminal investigations, Donald Trump is the most indicted president in U.S. history. After years of defying unwritten norms, he will now be subject to a criminal justice system defined by norms and precedents. What does due process look like for a former president?
Ken White is a former federal prosecutor, a practicing criminal defense lawyer and a co-host of the podcast “Serious Trouble.” He writes the popular newsletter The Popehat Report, extensively covering the ins and outs of criminal trials.</description></item><item><title>Boundaries, Burnout and the 'Goopification' of Self-Care | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360013/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Love it or hate it, self-care has transformed from a radical feminist concept into a multibillion-dollar industry. But the wellness boom doesn’t seem to be making a dent in Americans’ stress levels. In 2021, 34 percent of women reported feeling burned out at work, along with 26 percent of men.
Dr. Pooja Lakshmin, a psychiatrist, has observed how wellness culture fails her patients, who she says are often burned out because of systemic failures, from the stresses that come with financial precariousness to the lack of paid family leave.</description></item><item><title>America’s Top Librarian on the Rise of Book Bans | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360014/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Public libraries around the country have become major battlegrounds for today’s culture wars. In 2022, the American Library Association noted a record 1,269 attempts at censorship — almost double the number recorded in 2021. Library events like drag story times and other children’s programming have also attracted protest. How should we understand these efforts to control what stories children can freely access?
Emily Drabinski is the president of the American Library Association and an associate professor at the Queens College Graduate School of Library and Information Studies.</description></item><item><title>What Have We Learned From a Summer of Climate Reckoning? | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360015/</guid><description>Podcast Description This summer has been a parade of broken climate records. June was the hottest June and July was not just the hottest July but the hottest month ever on record. At the same time, it looks like we are at the start of a green revolution: Decarbonization efforts have gone far better than what many had hoped for just a few years ago, and renewable energy is getting cheaper.</description></item><item><title>It’s Time to Talk About ‘Pandemic Revisionism’ | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Should schools have been closed down? Were lockdowns a mistake? Was masking even effective? Was the economic stimulus too big?
These are the questions that have defined the national conversation about Covid in recent months. They have been the subject of congressional hearings led by Republicans, of G.O.P. candidate stump speeches and of too many Twitter debates to count.
Katelyn Jetelina is an epidemiologist and the author of the popular newsletter Your Local Epidemiologist.</description></item><item><title>When Great Power Conflict and Climate Action Collide | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360017/</guid><description>Podcast Description The global decarbonization effort is colliding headfirst with the realities of great power politics. China currently controls more than 75 percent of the world’s electric vehicle battery and solar photovoltaic manufacturing supply chains. It also processes the bulk of the so-called critical minerals, like lithium, cobalt and graphite, that are essential to building out clean energy technologies. There is no clean energy revolution without China.
What would happen if China decided to weaponize its clean energy resources in the same way Russia recently weaponized its oil and gas?</description></item><item><title>This Conservative Thinks America’s Institutions ‘Earned’ Their Distrust | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360018/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360018/</guid><description>Podcast Description You can’t understand the modern Republican Party without understanding the complete collapse of trust in mainstream institutions that has taken place among its voters over the last half-century.
In 1964, 73 percent of Republicans said they trusted the federal government to do the right thing always or most of the time. Today, that number is down to 9 percent. And it’s not just government. Pew found that only 35 percent of Republicans trust national news and 61 percent think public schools are having a negative effect on the country.</description></item><item><title>A Conservative on How His Party Has Changed Since 2016 | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360019/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 2024 Republican presidential primary is officially underway, and Donald Trump is dominating the field. But this is a very different contest than it was in 2016. Back then, the Republican Party was the party of foreign policy interventionism, free trade and cutting entitlements, and Trump was the insurgent outsider unafraid to buck the consensus. Today, Trump and his views have become the consensus.
The primary, then, raises some important questions: How has Donald Trump changed the Republican Party over the past eight years?</description></item><item><title>How Martin Wolf Understands This Global Economic Moment | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360020/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360020/</guid><description>Podcast Description The world economy has experienced many shocks over the past few years: A pandemic. Russia’s invasion of Ukraine. Skyrocketing inflation. These are the stories that have dominated headlines — and for good reason.
But they’ve also overshadowed a set of deeper, more fundamental shifts — the rise of China as an economic superpower, the fracturing of trade relations, the realities of the climate crisis — that are transforming the global economic order and prompting ambitious policy responses from leaders across the world.</description></item><item><title>Biden, Psychedelics, Twitter, My New Book — and So Much More | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360021/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360021/</guid><description>Podcast Description As I head into a three-month book leave, I wanted to take some time to address a wide array of listeners’ questions. My column editor, Aaron Retica, joins me for a conversation that ranges from the content of my forthcoming book and President Biden’s climate record to the simulation hypothesis and legalized psychedelic therapy.
We also discuss what the I-95 collapse — and remarkably quick repairs — tell us about government’s ability to build quickly, the problems with everything-bagel liberalism, what it would mean to treat climate change like the emergency that it is, why I dislike analogies between Biden and Franklin Roosevelt, why health care reform has receded from the center of American political debate, whether liberals are being too soft on Hunter Biden, why I am staunchly against term limits for Congress, what kinds of work are most undervalued in American society, why I’ve become less pessimistic about artificial intelligence disinformation, why I left Twitter but have been enjoying Threads, the challenges of keeping a Sabbath practice and more.</description></item><item><title>Barbara Kingsolver Thinks Urban Liberals Have It All Wrong on Appalachia | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360022/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Barbara Kingsolver set out to write her latest novel, “Demon Copperhead,” she was already considered one of the most accomplished writers of our time. She had won awards including the Women’s Prize for Fiction and a National Humanities Medal, and had a track record of best-selling books, including “The Poisonwood Bible” and “Unsheltered.” But she felt there was one giant stone left unturned: to write “the great Appalachian novel.</description></item><item><title>What We Learned From the Deepest Look at Homelessness in Decades | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360023/</guid><description>Podcast Description California has around half of the nation’s unsheltered homeless population. The state’s homelessness crisis has become a talking point for Republicans and a warning sign for Democrats in blue cities and states across the country.
Last month, the Benioff Homelessness and Housing Initiative at the University of California, San Francisco, released a landmark report about homelessness in the state, drawing from nearly 3,200 questionnaires and 365 in-depth interviews. It is the single deepest study on homelessness in America in decades.</description></item><item><title>What Tom Hanks Thinks of America | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360024/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360024/</guid><description>Podcast Description There are few actors as widely beloved as Tom Hanks. Hanks has acted in over 75 films in his 46-year career, winning the best actor Academy Award two years in a row, for “Philadelphia” and “Forrest Gump.” And more recently, he’s the author of the short story collection “Uncommon Type” and the novel “The Making of Another Major Motion Picture Masterpiece.”
What is the source of Hanks’s near-universal admiration?</description></item><item><title>A.I. Could Solve Some of Humanity’s Hardest Problems. It Already Has. | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360025/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Since the release of ChatGPT, huge amounts of attention and funding have been directed toward chatbots. These A.I. systems are trained on copious amounts of human-generated data and designed to predict the next word in a given sentence. They are hilarious and eerie and at times dangerous.
But what if, instead of building A.I. systems that mimic humans, we built those systems to solve some of the most vexing problems facing humanity?</description></item><item><title>This Taught Me a Lot About How Decarbonization Is Really Going | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360026/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360026/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Inflation Reduction Act was the largest piece of climate legislation ever passed in the United States, setting aside hundreds of billions of dollars for decarbonizing the economy. But the money was always just a first step. The fate of the act’s goals hinges on whether those investments can build the energy system of the future — everything from transmission lines and wind farms to electric vehicle factories and green hydrogen hubs.</description></item><item><title>Best Of: A Revelatory Tour of Martin Luther King Jr.’s Forgotten Teachings | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360027/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360027/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s hard to think of a more celebrated figure of the 20th century than Martin Luther King Jr.
He has a national memorial in Washington, D.C. His birthday is one of just 11 federal holidays. His words and legacy are routinely evoked by politicians of both major parties. I would go as far as to say he should be considered one of America’s founding fathers, which is one reason why I wanted to revisit this episode on Independence Day.</description></item><item><title>What’s Really Going On in Russia? | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360028/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last weekend, in the course of about 36 hours, Vladimir Putin faced — and then survived — one of the most serious challenges to his rule in over 20 years. An armed rebellion led by Yevgeny Prigozhin, the head of a Russian mercenary group, took control of a southern military town, and then advanced toward Moscow, coming within about 125 miles of the city. Then, as suddenly as the rebellion began, it was over: Prigozhin was quickly exiled to Belarus without facing criminal charges — an outcome that shocked many Russia watchers.</description></item><item><title>How ‘Being Animal’ Could Help Us Be Better Humans | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360029/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360029/</guid><description>Podcast Description One of the oldest human ideas is that we are somehow different from animals, somehow superior to them. That’s a mistake, argues the environmental philosopher Melanie Challenger. “Many of the things we most value — our relationships, the romantic sensations of attraction and love, pregnancy and childbirth, the pleasures of springtime, of eating a meal — are physical, largely unconscious and demonstrably animal,” she writes in her book “How to Be Animal: A New History of What It Means to Be Human.</description></item><item><title>Why This Economist Wants to Give Every Poor Child $50,000 | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360030/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360030/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Wealth is the paramount indicator of economic prosperity and well-being,” says the economist Darrick Hamilton. He’s right. Policy analysis tends to focus on income, but it is wealth that often determines whether we can send our kids to college, pay for an illness, quit a job, start a business or make a down payment on a home. Wealth is also the source of some of our deepest social inequalities: The top 10 percent of households in the U.</description></item><item><title>What the Heck Is Going on With These U.F.O. Stories? | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360031/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Earlier this month, a news outlet called The Debrief published a story that included, to put it mildly, some explosive material.
The story, reported by Leslie Kean and Ralph Blumenthal, centered on David Grusch, a decorated former combat veteran who has worked in multiple government intelligence agencies and served on the Pentagon’s Unidentified Aerial Phenomena Task Force. In the story, Grusch said he had decided to come forward as a whistle-blower, testifying under oath to Congress that there are longstanding covert programs within the U.</description></item><item><title>Why Do So Few Democrats Want Biden to Run in 2024? | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360032/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360032/</guid><description>Podcast Description A recent AP-NORC poll found that just a quarter of voters, including only around half of Democrats, want to see Joe Biden run for president again. Many voters are concerned about his age in particular.
That’s a problem for Biden, but it’s not as unusual as it might seem. In 1982, only 37 percent of voters wanted Ronald Reagan, another older president, to run again; he then won the 1984 election in a landslide.</description></item><item><title>What We Learned Reading Ron DeSantis's Books | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360033/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Although 12 candidates have entered the Republican presidential race so far, only Gov. Ron DeSantis of Florida is polling anywhere close to Donald Trump. What does DeSantis actually believe? How has he governed? And what case will he make to Republicans to vote for him over Trump?
To answer those questions, I wanted to spend some time reading DeSantis in his own words. So I invited Carlos Lozada — the Pulitzer Prize-winning former book critic for The Washington Post, current Times Opinion columnist and the author of “What Were We Thinking: A Brief Intellectual History of the Trump Era” — to join me.</description></item><item><title>What Communes and Other Radical Experiments in Living Together Reveal | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360034/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360034/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Today’s future-positive writers critique our economies while largely seeming to ignore that anything might be amiss in our private lives,” writes Kristen Ghodsee. Even our most ambitious visions of utopia tend to focus on outcomes that can be achieved through public policy — things like abundant clean energy or liberation from employment — while ignoring many of the aspects of our lives that matter to us the most: how we live, raise our children, and tend to our most meaningful relationships.</description></item><item><title>The Book I Wish Every Policymaker Would Read | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360035/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360035/</guid><description>Podcast Description My pitch for this episode is simple: Jennifer Pahlka has written one of the best policy books I’ve ever read.
Pahlka served as deputy chief technology officer in the Obama White House, and she’s the founder and a former executive director of Code for America, a nonprofit that works to enhance government digital services. Over the course of her career, Pahlka has become obsessed with an area of policy that is too often ignored by policymakers: implementation.</description></item><item><title>Beyond the ‘Matrix’ Theory of the Mind | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360036/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Some thoughts on how humans think, how economies grow and why the technologies we think will help so often hurt.
Column:
“Beyond the ‘Matrix’ Theory of the Mind” by Ezra Klein
Episode Recommendations:
Maryanne Wolf on how reading shapes our brains
Cal Newport on the problems with the way we work
My A.M.A. on A.I.
Gary Marcus on the limits of A.I.
Thoughts? Guest suggestions? Email us at ezrakleinshow@nytimes.</description></item><item><title>Fareed Zakaria on Where Russia’s War in Ukraine Stands — and Much More | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360037/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360037/</guid><description>Podcast Description A lot about the world has changed since February 2022, when Russia invaded Ukraine. The war itself has brought a number of surprises, from the tenacity of Ukraine’s resistance to the limits of Western sanctions. Meanwhile, competition between the United States and China has escalated into something resembling a new Cold War, India just surpassed China as the most populous country in the world and countries representing about two-thirds of the world’s population have chosen not to align themselves with the U.</description></item><item><title>Matter of Opinion: A Look at the 2024 G.O.P. Primary Field | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360038/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we’re bringing you an episode from the latest New York Times Opinion podcast, “Matter of Opinion.” It’s a chat show, hosted by my colleagues Michelle Cottle, Ross Douthat, Carlos Lozada and Lydia Polgreen. Each week, they discuss an issue in the news, the culture or their own work and try to make sense of what is a weird and fascinating time to be alive.
In this episode, the hosts take a tour of the 2024 Republican primary field to understand what it takes to survive in the present-day Republican ecosystem — and maybe even beat the Trump in the room.</description></item><item><title>If You’re Reading This, You’re Probably ‘WEIRD’ | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360039/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Here’s a little experiment. Take a second to think about how you would fill in the blank in this sentence: “I am _____.”
If you’re anything like me, the first descriptors that come to mind are personal attributes (like “curious” or “kind”) or identities (like “a journalist” or “a runner”). And if you answered that way, then I have some news for you: You are weird.
I mean that in a very specific way.</description></item><item><title>The Teen Mental Health Crisis, Part 2 | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360040/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360040/</guid><description>Podcast Description The data is clear: Levels of anxiety, depression, self-harm and suicide have spiked for American teenagers over the last decade. Last Friday’s episode with the psychologist Jean Twenge sifted through that data to uncover both the scale of the crisis and its possible causes. Today’s episode focuses on the experiences behind that data: the individuals who are struggling, and what we can do as friends, parents and a broader society to help them.</description></item><item><title>The Teen Mental Health Crisis, Part 1 | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360041/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360041/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re in the midst of a serious teen mental health crisis. The number of teenagers and young adults with clinical depression more than doubled between 2011 and 2021. The suicide rate for teenagers nearly doubled from 2007 to 2019, and tripled for 10- to 14-year- olds in particular. According to the C.D.C., nearly 25 percent of teenage girls made a suicide plan in 2021. What’s going on in the lives of teenagers that has produced such a startling uptick?</description></item><item><title>A Libertarian and I Debate the Debt Ceiling | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360042/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360042/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Jan. 19, the United States officially hit its debt limit. In response, the Treasury Department began using accounting maneuvers known as “extraordinary measures” to continue paying the government’s obligations temporarily. But according to Treasury Secretary Janet Yellen, that money could run out as soon as June 1. If the United States hasn’t raised or suspended its borrowing cap, known as the debt ceiling, by then, America will default on its debt.</description></item><item><title>Best Of: A Weird, Wonderful Conversation with Kim Stanley Robinson | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360043/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kim Stanley Robinson is one of the great living science fiction writers and one of the most astute observers of how planets look, feel and work. His Mars Trilogy imagined what it might be like for humans to settle on the red planet. His best-selling novel “The Ministry for the Future” is a masterful effort at envisioning what might happen to Earth in a future of unchecked climate change.</description></item><item><title>Best Of: Why Adults Lose the ‘Beginner’s Mind’ | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360044/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Here’s a sobering thought: The older we get, the harder it is for us to learn, to question, to reimagine. This isn’t just habit hardening into dogma. It’s encoded into the way our brains change as we age. And it’s worsened by an intellectual and economic culture that prizes efficiency and dismisses play.
Alison Gopnik is a professor of psychology and philosophy at the University of California, Berkeley, where she runs the Cognitive Development and Learning Lab; she’s also the author of over 100 papers and half a dozen books, including “The Gardener and the Carpenter” and “The Philosophical Baby.</description></item><item><title>Best Of: How the Fed Is ‘Shaking the Entire System’ | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360045/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360045/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Monday, First Republic Bank folded before being sold by regulators to JPMorgan Chase. At the time, it was the 14th largest bank in the U.S. and it is the second-largest American bank by assets to ever collapse.
The story of First Republic’s fall is similar to that of Silicon Valley Bank and Signature before it – the value of the bank’s assets began to plummet as the Fed raised interest rates to fight inflation, causing a crisis of confidence among investors and depositors.</description></item><item><title>The Culture Creating A.I. Is Weird. Here’s Why That Matters. | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360046/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360046/</guid><description>Podcast Description In recent months, we’ve witnessed the rise of chatbots that can pass law and business school exams, artificial companions who’ve become best friends and lovers and music generators that produce remarkably humanlike songs. It’s hard to know how to process it all. But if there’s one thing that’s certain, it’s this: The future — shaped by technologies like artificial intelligence — is going to be profoundly weird. It’s going to look, feel and function differently from the world we have grown to recognize.</description></item><item><title>Democrats: Pay Attention to What’s Happening in California | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360047/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360047/</guid><description>Podcast Description California is a land of contrasts. The state is home to staggering wealth, world-remaking tech companies, and some of the world’s boldest climate policy. It also has immense income inequality, arguably the worst housing crisis in the country, and the highest poverty rate in the nation when you factor in housing costs.
The dysfunction of our national politics is often attributed to division and gridlock. But in California, Democrats are at the wheel.</description></item><item><title>Best Of: The War Within the Republican Party | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360048/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360048/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Monday, Fox News abruptly announced that the network and its star primetime host, Tucker Carlson, “have agreed to part ways” after more than a decade. The announcement came less than a week after Fox agreed to pay $787.5 million in a defamation lawsuit that prominently featured Carlson’s show and its role in spreading misinformation about the 2020 election.
The news is just the latest instantiation of a broader story: In recent years, the Republican Party has morphed from a coherent institution into a fractured movement at war with itself.</description></item><item><title>Matthew Desmond On America’s Addiction to Poverty | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360049/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360049/</guid><description>Podcast Description According to the Center on Poverty and Social Policy at Columbia University, 14.3 percent of Americans — nearly 50 million people — were living in poverty in December. The scale of poverty in the U.S. dwarfs that of most of our peer countries. And it raises the question: Why does so much poverty persist in one of the richest countries in the world?
For the Princeton sociologist Matthew Desmond, the answer is simple: Poverty is a policy choice.</description></item><item><title>The ‘Quiet Catastrophe’ Brewing in Our Social Lives | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360050/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360050/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s impossible to deny that the U.S. has a serious loneliness problem. One 2018 report by the Kaiser Family Foundation found that 22 percent of all adults — almost 60 million Americans — said they often or always felt lonely or socially isolated. That was a full two years before the Covid pandemic. And Americans appear to be getting lonelier over time: From 1990 to 2021, there was a 25 percentage point decrease in the number of Americans who reported having five or more close friends.</description></item><item><title>This Philosopher Wants Liberals to Take Political Power Seriously | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360051/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360051/</guid><description>Podcast Description America today faces a crisis of governance. In the face of numerous challenges — from climate change, to housing shortages, to pandemics — our institutions struggle to act quickly and decisively. Democratic processes often get captured by special interests or paralyzed by polarization. And, in response, public faith in government has reached a new low.
For the political philosopher Danielle Allen, this crisis requires a complete transformation of our democratic institutions.</description></item><item><title>What Biden’s Top A.I. Thinker Concluded We Should Do | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360052/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360052/</guid><description>Podcast Description In October, the White House released a 70-plus-page document called the “Blueprint for an A.I. Bill of Rights.” The document’s ambition was sweeping. It called for the right for individuals to “opt out” from automated systems in favor of human ones, the right to a clear explanation as to why a given A.I. system made the decision it did, and the right for the public to give input on how A.</description></item><item><title>Why A.I. Might Not Take Your Job or Supercharge the Economy | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360053/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Typically when we put out a call for audience questions, there’s no single topic that dominates. This time was different. The questions we received were overwhelmingly focused on artificial intelligence: Do A.I. systems pose an existential threat to humanity? Will robots take our jobs? How could these machines potentially make our lives — and the lives of our children — better?
So I asked the show’s senior editor, Roge Karma, to join me to talk through them.</description></item><item><title>The Most Amazing — and Dangerous — Technology in the World | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360054/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360054/</guid><description>Podcast Description “We rarely think about chips, yet they’ve created the modern world,” writes the historian Chris Miller.
He’s not exaggerating. Semiconductors don’t just power our phones and computers; they also enable our cars, planes and home appliances to function. They are essential to everything from developing advanced military equipment to training artificial intelligence systems. Chips are the foundation of modern economic prosperity, military strength and geopolitical power.
But semiconductors are also part of one of the most concentrated supply chains of any technology today.</description></item><item><title>Best Of: A Powerful Theory of Why the Far Right Is Thriving Across the Globe | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360055/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360055/</guid><description>Podcast Description In last November&amp;rsquo;s midterm elections, voters placed the Republican Party in charge of the House of Representatives. In 2024, it’s very possible that Republicans will take over the Senate as well and voters will elect Donald Trump — or someone like him — as president.
But the United States isn’t alone in this regard. Over the course of 2022, Italy elected a far-right prime minister from a party with Fascist roots; a party founded by neo-Nazis and skinheads won the second-highest number of seats in Sweden’s Parliament; Viktor Orban’s Fidesz party in Hungary won its fourth consecutive election by a landslide; Marine Le Pen won 41 percent of the vote in the final round of France’s presidential elections; and Jair Bolsonaro came dangerously close to winning re-election in Brazil.</description></item><item><title>Trump’s Legal Jeopardy and America’s Political Crossroads | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360056/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Donald Trump’s legal troubles are mounting. A Manhattan grand jury investigation into the hush-money payment to Stormy Daniels could soon make Trump the first former American president ever to be criminally indicted.
But the Manhattan case isn’t the only source of legal risk for Trump. In Georgia, the Fulton County district attorney is considering criminal charges for Trump’s efforts to influence the 2020 election, and the Department of Justice is investigating his role in the Jan.</description></item><item><title>A Radical Way of Thinking About Money | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360057/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360057/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s been two weeks since the Silicon Valley Bank run, and we’re still feeling the ripple effects — not just at banks like Signature, First Republic and Credit Suisse, which are definitely taking a beating. Across the industry, too, banks are on edge, and regulators are rushing to keep the system together.
Every financial crisis is different. And every financial crisis is the same. Assets that a lot of people thought were safe — mortgage-backed securities in the 2008 crisis and long-term Treasury bonds in this latest bank run — end up not being so secure.</description></item><item><title>Freaked Out? We Really Can Prepare for A.I. | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360058/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360058/</guid><description>Podcast Description OpenAI last week released its most powerful language model yet: GPT-4, which vastly outperforms its predecessor, GPT-3.5, on a variety of tasks.
GPT-4 can pass the bar exam in the 90th percentile, while the previous model struggled around in the 10th percentile. GPT-4 scored in the 88th percentile on the LSAT, up from GPT-3.5’s 40th percentile. And on the advanced sommelier theory test, GPT-4 performed better than 77 percent of test-takers.</description></item><item><title>My View on A.I. | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360059/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360059/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is something a bit different: Not an interview, but a commentary of my own.
We’ve done a lot of shows on A.I. of late, and there are more to come. On Tuesday, GPT-4 was released, and its capabilities are stunning, and in some cases, chilling. More on that in Tuesday’s episode. But I wanted to take a moment to talk through my own views on A.I. and how I’ve arrived at them.</description></item><item><title>Why Silicon Valley Bank Collapsed — And What Comes Next | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360060/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last Friday, in the largest bank failure since 2008, Silicon Valley Bank failed.
Banks fail all the time. But unless it’s a big or highly-connected bank, most of us don’t pay much attention. That’s because at the average bank, about half of all accounts are F.D.I.C.-insured. That means, if a typical bank fails, the F.D.I.C. will step in and pay every depositor back up to $250,000.
But Silicon Valley Bank was not a typical bank.</description></item><item><title>How China Went From Economic Superstar to Faltering Giant | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360061/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360061/</guid><description>Podcast Description In just a few years, the narrative on China has almost completely flipped. The dominant sentiments in America had been awe, envy and a kind of fear. China’s growth seemed relentless. Its manufacturing prowess was lapping ours. It weathered the pandemic without the mass death seen in the West. It could build housing and transit and infrastructure at a speed we could no longer even imagine.
And then, as 2022 ticked over to 2023, things changed.</description></item><item><title>The Men — and Boys — Are Not Alright | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360062/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 11:23:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360062/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1972, when Congress passed Title IX to tackle gender equity in education, men were 13 percentage points more likely to hold bachelor’s degrees than women; today women are 15 points more likely to do so than men. The median real hourly wage for working men is lower today than it was in the 1970s. And men account for almost three out of four “deaths of despair,” from overdose or suicide.</description></item><item><title>If You Read the G.O.P.’s Anti-Trans Policies, You’ll See What It Really Wants | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360063/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360063/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the 2023 legislative session alone, Republican state legislators have introduced more than a hundred bills seeking to restrict transgender people’s freedoms, rights and health care access. To put that in perspective, in the 2018 legislative session, fewer than 20 such bills restricting transgender rights were proposed.
Over the weekend, at the Conservative Political Action Conference, the commentator Michael Knowles said that “transgenderism must be eradicated from public life entirely.</description></item><item><title>The Art of Noticing – and Appreciating – Our Dizzying World | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360064/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360064/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Poetry is the attempt to understand fully what is real, what is present, what is imaginable, what is feelable, and how can I loosen the grip of what I already know to find some new, changed relationship,” the poet Jane Hirshfield tells me. Through poetry, she says, “I know something new and I have been changed.”
Hirshfield is the award-winning author of many books of poetry and two illuminating essay collections about what poetry does to us and in the world: “Nine Gates: Entering the Mind of Poetry” and “Ten Windows: How Great Poems Transform the World.</description></item><item><title>Our Brains Weren’t Designed for This Kind of Food | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360065/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our society’s dominant narrative is that body size is a product of individual willpower. We are skinny or fat because of the choices we make: the kinds of food we buy, the amounts we eat, the exercise regimens we follow.
Research has never been kind to this thesis. It’s a folk narrative we use to punish people, not an empirical account of why residents of most rich countries are getting heavier over time.</description></item><item><title>Inside the Minds of Spiders, Octopuses and Artificial Intelligence | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360066/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adrian Tchaikovsky’s “Children of Time” is about an advanced civilization built by sentient spiders. A sequel, “Children of Ruin,” is about a society run by superintelligent octopuses. I love these books. They’re remarkably serious about their premises, and by the end, it’s human civilization and our limited sensorium that come to seem strange.
But Tchaikovsky’s latest book, “Children of Memory,” ostensibly about crows, read as something very different to me: the best fictional representation I’ve read of what it is like to interact with, and perhaps even be, an artificial intelligence system like ChatGPT.</description></item><item><title>This Book Changed My Relationship to Pain | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360067/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Physical pain is a universal human experience. And for many of us, it’s a constant one. Roughly 20 percent of American adults — some 50 million people — suffer from a form of chronic pain. For some, that means having terrible days from time to time. For others, it means a life of constant suffering. Either way, the depth and scale of pain in our society is a massive problem.</description></item><item><title>The Inflation Story Has Changed Dramatically. Paul Krugman Breaks It Down. | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360068/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360068/</guid><description>Podcast Description In recent months, the story of the U.S. economy has changed significantly. The January Consumer Price Index showed that annual inflation slowed for the seventh straight month. That month, the economy also added over half a million jobs, and unemployment reached 3.4 percent, its lowest level since 1969. In light of these trends, comparisons to the 1970s stagflation crisis have weakened, and the possibility of a “soft landing” looks increasingly likely.</description></item><item><title>How the $500 Billion Attention Industry Really Works | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360069/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360069/</guid><description>Podcast Description For most of us, seeing an advertisement pop up while we’re scrolling on Instagram or reading an article or watching a video is the most banal experience possible. But in the background of those experiences is a $500 billion marketplace where our attention is being bought, packaged and sold at split-second speeds virtually every minute of every day. Online advertising is the economic engine of the internet, and that engine is fueled by our attention.</description></item><item><title>The Tao of Rick Rubin | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360070/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Reading Rick Rubin’s production discography is like taking a tour through the commanding heights of American music over the past few decades. Jay-Z. Run-DMC. Beastie Boys. Slayer. The Red Hot Chili Peppers. Johnny Cash. Kanye West. Neil Diamond. Brandi Carlile. Eminem. Adele. And it’s not just his production credits: Rubin co-founded Def Jam Recordings and was a co-chairman of Columbia Records. What’s allowed him to work with so many different kinds of artists, across such a stunning range of genres, so successfully?</description></item><item><title>How Liberals — Yes, Liberals — Are Hobbling Government | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360071/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360071/</guid><description>Podcast Description In my columns and on this show over the past few years, I’ve argued that to achieve the goals liberals hold most dear, we need a liberalism that builds. A liberalism that builds everything from multifamily housing and mass transit systems to transmission lines and solar farms. And we need a liberalism that can build it all quickly, cheaply and effectively. But even in the places where liberals have governing power, they are often failing to do exactly that.</description></item><item><title>Best Of: Why Housing Is So Expensive — Particularly in Blue States | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360072/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ezra is out sick, so today, we’re sharing one of our favorite conversations — with Jenny Schuetz, a senior fellow at the Brookings Institution whose 2022 book “Fixer Upper: How to Repair America’s Broken Housing Systems,” is perhaps the best, clearest overview of America’s housing problems to date.
In this conversation, recorded in July 2022, Schuetz breaks down the politics and policies that have contributed to America’s multiple housing crises — from housing shortages and high homelessness rates in major cities to the increasing elusiveness of homeownership for many young Americans.</description></item><item><title>First Person: How the Left Is Cannibalizing Its Own Power | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360073/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ezra is out sick, so today, we&amp;rsquo;re sharing an episode from the New York Times Opinion podcast, “First Person.” Each week, the host Lulu Garcia-Navarro sits down with people living through the headlines for intimate and surprising conversations that help us make sense of our complicated world. This episode features Maurice Mitchell, the head of the Working Families Party.
Mitchell has been an organizer for two decades, working in progressive politics and the Movement for Black Lives.</description></item><item><title>Is This How a Cold War With China Begins? | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360074/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360074/</guid><description>Podcast Description There are few issues on which the dominant consensus in Washington has changed as rapidly in recent years as it has on China. Donald Trump made taking on China a core pillar of his campaign and presidency. And while Joe Biden has toned down the harsh anti-China rhetoric of his predecessor, many of his administration’s policies have gone even further than Trump’s did.
In October the Biden administration unveiled sweeping controls on advanced chip exports to China — a move that former Trump officials have described as a sharp break from where their administration’s policies were.</description></item><item><title>There’s Been a Revolution in How China Is Governed | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360075/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360075/</guid><description>Podcast Description There are few stories that are more crucial to the world’s future than what’s happening in China. Take any of the most important issues of our time — climate change, geopolitics, the global economy, advanced technologies — and China is at the center of them. American politics itself has increasingly come to revolve around competition with China.
In other words, what happens in China doesn’t stay in China — it reverberates through the global economy, the American political system and the international order.</description></item><item><title>How Right-Wing Media Ate the Republican Party | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360076/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360076/</guid><description>Podcast Description In recent weeks, America got a preview of how the new Republican House majority would wield its power. In attempting to perform a basic function of government — electing a speaker — a coalition of 20 House members caused Kevin McCarthy to lose 14 rounds of votes, decreasing his power with each compromise and successive vote.
This is not normal. Party unity ebbs and flows, but the G.O.P. in recent decades has come apart at the seams.</description></item><item><title>A Revelatory Tour of Martin Luther King Jr.’s Forgotten Teachings | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360077/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360077/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s hard to think of a more celebrated figure of the 20th century than Martin Luther King Jr.
He has a national memorial in Washington, D.C. His birthday is one of just 11 federal holidays. And his words and legacy are routinely evoked by politicians of both major parties.
But the paradox of King’s legacy is that while many revere him, very few actually read him. Most of us can cite a handful of his most famous quotes, but King’s actual teachings span five books, countless speeches and sermons, and years of detailed correspondence.</description></item><item><title>A Guide to the ‘Legal Fictions’ That Create Wealth, Inequality and Economic Crises | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360078/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360078/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Capitalism, it turns out, is more than just the exchange of goods in a market economy,” Katharina Pistor writes. “It is a market economy in which some assets are placed on legal steroids.”
Pistor is a professor of comparative law at Columbia Law School, the director of the Center on Global Legal Transformation at Columbia University and the author of “The Code of Capital: How the Law Creates Wealth and Inequality.</description></item><item><title>Dan Savage on Polyamory, Chosen Family and Better Sex | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360079/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Even if you don’t recognize the advice columnist Dan Savage by name, it’s possible that his ideas have influenced how you think about sex and relationships. For decades now, Savage has been arguing that our expectations for long-term partnerships are way too high; that healthy relationships are about acknowledging our vast spectrum of desires, not repressing them; and that monogamy is not the ideal setup for every partnership. Through over 30 years of writing “Savage Love,” one of the most widely read sex advice columns in the country, and more than 17 years of hosting the podcast “Savage Lovecast,” he has been one of America’s most subtly influential public intellectuals on the topic of how humans conduct our most intimate — and important — relationships.</description></item><item><title>A Skeptical Take on the A.I. Revolution | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360080/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360080/</guid><description>Podcast Description The year 2022 was jam-packed with advances in artificial intelligence, from the release of image generators like DALL-E 2 and text generators like Cicero to a flurry of developments in the self-driving car industry. And then, on November 30, OpenAI released ChatGPT, arguably the smartest, funniest, most humanlike chatbot to date.
In the weeks since, ChatGPT has become an internet sensation. If you’ve spent any time on social media recently, you’ve probably seen screenshots of it describing Karl Marx’s theory of surplus value in the style of a Taylor Swift song or explaining how to remove a sandwich from a VCR in the style of the King James Bible.</description></item><item><title>Sabbath and the Art of Rest | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360081/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do we know how to truly rest? Who would we be if we did?
I’ve been wrestling with these questions since I read Abraham Joshua Heschel’s stunning book “The Sabbath” in college. The ancient Jewish ritual of the Sabbath reserves a full day per week for rest. As it’s commonly practiced, that means about 25 hours every week of no work, very little technology and plenty of in-person gathering.</description></item><item><title>Best Of: How America's Poet Laureate Sees Our World | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360082/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360082/</guid><description>Podcast Description ​​“One of the biggest things about poetry is that it holds all of humanity,” the poet Ada Limón tells me. “It holds the huge and enormous and tumbling sphere of human emotions.”
At the end of a turbulent year, we thought revisiting this May 2022 conversation with Limón would be fitting. Just months after our conversation, Limón was named U.S. poet laureate.
Limón’s work is a salve for all that the world faces: her books of poetry are filled with meditations on grief and infertility, as well as striking moments of insight about friendship, lust and our fellowship with animals.</description></item><item><title>Best Of: Want to Save Democracy? Run For Office. | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360083/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360083/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, we’re revisiting some of our favorite episodes from the year. For those who make New Year’s resolutions, today’s conversation might plant the seed for a bold one: Running for office.
Amanda Litman is a co-founder of Run for Something, which recruits and supports young, progressive candidates who want to run for office. We spoke in February 2022, but our conversation remains relevant as ever. It’s about the mechanics of American democracy, the confusions and myths that keep so many of us from participating in them and the practical question of what it means to step off the sidelines and, well, run for something.</description></item><item><title>Best Of: Who Wins — and Who Loses — in the A.I. Revolution? | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360084/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360084/</guid><description>Podcast Description This past year, we’ve witnessed considerable progress in the development of artificial intelligence, from the release of the image generators like DALL-E 2 to chat bots like ChatGPT and Cicero to a flurry of self-driving cars. So this week, we’re revisiting some of our favorite conversations about the rise of A.I. and what it means for the world.
Today’s conversation is with Sam Altman. He’s the C.E.O. of OpenAI, the company behind ChatGPT.</description></item><item><title>Best Of: Is A.I. the Problem? Or Are We? | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360085/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360085/</guid><description>Podcast Description This past year, we’ve witnessed considerable progress in the development of artificial intelligence, from the release of the image generators like DALL-E 2 to chat bots like ChatGPT and Cicero to a flurry of self-driving cars. So this week, we’re revisiting some of our favorite conversations about the rise of A.I. and what it means for the world.
Brian Christian’s “The Alignment Problem” is the best book on the key technical and moral questions of A.</description></item><item><title>What I'm Thinking About at the End of 2022 | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360086/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360086/</guid><description>Podcast Description As 2022 comes to a close, we decided to invite listeners to send in questions for an ask-me-anything episode. And boy, did you all deliver. We received hundreds of fantastic questions, and my column editor, Aaron Retica, joined me to ask some of them. Is equality of opportunity preferable to equality of outcomes? What would a better version of Twitter look like? Are Republicans more politically savvy than Democrats?</description></item><item><title>Time Is Way Weirder Than You Think | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360087/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360087/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s not an exaggeration to say that “clock time” runs our lives. From the moment our alarms go off in the morning, the clock reigns supreme: our meetings, our appointments, even our social plans are often timed down to the minute. We even measure the quality of our lives with reference to time, often lamenting that time seems to “fly by” when we’re having fun and “drags on” when we’re bored or stagnant.</description></item><item><title>Three Signals We’ve Entered a New Economic Era | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360088/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360088/</guid><description>Podcast Description “From the U.S. Federal Reserve’s initial misjudgment that inflation would be ‘transitory’ to the current consensus that a probable U.S. recession will be ‘short and shallow,’ there has been a strong tendency to see economic challenges as both temporary and quickly reversible,” writes the economist Mohamed El-Erian. “But rather than one more turn of the economic wheel, the world may be experiencing major structural and secular changes that will outlast the current business cycle.</description></item><item><title>There’s Been a Massive Change in Where American Policy Gets Made | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360089/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Since 2021, Democrats have controlled the House, the Senate and the presidency, and they’ve used that power to pass consequential legislation, from the American Rescue Plan to the Inflation Reduction Act. That state of affairs was exceptional: In the 50 years between 1970 and 2020, the U.S. House, Senate and presidency were only under unified party control for 14 years. Divided government has become the norm in American politics.</description></item><item><title>A Conservative’s Take on the Chaotic State of the Republican Party | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360090/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Republicans already hold tremendous power in America. They have appointed six of the nine current Supreme Court justices. They have more state trifectas (control of both legislative houses, as well as the governor’s seat) than Democrats. And come 2023, they will also control the House of Representatives.
But there’s a hollowness at the core of the modern G.O.P. It’s hard to identify any clear party leader, coherent policy agenda or concerted electoral strategy.</description></item><item><title>The Hidden Costs of Cheap Meat | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360091/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360091/</guid><description>Podcast Description About 50 years ago, beef cost more than $7 a pound in today’s dollars. Today, despite high inflation, beef is down to about $4.80 a pound, and chicken is just around $1.80 a pound. But those low prices hide the true costs of the meat we consume — costs that the meat and poultry industries have quietly offloaded onto not only the animals we consume but us humans, too.</description></item><item><title>This Conversation About the 'Reading Mind' Is a Gift | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360092/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Every day, we consume a mind-boggling amount of information. We scan online news articles, sift through text messages and emails, scroll through our social-media feeds — and that’s usually before we even get out of bed in the morning. In 2009, a team of researchers found that the average American consumed about 34 gigabytes of information a day. Undoubtedly, that number would be even higher today.
But what are we actually getting from this huge influx of information?</description></item><item><title>Bill McKibben on the Power That Could Save the Planet | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360093/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360093/</guid><description>Podcast Description The fight against climate change is at a crossroads.
This past year, the climate movement in the United States achieved significant success. The recently passed Inflation Reduction Act represents the single largest investment in emissions reduction in U.S. history. More than a dozen states have taken some form of climate action in 2022 alone. Earlier this year, California — which, if it were a country, would have the fifth largest economy in the world — approved a record $54 billion in climate spending alongside sweeping new restrictions on fossil fuel development.</description></item><item><title>I Don’t Quite Buy the DeSantis Narrative, and Other Midterm Thoughts | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360094/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360094/</guid><description>Podcast Description The results of Tuesday’s midterm elections are still trickling in, but the broader story is clear: The red wave that many anticipated never materialized. Republicans gained 54 House seats against Bill Clinton in 1994 and 63 seats against Barack Obama in 2010. It doesn’t look as though the G.O.P. will secure anything close to that in 2022, and Democrats could retain their narrow control of the Senate — all against the backdrop of raging inflation and low approval ratings for President Biden.</description></item><item><title>George Saunders on the ‘Braindead Megaphone’ That Makes Our Politics So Awful | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360095/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360095/</guid><description>Podcast Description George Saunders is regarded as one of our greatest living fiction writers. He won the Booker Prize in 2017 for his novel “Lincoln in the Bardo” and has published numerous short-story collections to wide acclaim, including his most recent book, “Liberation Day.” He also happens to be one of my favorite people to read and to talk to.
Saunders is an incredibly prescient and sharp observer of American political culture.</description></item><item><title>Inflation Does More Than Raise Prices. It Destroys Governments. | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360096/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360096/</guid><description>Podcast Description “One can usually pretend that there is a logic to the distribution of wealth — that behind a person’s prosperity lies some rational basis, whether it is that person’s hard work, skill and farsightedness or some ancestor’s,” writes J. Bradford DeLong. “Inflation — even moderate inflation — strips the mask.”
DeLong is an economic historian at the University of California, Berkeley, a former deputy assistant secretary of the Treasury and the author of “Slouching Towards Utopia” — a new book about the wave of economic growth that transformed the world in the 20th century.</description></item><item><title>A Powerful Theory of Why the Far Right Is Thriving Across the Globe | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360097/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360097/</guid><description>Podcast Description As we approach the 2022 midterms, the outlook for American democracy doesn’t appear promising. An increasingly Trumpist, anti-democratic Republican Party is poised to take over at least one chamber of Congress. And the Democratic Party, facing an inflationary economy and with an unpopular president in office, looks helpless to stop them.
But the United States isn’t alone in this regard. Over the course of 2022, Italy elected a far-right prime minister from a party with Fascist roots, a party founded by neo-Nazis and skinheads won the second-highest number of seats in Sweden’s Parliament, Viktor Orban’s Fidesz party in Hungary won its fourth consecutive election by a landslide, Marine Le Pen won 41 percent of the vote in the final round of France’s presidential elections and — just this past weekend — Jair Bolsonaro came dangerously close to winning re-election in Brazil.</description></item><item><title>These Political Scientists Surveyed 500,000 Voters. Here Are Their Unnerving Conclusions. | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360098/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360098/</guid><description>Podcast Description How does the popularity of a president’s policies impact his or her party’s electoral chances? Why have Latinos — and other voters of color — swung toward the Republican Party in recent years? How does the state of the economy influence how people vote, and which economic metrics in particular matter most?
We can’t answer those questions yet for 2022. But we can look at previous elections for insights into how things could play out.</description></item><item><title>A Step-by-Step Guide to Becoming a Trump Enabler | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360099/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360099/</guid><description>Podcast Description ​​“What would you do for your relevance?” the political journalist Mark Leibovich asks in his new book, “Thank You for Your Servitude: Donald Trump’s Washington and the Price of Submission.” “How badly did you want into the clubhouse, no matter how wretched it became inside?” For Leibovich, you can’t truly understand the current Republican Party without taking stock of the almost Shakespearean drama that unfolded during the Trump presidency — in which Republican after Republican bowed to the will of their ascendant party leader.</description></item><item><title>There’s Been a ‘Regime Change’ in How Democrats Think About Elections | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360100/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360100/</guid><description>Podcast Description According to the conventional rules of politics, Democrats should be on track for electoral disaster this November. Joe Biden’s approval rating is stuck around 42 percent, inflation is still sky-high and midterms usually swing against the incumbent president’s party — a recipe for the kind of political wipeouts we saw in 2018, 2010 and 1994.
But that’s not what the polls show. Currently, Democrats are on track to hold the Senate and lose narrowly in the House, which raises all kinds of questions: Why are Republicans failing to capitalize on such a favorable set of circumstances?</description></item><item><title>A Legendary World-Builder on Multiverses, Revolution and the ‘Souls’ of Cities | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360101/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360101/</guid><description>Podcast Description N.K. Jemisin is a fantasy and science-fiction writer who won three consecutive Hugo Awards — considered the highest honor in science-fiction writing — for her “Broken Earth” trilogy; she has since won two more Hugos, as well as other awards. But in imagining wild fictional narratives, the beloved sci-fi and fantasy writer has also cultivated a remarkable view of our all-too-real world. In her fiction, Jemisin crafts worlds that resemble ours but get disrupted by major shocks: ecological disasters, invasions by strange, tentacled creatures and more — all of which operate as thought experiments that can help us think through how human beings could and should respond to similar calamities.</description></item><item><title>What Rachel Maddow Has Been Thinking About Offscreen | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360102/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360102/</guid><description>Podcast Description “The Rachel Maddow Show” debuted in the interregnum between political eras. Before it lay the 9/11 era and the George W. Bush presidency. Days after the show launched in 2008, Lehman Brothers collapsed, and a few weeks later Barack Obama was elected president.
And then history just kept speeding up. The Tea Party. The debt ceiling debacles. Donald Trump. The coronavirus pandemic. January 6th. The big lie. Maddow covered and tried to make sense of it all.</description></item><item><title>Hard Fork: Elon’s Hidden Motives + A Meetup in the Metaverse | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360103/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we’re bringing you an episode from the recently launched New York Times podcast, Hard Fork. Hosted by veteran tech journalists Kevin Roose and Casey Newton, Hard Fork is a rigorous and fun exploration of Silicon Valley’s already-emerging future — and its evolving imprint on the rest of the world.
In this episode, Kevin and Casey discuss Elon Musk’s on-again-off-again – and recently on-again – interest in Twitter, as the billionaire signals once again that he’s buying the social media platform.</description></item><item><title>How the Fed Is ‘Shaking the Entire System’ | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360104/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360104/</guid><description>Podcast Description “There are moments when history making creeps up on you,” writes the economic historian Adam Tooze. “This is one of those moments.”
Countries across the world are raising interest rates at unprecedented speeds. That global monetary tightening is colliding with spiking food and energy prices, financial market instability, high levels of emerging market debt and economies still struggling to recover from the Covid pandemic. Alone, each of these factors would warrant concern; combined, they could be catastrophic.</description></item><item><title>When You Can’t Trust the Stories Your Mind Is Telling | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360105/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360105/</guid><description>Podcast Description The National Institute of Mental Health estimates that nearly one in five adults in America lives with a mental illness. And we have plenty of evidence — from suicide rates to the percentage of Americans on psychopharmaceuticals — that our collective mental health is getting worse. But beyond mental health diagnoses lies a whole, complicated landscape of difficult, often painful, mental states that all of us experience at some point in our lives.</description></item><item><title>Ethereum’s Founder on What Crypto Can — and Can’t — Do | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360106/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360106/</guid><description>Podcast Description When most people hear “crypto,” the first thing they think of is “currencies.” Cryptocurrencies have skyrocketed in popularity over the past few years. And they’ve given rise to an entire ecosystem of financial speculation, get rich quick schemes, and in some cases outright fraud.
But there’s another side of crypto that gets less attention: the segment of the community that is interested in the way the technology that powers crypto can decentralize decision making, make institutions more transparent and transform the way organizations are governed.</description></item><item><title>We Know So Little About What Makes Humanity Prosper | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360107/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why do some countries produce far more science Nobel laureates than others? Why did Silicon Valley happen in California rather than Japan or Boston? Why did the Industrial Revolution happen when it did and where it did?
These are just some of the questions that have inspired the formation of a new intellectual movement called “progress studies.” The basic idea is this: For hundreds of thousands of years, human history played out without any rapid, marked advance in material living standards.</description></item><item><title>Why Russia Is Losing the War in Ukraine | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360108/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360108/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Russia invaded Ukraine in February, the question most analysts were asking was not whether Russia would win. It was how fast. On almost every quantifiable metric from military strength to economic size Russia has decisive advantages over Ukraine. A swift Russian victory appeared inevitable.
Of course, that swift victory didn’t happen. And in recent weeks, the direction of the war has begun to tilt in Ukraine’s direction. On Sept.</description></item><item><title>The Single Best Guide to Decarbonization I’ve Heard | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360109/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360109/</guid><description>Podcast Description In August, Joe Biden signed into law the Inflation Reduction Act, which included $392 billion towards a new climate budget — the single largest investment in emissions reduction in U.S. history. The CHIPS and Science Act and the Bipartisan Infrastructure Act bring that number up to around $450 billion. All of that spending is designed with one major objective in mind: to put the United States on a path to a decarbonized economy, with the goal of reaching net zero emissions by 2050.</description></item><item><title>Now All Biden Has to Do Is Build It | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360110/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360110/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the past few months, Joe Biden’s agenda has gone from a failed promise to real legislation.
Taken together, the CHIPS and Science Act and the Inflation Reduction Act (along with the Bipartisan Infrastructure Act) have the potential to put America on a path to decarbonization, develop some of the most advanced and crucial supply chains in the world, and build all kinds of next-generation technologies. It’s hard to overstate just how transformative these plans could be if they are carried out in the right way.</description></item><item><title>We Build Civilizations on Status. But We Barely Understand It. | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360111/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360111/</guid><description>Podcast Description “We see status virtually everywhere in social life, if we think to look for it,” writes Cecilia Ridgeway. “It suffuses everyday possessions, the cars we drive, the clothes we wear, the food brands we prefer, and the music we listen to.” And that’s only a partial list. Status influences the neighborhood we live in, the occupation we pursue, the friends we choose. It attaches itself to our race, gender, class and age.</description></item><item><title>Opinion Roundtable: Behind America’s Public School Battles | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360112/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we’re bringing you a special episode from New York Times Opinion: a roundtable, hosted by Lulu Garcia-Navarro, about how parents view the role of school. America’s schools have emerged as a battleground for the country’s most fervent cultural disagreements, and in many places, parents are finding themselves on the front lines. Three parents of public school students joined Lulu Garcia-Navarro to discuss the big questions underlying the new era of parental activism.</description></item><item><title>The Subtle Art of Appreciating ‘Difficult Beauty’ | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360113/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360113/</guid><description>Podcast Description When is the last time you paused — truly paused the flow of life — to appreciate something beautiful? For as long as we know, humans have sought out beauty, believing deeply that beautiful things and experiences can enhance our lives. But what does beauty really do to us? How can it fundamentally alter our experience of the world?
Beauty is always “teaching me something about my own mind,” says the writer and philosopher Chloé Cooper Jones.</description></item><item><title>Best Of: This Conversation With Richard Powers Is a Gift | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360114/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we&amp;rsquo;re revisiting one of our favorite conversations from 2021 with the novelist Richard Powers. Enjoy!
There are certain conversations I fear trying to fit into a description. There’s just more to them than I’m going to be able to convey. This is one of them.
Richard Powers is the author of 13 novels, including the 2019 Pulitzer Prize-winning “The Overstory.” If you haven’t read it, you should. It’ll change you.</description></item><item><title>A Grammy-Nominated Singer Performs and Explores Music's Power | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360115/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360115/</guid><description>Podcast Description In times of deep sorrow or joy, humans have always turned to music. Archaeologists have found evidence of instruments among very early civilizations. Spiritual communities have centered on music for centuries. We teach our children their ABCs and how to brush their teeth with songs. We dance out our feelings and cry along with sad tunes. What is it about music that enables it to work so powerfully on our bodies, minds and emotions?</description></item><item><title>Best Of: Margaret Atwood on the Bible and the Future | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360116/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we&amp;rsquo;re revisiting one of our favorite episodes from this year, with the prolific writer Margaret Atwood.
A good rule of thumb is that whatever Margaret Atwood is worried about now is likely what the rest of us will be worried about a decade from now. The rise of authoritarianism. A backlash against women’s social progress. The seductions and dangers of genetic engineering. Climate change leading to social unrest.</description></item><item><title>Why the Evangelical Movement Is in ‘Disarray’ After Dobbs | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360117/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360117/</guid><description>Podcast Description With Roe now overturned, the evangelical movement has achieved one of its decades-old political priorities. But for many evangelicals, this isn’t the moment of celebration and unity it may have first appeared to be. In the wake of the decision in Dobbs v. Jackson Women’s Health Organization, Russell Moore — a former president of the Ethics &amp;amp; Religious Liberty Commission, the policy wing of the Southern Baptist Convention — described the state of evangelicalism as one of “disarray.</description></item><item><title>Best of: A Life-Changing Philosophy of Games | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360118/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360118/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we’re re-airing one of my favorite episodes of all time. It was originally recorded in February of 2022, but I&amp;rsquo;ve been unable to stop thinking about it ever since.
When we play Monopoly or basketball, we know we are playing a game. The stakes are low. The rules are silly. The point system is arbitrary. But what if life is full of games — ones with much higher stakes — that we don’t even realize we’re playing?</description></item><item><title>The Office is Dying. It’s Time to Rethink How We Work. | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360119/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over the past year, many places have returned to something approximating a prepandemic normal. Restaurants are filling up again. Airports and hotels are packed. Even movie theaters have made a comeback. But that hasn’t been the case for the office. Only about a third of office workers are back in the office full time. And that isn’t likely to change dramatically any time soon: Recent surveys asked executives about the share of their workers who would be back in the office five days a week in the future.</description></item><item><title>How Do We Face Loss With Dignity? | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360120/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360120/</guid><description>Podcast Description In his latest work, “The Last White Man,” the award-winning writer Mohsin Hamid imagines a world that is very like our own, with one major exception: On various days, white people wake up to discover that their skin is no longer white. It’s a heavy premise, but one of Hamid’s unique talents as a novelist is his ability to take on the most difficult of topics — racism, migration, loss — with a remarkably light touch.</description></item><item><title>Three Sentences That Could Change the World — and Your Life | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360121/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s show is built around three simple sentences: “Future people count. There could be a lot of them. And we can make their lives better.” Those sentences form the foundation of an ethical framework known as “longtermism.” They might sound obvious, but to take them seriously is a truly radical endeavor — one with the power to change the world and even your life.
That second sentence is where things start to get wild.</description></item><item><title>Gender Is Complicated for All of Us. Let’s Talk About It. | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360122/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360122/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s hard to think of anything changing more quickly in our society right now than our understanding of gender. There’s an explosion of young people identifying as gender nonconforming in some way or another, and others are coming out as transgender or nonbinary throughout their lives, from childhood to old age. But this sea change has brought with it an enormous amount of confusion and resistance. As of July, lawmakers in 21 states had introduced bills that focus on restricting gender-affirming medical care for transgender youth, such as hormone blockers, and 29 states had introduced bills banning transgender youth from sports.</description></item><item><title>The Argument: Who Can Write About What? | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360123/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360123/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we&amp;rsquo;re bringing you an episode from our friends at The Argument, about cultural appropriation in creative work. In recent years, book written by white authors like “American Dirt” and “The Help&amp;quot; have been criticized for their portrayals of characters of color. Artists’ job is to imagine and create, but what do we do when they get it wrong?
To discuss, Jane Coaston is joined by the Opinion writers Roxane Gay and Jay Caspian Kang.</description></item><item><title>Best Of: Ruth Ozeki’s Enchanted Relationship to Minds and Possessions | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360124/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we&amp;rsquo;re taking a short break and re-releasing one of our favorite episodes from 2022, a conversation with the novelist and Buddhist priest Ruth Ozeki. We&amp;rsquo;ll be back with new episodes next week!
The world has gotten louder, even when we’re alone. A day spent in isolation can still mean a day buffeted by the voices on social media and the news, on podcasts, in emails and text messages.</description></item><item><title>The Mid-Century Media Theorists Who Saw What Was Coming | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360125/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360125/</guid><description>Podcast Description “At the very heart of democracy is a contradiction that cannot be resolved, one that has affected free societies from ancient Greece to contemporary America,” write Zac Gershberg and Sean Illing in their new book, “The Paradox of Democracy.” In order to live up to its name, democracy must be open to free communication and expression; yet that very feature opens democracies up to the forces of chaos, fragmentation and demagoguery that undermine them.</description></item><item><title>A Top Mental Health Expert on Where America Went Wrong | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360126/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360126/</guid><description>Podcast Description There’s a paradox that sits at the center of our mental health conversation in America. On the one hand, our treatments for mental illness have gotten better and better in recent decades. Psychopharmaceuticals have improved considerably; new, more effective methods of psychotherapy have been developed; and we’ve reached a better understanding of what kinds of social support are most helpful for those experiencing mental health crises.
But at the same time, mental health outcomes have moved in exactly the wrong direction.</description></item><item><title>Why Housing Is So Expensive — Particularly in Blue States | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360127/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360127/</guid><description>Podcast Description America is experiencing a housing crisis — or, more accurately, multiple housing crises. A massive housing shortage in major cities has resulted in skyrocketing rents. Low- and middle-income individuals find themselves priced out of the places with the most opportunity. Homelessness is rampant in cities across the country. Developers often face the steepest obstacles to building in the places where new housing is needed most. And young people are increasingly viewing homeownership, once a vital part of the American dream, as hopelessly out of reach.</description></item><item><title>A Weird, Wonderful Conversation With Kim Stanley Robinson | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360128/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360128/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kim Stanley Robinson is one of the great living science fiction writers and one of the most astute observers of how planets look, feel and work. His Mars Trilogy imagined what it might be like for humans to settle on the red planet. His best-selling novel “The Ministry for the Future” is a masterful effort at envisioning what might happen to Earth in a future of unchecked climate change.</description></item><item><title>First Person: To Fight for Ukraine’s Freedom, He Went Back Into the Closet | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360129/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360129/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we&amp;rsquo;re bringing you an episode from the recently launched New York Times Opinion podcast, “First Person,” hosted by Lulu Garcia-Navarro. In each episode, Lulu sits down with people living through the headlines for intimate and surprising conversations that help us make sense of our complicated world. This particular episode is about one gay Ukranian soldier’s experience fighting against Russia.
Since the beginning of the war, Ukrainians of all backgrounds have come together to fight their common enemy, Russia.</description></item><item><title>Michelle Goldberg Grapples With Feminism After Roe | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360130/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360130/</guid><description>Podcast Description “It’s true: We’re in trouble,” writes Michelle Goldberg of the modern feminist movement. “One thing backlashes do is transform a culture’s common sense and horizons of possibility. A backlash isn’t just a political formation. It’s also a new structure of feeling that makes utopian social projects seem ridiculous.”
It wouldn’t be fair to blame the Supreme Court decision in Dobbs v. Jackson Women’s Health Organization and the ensuing wave of draconian abortion laws sweeping the nation on a failure of persuasion, or on a failure of the women’s movement.</description></item><item><title>Liberals Need a Clearer Vision of the Constitution. Here’s What It Could Look Like. | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360131/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360131/</guid><description>Podcast Description For decades now, the conservative legal movement has been on a mission to remake this nation’s laws from the bench. And it’s working. On Friday we released an episode with the legal scholar Kate Shaw that walked through case after case showing how conservative Supreme Court majorities have lurched this country’s laws to the right on guns, voting, gerrymandering, regulatory authority, unions, campaign finance and more in the past 20 years.</description></item><item><title>A Guide to the Supreme Court's Rightward Shift | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360132/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360132/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the past few weeks alone, the Supreme Court has delivered a firestorm of conservative legal victories. States now have far less leeway to restrict gun permits. The right to abortion is no longer constitutionally protected. The Environmental Protection Agency has been kneecapped in its ability to regulate carbon emissions, and by extension, all executive branch agencies will see their power significantly diminished.
But to focus only on this particular Supreme Court term is to miss the bigger picture: In the past few decades, conservative court majorities have dragged this country’s laws to the right on almost every issue imaginable.</description></item><item><title>The Supreme Court Went Off the Rails Long Before Dobbs | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360133/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360133/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Friday, a Supreme Court majority voted to overturn Roe v. Wade. On Sunday, we released an episode with Dahlia Lithwick that goes through the court’s decision in detail, and we will continue to come out with new episodes on the ruling — and its vast implications — in the days and weeks to come.
Today, we’re re-airing an episode that we originally released in February of this year with Columbia Law professor Jamal Greene — a conversation that is even more relevant now than it was when we originally released it.</description></item><item><title>The Dobbs Decision Isn’t Just About Abortion. It’s About Power. | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360134/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 09:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360134/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Friday, a Supreme Court majority voted to overturn Roe v. Wade. Nearly all abortions are already banned in at least nine states, home to 7.2 million women of reproductive age. And it is likely that other bans and restrictions will follow. As the court’s three liberal justices put it in their dissenting opinion, “One result of today’s decision is certain: the curtailment of women’s rights, and of their status as free and equal citizens.</description></item><item><title>The Case for Prosecuting Trump | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360135/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360135/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Jan. 6 hearings have made it clear that Donald Trump led a concerted, monthslong effort to overturn a democratic election. The extensive interviews — over 1,000 — that the House select committee conducted prove that Trump was told there was no evidence of election fraud, but he pressed his anti-democratic case regardless. And it appears that the hearings may be making an impact on public opinion: An ABC News/Ipsos survey released Sunday found that 58 percent of respondents believe Trump should be charged with a crime for his role in the Jan.</description></item><item><title>Two Years Later, We Still Don’t Understand Long Covid. Why? | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360136/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360136/</guid><description>Podcast Description Depending on the data you look at, between 10 and 40 percent of people who get Covid will still have symptoms months later. For some, those symptoms will be modest. A cough, some fatigue. For others, they’ll be life-altering: Debilitating brain fog. Exhaustion. Cardiovascular problems. Blood clotting.
This is what we call long Covid. It’s one term for a vast range of experiences, symptoms, outcomes. It’s one term that may be hiding a vast range of maladies and causes.</description></item><item><title>The End of 'The Everything Bubble' | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360137/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360137/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, the S&amp;amp;P 500 entered what analysts refer to as a bear market. The index has plunged around 22 percent from its most recent peak in January. Many growth stocks and crypto assets have crashed double or triple that amount.
New home sales declined 17 percent in April, causing some analysts to argue that the housing market has peaked. And, in response to rising inflation, the Federal Reserve just approved its largest interest rate increase since 1994, meaning asset prices could dip even lower.</description></item><item><title>Is Climate Change a Reason to Avoid Having Children? and Other Listener Questions Answered | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360138/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360138/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s that time of year, when we invite listeners to send in questions, and I answer them on the air. And as usual, you delivered. I’m joined by my producer Annie Galvin, who asks me some of the most intriguing questions of the many we received: Is climate change a reason to forgo having kids? What would happen if Trump were allowed to return to Twitter, in the event of an Elon Musk acquisition?</description></item><item><title>Socialism Is Supposed to Be a Working-Class Movement. Why Isn’t It? | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360139/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360139/</guid><description>Podcast Description American socialists today find themselves in a tenuous position. Over the past decade, the left has become a powerful force in American politics. Bernie Sanders seriously contested two presidential primaries. Democratic socialists have won local, state and congressional races. Organizations like Democratic Socialists of America and socialist publications like Jacobin have become part of the political conversation.
But the progressive left’s successes have been largely concentrated in well-educated, heavily blue districts, and the movement that claims to represent the interests of workers consistently fails to make meaningful inroads with working-class voters.</description></item><item><title>Thomas Piketty’s Case For ‘Participatory Socialism’ | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360140/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360140/</guid><description>Podcast Description The French economist Thomas Piketty is arguably the world’s greatest chronicler of economic inequality. For decades now, he has collected huge data sets documenting the share of income and wealth that has flowed to the top 1 percent. And the culmination of much of that work, his 2013 book “Capital in the Twenty-First Century,” quickly became one of the most widely read and cited economic texts in recent history.</description></item><item><title>A Conservative's View on Democrats' Biggest Weakness | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360141/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360141/</guid><description>Podcast Description “There is definitely a contest for the future of the center right,” says Reihan Salam, the president of the Manhattan Institute, a conservative think tank. In his telling, one side in this contest is “deeply pessimistic about the prospect of a diversifying America, explicitly anti-urban and increasingly willing to embrace redistribution and centralized power,” more so than conservatism before Donald Trump. This populist right has received a lot of attention since Trump’s election, and we’ve done other shows to try to understand it.</description></item><item><title>Sex, Abortion and Feminism, as Seen From the Right | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360142/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360142/</guid><description>Podcast Description For decades, the conservative position on abortion has been simple: Appoint justices who will overturn Roe V. Wade. That aspiration is now likely to become reality. The question of abortion rights will re-enter the realm of electoral politics in a way it hasn’t for 50 years. And that means Republicans will need to develop a new politics of abortion — a politics that may appeal not only to their anti-abortion base but to some of the many Americans who believe Roe should stand.</description></item><item><title>Best Of: Nikole Hannah-Jones and Ta-Nehisi Coates on the Fight Over U.S. History | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360143/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360143/</guid><description>Podcast Description What does it mean to reckon with the violence, the tragedy, and the numerous contradictions of America?
That is the focus of this conversation – originally aired in July of 2021 – with Nikole Hannah-Jones and Ta- Nehisi Coates. On one level, the conversation is a reflection on the fights over teaching critical race theory and the 1619 Project. But it is really focused on the deeper meaning behind those skirmishes: The ongoing fight over the story we tell about America and why that fight has so gripped our national discourse.</description></item><item><title>A Conversation With Ada Limón, in Six Poems | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360144/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360144/</guid><description>Podcast Description ​​“One of the biggest things about poetry is that it holds all of humanity,” the poet Ada Limón tells me. “It holds the huge and enormous and tumbling sphere of human emotions.”
When the news feels sodden with violence and division, it can be hard to know where to put the difficult emotions it provokes. Poetry may seem an unlikely destination for those emotions, especially to those who don’t read it regularly.</description></item><item><title>The Ethics of Abortion | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360145/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360145/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Justice Samuel Alito’s draft opinion on Dobbs v. Jackson Women’s Health Organization leaked a few weeks ago, it signaled that Roe v. Wade appears likely to be overturned in a matter of weeks. If Roe falls, questions about the right to abortion will re-enter the realm of electoral politics in a way they haven’t for 50 years. States will be solely in charge of determining whether abortion is permitted, under what conditions it should be permitted, and what the appropriate thresholds are for making those decisions.</description></item><item><title>Anne Applebaum on What Liberals Misunderstand About Authoritarianism | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360146/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360146/</guid><description>Podcast Description The experience of reading Hannah Arendt’s 1951 classic “The Origins of Totalitarianism” in the year 2022 is a disorienting one. Although Arendt is writing primarily about Nazi Germany and Stalinist Russia, her descriptions often capture aspects of our present moment more clearly than those of us living through it can ever hope to.
Arendt writes of entire populations who “had reached the point where they would, at the same time, believe everything and nothing, think that everything was possible and that nothing was true.</description></item><item><title>What Does the ‘Post-Liberal Right’ Actually Want? | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360147/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360147/</guid><description>Podcast Description “It begun to dawn on many conservatives that in spite of apparent electoral victories that have occurred regularly since the Reagan years, they have consistently lost, and lost overwhelmingly to progressive forces,” Patrick Deneen writes in a recent essay titled “Abandoning Defensive Crouch Conservatism.” He goes on to argue that conservatives need to reject liberal values like free speech, religious liberty and pluralism, abandon their defensive posturing and use the power of the state to actively fight back against what he calls “liberal totalitarianism.</description></item><item><title>Sway: 'Fear and Panic Are Bedfellows' in Ukraine | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360148/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360148/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we&amp;rsquo;re bringing you an episode from our friends at Sway about the war in Ukraine and the challenges of conflict-zone reporting.
Clarissa Ward has had, as she puts it, a “long and very complicated relationship” with Russia. The chief international correspondent for CNN, she has had stints in Moscow since the beginning of her career, and has struggled to get a Russian visa since she investigated the 2020 poisoning of the Russian opposition leader Aleksei Navalny.</description></item><item><title>Donald Trump Didn’t Hijack the G.O.P. He Understood It. | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360149/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360149/</guid><description>Podcast Description Right now, Republicans of all stripes — Ron DeSantis, J.D. Vance, Mike Pence, Glenn Youngkin — are trying to figure out how to channel the populist energies of Donald Trump into a winning political message. The struggle to achieve such a synthesis is the defining project on the American right today. Its outcome will determine the future of the Republican Party — and American politics.
To understand what the post-Trump future of the G.</description></item><item><title>The Argument: Why the G.O.P. Can't Stop Saying 'Gay' | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360150/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360150/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we&amp;rsquo;re bringing you an episode from our friends at The Argument about Florida&amp;rsquo;s “Don&amp;rsquo;t Say Gay” bill and the broader wave of anti-L.G.B.T.Q. legislation, spurred by the political right, that is spreading across the country. According to the Human Rights Campaign, this year alone, more than 300 anti-L.G.B.T.Q. bills have been introduced in state legislatures.
Why has this issue become a major focus of the Republican Party? And how is the way society treats individuals who identify as L.</description></item><item><title>Elon Musk Might Break Twitter. Maybe That's a Good Thing. | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360151/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360151/</guid><description>Podcast Description If Elon Musk’s bid to purchase Twitter comes to fruition, the world’s richest person will own one of its most important communications platforms. Twitter might have a smaller user base than Facebook, Instagram and even Snapchat, but it shapes the dominant narratives in key industries like politics, media, finance and technology more than any other platform. Attention — particularly that of elite leaders in these industries — is a valuable resource, one that Twitter manages and trades in.</description></item><item><title>Putin May Not Like How He’s Changed Europe | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360152/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360152/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vladimir Putin’s invasion of Ukraine has transformed Europe within a matter of weeks. A continent once fractured by the refugee crisis is now taking in millions of refugees. Countries such as Germany have made considerable pledges to increase military spending. The European Union said it would cut off Russian oil and gas “well before 2030” — a once unthinkable prospect. The European project seems more confident in itself than at any other time in recent history.</description></item><item><title>Emily St. John Mandel on Time Travel, Parenting and the Apocalypse | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360153/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360153/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Station Eleven” by Emily St. John Mandel was published in 2014. That book imagined the world after a pandemic had wiped out, well, almost everyone. It’s a gorgeous novel with a particular emotional power: it helps you grieve a life you still have. But then came a real pandemic, not as lethal as the one Mandel imagined, but a shock nonetheless. And “Station Eleven” — already a beloved international best seller — found a second life.</description></item><item><title>Can Democrats Turn Their 2022 Around? | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360154/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360154/</guid><description>Podcast Description With the midterms just over six months away, the electoral prospects for Democrats are looking bleak. President Biden’s approval rating is at 42 percent, around where Donald Trump’s was at this point in his presidency. Recent polls asking whether Americans want Republicans or Democrats in Congress found that Republicans are leading by about 2 percentage points. And with inflation spiking to its highest point in decades, Covid cases rising and Russia’s invasion of Ukraine continuing to send economic and humanitarian shock waves across the globe, things don’t look as if they are going to get better anytime soon.</description></item><item><title>Best Of: This Conversation Will Change How You Think About Trauma | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360155/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360155/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Trauma is much more than a story about something that happened long ago,” writes Dr. Bessel van der Kolk. “The emotions and physical sensations that were imprinted during the trauma are experienced not as memories but as disruptive physical reactions in the present.”
Van der Kolk, a psychiatrist by training, has been a pioneer in trauma research for decades now and leads the Trauma Research Foundation. His 2014 book “The Body Keeps the Score,” quickly became a touchstone on the topic.</description></item><item><title>A Ukrainian Philosopher on What Putin Never Understood About Ukraine | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360156/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360156/</guid><description>Podcast Description Russia’s invasion of Ukraine is only getting more brutal: We’ve seen the bodies of civilians strewn in the streets in Bucha, the city of Mariupol almost leveled and, just a few days ago, a Russian missile attack on a crowded train station in Kramatorsk killing at least 50 people. The United Nations has confirmed 1,793 civilian deaths in Ukraine, though the actual number is thought to be far higher.</description></item><item><title>Fiona Hill on Whether Ukraine Can Win — and What Happens if Russia Loses | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360157/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360157/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Russia-Ukraine war has changed considerably in recent weeks. Vladimir Putin is no longer talking explicitly about regime change in Ukraine. The Russian military has shifted its focus away from taking Kyiv and toward making territorial gains in Ukraine’s east. The prospect of an outright Ukrainian victory is no longer out of the question. And negotiations between the parties over a possible settlement appear to be making some progress.</description></item><item><title>The Most Thorough Case Against Crypto I've Heard | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360158/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360158/</guid><description>Podcast Description The hype around cryptocurrencies has reached a fever pitch. There are Super Bowl ads for crypto companies featuring celebrities like Matt Damon and Larry David. The Staples Center in Los Angeles is now the Crypto.com Arena. And behind that hype is a distinct vision: a more decentralized economy where individuals have more autonomy over their finances, a grass-roots internet free of the not-so-invisible hand of Big Tech, and a cultural ecosystem where artists and musicians can fairly monetize their work.</description></item><item><title>Sanctioning Russia Is a Form of War. We Need to Treat It Like One. | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360159/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360159/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Russian political scientist Ilya Matveev recently described the impact of the West’s sanctions on his country as “30 years of economic development thrown into the bin.” He’s not exaggerating. Economists expect the Russian economy to contract by at least 15 percent of G.D.P. this year. Inflation is spiking. An exodus of Russian professionals is underway. Stories of shortages and long lines for basic consumer goods abound.
The U.</description></item><item><title>I Keep Hoping Larry Summers Is Wrong. What if He’s Not? | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360160/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360160/</guid><description>Podcast Description “There is a chance that macroeconomic stimulus on a scale closer to World War II levels than normal recession levels will set off inflationary pressures of a kind we have not seen in a generation,” wrote Larry Summers in February 2021. A year later, the debate still rages over the first part of that sentence — the extent to which the American Rescue Plan is responsible for rising prices.</description></item><item><title>Margaret Atwood on Stories, Deception and the Bible | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360161/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360161/</guid><description>Podcast Description A good rule of thumb is that whatever Margaret Atwood is worried about now is likely what the rest of us will be worried about a decade from now. The rise of authoritarianism. A backlash against women’s social progress. The seductions and dangers of genetic engineering. Climate change leading to social unrest. Advertising culture permeating more and more of our lives. Atwood — the author of the Booker Prize-winning novels “The Blind Assassin” and “The Testaments,” as well as “The Handmaid’s Tale,” “Oryx and Crake” and, most recently, the essay collection “Burning Questions” — was writing about these topics decades ago, forecasting the unsettling world that we inhabit now.</description></item><item><title>How Energy Markets Are Shaping Putin’s Invasion — and the World | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360162/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360162/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nearly every dimension of the Ukraine-Russia conflict has been shaped by energy markets.
Russia’s oil and gas exports have long been the foundation of its economy and geopolitical strength. Vladimir Putin’s decision to invade Ukraine — like his annexation of Crimea in 2014 — coincided with high energy prices. While Western sanctions have dealt a major blow to Russia’s financial system, European carve-outs for Russian oil and gas have kept hundreds of millions of dollars flowing to Moscow every day.</description></item><item><title>A Realist Take on How the Russia-Ukraine War Could End | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360163/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360163/</guid><description>Podcast Description As we enter the fourth week of Russia’s invasion of Ukraine, many of the possible pathways this conflict could take are terrifying. A military quagmire that leads to protracted death and suffering. A Russian takeover of Kyiv and installation of a puppet government. An accidental strike on Polish or Romanian territory that draws America and the rest of NATO into war. Or, perhaps worst of all, a series of escalations that culminates in nuclear exchange.</description></item><item><title>Timothy Snyder on the Myths That Blinded the West to Putin’s Plans | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360164/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360164/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Americans and Europeans were guided through the new century by a tale about ‘the end of history,’ by what I will call the politics of inevitability, a sense that the future is just more of the present, that the laws of progress are known, that there are no alternatives, and therefore nothing really to be done,” writes the Yale historian Timothy Snyder in his 2018 book, “The Road to Unfreedom.</description></item><item><title>Masha Gessen on Putin’s 'Profoundly Anti-Modern’ Worldview | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360165/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360165/</guid><description>Podcast Description For Western audiences, the past few weeks have been a torrent of information about what’s happening in Russia and Ukraine. Daily updates of Russian military advances. Horrifying videos of buildings exploding and innocent civilians being killed. Announcements of increasingly severe economic sanctions and major corporate pullouts. Charts showing the collapse of the ruble. Story after story about the hardships facing the Russian economy.
Most Russians, however, are living in an alternate reality.</description></item><item><title>Fiona Hill on the War Putin Is Really Fighting | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360166/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360166/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vladimir Putin was looking for a swift invasion that would halt Ukraine’s drift toward the West, reveal NATO’s fractures and weaknesses and solidify Russia as a global power. In response, the West threatened moderate sanctions, but ultimately showed little interest in stepping between Russia and Ukraine.
Then came the war, and everything changed. Russia’s invasion met with valiant Ukrainian resistance. President Volodymyr Zelensky became an international hero. NATO countries unified behind a truly punishing sanctions regime and significant military support.</description></item><item><title>Fareed Zakaria Has a Better Way to Handle Russia — and China | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360167/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360167/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Russia’s utterly unprovoked, unjustifiable, immoral invasion of Ukraine would seem to mark the end of an era,” writes Fareed Zakaria, “one that began with the fall of the Berlin Wall in 1989.”
Many of us, myself included, grew up in that era. We came of age in a unipolar world, dominated by a single country whose military, economic, even cultural, hegemony remained largely uncontested. That world was by no means free of violence.</description></item><item><title>Can the West Stop Russia by Strangling its Economy? | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360168/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360168/</guid><description>Podcast Description There’s the Russia-Ukraine war that’s easy to follow in the news right now. We can watch Russian bombs falling on Ukraine, see Russian tanks smoking on the side of the road, hear from Ukrainian resistance fighters livestreaming their desperate defense.
But there’s another theater to this war that’s harder to see, but may well decide the outcome: the economic war that West is waging on Russia. Europe and the United States initially responded with a limited set of sanctions but then expanded them into a counterattack capable of crushing the Russian economy.</description></item><item><title>A Philosophy of Games That Is Really a Philosophy of Life | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360169/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360169/</guid><description>Podcast Description When we play Monopoly or basketball, we know we are playing a game. The stakes are low. The rules are silly. The point system is arbitrary. But what if life is full of games — ones with much higher stakes — that we don’t even realize we’re playing?
According to the philosopher C. Thi Nguyen, games and gamified systems are everywhere in modern life. Social media applies the lure of a points-based scoring system to the complex act of communication.</description></item><item><title>Best Of: Stop. Breathe. We Can’t Keep Working Like This. | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360170/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360170/</guid><description>Podcast Description We were promised, with the internet, a productivity revolution. We were told that we’d get more done, in less time, with less stress. Instead, we got always-on communication, the dissolution of the boundaries between work and home, the feeling of constantly being behind, lackluster productivity numbers, and, to be fair, reaction GIFs. What went wrong?
Cal Newport is a computer scientist at Georgetown and the author of books trying to figure that out.</description></item><item><title>A Critique of Government That Liberals Need to Hear | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360171/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360171/</guid><description>Podcast Description Government is a bureaucratic, slow-moving institution. It’s too easily captured by special interests. It’s often incapable of acting at the speed and scale our problems demand. And when it does act, it can make things worse. Look no further than the Food and Drug Administration’s slowness to approve rapid coronavirus tests or major cities’ inability to build new housing and public transit or Congress’s failure to pass basic voting rights legislation.</description></item><item><title>Relationships Are Hard. This Unusual Parenting Theory Can Help. | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360172/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360172/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is one of those episodes I feel I need to sell. Because on one level, it’s about an unusual theory of parenting known by the acronym RIE — for the nonprofit group Resources for Infant Educarers, which promotes its principles — that I’ve become interested in. But this isn’t a parenting podcast, and I know many of you don’t have young kids. The reason I’m doing this episode is that I think there’s something bigger here.</description></item><item><title>It's Not Your Fault You Can't Pay Attention. Here's Why. | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360173/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360173/</guid><description>Podcast Description “The sensation of being alive in the early 21st century consisted of the sense that our ability to pay attention — to focus — was cracking and breaking,” writes Johann Hari in his new book, “Stolen Focus.” Later he says, “It felt like our civilization had been covered with itching powder and we spent our time twitching and twerking our minds, unable to simply give attention to things that matter.</description></item><item><title>What the Heck Is Going on With the U.S. Economy? | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360174/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360174/</guid><description>Podcast Description Should we be celebrating a Biden boom? Lamenting inflation and its consequences? Both?
We know how to talk about booms, like the ’90s. We know how to talk about busts, like after the financial crisis. We know how to talk about stagnation. What we don’t know how to talk about is contradictory extremes coexisting together. But that’s the economy we have right now. And a lot rides on figuring out how to balance those extremes.</description></item><item><title>Let’s Talk About How Truly Bizarre Our Supreme Court Is | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360175/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360175/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Getting race wrong early has led courts to get everything else wrong since,” writes Jamal Greene. But he probably doesn’t mean what you think he means.
Greene is a professor at Columbia Law School, and his book “How Rights Went Wrong” is filled with examples of just how bizarre American Supreme Court outcomes have become. An information processing company claims the right to sell its patients’ data to drug companies — it wins.</description></item><item><title>Democrats Chase Shiny Objects. Here's How to Build Real Power. | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360176/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360176/</guid><description>Podcast Description There’s good reason to worry about the future of democracy, and little reason to believe Democrats have a viable plan for protecting it. They built their strategy around passing a major suite of voting reforms and protections through Congress, and a few weeks back, their whole agenda collapsed in the face of the filibuster. So what now? Is there a Plan B for protecting democracy?
Yes. But it begins with realizing that there is no national solution in a country that administers elections at the state and local levels.</description></item><item><title>Learning to Listen to the Voices Only You Hear | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360177/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360177/</guid><description>Podcast Description The world has gotten louder, even when we’re alone. A day spent in isolation can still mean a day buffeted by the voices on social media and the news, on podcasts, in emails and text messages. Objects have also gotten louder: through the advertisements that follow us around the web, the endless scroll of merchandise available on internet shopping sites and in the plentiful aisles of superstores. What happens when you really start listening to all these voices?</description></item><item><title>The View From the White House | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360178/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360178/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s been a year since Joe Biden was sworn in as the 46th president of the United States. And what a roller coaster of a year it’s been.
The Biden administration blew past its Covid vaccination goal of 100 million shots in 100 days, only to run into the realities of vaccine skepticism, the Delta wave and now Omicron. The president oversaw an unprecedented economic recovery — including the sharpest one-year drop in unemployment in American history — but now faces the highest inflation in decades, supply chain crises and souring approval ratings.</description></item><item><title>The Pandemic Lessons We Clearly Haven’t Learned | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360179/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360179/</guid><description>Podcast Description I remember thinking, as Covid ravaged the country in December 2020, that at least the holidays the next year would be better. There would be more vaccines, more treatments, more immunity. Instead, we got Omicron and a confusing new phase of the pandemic. What do you do with a variant that is both monstrously more infectious and somewhat milder? What do you say about another year when we didn’t have enough tests, enough ventilation or the best guidance on masks?</description></item><item><title>Chris Hayes on How Biden Can Have a Better 2022 | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360180/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nothing like a newborn and paternity leave to leave you feeling a bit out of the loop. So for my first podcast back since October, I wanted to wander through the thickets of where we are politically and how we got here.
Because where we are is strange: the Omicron wave and the breakdown of the liberal Covid consensus that preceded it; a hot economy with low unemployment, rising wages and high inflation; a Build Back Better bill for which the eventual compromise seems obvious even as the legislation is stalled; the anniversary of Jan.</description></item><item><title>Best Of: This Conversation Will Change How You Think About Thinking | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360181/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360181/</guid><description>Podcast Description For decades, our society’s dominant metaphor for the mind has been a computer. A machine that operates the exact same way whether it’s in a dark room or next to a sunny window, whether it’s been working for 30 seconds or three hours, whether it’s near other computers or completely alone.
But that’s wrong. Annie Murphy Paul’s “The Extended Mind” argues, convincingly, that the human mind is contextual. It works differently in different environments, with different tools, amid different bodily states, among other minds.</description></item><item><title>Best Of: Why Sci-Fi Legend Ted Chiang Fears Capitalism, Not A.I. | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360182/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360182/</guid><description>Podcast Description For years, I’ve kept a list of dream guests for this show. And as long as that list has existed, Ted Chiang has been atop it.
Chiang is a science fiction writer. But that undersells him. He has released two short story collections over 20 years — 2002’s “Stories of Your Life and Others” and 2019’s “Exhalation.” Those stories have won more awards than I can list, and one of them was turned into the film “Arrival.</description></item><item><title>Best Of: Noam Chomsky's Theory of the Good Life | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360183/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360183/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do you introduce Noam Chomsky? Perhaps you start here: In 1979, The New York Times called him “arguably the most important intellectual alive today.” More than 40 years later, Chomsky, at 92, is still putting his dent in the world — writing books, giving interviews, changing minds.
There are different sides to Chomsky. He’s a world-renowned linguist who revolutionized his field. He’s a political theorist who’s been a sharp critic of American foreign policy for decades.</description></item><item><title>Timeless Wisdom for Leading a Life of Love, Friendship and Learning | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360184/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360184/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Today, we are supercompetent when it comes to efficiency, utility, speed, convenience, and getting ahead in the world; but we are at a loss concerning what it’s all for,” Leon Kass writes in his 2017 book “Leading a Worthy Life.” “This lack of cultural and moral confidence about what makes a life worth living is perhaps the deepest curse of living in our interesting time.”
Kass spent more than 30 years as an award-winning teacher at the University of Chicago, where he gained a reputation among students for his commitment to the big questions of human existence and the study of classic texts.</description></item><item><title>Families Are Drowning in Care Costs. Here’s How To Change That. | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360185/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360185/</guid><description>Podcast Description Every day in the United States, more than 10,000 babies are born and 10,000 people turn 65. But America doesn’t have anything close to a comprehensive family policy. That means no guaranteed paid family leave, no universal child care or preschool and a patchwork system of elder and disability care that leaves millions without support.
American families are drowning as a result. In some states, the average cost of a full-time child-care program is nearing $20,000 a year; the median yearly cost of a private room in a nursing home is over $100,000 — a figure that well exceeds the median household income in the United States.</description></item><item><title>Predicting the Future Is Possible. ‘Superforecasters’ Know How. | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360186/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360186/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can we predict the future more accurately?
It’s a question we humans have grappled with since the dawn of civilization — one that has massive implications for how we run our organizations, how we make policy decisions, and how we live our everyday lives.
It’s also the question that Philip Tetlock, a psychologist at the University of Pennsylvania and a co-author of “Superforecasting: The Art and Science of Prediction,” has dedicated his career to answering.</description></item><item><title>Best Of: How Blue Cities Became So Outrageously Unaffordable | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360187/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360187/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joe Biden’s economic agenda is centered on a basic premise: The United States needs to build. To build roads and bridges. To build child care facilities and car-charging stations. To build public transit and affordable housing. And in doing so, to build a better future for everyone.
But there’s a twist of irony in that vision. Because right now, even in places where Democrats hold control over government, they are consistently failing to build cheaply, quickly and equitably.</description></item><item><title>Why Is Murder Spiking? And Can Cities Address It Without Police? | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360188/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360188/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2020 the United States experienced a nearly 30 percent rise in homicides from 2019. That’s the single biggest one-year increase since we started keeping national records in 1960. And violence has continued to rise well into 2021.
To deny or downplay the seriousness of this spike is neither morally justified nor politically wise. Violence takes lives, traumatizes children, instills fear, destroys community life and entrenches racial and economic inequality.</description></item><item><title>The Case Against Loving Your Job | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360189/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360189/</guid><description>Podcast Description The compulsion to be happy at work “is always a demand for emotional work from the worker,” writes Sarah Jaffe. “Work, after all, has no feelings. Capitalism cannot love. This new work ethic, in which work is expected to give us something like self-actualization, cannot help but fail.”
Jaffe is a Type Media Center reporting fellow, a co-host of the podcast “Belabored” and the author of “Work Won’t Love You Back: How Devotion to Our Jobs Keeps Us Exploited, Exhausted and Alone.</description></item><item><title>Are We Witnessing the Mainstreaming of White Power in America? | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360190/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360190/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over the course of Donald Trump’s presidency, the far-right fringe became a surprisingly visible and influential force in American politics. Eruptions of extremist violence — including the Unite the Right rally in Charlottesville, Va., in 2017 and the Jan. 6 Capitol insurrection — have made militant groups like the Proud Boys and conspiracy theories like QAnon into household names. On his popular cable news show, Tucker Carlson recently name-checked the “great replacement” conspiracy theory.</description></item><item><title>It's Time for the Media to Choose: Neutrality or Democracy? | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360191/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360191/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Making it harder to vote, and harder to understand what the party is really about — these are two parts of the same project” for the Republican Party, Jay Rosen writes. “The conflict with honest journalism is structural. To be its dwindling self, the G.O.P. has to also be at war with the press, unless of course the press folds under pressure.”
Rosen is a professor of journalism at N.</description></item><item><title>Two Acclaimed Writers on the Art of Revising Your Life | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360192/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360192/</guid><description>Podcast Description Many of the most contentious debates right now center on whether we, as individuals — and as a country — are willing to revise. To revise our understanding of history. To revise the kind of language we use. To revise the nature of our personal, and national, identities. To revise how we act in our everyday relationships.
Revision like this is often necessary, but that doesn’t mean it’s easy.</description></item><item><title>Best Of: How Octopuses Upend What We Know About Ourselves | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360193/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Nov 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360193/</guid><description>Podcast Description I’ve been on an octopus kick for a little while now. In that, I don’t seem to be alone. Octopuses (it’s incorrect to say “octopi,” to my despair) are having a moment: There are award-winning books, documentaries and even science fiction about them. I suspect it’s the same hunger that leaves many of us yearning to know aliens: How do radically different minds work? What is it like to be a truly different being living in a similar world?</description></item><item><title>The Life-Altering Differences Between White and Black Debt | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360194/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360194/</guid><description>Podcast Description Public policy in the United States often overlooks wealth. We tend to design, debate and measure our economic policies with regard to income alone, which blinds us to the ways prosperity and precarity tangibly function in people’s lives. And that blind spot can ultimately prevent us from addressing social inequality at its roots.
Take the debate over student loan cancellation. Cancellation is often framed as an economically regressive policy — an elite giveaway of sorts — with the majority of benefits going to individuals toward the top end of the income distribution.</description></item><item><title>Why This Conservative Wants a More Radical Republican Party | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360195/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360195/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Progressives understand that culture war means discrediting their opponents and weakening or destroying their institutions. Conservatives should approach the culture war with a similar realism,” Sohrab Ahmari writes. “To recognize that enmity is real is its own kind of moral duty.”
Five years ago, Ahmari was a self-described “secular mainstream conservative” working for The Wall Street Journal. Now a contributing editor at The American Conservative and the recently departed op-ed editor at The New York Post, Ahmari has become a fierce critic of the Republican Party as it existed before the rise of Donald Trump, a champion of right-wing populist leaders like Hungary’s Viktor Orban and a devout Catholic who believes social conservatives need to take a far more aggressive posture in the culture war.</description></item><item><title>Long Covid and the Blind Spots of American Medicine | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360196/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360196/</guid><description>Podcast Description One of the most frightening, least understood aspects of the coronavirus pandemic is what’s come to be known as “long Covid.” Stories abound of young, healthy adults who experienced mild or asymptomatic coronavirus infections and recovered fairly quickly, only to experience an onset of debilitating symptoms weeks or even months later. One major study of almost two million Covid patients in the United States found that nearly a quarter sought medical treatment for new conditions one month or more after their initial infection.</description></item><item><title>What Keeping American Democracy Alive Looks Like | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360197/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360197/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the wake of the “Stop the Steal” campaign, the Jan. 6 attack on the Capitol and the wave of voter suppression bills making their way through Republican legislatures across the country, the struggle for American democracy feels, for many, visceral and even existential. But for Martha S. Jones, a legal and cultural historian at Johns Hopkins University, the moment we find ourselves in is anything but an aberration.</description></item><item><title>The Story of America's Founding You Weren’t Taught in School | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360198/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360198/</guid><description>Podcast Description There are few periods of U.S. history that are as vigorously debated, as emotionally and civically charged as the American Revolution. And for good reason: How Americans interpret that period — its heroes, its villains, its legacy — shapes how we understand our social foundations, our national identity, our shared political project.
Woody Holton is a historian at the University of South Carolina, a leading scholar of America’s founding and the author of numerous books on the period, including, most recently, “Liberty Is Sweet: The Hidden History of the American Revolution.</description></item><item><title>A Crypto Optimist and a Crypto Skeptic Walk Into a Podcast Studio | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360199/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360199/</guid><description>Podcast Description I’ve been wanting to explore the world crypto and blockchain technologies could build on the show for a while. In certain ways, I’m an optimist: I think these technologies matter, and many of them will work. In other ways, I’m a skeptic: I’m unconvinced that their wide adoption will lead to the glittering, decentralized digital world that many crypto proponents imagine.
So this is a crypto conversation that goes way beyond Bitcoin.</description></item><item><title>Lessons on Living Well, From Nick Offerman | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360200/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360200/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nick Offerman is best known for his role as Ron Swanson, the mustachioed, libertarian outdoorsman who led the Pawnee, Ind., Parks and Recreation Department on the beloved show “Parks and Recreation.” But there’s more to Offerman than Swanson: His new book, “Where the Deer and the Antelope Play,” was inspired in part by his conversation with the agrarian poet-philosopher Wendell Berry, and a hiking trip he took with the writer George Saunders and the musician Jeff Tweedy (both of whom you may remember from past episodes of this show).</description></item><item><title>Let's Talk About the Anxiety Freedom Can Cause | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360201/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360201/</guid><description>Podcast Description Maggie Nelson is a poet, critic and cultural theorist whose work includes the award-winning 2016 book “The Argonauts.” Her newest work, “On Freedom,” pierces right into the heart of America’s founding idea: What if there’s no such thing as freedom, at least not freedom as a state of enduring liberation?
And more than that: What if we don’t want to be free? Perhaps that’s the great lie in the American dream: We’re taught to want freedom, but many of us recoil from its touch.</description></item><item><title>How to Do the Most Good | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360202/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360202/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do we actually know how much good our charitable donations do?
This is the question that jump-started Holden Karnofsky’s current career. He was working at a hedge fund and wanted to figure out how to give his money away with the certainty that it would save as many lives as possible. But he couldn’t find a service that would help him do that, so he and his co-worker Elie Hassenfeld decided to quit their jobs to build one.</description></item><item><title>Eric Adams Has a Message for the Democratic Party | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360203/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360203/</guid><description>Podcast Description In July, Eric Adams narrowly won the Democratic nomination for mayor of New York, making him the odds-on favorite to win in November. And he won the nomination by running directly against the verities of today’s progressives: asserting that the police are the answer, not the problem; that “defund the police” misjudged what communities of color actually want; that Democrats had lost touch with the multiracial working-class voters they claim to represent.</description></item><item><title>This Conversation With Richard Powers Is a Gift | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360204/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360204/</guid><description>Podcast Description There are certain conversations I fear trying to fit into a description. There’s just more to them than I’m going to be able to convey. This is one of them.
Richard Powers is the author of 13 novels, including the 2019 Pulitzer Prize-winning “The Overstory.” If you haven’t read it, you should. It’ll change you. It changed me. I haven’t walked through a forest the same way again. And I’m not alone in that.</description></item><item><title>Opinion Crossover: California Republicans, Facebook and Media Navelgazing | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360205/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360205/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we’re doing something a little different. Instead of a normal interview, we wanted to let you in on a special round table discussion I recently had with my fellow Opinion Audio hosts: Jane Coaston of “The Argument” and Kara Swisher of “Sway.” We discuss California’s recall election, the future of the Republican Party, the recent “Facebook Files” revelations, the case for and against breaking up Big Tech, why so many Americans distrust the media and much more.</description></item><item><title>We’re on the Precipice of a Post-Roe World | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360206/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360206/</guid><description>Podcast Description A few weeks ago, the Supreme Court let stand a Texas law creating a system of vigilante legal enforcement against anyone who participates in an abortion after the point of fetal cardiac activity. In effect, Texas’ law bans abortions after about six weeks, which is long before many women even know they’re pregnant. And soon the court will hear arguments on a Mississippi abortion ban that will give the justices the chance to overturn Roe v.</description></item><item><title>Economics Needs to Reckon With What It Doesn’t Know | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360207/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360207/</guid><description>Podcast Description “The world discovered that John Maynard Keynes was right when he declared during World War II that ‘anything we can actually do, we can afford,’” writes Adam Tooze. “Budget constraints don’t seem to exist; money is a mere technicality. The hard limits of financial sustainability, policed, we used to think, by ferocious bond markets, were blurred by the 2008 financial crisis. In 2020, they were erased.”
Tooze is an economic historian at Columbia University, co-hosts the podcast “Ones and Tooze,” writes the brilliant Chartbook blog and is the author of “Crashed,” the single best history of the 2008 financial crisis.</description></item><item><title>How Colson Whitehead Writes About Our ‘Big Wild Country’ | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360208/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360208/</guid><description>Podcast Description “If he got a thrill out of transforming these ill-gotten goods into legit merchandise, a zap-charge in his blood like he’d plugged into a socket, he was in control of it and not the other way around,” writes Colson Whitehead in his new novel, “Harlem Shuffle.” “Dizzying and powerful as it was. Everyone had secret corners and alleys that no one else saw — what mattered were your major streets and boulevards, the stuff that showed up on other people’s maps of you.</description></item><item><title>Tyler Cowen on the Great Stagnation’s End | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360209/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360209/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tyler Cowen is an economist at George Mason University, the co-founder of the blog Marginal Revolution, and host of the podcast “Conversations With Tyler.” But more than that, he’s a genuine polymath who reads about everything, goes everywhere and talks to everyone. I’ve known him for years, and while I disagree with him on quite a bit, there are few people I learn more from in a single conversation.</description></item><item><title>Can We Change Our Sexual Desires? Should We? | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360210/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360210/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Feminists have long dreamed of sexual freedom,” writes Amia Srinivasan. “What they refuse to accept is its simulacrum: sex that is said to be free, not because it is equal, but because it is ubiquitous.”
Srinivasan is an Oxford philosopher who, in 2018, wrote the viral essay “Does Anyone Have the Right to Sex?” Her piece was inspired by Elliot Rodger’s murderous rampage and the misogynist manifesto he published to justify it.</description></item><item><title>This Isn’t Your Grandpa’s Joe Biden | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360211/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360211/</guid><description>Podcast Description President Biden’s economic policy isn’t what you would have expected from his long career. That’s true in the legislation he’s backing, which is bigger and bolder than anything we’ve seen from him before, but it’s even truer in the appointments he’s making and the theories he’s embracing. On everything from antitrust to inflation to employment to power, Biden is reflecting a new strain of progressive economics thoughts — one that wants to direct markets, not just correct them.</description></item><item><title>Ask Ezra Anything: Degrowth, Third Parties, Reading and More | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360212/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360212/</guid><description>Podcast Description We asked for your questions, and you answered. Hundreds and hundreds of fantastic questions poured in, and our producer Annie Galvin joined me to ask some of the best of them. Does the infrastructure bill mean there’s more hope for bipartisanship than we thought? What’s my view on the degrowth movement? What do I think my book, “Why We’re Polarized,” got right, and what did it get wrong? Will plant- and cell-based meats ever be cheaper than eating animals, given the subsidies the meat industry gets?</description></item><item><title>The Foreign Policy Conversation Washington Doesn’t Want to Have | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360213/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360213/</guid><description>Podcast Description Everything about the Afghanistan withdrawal is tragic. But that tragedy is the result not of the withdrawal, but the occupation, and America’s profound misjudgment of its own power and limits.
This is the foreign policy conversation much of Washington is trying desperately to avoid. The answer for the horrors of war is always more war. The bomb attack at the Kabul airport on Thursday reflects this dynamic perfectly: It’s being wielded as a cudgel by those who support a permanent American occupation of Afghanistan, guaranteeing more U.</description></item><item><title>This Conversation Will Change How You Think About Trauma | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360214/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360214/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Trauma is much more than a story about something that happened long ago,” writes Dr. Bessel van der Kolk. “The emotions and physical sensations that were imprinted during the trauma are experienced not as memories but as disruptive physical reactions in the present.”
Van der Kolk, a psychiatrist by training, has been a pioneer in trauma research for decades now and leads the Trauma Research Foundation. His 2014 book “The Body Keeps the Score,” quickly became a touchstone on the topic.</description></item><item><title>The Argument: Should We Say "Hi" to Aliens? | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360215/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360215/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;rsquo;re taking this week off from publishing new episodes, so today we&amp;rsquo;re bringing you an episode from &amp;ldquo;The Argument&amp;rdquo; about one of my favorite topics: aliens. We&amp;rsquo;ll be back with new episodes of &amp;ldquo;The Ezra Klein Show&amp;rdquo; on Tuesday.
With the U.S. government puzzling over U.F.O.s, and potentially habitable exoplanets in our telescopes, earthlings are closer than ever to finding other intelligent life in the universe. So the existential question is: Should we try to communicate with whatever we think might be out there?</description></item><item><title>Best of: George Saunders on Kindness in a Cruel World | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360216/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360216/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re taking a week off from releasing new episodes, so today I wanted to re-up one of my favorite episodes of the show, a conversation with fiction writer George Saunders that covers much more than just his writing.
Saunders is one of America’s greatest living writers. He’s the author of dozens of critically acclaimed short stories, including his 2013 collection, “Tenth of December”; his debut novel, “Lincoln in the Bardo,” won the 2017 Booker Prize; and his nonfiction work has empathy and insight that leave pieces from more than a decade ago ringing in my head today.</description></item><item><title>How Identity Politics Took Over the Republican Party | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360217/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360217/</guid><description>Podcast Description One problem with the conversation around political polarization is that it can imply that polarization is a static, singular thing. That our divisions are fixed and unchanging. But that’s not how it is at all. The dimensions of conflict change, and they change quickly. In the Obama era, Republicans mobilized against government spending and deficits but didn’t think much about election administration. Now, a trillion-dollar infrastructure package has passed the Senate with bipartisan support, but the divisions over democracy and voting access are deep.</description></item><item><title>We’re Living in the World the War on Terror Built | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360218/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360218/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Sept, 11 attacks might have taken place almost 20 years ago, but we’re still living in the America that the war on terror built. Its legacy is not just mass surveillance and drone strikes but birtherism, nativism and Donald Trump. And much of it has been — and continues to be — a bipartisan effort.
That’s the argument of Spencer Ackerman’s new book, “Reign of Terror.” Ackerman is the author of the newsletter Forever Wars, a contributing editor at The Daily Beast, and a member of the Pulitzer Prize-winning team at The Guardian that reported on Edward Snowden’s surveillance revelations.</description></item><item><title>The Good and Bad News About the Delta Variant | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360219/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360219/</guid><description>Podcast Description “The war has changed.” That’s what the leaked C.D.C. document says about the way the Delta variant has upended our coronavirus policies. Delta is astonishingly contagious. It can generate 1,000 times the viral load of the original coronavirus strain, and it spreads with the ease of chickenpox. The vaccinated can no longer assume immunity. The unvaccinated are at more risk than ever. Masks are back. New York City is essentially imposing a vaccine mandate.</description></item><item><title>41 Questions For The Technologies We Use, and That Use Us | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360220/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360220/</guid><description>Podcast Description We all know by now that Zoom causes fatigue, social media spreads misinformation and Google Maps is wiping out our sense of direction. We also know, of course, that Zoom allows us to cooperate across continents, that social media connects us to our families and Google Maps keeps us from being lost. A lot of technological criticism today is about weighing whether a technology is good or bad, or judging its various uses.</description></item><item><title>Nikole Hannah-Jones and Ta-Nehisi Coates on the Fight Over U.S. History | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360221/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360221/</guid><description>Podcast Description You’ve heard plenty by now about the fights over teaching critical race theory and the 1619 Project. But behind those skirmishes is something deeper: A fight over the story we tell about America. Why that fight has so gripped our national discourse is the question of this podcast: What changes when a country’s sense of its own history changes? What changes when who gets to tell that story changes?</description></item><item><title>Ross Douthat Has Been ‘Radicalized a Little Bit, Too’ | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360222/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360222/</guid><description>Podcast Description Am I too panicked about the future of American democracy?
My colleague Ross Douthat thinks so. He points to research suggesting that voter ID laws and absentee voting have modest effects on elections and the reality that Republican state officials already have tremendous power to alter election outcomes — powers they did not use in the aftermath of 2020 and show few signs of preparing to use now.</description></item><item><title>How Blue Cities Became So Outrageously Unaffordable | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360223/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360223/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joe Biden’s economic agenda is centered on a basic premise: The United States needs to build. To build roads and bridges. To build child care facilities and car-charging stations. To build public transit and affordable housing. And in doing so, to build a better future for everyone.
But there’s a twist of irony in that vision. Because right now, even in places where Democrats hold control over government, they are consistently failing to build cheaply, quickly and equitably.</description></item><item><title>Our Workplaces Think We’re Computers. We’re Not. | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360224/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360224/</guid><description>Podcast Description For decades, our society’s dominant metaphor for the mind has been a computer. A machine that operates the exact same way whether it’s in a dark room or next to a sunny window, whether it’s been working for 30 seconds or three hours, whether it’s near other computers or completely alone.
But that’s wrong. Annie Murphy Paul’s “The Extended Mind” argues, convincingly, that the human mind is contextual. It works differently in different environments, with different tools, amid different bodily states, among other minds.</description></item><item><title>Ibram X. Kendi on What Conservatives—and Liberals—Get Wrong About Antiracism | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360225/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360225/</guid><description>Podcast Description Transcript</description></item><item><title>How Octopuses Upend What We Know About Ourselves | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360226/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360226/</guid><description>Podcast Description I’ve spent the past few months on an octopus kick. In that, I don’t seem to be alone. Octopuses (it’s incorrect to say “octopi,” to my despair) are having a moment: There are award-winning books, documentaries and even science fiction about them. I suspect it’s the same hunger that leaves many of us yearning to know aliens: How do radically different minds work? What is it like to be a truly different being living in a similar world?</description></item><item><title>Critical Race Theory, Comic Books and the Power of Public Schools | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360227/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360227/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eve Ewing’s work as a sociologist, poet, visual artist, podcaster and comic book writer manages to do two things that are often in tension: it gives us a clear picture of how race, power and education work in America right now, and envisions a world that could work radically differently.
“Dreaming and imagination and possibility are very much key words for the kind of work I want to do,” Ewing says.</description></item><item><title>Best of: What ‘Drained-Pool’ Politics Costs America | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360228/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360228/</guid><description>Podcast Description In February, I spoke with Heather McGhee. I’ve been thinking about the conversation ever since.
“The American landscape was once graced with resplendent public swimming pools, some big enough to hold thousands of swimmers at a time,” writes McGhee in her recent book, “The Sum of Us: What Racism Costs Everyone and How We Can Prosper Together.” These pools were the pride of their communities, monuments to what public investment could do.</description></item><item><title>Wilco’s Jeff Tweedy Wants You to Be Bad at Something. It’s for Your Own Good. | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360229/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360229/</guid><description>Podcast Description Recently, I picked up Jeff Tweedy’s “How to Write One Song.” It was a bit of a lark. Tweedy is the frontman for Wilco, one of my favorite bands, but I’m not a songwriter, and I don’t plan to become one. But, unexpectedly, I loved the book. It’s the most generous and approachable guide to the creative process I’ve read.
It’s also relentlessly practical: To Tweedy, this really is a process, replete with practices that you can enjoy doing daily.</description></item><item><title>Why Do We Work So Damn Much? | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360230/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360230/</guid><description>Podcast Description Historically speaking, we live in an age of extraordinary abundance. We have long since passed the income thresholds when past economists believed our needs would be more than met and we’d be working 15-hour weeks, puzzling over how to spend our free time. And yet, few of us feel able to exult in leisure, and even many of today’s rich toil as if the truest reward for work is more work.</description></item><item><title>Republicans Are Setting Off a ‘Doom Loop’ for Democracy | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360231/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360231/</guid><description>Podcast Description The insurrection at the Capitol on Jan. 6 failed. Donald Trump is not the president. But at the state level, the Republican war on elections is posting startling wins. They are trying to do what Trump failed to do: neuter elections as a check on Republican power.
A new report by three voting rights groups found that 24 laws have been passed in 14 states this year that will allow state legislatures to “politicize, criminalize and interfere in election administration.</description></item><item><title>Sarah Schulman’s Radical Approach to Conflict, Communication and Change | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360232/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360232/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sarah Schulman’s work — as a nonfiction writer, novelist, activist, playwright and filmmaker — confronts the very thing most people try to avoid: conflict. Schulman, far from running from it, believes we need more of it.
This was true in Schulman’s 2016 book, “Conflict Is Not Abuse,” which argues that people often mislabel conflict as abuse without recognizing the power that they have to potentially abuse others. Viewing oneself as a victim can be one way to earn compassion.</description></item><item><title>Welcome to the ‘Take This Job and Shove It’ Economy | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360233/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360233/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a strange moment in the economy. Wages are up, but so is inflation. Jobs are growing, but maybe not fast enough. Quit rates are at a 21st-century high. It isn’t clear what’s a trend, what’s a blip, what’s a transition and what’s now normal. And all this as the virus continues to stalk us and we process the trauma of the last 18 months.
“We all will have various times in our life where we’ll stop and say, ‘Whoa — am I going in the right direction?</description></item><item><title>The Freeing of the American Mind | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360234/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360234/</guid><description>Podcast Description Free minds. Freedom fries. Free speech. The Freedom Caucus. Freedom from. Freedom to. What do Americans really mean when they talk about freedom?
Louis Menand’s “The Free World” is a 700-plus-page intellectual history of the Cold War period that traces the opening of the American mind to new ideas in art, literature, politics, music, foreign policy, criticism, higher education and campus activism. John Cage was making silent music, Jackson Pollock was throwing paint on canvases, Pauline Kael was giving us permission to actually enjoy movies.</description></item><item><title>Sam Altman on the A.I. Revolution, Trillionaires and the Future of Political Power | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360235/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360235/</guid><description>Podcast Description “The technological progress we make in the next 100 years will be far larger than all we’ve made since we first controlled fire and invented the wheel,” writes Sam Altman in his essay “Moore’s Law for Everything.” “This revolution will generate enough wealth for everyone to have what they need, if we as a society manage it responsibly.”
Altman is the C.E.O. of OpenAI, one of the biggest, most important players in the artificial intelligence space.</description></item><item><title>Employers Are Begging for Workers. Maybe That’s a Good Thing. | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360236/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360236/</guid><description>Podcast Description There has been a bit of panic lately over employers who say not enough people want to apply for open jobs. Are we facing a labor shortage? Have stimulus checks and expanded unemployment insurance payments created an economy full of people who don’t want to work — and who are holding back the economic recovery? That’s one theory, anyway. But it’s leading to real policy change: 25 Republican governors have cut off expanded unemployment benefits early.</description></item><item><title>Is A.I. the Problem? Or Are We? | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360237/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360237/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you talk to many of the people working on the cutting edge of artificial intelligence research, you’ll hear that we are on the cusp of a technology that will be far more transformative than simply computers and the internet, one that could bring about a new industrial revolution and usher in a utopia — or perhaps pose the greatest threat in our species’s history.
Others, of course, will tell you those folks are nuts.</description></item><item><title>Obama Explains How America Went From ‘Yes We Can’ to ‘MAGA’ | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360238/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360238/</guid><description>Podcast Description “My entire politics is premised on the fact that we are these tiny organisms on this little speck floating in the middle of space,” Barack Obama told me, sitting in his office in Washington, D.C.
To be fair, I was the one who had introduced the cosmic scale, asking how proof of alien life would change his politics. But Obama, in a philosophical mood, used the question to trace his view of humanity.</description></item><item><title>Sway: How Online Sleuths Pantsed Putin | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360239/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360239/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, while I&amp;rsquo;m on vacation, we&amp;rsquo;re sharing an episode from Sway, a fellow New York Times Opinion podcast. Host Kara Swisher talks to Eliot Higgins, CEO of the open source investigative operation Bellingcat. Kara presses Higgins about the perils of taking on Vladimir Putin and how Bellingcat’s work, which Kara calls “gumshoe journalism,” differs from online vigilantism.
We&amp;rsquo;ll be back to our regular programming on Tuesday.
Thoughts? Guest suggestions?</description></item><item><title>The Argument: Should We Cancel Student Loan Debt? | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360240/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360240/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, while I&amp;rsquo;m on vacation, we&amp;rsquo;ll be sharing work from two other New York Times Opinion podcasts. First up, an episode from our friends at The Argument about how to cancel student-loan debt. Host Jane Coaston is joined by activist Astra Taylor and economist Sandy Baum, who agree that addressing the crisis requires dramatic measures but disagree on how to get there.
Thoughts? Guest suggestions? Email us at ezrakleinshow@nytimes.</description></item><item><title>Violent Crime Is Spiking. Do Liberals Have an Answer? | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360241/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360241/</guid><description>Podcast Description Early estimates find that in 2020, homicides in the United States increased somewhere between 25 percent and nearly 40 percent, the largest spike since 1960, when formal crime statistics began to be collected. And early estimates indicate that the increase has carried over to 2021.
Violent crime is a crisis on two levels. The first, and most direct, is the toll it takes on people and communities. The lost lives, the grieving families, the traumatized children, the families and businesses that flee, leaving inequality and joblessness for those who remain.</description></item><item><title>The Spectacle of the G.O.P.'s Shrinking Tent | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360242/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360242/</guid><description>Podcast Description On May 12, House Republicans voted to remove Representative Liz Cheney, the third-ranking Republican in the House, from her leadership post. Her transgression? Vocally rebuking the claim that the 2020 election was stolen from Donald Trump.
But Cheney’s ouster is just the latest plot development in a story about the contemporary G.O.P. that goes back farther than Nov. 3, 2020, and even Nov. 8, 2016. Over the past decade, the party has decimated its former leadership class.</description></item><item><title>Status Games, Polyamory and the Merits of Meritocracy | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360243/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360243/</guid><description>Podcast Description Agnes Callard is an ethical philosopher who dissects, in dazzlingly precise detail, familiar human experiences that we think we understand. Whether her topic is expressing anger, fighting with others, jockeying for status, giving advice, or navigating jealousy, Callard provokes us to rethink the emotions and habits that govern how we live. She also happens to be one of my favorite columnists.
In this conversation, I wanted to hear what Callard had to say about a tangle of topics we’ve explored before on the show: how we measure and trade status, and how that feeds into the amorphous thing we call “the meritocracy.</description></item><item><title>Michael Lewis Is Asking the Right Question | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360244/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360244/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michael Lewis’s new book, “The Premonition,” is about one of the most important questions of this moment: Why, despite having the most money, the brightest minds and the some of the most robust public health infrastructure in the world, did the United States fail so miserably at handling the Covid-19 pandemic? And what could we have done differently?
The villain of Lewis’s story is not Donald Trump; it’s the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.</description></item><item><title>Elizabeth Warren on What We Get Wrong About Inequality | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360245/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360245/</guid><description>Podcast Description One lesson of covering policy over the past 20 years is that whatever Elizabeth Warren is thinking about now is what Washington is going to be talking about next.
So when I read Senator Warren’s new book, “Persist,” I read it with an eye toward that question: Where is Warren trying to drive the policy debate next? And two answers emerged. First, toward a truly pro-family progressivism, one that puts children’s well-being and care at the center of the agenda.</description></item><item><title>How to Have Better Conversations About Hard Things | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360246/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360246/</guid><description>Podcast Description Anna Sale is one of my favorite interviewers. As the host of WNYC Studios’ “Death, Sex and Money,” she has an uncanny ability to get her guests to open up about the most personal, tragic, beautiful and embarrassing parts of their lives, whether it’s childhood trauma, the death of a partner or losing control of one’s limbs.
The kinds of conversations Sale has on her show are hard to have in real life.</description></item><item><title>How Chuck Schumer Plans to Win Over Trump Voters | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360247/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360247/</guid><description>Podcast Description In his 100 days address this week, Joe Biden outlined his plans for a big, bold legislative agenda to come. He previewed a two-pronged economic package: the $2.25 trillion American Jobs Plan and the $1.8 trillion American Families Plan. He spoke about the need to pass universal background checks for firearms, comprehensive immigration reform, and the George Floyd Justice in Policing Act.
The success of that agenda hinges on whether 50 Senate Democrats — ranging from Bernie Sanders to Joe Manchin — can come together and pass legislation.</description></item><item><title>Shame, Safety and Moving Beyond Cancel Culture | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360248/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360248/</guid><description>Podcast Description I’ve been thinking lately about how to move beyond the binary debate over cancel culture. And a good place to start is with the deeper question we’re all trying to ask: What is the kind of politics — the kind of society — we’re trying to achieve in our fights over acceptable speech?
To talk through this question, I wanted to bring on two guests, both of whom have been canceled — one by the left and one by the right — and have since dedicated parts of their work to grappling with both the good and the bad of the phenomenon.</description></item><item><title>Noam Chomsky’s Theory of the Good Life | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360249/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360249/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do you introduce Noam Chomsky? Perhaps you start here: In 1979, The New York Times called him “arguably the most important intellectual alive today.” More than 40 years later, Chomsky, at 92, is still putting his dent in the world — writing books, giving interviews, changing minds.
There are different sides to Chomsky. He’s a world-renowned linguist who revolutionized his field. He’s a political theorist who’s been a sharp critic of American foreign policy for decades.</description></item><item><title>That Anxiety You’re Feeling? It’s a Habit You Can Unlearn. | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360250/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360250/</guid><description>Podcast Description This has been a bad year for the anxious among us — myself very much included. The pandemic was objectively terrifying. And many of us were trapped inside, with nothing we could do about it, severed from social connection and routine, with plenty of time to fret.
But that almost gives anxiety, at least as I experience it, too much credit. This year, anyway, being anxious made sense. It so often doesn’t.</description></item><item><title>Why Adults Lose the ‘Beginner’s Mind’ | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360251/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360251/</guid><description>Podcast Description Here’s a sobering thought: The older we get, the harder it is for us to learn, to question, to reimagine. This isn’t just habit hardening into dogma. It’s encoded into the way our brains change as we age. And it’s worsened by an intellectual and economic culture that prizes efficiency and dismisses play.
Alison Gopnik is a professor of psychology and philosophy at the University of California, Berkeley, where she runs the Cognitive Development and Learning Lab; she’s also the author of over 100 papers and half a dozen books, including “The Gardener and the Carpenter” and “The Philosophical Baby.</description></item><item><title>Your Success Probably Didn’t Come From Merit Alone | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360252/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360252/</guid><description>Podcast Description Prepping for a conversation with Tressie McMillan Cottom is intimidating. McMillan Cottom is a sociologist at the University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill, a 2020 MacArthur fellow, co-host of the podcast “Hear to Slay,” and the author of the essay collection “Thick,” which was a National Book Award finalist. And she’s one of those people who can seemingly write on anything: The way for-profit colleges generate inequality, the cultural meaning of Dolly Parton, the way the U.</description></item><item><title>The Best Explanation of Biden's Thinking I’ve Heard | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360253/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360253/</guid><description>Podcast Description With the $2 trillion American Jobs Plan, the economic theory that is Bidenomics is taking shape. It’s big. It puts climate at the center of everything. It is more worried about political risks — losing the House, giving Donald Trump a path back to power — than some traditional economic risks, like wasting money and bumping up inflation. It prefers to err on the side of spending more and making sure people know they got a bridge or a job than doing less and having people question whether government is working for them.</description></item><item><title>Did the Boomers Ruin America? A Debate. | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360254/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360254/</guid><description>Podcast Description Donald Trump was the fourth member of the baby boomer generation to be elected president, after Barack Obama, George W. Bush and Bill Clinton. The Senate majority leader, Chuck Schumer, is a boomer. Chief Justice John Roberts is a boomer. The Federal Reserve chair, Jerome Powell, is a boomer. President Joe Biden and Speaker Nancy Pelosi and the Senate minority leader, Mitch McConnell, were born a few years too early to officially qualify as boomers, but they’re close.</description></item><item><title>Humanity’s Awesome, Terrifying Takeover of Evolution | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360255/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360255/</guid><description>Podcast Description For years now, I’ve had the same recurring worry: Am I focusing on the trivial? When future generations look back on this moment in history, will they remember the daily political fights — or will everything just look like a sideshow compared to humans being able to edit genetic code?
The technology I’m referring to, known as CRISPR, could cure genetic diseases like sickle-cell anemia and Huntington’s. It could let us regulate height, hair color, and vulnerabilities in our children.</description></item><item><title>The Author Behind ‘Arrival’ Doesn’t Fear AI. ‘Look at How We Treat Animals.’ | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360256/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360256/</guid><description>Podcast Description For years, I’ve kept a list of dream guests for this show. And as long as that list has existed, Ted Chiang has been atop it.
Chiang is a science fiction writer. But that undersells him. He has released two short story collections over 20 years — 2002’s “Stories of Your Life and Others” and 2019’s “Exhalation.” Those stories have won more awards than I can list, and one of them was turned into the film “Arrival.</description></item><item><title>A Top G.O.P. Pollster on Trump 2024, QAnon and What Republicans Really Want | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360257/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360257/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the aftermath of the Capitol attack, the polling firm Echelon Insights decided to ask voters a simple question: Do they think the goal of politics is more about “enacting good public policy” or “ensuring the country’s survival as we know it?”
Only 25 percent of Republicans said politics is about policy; nearly half said it’s about survival. That’s today’s Republican Party in a nutshell.
I’ve had some recent conversations with Republicans who are trying to reform their party, to push it back toward policy and, in some cases, reality.</description></item><item><title>An Unusually Optimistic Conversation With Bernie Sanders | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360258/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360258/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bernie Sanders didn’t win the 2020 election. But he may have won its aftermath.
If you look back at Joe Biden and Bernie Sanders’s careers, the $1.9 trillion stimulus package, the American Rescue Plan, looks a lot like the proposals Sanders has fought for forever, without much of the compromise or concerns that you used to see from Senator Joe Biden. That’s not to take anything away from Biden.</description></item><item><title>Andrew Cuomo and the Performance of Power | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360259/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360259/</guid><description>Podcast Description Six months ago, Andrew Cuomo was on top of the world. He was touted as the anti-Donald Trump — the calm, fact-driven coronavirus leader the country needed. Now, amid allegations of hiding the true number of Covid-19 deaths in New York nursing homes and of workplace sexual harassment and abusive behavior, most of the state’s major Democratic politicians are calling for Cuomo’s resignation.
Rebecca Traister is a writer at large at New York magazine and the author of “Good and Mad: The Revolutionary Power of Women’s Anger.</description></item><item><title>Mark Bittman Cooked Everything. Now He Wants to Change Everything. | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360260/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360260/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mark Bittman taught me to cook. I read his New York Times cooking column, “The Minimalist,” religiously. I bought “How to Cook Everything,” that red brick of a cookbook, and then, when I gave up meat, I bought its green companion, “How to Cook Everything Vegetarian.” He was like my cranky, no-B.S. food uncle.
But now Bittman wants to do more than teach me, or you, how to cook.</description></item><item><title>How America’s Covid-19 Nightmare Ends | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360261/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360261/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Jan. 28, I published a column that began like this: “I hope, in the end, that this article reads as alarmism. I hope that a year from now it’s a piece people point to as an overreaction.”
Today, that column, thankfully, does look like alarmism. Cases fell, and kept falling, even in places beset by new variants. The U.S. vaccination effort accelerated. And there’s going to be vastly more vaccine supply in the coming months.</description></item><item><title>What Does Toxic Stress Do to Children? | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360262/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360262/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Nadine Burke Harris’s pioneering work on how childhood trauma shapes adult outcomes led to her being named the first surgeon general of California. That was in 2019. And then, of course, the novel coronavirus hit. The job of California’s surgeon general in 2020 was not what it was in 2019. But in some ways, Burke Harris’s expertise was more necessary than ever.
This conversation is about the growing evidence that difficult experiences we face as children reverberate in our lives decades later.</description></item><item><title>Stop. Breathe. We Can’t Keep Working Like This. | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360263/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360263/</guid><description>Podcast Description We were promised, with the internet, a productivity revolution. We were told that we’d get more done, in less time, with less stress. Instead, we got always-on communication, the dissolution of the boundaries between work and home, the feeling of constantly being behind, lackluster productivity numbers, and, to be fair, reaction GIFs. What went wrong?
Cal Newport is a computer scientist at Georgetown and the author of books trying to figure that out.</description></item><item><title>What a More Responsible Republican Party Would Look Like | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360264/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360264/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you watched this past weekend’s Conservative Political Action Conference, you heard a lot of debunked election conspiracies, dire warnings about “cancel culture” and unwavering fealty to Donald Trump. What you didn’t hear was much in the way of policy ideas to raise wages, improve health care or support families. This is the modern G.O.P.: a post-policy party obsessed with symbolic fights and curiously uninterested in the actual work of governing.</description></item><item><title>How the Texas Crisis Could Become Everyone's Crisis | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360265/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360265/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last week, freezing temperatures overwhelmed the Texas power grid, setting off rolling blackouts that left millions without power during an intense winter storm. But this story is a lot bigger than Texas: Our world is built around a model of the climate from the 19th and 20th centuries. Global warming is going to crack that model apart, and with it, much of the physical and political infrastructure civilization relies on.</description></item><item><title>A Radical Proposal for True Democracy | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360266/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360266/</guid><description>Podcast Description One thing I want to do on this show is give space to truly radical ideas, to expand the boundaries of our political and moral imaginations. And Hélène Landemore, a political scientist at Yale, has one of those ideas. She calls it “open democracy,” and the premise is simple: What we call democracy is not very democratic.
The role of the people is confined to elections, to choosing the elites who will represent us.</description></item><item><title>What It Means to be Kind in a Cruel World | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360267/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360267/</guid><description>Podcast Description George Saunders is one of America’s greatest living writers. He’s the author of dozens of critically acclaimed short stories, including his 2013 collection, “Tenth of December”; his debut novel, “Lincoln in the Bardo,” won the 2017 Booker Prize; and his nonfiction work has empathy and insight that leave pieces from more than a decade ago ringing in my head today. His most recent book, “A Swim in A Pond in the Rain,” is a literary master class built around seven Russian short stories, analyzing how they work, and what they reveal about how we work.</description></item><item><title>What ‘Drained-Pool’ Politics Costs America | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360268/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360268/</guid><description>Podcast Description “The American landscape was once graced with resplendent public swimming pools, some big enough to hold thousands of swimmers at a time,” writes Heather McGhee in her new book, “The Sum of Us: What Racism Costs Everyone and How We Can Prosper Together.” These pools were the pride of their communities, monuments to what public investment could do. But they were, in many places, whites-only. Then came the desegregation orders.</description></item><item><title>The Senate Is Making a Mockery of Itself | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360269/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360269/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Senate is where Joe Biden’s agenda will live or die. More specifically, the intricacies of archaic Senate rules — the budget reconciliation process, the filibuster, the majority leader’s ability to control the floor — combined with the fealty today’s senators have to yesterday’s structures will decide the agenda’s fate. It would be the gravest mistake for progressives, or anyone else, to consider the fight over how the Senate works to be a sideshow compared with debates over a $15 minimum wage, a Green New Deal or democracy reform.</description></item><item><title>Should We Dim the Sun? Will We Even Have a Choice? | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360270/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360270/</guid><description>Podcast Description “We are as gods and might as well get good at it,” Stewart Brand famously wrote in “The Whole Earth Catalogue.” Human beings act upon nature at fantastic scale, altering whole ecosystems, terraforming the world to our purposes, breeding new species into existence and driving countless more into extinction. The power we wield is awesome. But Brand was overly optimistic. We did not get good at it. We are terrible at it, and the consequences surround us.</description></item><item><title>An Appalled Republican Considers the Future of the G.O.P. | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360271/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360271/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;ldquo;I don’t think conservatism can do its job in a free society in opposition to the institutions of that society,” Yuval Levin told me. “I think it can only function in defense of them.”
Levin is the director of social, cultural and constitutional studies at the American Enterprise Institute, as well as the author of a number of great books, most recently, “A Time to Build.” I wanted to talk to him about a very specific question, though: What will the Republican Party become?</description></item><item><title>To Understand This Era, You Need to Think in Systems | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360272/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360272/</guid><description>Podcast Description As my colleague Ben Smith wrote in an August profile, sociologist Zeynep Tufekci has “made a habit of being right on the big things.” She saw the threat of the coronavirus early and clearly. She saw that the public health community was ignoring the evidence on masking, and raised the alarm persuasively enough that she tipped the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention toward new, lifesaving guidance. Before Tufekci was being prescient about the coronavirus, she was being prescient about disinformation online, about the way social media was changing political organizing, about what election forecasting models could actually tell us, about the rising threat of authoritarianism in America.</description></item><item><title>What’s Happening to Our Economy Is Like a Natural Disaster | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360273/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360273/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Biden administration’s first legislative priority is a $1.9 trillion economic rescue package. It’s the kind of mega-package where the individual policies contained inside it — a $15 minimum wage, $1,400 checks, a huge child tax credit expansion, a $50 billion virus testing infrastructure — would be big deals on their own. But together, this would be one of the most consequential packages ever passed.
So there’s a lot to talk about here.</description></item><item><title>The Man With the Plan to Beat the Pandemic | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360274/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360274/</guid><description>Podcast Description I’ve never covered a moment that simultaneously merits so much despair and so much hope. It’s dizzying. The Biden administration takes office with over 25 million Covid-19 cases nationwide, over 420,000 Americans dead, and new, highly contagious variants of the virus stalking our future. It’s as grim a situation as I’ve seen.
But for the first time, we can do more than hide. We can immunize. Getting a population of 330 million to herd immunity is a hellishly difficult undertaking in the best of circumstances, and these are not the best of circumstances.</description></item><item><title>Coming Soon: The Ezra Klein Show | The Ezra Klein Show</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9158360275/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 01:42:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9158360275/</guid><description>Podcast Description Every Tuesday and Friday, Ezra Klein invites you into a conversation about something that matters. How do we address climate change if the political system fails to act? Has the logic of markets infiltrated too many aspects of our lives? What is the future of the Republican Party? What do psychedelics teach us about consciousness? What does sci-fi understand about our present that we miss? Can our food system be just to humans and animals alike?</description></item></channel></rss>