<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Do The Work on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/do-the-work/</link><description>Recent content in Do The Work on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/do-the-work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>49: Cheating, the mind of a cheater and debunking 'once a cheater always a cheater' with The Angry Therapist John Kim! | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910001/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910001/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode of Do the Work, Sabrina is joined by LMFT John Kim to talk about cheaters, cheating,debunking the myth 'once a cheater always a cheater' and how to move on from someone who cheated on you. Want to work with John? HERE!
Want to work with Sabrina? HERE!
Dont forget to follow Sabrina and Do the Work on instagram and Sabrina on Tik tok!
Please support our sponsors!</description></item><item><title>48: Healing from a narcissistic marriage, inner work post divorce and how to navigate co parenting with a narcissist with Helen Zohar! | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910002/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910002/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode of Do the Work, Sabrina is joined by her mom Helen to go over healing from a narcissistic marriage, inner work post divorce and how to navigate co parenting with a narcissist. Want to work with Sabrina? HERE!
Dont forget to follow Sabrina and Do the Work on instagram and Sabrina on Tik tok! Want to shop Softwear? Get 20% off your first order with code- DOTHEWORK Get 3 free towels and 20% off Miracle brands HERE</description></item><item><title>47: Conflict/ resolution in dating and why the cool girl doesn’t exist with Matthias J Barker and Masha Kay!! | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910003/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910003/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode of Do the Work, Sabrina is joined by Matthias J Barker and Masha Kay to go over how important conflict is in dating, steps for resolution and why the 'cool girl' doesn't exist. Want to work with Sabrina? HERE!
Dont forget to follow Sabrina and Do the Work on instagram and Sabrina on Tik tok! Please support our sponsors!
Want to shop Softwear? Get 20% off your first order with code- DOTHEWORK Receive your first month of Henry Meds and $50 off your first month HERE!</description></item><item><title>46: Stepping into your power and how to show up for yourself and your partner in dating! | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910004/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910004/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode of Do The Work, Sabrina talks about stepping into your power, what that looks like, how to etc and the importance of showing up for your partner in the same ways you want them to show up for you.
Want to work with Sabrina? HERE!
Dont forget to follow Sabrina and Do the Work on instagram and Sabrina on Tik tok! Please support our sponsors!</description></item><item><title>45: From Fboy to securely attached, debunking ‘if he wanted to he would,' ‘ sleeping with them will ruin things’ and more with Eli Vazquez! | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910005/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910005/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode of Do the Work podcast, Sabrina is joined by Eli Vazquez to chat about how Eli went from a F-boy to securely attached, debunking myths like 'if he wanted to he would', when to sleep together with someone, fear of commitment, breakups not being personal and SO much more!!
Follow Eli on TIK TOK or work with him HERE!
Want to work with Sabrina? HERE!</description></item><item><title>44: BONUS EPISODE! How human design can help understand you and others, how to navigate dating and understand yourself deeper with Erin Claire Jones! | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910006/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910006/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks bonus episode of Do the Work Podcast, Sabrina is joined by Erin Claire Jones , founder of Human Blueprint to chat about how human design can help understand you and others, how to navigate dating and understand yourself deeper and how to interpret your human design to help your dating life! A bit more about Erin and human design- Human Design is a synthesis of ancient wisdom and modern science that sheds light on a person’s energetic makeup, as well as specific tools they can use to live at their happiest, healthiest, highest potential.</description></item><item><title>43: When and how to define the relationship, “what are we” conversation and milestones in dating! | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910007/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910007/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode of Do the Work, Sabrina talks solo about when and how to define the relationship, “what are we” conversation and milestones in dating! She answers questions like:
Timeline to date before committing?
Insecure in relationship vs single?
How to figure out which to pick when dating multiple people?
and so much more!
Want to work with Sabrina? Click HERE
Dont forget to follow Sabrina and Do the Work on instagram and Sabrina on Tik tok!</description></item><item><title>42: Attachment styles in dating and navigating early dating securely with Dr Stan Tatkin! | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910008/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910008/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode of Do the Work, Sabrina is joined by Dr Stan Tatkin of the Pact Institute to go over how each attachment style shows up in dating and how to navigate early dating securely! Get Dr Stans book HERE!
La Event 11/9 tickets HERE!
Want to work with Sabrina? Click HERE
Dont forget to follow Sabrina and Do the Work on instagram and Sabrina on Tik tok!</description></item><item><title>41: Letting go of control, what it actually means to show up intentionally, detachment and surrendering to the outcome with Masha Kay! | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910009/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910009/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode of 'Do the work' Sabrina is joined by Masha Kay to go over letting go of control, what it actually means to show up intentionally, detachment and surrendering to the outcome. La Event 11/9 tickets HERE!
Get $300 off Mashas course with the code DOTHEWORK300 HERE
Want to work with Masha? Check her instagram out!
Want to work with Sabrina? Click HERE
Dont forget to follow Sabrina and Do the Work on instagram and Sabrina on Tik tok!</description></item><item><title>40: Ep. 40 Breakups, no contact and building self esteem to date again. | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910010/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910010/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode of Do the Work, Sabrina goes over how to handle a breakup, how different attachment styles handle breakups, why no contact is so important after a breakup and how to rebuild your self esteem. Want to work with Sabrina? click HERE!
Shop Softwear and get 20% off with code- DOTHEWORK HERE!
Shop Hello Fresh and get 50% off plus FREE shipping! Code- 50dothework HERE!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>39: Ep.39 How to get ‘unstuck’ with Neuropsychotherapist Britt Frank! | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910011/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910011/</guid><description>Podcast Description On This week Episode Sabrina is joined by Neuropsychotherapist Britt Frank! Britt and Sabrina chat about what it means to feel 'stuck', how the brain reacts to being stuck and how to navigate the feelings and get unstuck!
Want to work with Sabrina? Click HERE!
Get Britts book HERE! Get your Lume starter kit HERE! Code is DOTHEWORK Transcript</description></item><item><title>38: Ep. 38 TECH GUY EPISODE! Our relationship formation and debunking the modern dating experience with Tech guy! | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910012/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910012/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode of do the work, Sabrina is joined by her partner Tech Guy to chat about their relationship journey as well as debunk modern dating taboos.
Want to work with Sabrina? Click HERE
Dont forget to follow Sabrina and Do the Work on instagram and Sabrina on Tik tok! Please support our sponsors!
Try AG1 and get 5 travel packs and 1 year supply of Vitamin D HERE!</description></item><item><title>37: Ep. 37 Falling for potential and chasing the feeling in dating. | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910013/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910013/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode, Sabrina talks about chasing the feeling in dating, dating potential and boundaries to set to avoid a love bomber! Want to work with Sabrina? Click HERE
Answer the dating app survey HERE!
Dont forget to follow Sabrina and Do the Work on instagram and Sabrina on Tik tok! Please support our sponsor!
Give online therapy a try and get 10% off a month with Betterhelp!</description></item><item><title>36: Ep.36 Fear of abandonment and rejection with Masha Kay! | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910014/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910014/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode of Do The Work, Sabrina is joined by Masha Kay to go over the fear of abandonment and rejection! Sabrina and Masha go over where the fear of abandonment and rejection stem from in dating as well as personal experience with both! Get $300 off Mashas course with the code DOTHEWORK300 HERE
Want to work with Masha? Check her instagram out!
Want to work with Sabrina?</description></item><item><title>35: Ep.35 Mindset, Overcoming adversity and turning pain into purpose with Doug Bopst! | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910015/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on Do the Work Podcast, Sabrina is joined by Doug Bopst to talk about mindset, overcoming adversity and turning pain into purpose. Doug is an award winning author, fitness trainer, and speaker who has an amazing story to share of how he turned a jail sentence and drug addiction into a life of health and healing.
Listen to Dougs Podcast on Spotify or apple! Want to shop Softwear?</description></item><item><title>34: Ep. 34 First date questions, trauma dumping vs getting deep and how to ask questions of depth on a date? | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910016/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks solo episode, Sabrina goes over a SLEW of questions you can ask on the first or second date that range from light/fluff to deeper more emotionally available questions!
Want to work with Sabrina? Click HERE!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>33: Ep.33 What does a secure relationship look like, how to move to secure in dating and handle feeling ‘rejected' with Therapy Jeff! | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910017/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910017/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode of Do the Work, Sabrina is joined by Therapy Jeff to chat about what does a secure relationship look like, how to move to secure in dating and handle feeling ‘rejected.' Sabrina and Jeff also chat about what the 'spark' is in dating and the realities of being in a secure relationship. Want to connect with Jeff? Click HERE!
Want to work with Sabrina? Click HERE!</description></item><item><title>32: Ep. 32 Healing while single vs dating, the importance of triggers in dating and neurodivergent dating with Lewis Huckstep! | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910018/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910018/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode, Sabrina is joined by Lewis Huckstep to chat about healing while single or dating, the importance of triggers and what they teach you about your relationship. Want to work with Lewis? Click HERE
Want to work with Sabrina? Click HERE
Want to shop Softwear? Get 20% off your first order with code DOTHEWORK HERE
Transcript</description></item><item><title>31: Ep 31. Limerence in dating and dating multiple people | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910019/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910019/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode of Do the Work, Sabrina goes over what is limerence and the pros of dating multiple people early on in dating!
Want to work with Sabrina? HERE
Shop softwear and get 20% off with code DOTHEWORK HERE
Free MONTH of open mediation HERE
Transcript</description></item><item><title>30: Ep. 30 Overcoming heartbreak and finding love in a long distance relationship with Lindsey Harrod | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910020/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910020/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode of Do the Work Podcast, Sabrina is joined by fitness influencer and badass babe Lindsey Harrod to go over overcoming heartbreak, doing the work to heal, and getting the love of her life in a successful long distance relationship! Find Lindsey on tik tok! Use the code 'dothework' for 5 FREE classes on the Lindsey Harrod Fitness app found HERE! Transcript</description></item><item><title>29: Ep. 29 High functioning anxiety and how to do the inner child work to heal through anxiety | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910021/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910021/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode of Do the Work podcast, Sabrina is joined by Dr Lalitaa Suglani to chat about high functioning anxiety, overthinking and how to do the inner child work to start healing through it.
Want to work with Sabrina? Click HERE!
Free month of open meditation!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>28: Ep. 28 Red + Green flags in dating and going slow vs ambivalence in dating! | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910022/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode of 'Do the work' podcast, Sabrina goes over what are red and green flags and the difference between someone going slow and ambivalence in dating.
Follow Do the work podcast on Instagram, Facebook support group or follow Sabrina on Tik Tok! Want to work with Sabrina? Click HERE
Transcript</description></item><item><title>27: Ep. 27 Emotionally unavailable and anxious/avoidant trap with therapist Zoe Crook | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910023/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910023/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode of Do the Work, Sabrina is joined by therapist Zoe Crook to chat about emotionally unavailable, anxious/avoidant trap and debunk the myth that avoidants are the 'bad' people in dating.
Zoes Book HERE!
Zoes website HERE!
Free month of open meditation!
Want to work with Sabrina? HERE
Transcript</description></item><item><title>26: Ep. 26 Buzzwords part 2! Situationships, breadcrumbing, stonewalling, slow fade, negging and emotionally unavailable | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910024/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910024/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode of Do The Work, Sabrina goes over buzzwords part 2! Situationships, bread crumbing, stonewalling, slow fade, negging and emotionally unavailable. She goes over how to identify each and what to do when you do.
All resources (dating app audit, ask me a question, free guided) HERE!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>25: Ep. 25 Masha Pt 5! How to 'sit in the discomfort' , feel your emotions and work through rejection/abandonment. | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910025/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910025/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode of Do The Work podcast Masha Kay is back! We talk about what it means to sit in discomfort, feeling your emotions and the disconnection between the mind and body when youre trying to heal abandonment or rejection wounds.
One month FREE on open !
Join Mashas program HERE
Work with Sabrina HERE
Transcript</description></item><item><title>24: Ep. 24 'Doing the work' and what healing looks like with Leo Skepi! | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910026/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910026/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode of 'do the work' podcast Leo Skepi and I engage in authentic conversations about personal growth, resilience, and empowerment. We discuss the unique challenges faced by LGBTQ+ individuals, including societal norms, discrimination, and stigma. What 'doing the work' looks like to me and Leo as well as the toxicity in the Gay community. Transcript</description></item><item><title>23: Ep. 23 Attachment styles with therapist Flynn Skidmore | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910027/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sabrina and Therapist Flynn Skidmore provide valuable insights and practical strategies for listeners seeking to deepen their understanding of attachment styles and their impact on relationships. Through engaging discussions and real-life examples, they explore the complexities of attachment patterns and guide listeners towards developing healthier, more secure connections.
"Do the Work" offers a safe and supportive space for individuals to explore their own attachment styles, gain self-awareness, and discover practical tools for growth.</description></item><item><title>22: Ep 22. Mindset and dating with Case Kenny | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910028/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910028/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode of Do The Work, Sabrina chats with Case Kenny to go over how mindset affects dating and the importance of doing the work on yourself to show up the best you can in dating!
Buy Case Book here! Transcript</description></item><item><title>21: Ep 21. All things dating apps, how to navigate them and dos/donts with Lisa Holden | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910029/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910029/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode of Do the Work, Sabrina is joined by Lisa Holden to talk about all things dating apps! How to set one up successfully, how to handle dating app burnout, how to date more healthy on the apps and the dos/donts of navigating them.
Want to work with Lisa? Click HERE
Transcript</description></item><item><title>20: Ep 20. LGBTQ dating with Cammie Scott!! | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910030/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910030/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode of Do the Work we are joined by Cammie Scott! Cammie is a content creator, LGBTQ advocate and podcast host of Staying Up Podcast! This week Sabrina and Cammie go over LGBTQ dating, the toxicity in the community and how to stay true to yourself and navigate it. Transcript</description></item><item><title>19: Ep 19. Masha pt 4! Self sabotage + the shame around your insecure attachment style | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910031/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Masha joins us for another amazing episode of Do the Work! This week we go over befriending the nervous system, removing shame and what 'self sabotage' actually means. Want to work with Masha? Click HERE
Want to join Mashas program? Click HERE
Want to work with Sabrina? Click HERE
Transcript</description></item><item><title>18: Ep 18. Pt 1 Dating Buzzwords- Ghosting, lovebombing, gaslighting, orbiting and future faking | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910032/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 12:44:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910032/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode of Do The Work, Sabrina goes head in on part 1 of dating 'buzzwords.' Ghosting, orbiting, gaslighting and future faking. She dissects what each one means and the reasoning behind it!
Want to work with Sabrina? Click HERE
Transcript</description></item><item><title>17: Ep. 17 Narcissism, avoidants and why anxious attachers date unavailable people with LMHC Jessica Baum | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910033/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910033/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode Sabrina is joined by Jessica Baum LMHC to go over narcissism, anxious and avoidant dynamics, how to date and spot a narcissist and so much more!
Get Jessicas Book HERE! Check out Jessicas practice HERE!
Want to work with Sabrina? Check it out
Transcript</description></item><item><title>16: Ep.16 Joe Pt 2 answering your most asked questions in dating and more! | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910034/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910034/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode Joe is back to answer your most asked questions in dating! Why do guys lie about their intentions, is it true guys know 3-6 months dating youre ‘the one?’, and what 'not ready for a relationship' truly means and so much more!
Want to work with Joe? Dm him on insta HERE! Want to work with Sabrina? Book HERE! Transcript</description></item><item><title>15: Ep 15. Masha pt 3 How your anxiety and patterns in dating are playing out and what does the process of growth and change really look like? | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910035/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 11:00:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910035/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode, Sabrina is joined by Masha for a part 3 of our nervous system and anxiety talk! This week the girls chat about how your anxiety and patterns in dating are playing out in other areas of your life. What does the process of growth and change really look like? How your fears and insecurities play out in other areas of your life besides dating, why your nervous system hates change, and what 'doing the work' actually looks like.</description></item><item><title>14: Ep. 14 How does meditation help anxiety with Manoj Dias of Open | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910036/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 11:00:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910036/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode of Do The Work, Sabrina Is joined by Manoj Dias the Co-Founder of Open. They discuss how meditation helps with anxiety and how to utilize breath work, movement and meditation to manage anxious attachment and the narrative that plays.
Try Open for 30 days FREE! Click HERE
Transcript</description></item><item><title>13: Ep. 13 How to be a healthier dater | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910037/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 11:00:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910037/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode Sabrina goes over how to be a healthier dater and date with more intentionality. She goes over how to be comfortable alone, not attaching to the outcome, ghosting, questions to ask on dates and so so so much more!! Want to book with Sabrina or ask her for advice? CLICK HERE
Transcript</description></item><item><title>12: Ep. 12 Communication in dating, relationships and how to have the 'what are we' talk. | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910038/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 11:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910038/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode of Do The Work, Sabrina dives into Communication in dating, how to communicate effectively in dating and relationships and how to have the 'what are we' conversation!
Want to work with Sabrina? Click HERE! Transcript</description></item><item><title>11: Ep. 11 BONUS EPISODE! How my dogs passing changed the way I dated | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 23:07:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910039/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks subscription bonus episode, Sabrina shares her very personal experience with her dogs passing and how it changed the way she dated and ultimately landed her in the healthiest and best relationship she&amp;rsquo;s ever had.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>10: Ep 10. Inner child work, Ketamine treatments and what 'reparenting' looks like | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910040/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 11:00:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910040/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Sabrina opens up about her inner child healing journey, how ketamine treatments helped her connect to 'little sab' and what reparenting your inner child looks like. Want to work with Sabrina? Click here! Transcript</description></item><item><title>9: Ep. 9 Male/Female perspective with Sabrinas big brother and dating coach Joe Zohar | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910041/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910041/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Sabrina is joined by her big brother Joe who is also a dating coach and here to spill the tea! On this episode Joe and Sabrina dive into the male and female perspective on dating (coming from an avoidant male and anxious female), courtship and bust myths on things like 'does sleeping together first date ruin things?' or is 'not ready for a relationship' an excuse? Want to book a 1-1 session or ask Sabrina a question?</description></item><item><title>8: Ep.8 Intuition vs anxiety, calming your nervous system and learning to trust yourself with Masha Kay! | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910042/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 13:10:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910042/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Sabrina is joined by Masha Kay to talk all things nervous system pt 2! They go over differentiating intuition vs anxiety, calming your nervous system and ways to self sooth and learning to trust yourself! Want to work with Sabrina? BOOK NOW Want to work with Masha? BOOK NOW
Nervous system audit 90 min 1-1 session with Masha Code: SABRINA for $97 session (normally $275)
Follow her on Instagram and Tik Tok!</description></item><item><title>7: Ep 7. Boundaries, non negotiables and how to set them in dating. | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910043/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2023 14:25:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910043/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode of do the work podcast, Sabrina dives into the 7 boundaries we all need and her 6 non negotiables that changed her dating life. Want a 1-1 session with Sabrina? Book here Want to ask Sabrina a specific question about your dating life/situation? ASK HERE
Dating show application!! Transcript</description></item><item><title>6: Ep. 6 FIVE hard truths in dating we all need to hear | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910044/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 16:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910044/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Sabrina talks about 5 hard truths in dating we ALL need to hear. From texting in dating to ghosting, Sabrina breaks down each of the truths and gives a different perspective on dating. Dont forget to join the Patreon if you want to ask Sabrina for advice 1-1! Transcript</description></item><item><title>5: Ep. 5 Attachment Styles + Nervous system regulation with Masha K | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910045/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 23:24:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910045/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Sabrina is joined by Masha Kay to talk all things nervous system! They break down the 4 attachment styles, how they affect your nervous system and debunking myths about attachment styles!
Want to work with Masha? BOOK NOW Nervous system audit
90 min 1-1 session with Masha Code: SABRINA for $97 session (normally $275) Follow her on Instagram and Tik Tok! Transcript</description></item><item><title>4: Ep. 4 All things Breakups, healing and the way anxious/avoidant handles relationships ending. | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910046/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 16:00:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910046/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode, Sabrina goes over how anxious/avoidant handle breakups, how to move through it, what to do after, and things to do when youre anxious and dealing with a breakup! Transcript</description></item><item><title>3: Ep. 3 What does ' do the work' mean? | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910047/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 21:43:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910047/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this weeks episode Sabrina dives into what it means to 'do the work' on yourself. Finding your core wounds and traumas, reparenting the littler you and how to date differently once you've healed. Transcript</description></item><item><title>2: Ep 2. Texting in Dating | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910048/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 00:07:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910048/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Sabrina is back with a HOT topic: Texting in dating. She goes over the dos and donts with texting in the talking and dating phase, how to work and sit through your anxiety/anxious attachment with texting and try something new! Transcript</description></item><item><title>1: Ep 1. Anxious attachment and how it manifests in relationships | Do The Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4091910049/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 23:33:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4091910049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to the first episode of Do The Work podcast! On this episode, Sabrina shares her journey with anxiety, anxious attachment style, and ways she healed it and how to 'do the work' authentically. Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>