<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Video Transcripts on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/tags/video-transcripts/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Video Transcripts on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 22:09:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/video-transcripts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Homeopathy Explained – Gentle Healing or Reckless Fraud？ ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/8hsluzw35mc/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 22:09:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/8hsluzw35mc/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Homeopathy may be the most controversial but also the most popular alternative medicine.
While some argue against it, others swear by its great power and effectiveness.
How does homeopathy work?
How did it become what it is today, and what can modern medicine learn from it?
The first principle of homeopathy is &amp;ldquo;like cures like.&amp;rdquo;
Remedies use ingredients that cause the symptoms you want to cure.
In practice, that means that remedies against fever could, for example, be made from belladonna, which also causes fever.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>How Far Can We Go？ Limits of Humanity (Old Version – Watch the New One) ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/zl4yyhddsws/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 21:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/zl4yyhddsws/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Is there a border we will never cross?
Are there places we will never reach, no matter how hard we try?
Turns out there are.
Even with science fiction technology, we are trapped in our pocket of the universe.
How can that be?
And how far can we go?
We live in a quiet arm of the Milky Way
a spiral galaxy of average size about one hundred thousand light years across,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>How to Cure Aging – During Your Lifetime？ ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/mjdpr-ty6qu/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 21:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/mjdpr-ty6qu/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Health is the most valuable thing we have in life, but we tend to forget that until we lose it.
We&amp;rsquo;re living longer than ever before, which is great,
but an unforeseen consequence of this is that we also spend a larger and larger portion of our lives being sick.
Getting old currently means spending more time in pain.
So scientists are trying to shift the attention of the medical community from optimizing lifespans to optimizing healthspans,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>How to Make an Elephant Explode – The Size of Life 2 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/muwuhf-rzks/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 20:51:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/muwuhf-rzks/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Let&amp;rsquo;s shrink an elephant to the size of a mouse
and enlarge a mouse, and make it the size of an elephant,
because this is our video, and we want to see what happens.
First: our now tiny elephant, stumbles around and then drops dead.
Tiny elephant buddy is very cold; frozen to death in minutes.
Our giant mouse looks very uncomfortable for a moment, and then it explodes.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>How Bacteria Rule Over Your Body – The Microbiome ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/vzpd009qtn4/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 20:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/vzpd009qtn4/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Microbes are everywhere,
on your phone,
in your water bottle,
on your hands before you wash them,
on your hands after you wash them,
and literally everywhere else on top of you too.
Microbes are omnipresent at any moment, and there is nothing we can do about it
So, millions of years ago we made a pact,
we give them shelter and food,
and in turn they work for us.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>How To Terraform Venus (Quickly) ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/g-wo-z-quwi/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 18:50:06 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/g-wo-z-quwi/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Leaving earth to find new homes in space is an old dream of humanity and will sooner or
later be necessary for our survival. The planet that gets the most attention is Mars, a small,
toxic and energy poor planet that just about seems good enough for a colony of depressed
humans huddled in underground cities.
But what if we think bigger? What if we take Venus, one of the most hostile and deadly</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>How Facebook is Stealing Billions of Views ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/t7ta3nnkf0q/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 18:34:15 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/t7ta3nnkf0q/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿A few days ago Facebook proudly announced that
they&amp;rsquo;d achieved eight billion video views a day.
That&amp;rsquo;s really impressive,
until you learn
that in the first quarter of 2015,
seven hundred and twenty-five
of the 1000 most-viewed videos on Facebook
were stolen,
amassing a total of 17 billion views.
Sites and content aggregators
steal videos from YouTube
to go viral on Facebook.
These videos go viral
because Facebook is cheating.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>How Big is the Moon？ MM#1 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/tqt9hzcwhjm/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 18:29:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/tqt9hzcwhjm/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿How big is the moon?
In the night sky the moon seems rather small, but in reality it really isn&amp;rsquo;t.
Central Europe would easily fit under it.
The surface area of the moon is huge.
To give you some perspective, it&amp;rsquo;s as big as the whole European continent, China, the USA, Brazil, and South Africa together.
Weight-wise, the moon is only about 1/81th of the mass of Earth,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>How To Terraform Mars - WITH LASERS ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/hpctjw4ur54/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 17:19:36 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/hpctjw4ur54/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Mars is a disappointing hellhole lacking practically everything we need to stay alive. It looks like we’ll only ever have small crews spend a miserable time hidden underground. Except, we could terraform it into a green new world. But to solve the planet’s problems, we first need to make it worse and turn it into oceans of lava with gigantic lasers.
This isn’t a far-fetched science fiction tale. Terraforming Mars is possible, on the kind of time scale our ancestors built great monuments in.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>How We Make Money on YouTube with 20M Subs ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1x-i9z617z4/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 16:46:35 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1x-i9z617z4/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿In 2023 Kurzgesagt has existed for 10 years, insanely long in internet years. We are among the largest sciency channels on Youtube and still a bit of a black box to people. So let us talk about ourselves a bit in three parts: Our backstory, how we finance our work and the values of Kurzgesagt!
Let’s jump to a more innocent time.
From humble beginnings to Today
Kurzgesagt’s foundation was laid when Philipp, our founder, dropped out of high school as a teenager.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>HIDDEN WORLDS - Limited Edition Calendar! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/fmjqwd7_-nu/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 16:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/fmjqwd7_-nu/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Come in and have a look at this top secret project we&amp;rsquo;ve been working on.
It&amp;rsquo;s finally time to push the button and put the MIGHTY SHRINK LAZORRR to the test!
I’m ready.
We did it!
It worked.
Right under our noses there is so much hidden that we never get to see with our own eyes
– entire realms of bizarre structures and outlandish creatures.
What a magical place this is.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>How to Make a Kurzgesagt Video in 1200 Hours ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/ufk0mgljtns/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 16:21:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/ufk0mgljtns/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿For years, people have asked how we make our videos.
So. let&amp;rsquo;s finally talk about it.
How to Make a Kurzgesagt Video in 1,200 Hours or More
(Kurzgesagt intro)
Kurzgesagt in a Nutshell
But first things first, we need a topic.
Our potential topic list is already endless, and every time we research something, it grows longer.
So, we just work on whatever we find exciting at the time.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>How Small Is An Atom？ Spoiler： Very Small. ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/_lnf3_30lue/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 14:30:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/_lnf3_30lue/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Atoms are ridiculous and unbelievably small.
A single human hair is about as thick as
500,000 carbon atoms stacked over each other.
Look at your fist, it contains trillions and trillions of atoms.
If one atom in it were about as big as a marble, how big would your fist be?
Well… about the size of Earth. Hm… still hard to imagine?
Let’s try something different
Look at your little finger.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>How Large Can a Bacteria get？ Life &amp; Size 3 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/e1kkqrfel2i/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 13:43:25 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/e1kkqrfel2i/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿In and out, in and out.
Staying alive is about doing things. This very second, your cells are combusting glucose molecules with oxygen
to make energy available, which keeps you alive for another precious moment.
To get the oxygen to your cells you are breathing.
Breathing is an answer to a very hard problem: How do you get the resources that your cells need to survive,
from the outside, to the inside of your cells?</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>How The Immune System ACTUALLY Works – IMMUNE ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/lxfek8g8cui/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 12:35:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/lxfek8g8cui/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿The human immune system is the most complex biological system we know, after the human brain,
and yet most of us never learn how it works.
Or, what it is.
Your immune system consists of hundreds of tiny—and two large—organs.
It has its own transport network spread throughout your body.
Every day, it makes hundreds of billions of fresh cells organized like an army.
With soldiers, captains, intelligence officers, heavy weapons, and crazy suicide bombers.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>How to catch a Dwarf Planet -- Triton MM#3 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/cr9uphgmz8u/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 11:11:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/cr9uphgmz8u/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿The 14 moons of Neptune are a strange bunch.
Most of them are small potato shaped pieces of ice and rock.
Some are so far away from Neptune that they need 29 years to circle Neptune once.
Almost all of them are asteroids trapped by Neptune&amp;rsquo;s gravity.
99.5% of all the mass around Neptune is concentrated in Triton.
It&amp;rsquo;s the 7th biggest moon, and more massive than all other known moons</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>How A Nuclear War Will Start - Minute by Minute ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/wmp3mbjsx20/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 11:08:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/wmp3mbjsx20/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Mr. President! Nuclear missiles will strike our country in 14 minutes.
I know it’s your first day in office so I’m going to walk you through it, but you’re the only one
who can authorize our nuclear retaliation in response and you’ve only got a few minutes to make a decision!
As you know tensions have escalated rapidly in the past few days.
Today’s joint allied aerial defense exercise began just minutes before we detected the launch.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>How We Could Build a Moon Base TODAY – Space Colonization 1 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/ntqkz0arde8/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 10:47:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/ntqkz0arde8/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Humans dream about leaving Earth and traveling through the galaxy. But we were born too early to be part of it. Or were we? The reality is, we could begin our dream by building a Moon base today. We actually do have the technology and current estimates from NASA and the private sector say it could be done for 20 to 40</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>How to Build a Dyson Sphere - The Ultimate Megastructure ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/pp44epbmb8a/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 09:37:02 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/pp44epbmb8a/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Human history is told by the energy we use. At first we had to use our muscles, then we learned to control fire.
We industrialized the world using coal and oil and entered the Atomic Age when we learned how to split a nucleus.
At each step, we increased our energy harvest to a scale never seen before and advanced as a species.
Currently, we&amp;rsquo;re slowly transitioning to renewables and if we&amp;rsquo;re lucky, fusion energy will become viable in the future.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>How to Make Money on YouTube with 20M Subs ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1x-i9z617z4/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 09:21:12 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1x-i9z617z4/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿In 2023 Kurzgesagt has existed for 10 years, insanely long in internet years. We are among the largest sciency channels on Youtube and still a bit of a black box to people. So let us talk about ourselves a bit in three parts: Our backstory, how we finance our work and the values of Kurzgesagt!
Let’s jump to a more innocent time.
From humble beginnings to Today
Kurzgesagt’s foundation was laid when Philipp, our founder, dropped out of high school as a teenager.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>How Evolution works ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/hofrn0kihou/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 08:38:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/hofrn0kihou/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Mechanisms of evolution
What is evolution?
Evolution is the development of life on Earth.
This is a process that began billions of years ago and is still continuing to this day.
Evolution tells us how it was possible for the enormous diversity of life to develop.
It shows us how primitive Protozoa could become the millions of different species that we see today.
Evolution, then, is the answer to the question that we have all asked on seeing a Daschund and a Great Dane together:</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>How The Stock Exchange Works (For Dummies) ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/f3qpgxbtdeo/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 07:39:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/f3qpgxbtdeo/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿What is the Stock Exchange and how does it work?
The Stock Exchange is nothing more than a giant globally network
tend to organize the market place where every day huge sums of money are moved back and forth.
In total over sixty trillion (60,000,000,000,000) Euros a year are traded.
More than the value of all goods and services of the entire world economy.
However it&amp;rsquo;s not apples or second hand toothbrushes that are traded on this marketplace.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>How to Move the Sun： Stellar Engines ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/v3y8aiex_du/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/v3y8aiex_du/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Nothing in the universe is static. In the Milky Way, billions of stars orbit the galactic center.
Some, like our Sun, are pretty consistent, keeping a distance of around
30,000 light years from the galactic center, completing an orbit every 230 million years.
This dance is not an orderly ballet, more like a skating rink filled with drunk toddlers.
This chaos makes the galaxy dangerous.
Our solar neighborhood is constantly changing, with stars moving hundreds of kilometers every second.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Change Your Life – One Tiny Step at a Time ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/75d_29qwelk/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 23:55:33 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/75d_29qwelk/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿If you are like most people, there is a gap between the person you are and the person you wish to be. There are little things you think you should do and big things you ought to achieve.
From working out regularly, eating healthily, learning a language, working on your novel, reading more or simply actually doing your hobby instead of browsing reddit.
But it sometimes seems that to achieve your goals, you have to become a different person.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Do Robots Deserve Rights? What if Machines Become Conscious? ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/dhyuyg8x31c/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 22:53:29 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/dhyuyg8x31c/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Imagine a future where your toaster anticipates what kind of toast you want.
During the day, it scans the Internet for new and exciting types of toast.
Maybe it asks you about your day, and wants to chat about new achievements in toast technology.
At what level would it become a person?
At which point will you ask yourself if your toaster has feelings?
If it did, would unplugging it be murder?</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Fusion Power Explained – Future or Failure ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/mzsaaturr6e/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 22:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/mzsaaturr6e/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿The fundamental currency of our universe is energy.
It lights our homes, grows our food, powers our computers.
We can get it lots of ways:
Burning fossil fuels, splitting atoms,
or sunlight striking photovoltaics.
But there&amp;rsquo;s a downside to everything
Fossil fuels are extremely toxic,
Nuclear waste is&amp;hellip; well, nuclear waste,
And, there are not enough batteries to store sunlight for cloudy days yet.
And yet the sun seems to have virtually limitless free energy.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Geoengineering： A Horrible Idea We Might Have to Do ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/dsu5sxmsur4/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 22:08:45 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/dsu5sxmsur4/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿By the end of the 21st century, humanity is becoming desperate. Decades of heatwaves and droughts have led to unusually poor harvests, while the warming oceans yield fewer fish each year. In the tropical zones, millions suffer from famine and resource wars have made millions more flee to the north. As things quickly get worse, in an act of desperation, the world&amp;rsquo;s governments decide to enact an emergency plan&amp;hellip;</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Death From Space — Gamma-Ray Bursts Explained ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/rlykc1vn7ny/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 22:02:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/rlykc1vn7ny/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Imagine if you could gather the energy from every star within a hundred million light years.
From thousands of galaxies, each with billions of stars.
Imagine, you could take this kind of power, and use it to fire the biggest super-weapon in the universe.
Imagine the damage you could do.
It turns out, you don&amp;rsquo;t need to imagine it.
These exist, and they&amp;rsquo;re called gamma ray bursts.
But what are these cosmic snipers?</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Emergence – How Stupid Things Become Smart Together ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/16w7c0mb-re/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 21:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/16w7c0mb-re/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿An ant is pretty stupid.
It doesn&amp;rsquo;t have much of a brain, no will, no plan,
and yet, many ants together are smart.
An ant colony can construct complex structures.
Some colonies keep farms of fungi, others take care of cattle. They can wage war or defend themselves.
How is this possible?
How can a bunch of stupid things do smart things together?
This phenomenon is called emergence,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>End of Space – Creating a Prison for Humanity ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/ys1ibdimayu/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 20:06:23 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/ys1ibdimayu/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Space travel is the most exciting and challenging adventure humanity has ever undertaken.
But in an irony of history,
we may stop ourselves from going into space the more we do it.
With every rocket launched
and with every satellite deployed,
we&amp;rsquo;re creating a trap for ourselves that gets deadlier and more dangerous every year.
If it&amp;rsquo;s ever activated,
it could end the Space Age
and trap us on our planet for decades,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Genetic Engineering and Diseases – Gene Drive &amp; Malaria ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/tnzcwtyr6ce/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 16:09:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/tnzcwtyr6ce/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿What if you could use genetic engineering to stop humanity&amp;rsquo;s most
dangerous predator, the deadliest animal on the planet responsible for the death
of billions, the mighty mosquito? Along with other diseases it plays host to
Malaria, one of the cruelest parasites on Earth
possibly the single biggest killer of humans in history.
In 2015 alone
hundreds of millions were infected and almost half a million people died.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Everything You Need to Know About Planet Earth ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/jgxi_9a__vc/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 15:07:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/jgxi_9a__vc/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Planet Earth is the home of every lifeform,
known to us, in the universe.
Its age is about 1/3 of the age of the universe
and, admitted,
It is a thing of beauty.
a slightly squashed fair with a heavy metal core,
and a lighter surface crust,
wrapped in a thin sliver of sweet air to breathe,
with vast oceans,
fertile plains,
magnificent mountains,
fresh water rivers, streams, lakes and aquifers,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Can YOU Fix Climate Change？ ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/yiw6_jakzfc/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 13:51:50 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/yiw6_jakzfc/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Never before in human history have we been richer, more advanced or powerful.
And yet we feel overwhelmed in the face of rapid climate change.
It seems simple on the surface.
Greenhouse gases trap energy from the Sun and transfer it to our atmosphere.
This leads to warmer winters, harsher summers.
Dry places become drier and wet places wetter.
Countless ecosystems will die while the rising oceans swallow coasts and the cities we build</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Could Solar Storms Destroy Civilization？ Solar Flares &amp; Coronal Mass Ejections ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/ohhssjdj4oo/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 10:59:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/ohhssjdj4oo/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿The Sun,
smooth and round and peaceful.
Except when it suddenly vomits radiation and plasma in random directions.
These solar flares and coronal mass ejections, or CMEs,
can hit Earth and have serious consequences for humanity.
How exactly do they work?
How bad could they be?
And can we prepare for them?
[Intro music]
While the Sun seems pretty solid, it&amp;rsquo;s actually like a very hot ocean.
So hot that it rips atoms into electrons and nuclei, all flowing around each other in a plasma.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Could Your Phone Hurt You? Electromagnetic Pollution ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/ffgt6zx4k3q/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 07:35:01 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/ffgt6zx4k3q/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Electricity is all around us all the time.​
It makes our lives easier, safer, more fun,​
and most of us never think about it.​
But is there such a thing as too much electricity?​
Could the thing that is the foundation of the modern world​
slowly be killing us?​
Before we dive deeper,​
let&amp;rsquo;s try to understand what electricity is,​
and how it affects us.​
Electricity is the movement of an electric charge.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Genetic Engineering Will Change Everything Forever – CRISPR ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/jahjpd4unfy/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 05:29:41 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/jahjpd4unfy/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿magine you were alive back in the 1980&amp;rsquo;s,
and were told that computers would soon take over everything:
from shopping, to dating, and the stock market,
that billions of people would be connected via a kind of web,
that you would own a handheld device, orders of magnitudes more powerful than supercomputers.
It would seem absurd, but then, all of it happened.
Science fiction became our reality, and we don&amp;rsquo;t even think about it.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Can You Trust Kurzgesagt Videos？ ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/jtuaaxe_0vi/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 05:12:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/jtuaaxe_0vi/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Can you trust Kurzgesagt videos?
To answer this question, we&amp;rsquo;ll first explain how we research them
and then talk a bit about past videos,
and what we want to achieve with the channel.
Making a Kurzgesagt video always begins with a question or an issue.
For example, after our meat video,
many viewers asked about the health effects of meat on humans.
We had no idea, and were pretty curious too,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Do we Need Nuclear Energy to Stop Climate Change？ ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/ehaemz1v7dq/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 02:29:16 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/ehaemz1v7dq/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿do we need nuclear energy to stop climate change
more and more voices from science environmental activists and the press
have been saying so in recent years but this comes as a shock to those who are
fighting against nuclear energy and the problems that come with it
so who&amp;rsquo;s right well
it&amp;rsquo;s complicated to slow rapid climate change the world
needs to reduce greenhouse gas emissions to net zero</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Fracking explained: opportunity or danger ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/uti2niw2bra/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 00:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/uti2niw2bra/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿What is hydraulic fracturing – or fracking ?
Since the industrial revolution our energy consumption has risen unceasingly.
The majority of this energy consumption is supplied by fossil fuels like coal or natural gas.
Recently there has been a lot of talk about a controversial method of extracting natural gas:
Hydraulic fracturing or fracking.
Put simply, fracking describes the recovery of natural gas from deep layers inside the earth.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Are You Alone? (In The Universe) ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/pkmqzkiib0y/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 21:02:10 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/pkmqzkiib0y/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Are you alone in the universe?
Or are you connected to anything?
First of all, you’re part of a group of mammals that’s still very young,
but we can make YouTube videos already,
and build Large Hadron Colliders!
We’ve also split the atom and invented Pokémon.
We stem from an ancient lifeform
that began living about three and a half billion years ago.
We feel like we’re in control of this planet, but we aren’t really.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Are There Lost Alien Civilizations in Our Past? ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/krvv0qdrumq/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 20:43:56 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/krvv0qdrumq/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿When we think about alien civilizations we tend to look into the vastness of space, to far away planets. But there is another incredibly vast dimension that we might be giving too little thought to: time.
Could it be that over the last hundreds of millions of years, other civilizations existed on earth? Indigenous technological species that rose and died out? And that they or their artifacts are buried beneath our feet?</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Building a Marsbase is a Horrible Idea: Let&#39;s do it! ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/uqkgrezs6-w/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 14:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/uqkgrezs6-w/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿From hostile deserts, to lonely islands and the highest mountains,
wherever there is space to expand into humans do so.
So, it&amp;rsquo;s hardly surprising that we&amp;rsquo;re already making preparations
to set foot on Mars,
and to create the first permanent colony outside of Earth &amp;ndash;
maybe even terraform another planet and turn it into a second blue home.
But wait,
before we can get to the nice future stuff,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Atoms As Big As Mountains — Neutron Stars Explained ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/zw3av7u-aik/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 12:47:58 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/zw3av7u-aik/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Neutron stars are one of the most extreme things in the universe.
They’re like giant atom cores.
Kilometers in diameter, unbelievably dense and violent.
But how can something like this even exist?
The life of a star is dominated by two forces being in balance.
Its own gravity and the radiation pressure of its fusion reaction.
In the core of stars, hydrogen is fused into helium.
Eventually, the hydrogen in the core is exhausted.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Banking Explained – Money and Credit ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/fttgalarzoc/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 12:08:26 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/fttgalarzoc/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿The international banking system is an enigma.
There are more than 30.000 different banks world wide, and they hold unbelievable amounts of assets.
The top 10 banks alone account for roughly 25 trillion US-Dollars.
Today, banking can seem very complex, but originally, the idea was to make life simpler.
11th century Italy was the centre of European trading.
Merchants from all over the continent met to trade their goods, but there was one problem:</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Aliens exist on rogue planets beneath the ice. ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/m7ckdb5z9py/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 10:56:53 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/m7ckdb5z9py/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Rogue planets are planets that travel through the universe alone.
They inhabit the dark and vast space between the stars.
Drifting alone through eternal darkness, no light warms their surfaces,
and they&amp;rsquo;re exposed to the freezing cold of outer space.
They know no seasons, no days, and no nights, which could give away the passing of time.
And yet, rogue planets might carry alien life
to all corners of the galaxy.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Black Holes Explained – From Birth to Death ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/e-p5iftqb98/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 04:01:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/e-p5iftqb98/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Black holes are one of the strangest things in existence.
They don&amp;rsquo;t seem to make any sense at all.
Where do they come from&amp;hellip;
&amp;hellip;and what happens if you fall into one?
Stars are incredibly massive collections of mostly hydrogen atoms
that collapsed from enormous gas cloud under their own gravity.
In their core, nuclear fusion crushes hydrogen atoms into helium
releasing a tremendous amount of energy
This energy, in the form of radiation,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>An antidote to dissatisfaction. ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/wpppfqsecz0/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 03:05:07 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/wpppfqsecz0/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Everybody is familiar with the feeling
that things are not as they should be.
That you&amp;rsquo;re not successful enough,
your relationship&amp;rsquo;s not satisfying enough,
that you don&amp;rsquo;t have the things you crave.
A chronic dissatisfaction
that makes you look outwards with envy
and inwards with disappointment.
Pop culture, advertising, and
social media make this worse
by reminding you that aiming for anything
less than your dream job is failure,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Are GMOs Good or Bad? Genetic Engineering &amp; Our Food ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/7tmcxyp8xu4/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 02:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/7tmcxyp8xu4/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿GMOs are one of the most controversial areas of science.
Genetic engineering is used in many fields, but even though medical applications like GM insulin are widely accepted,
The debate heats up when it comes to food and agriculture.
Why is that?
Why is the same thing treated so differently?
Let&amp;rsquo;s try to get to the bottom of this and explore the facts, the fears, and the future of GMOs.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Ancient life is as old as the universe. ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/joigei9pqbs/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 02:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/joigei9pqbs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿The 12,024 Calendar is here! Get it now before it sells out.
And stay tuned until the end of this video for a sneak peek that’s out of this world.
Life has existed on one planet for about 4 billion years, as far as we know. But it might
have started right after the Big Bang, when the universe was much stranger and more fantastic
than today. A universe that might have allowed life to develop absolutely anywhere.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Black Hole Star – The Star That Shouldn&#39;t Exist ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/aewyp2vxxqa/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 00:04:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/aewyp2vxxqa/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Black hole stars may have been the largest stars to ever exist. They burned brighter than galaxies and were Larger than any star today or that could ever exist in the future. But besides their scale, what makes them special and weird is that deep inside, they were occupied by a cosmic parasite, an endlessly hungry black hole. How is that even possible?
Black hole stars take the weirdness of black holes and go beyond to break everything we know about how stars form and grow.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Reasons Why Nuclear Energy Is Terrible! 2/3 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/heybgyl5n1g/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 22:47:42 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/heybgyl5n1g/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿three reasons why we should stop using nuclear energy
one. nuclear weapons proliferation
nuclear technology made a violent entrance onto the world stage
just one year after the world&amp;rsquo;s first-ever nuclear test explosion in
1944
two large cities were destroyed by just two single bombs
after that, reactor technology slowly evolved as a means of generating
electricity but it&amp;rsquo;s always been intimately connected with nuclear
weapons technology
it&amp;rsquo;s nearly impossible to develop nuclear weapons without access to reactor</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>1,000km Cable to the Stars - The Skyhook ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/dqwpqarrdwk/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 17:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/dqwpqarrdwk/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Getting to space is hard.
Right now, it’s like going up on a mountain on a unicycle-
with a backpack full of explosives.
Incredibly slow, you can’t transport a lot of stuff, and you might die.
A rocket needs to reach a velocity about 40,000km an hour to escape from Earth.
To get to that speed, rockets are mostly containers for fuel with a tiny tip of payload.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A Selfish Argument for Making the World a Better Place – Egoistic Altruism ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/rvskmhn0sqq/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 12:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/rvskmhn0sqq/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Until recently, the vast majority of the world population worked on farms
and the total production of the world&amp;rsquo;s economy
was mostly the total agricultural output.
And this output was limited by the fixed size of the land.
The total output of the economy did not change a lot year by year.
The size of the pie was fixed; the world was a zero-sum game.
In such a stagnating world, the only way to get better off is if someone else gets worse off.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Arguments Why Marijuana Should Stay Illegal Reviewed ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/kp15q815saw/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 10:57:51 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/kp15q815saw/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿All around the world,
marijuana is being decriminalized, or even made legal.
But is this really a good idea?
In the online debate,
the harmful sides are often downplayed.
So let&amp;rsquo;s look at the three most powerful arguments
against legalizing marijuana.
[Intro - Kurzgesagt]
Argument number 1:
In the last few decades,
marijuana has been engineered to become much more potent.
Today, marijuana is so potent,
that it&amp;rsquo;s actually a strong drug that may cause psychosis.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>3 Reasons Why Nuclear Energy Is Awesome! 3/3 ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/pvbllnmxiby/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 02:58:30 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/pvbllnmxiby/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Three reasons why we should continue using nuclear energy.
One: nuclear energy saves lives.
In 2013, a study conducted by NASA found that nuclear energy has prevented
around 1.8 million deaths.
Even if you include the death tolls from Chernobyl and Fukushima,
nuclear energy ranks last in death per energy unit produced.
While nuclear waste is really toxic, it’s usually stored somewhere,
while the toxic byproducts of fossil fuels are pumped into the air</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>A New History for Humanity – The Human Era ｜ Kurzgesagt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/czgowmtgvgs/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 03:10:49 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/czgowmtgvgs/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ﻿Humans have existed for millions of years, as part of nature.
But then, something changed. And in an incredibly short amount of time..
..We terraformed this planet and designed it to fit our needs.
As far as we know, we&amp;rsquo;re the first beings to awaken and completely take over a planet.
The transition from hunting and gathering to farming and building, was so breathtakingly fast,
that many of our ways of thinking about the world are no longer useful.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Apple - WWDC 2023 — June 5</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3003100012/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3003100012/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ♪ ♪
♪ Spirals are spinning ♪
♪ Don&amp;rsquo;t fly away ♪
♪ Light comes to anywhere you like ♪
♪ And I hope that you feel it ♪
♪ There&amp;rsquo;s no time to waste ♪
♪ Just take me to where we collide ♪
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Whoo! ♪
♪ ♪
♪ ♪
♪ And I hope that you feel it ♪</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Apple - Apple Event — September 7</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3003100011/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3003100011/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ♪ ♪
♪ ♪
♪ ♪
♪ ♪
Tim Cook: Good morning.
We&amp;rsquo;re so glad you could join us.
At Apple, we&amp;rsquo;re fortunate to be surrounded by people
who strive to innovate together
to create products and experiences that enrich people&amp;rsquo;s lives,
products that are intuitive and easy to use,
that have a unique integration of hardware and software,
and that are incredibly personal.
Today, we&amp;rsquo;re here to talk about three products</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Apple - WWDC 2022 - June 6</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3003100010/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3003100010/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ♪ ♪
♪ ♪
♪ ♪
♪ ♪
Tim Cook: Good morning, and welcome to WWDC.
We have a big day of announcements
about our latest technologies and platforms.
These platforms, and the products they drive,
deliver amazing experiences for our users
and provide developers with incredible opportunities
so they can use their superpowers to innovate, create,
and collaborate, making apps that continue to change the world.
And WWDC is designed to give this community</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Apple - Apple Event — March 8</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3003100009/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3003100009/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript [upbeat music]
[♪ ♪]
Tim: Good morning, and welcome back to Apple Park!
Thank you for joining us for our first event of 2022.
Today we have some great announcements to share.
We&amp;rsquo;ve been working hard to deliver new products and services
that help you stay connected, productive, and entertained.
So let&amp;rsquo;s start with Apple TV+.
Like many of you, I&amp;rsquo;ve been watching a lot of shows and movies</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Apple - Apple Event — October 18</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3003100008/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3003100008/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript [steady clicking]
[Mac startup sound chimes]
[keys clacking lightly]
[Mac startup sound chimes]
[tone chimes lower]
[startup tone chimes]
[tone of startup chime modulating]
[light chiming]
[case snapping]
♪ ♪
♪ ♪
[scroll wheel clicking]
[mechanical beat playing]
♪ ♪
♪ ♪
♪ ♪
[high-pitched ringing]
[Mac startup tone chimes]
♪ ♪
Tim: Good morning!
Welcome back to Apple Park for our second event
in just over a month.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Apple - Apple Event — September 14</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3003100007/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3003100007/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript [lively violin playing]
[upbeat rock music]
Like a sound you hear that lingers in your ear
But you can&amp;rsquo;t forget from sundown to sunset
It&amp;rsquo;s on in the air, you hear it everywhere
No matter what you do
It&amp;rsquo;s gonna grab a hold on you
California soul
California soul
They say the sun comes up every morning now
And if you listen, oh so carefully
The winds that rise on the high tide</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Apple - WWDC 2021 — June 7</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3003100006/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3003100006/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript [person] For me, WW is the Super Bowl.
[person] You can feel the energy.
[person] It&amp;rsquo;s like really deep insights
of what it feels like being a developer.
[person] Really?
[person] Wow.
[laughs]
[person] Okay, we open on black.
The curtain slowly opens.
Have a DeLorean on the stage.
Tim Cook gets out of that DeLorean,
showing the phone&amp;rsquo;s flux capacitor.
[person] I would probably not start there.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Apple - Apple Event — April 20</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3003100005/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3003100005/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript ♪ &amp;ldquo;The Darkness That You Fear&amp;rdquo; by The Chemical Brothers ♪
♪ Let your heart ♪
♪ See the colors ♪
♪ All around you ♪
♪ I&amp;rsquo;ll be loving you, Yes, I will ♪
♪ I&amp;rsquo;ll be loving you ♪
♪ I&amp;rsquo;ll be loving you, Yes, I will ♪
♪ I&amp;rsquo;ll be loving you ♪
♪ Let your heart ♪
♪ See the colors ♪
♪ All around you ♪</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Apple - Apple Event — November 10</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3003100004/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3003100004/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript [pop music playing]
Hello and welcome back.
It&amp;rsquo;s great to have you join us.
I&amp;rsquo;m really excited for today and the news we have to share with you.
It&amp;rsquo;s amazing to think that this is our third major event
in just the past two months.
In the midst of enormous challenges this year,
our teams have remained focused,
and they haven&amp;rsquo;t stopped innovating.
We&amp;rsquo;re on an unbelievable pace of new product releases,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Apple - Apple Event — October 13</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3003100003/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3003100003/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript [&amp;ldquo;Good Day for Dreaming&amp;rdquo; by Ruelle playing]
Hello and welcome back to Apple Park.
I am so glad you could join us today.
Just last month we were here to introduce some great new products:
Apple Watch Series 6,
Apple Watch SE,
as well as the eighth-generation iPad
and the all-new iPad Air.
And we&amp;rsquo;ve got some more huge announcements for you today.
So let&amp;rsquo;s get started with an exciting new product for the home</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Apple - Apple Event — September 15</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3003100002/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3003100002/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript Good morning and welcome.
We are so pleased that you could join us today.
We&amp;rsquo;ve got some really exciting product announcements to share with you.
As we all continue to make our way through these difficult times
and face the challenges that COVID-19 is causing
in our communities around the world,
it&amp;rsquo;s so inspiring how people everywhere have adapted:
working remotely,
learning from home
and gathering virtually to stay close to family and friends.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Apple - WWDC 2020 Special Event Keynote</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3003100001/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3003100001/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript [&amp;ldquo;Daydreamer&amp;rdquo; by Aurora playing]
Good morning. And welcome to WWDC.
WWDC is an incredibly important event to Apple, our developers and our users.
It&amp;rsquo;s here that we bring some of our biggest innovations to life.
And we have not stopped innovating,
doing the work that will enrich people&amp;rsquo;s lives for years to come.
Because we&amp;rsquo;re all looking forward to a more hopeful tomorrow.
That&amp;rsquo;s why we believe it&amp;rsquo;s so important to have WWDC this year.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Columbia University - President Bollinger Gives His Final Commencement Address at Columbia University</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3002600001/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3002600001/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript Family and friends in attendance.
The president of the university, Lee C.
Bollinger.
It is my very, very great honor indeed.
Privilege and joy
to welcome you all here
on this very special morning
in this glorious academic setting
to this magnificent occasion.
I am especially sentimental today
as this will be my last commencement speech.
After serving more than two decades
as president of Columbia University,
I. I like to think</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Duke University - Duke Commencement Ceremony 2023</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3002800001/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3002800001/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript WELCOME TO DUKE UNIVERSITY&amp;rsquo;S 171ST COMMENCEMENT. PLEASE DIRECT YOUR ATTENTION TO
THE END OF THE FIELD AND WELCOME THE DUKE UNIVERSITY CLASS OF 2023.
NOW ENTERING THE STADIUM AND THROUGHOUT THE PROCESSIONAL MARCH ARE THE CANDIDATE&amp;rsquo;S
DEGREES FROM ARTS AND SCIENCES WHO ARE JOINED THIS YEAR WHO ARE JOINED BY THE UNIVERSITY.
ENTERING NOW ARE THE CANDIDATES FROM THE SCHOOL OF ENGINEERING.
NEXT PLEASE WELCOME THE CANDIDATES FROM THE SANFORD SCHOOL OF PUBLIC POLICY.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Harvard Law School - Michelle Yeoh addresses the Harvard Law School Class of 2023</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3002100001/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3002100001/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript Wow. What an introduction that was.
Good afternoon, and thank you,
Dean Manning, Dean Ball,
and Dean Bok for this rare and distinguished honor,
and congratulations to the class of 2023.
[APPLAUSE] What an incredible day.
Ladino Moore of an impressive academic journey.
Congratulations as well to parents, partners,
and family members of all the students here today.
I can only imagine the pride and joy you must</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Harvard Medical School - 2023 Class Day Student Address: Leen Al Kassab</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3003000001/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3003000001/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript It is my pleasure to now introduce
the next Harvard Medical School 2023 speaker, Leen Al Kassab.
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
For those of you who have not seen her featured
on Harvard&amp;rsquo;s Instagram feed, you may remember her
as Cannon&amp;rsquo;s birthday baker or more infamously
as the perpetrator of the Vandy 2019 kitchen fire.
[LAUGHTER]
Believe me when I say I was not amused at the time.
I still remember standing in the freezing cold when it was</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Harvard University - Tom Hanks delivers the Commencement Address | Harvard Commencement 2023</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3001900001/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3001900001/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript Now listen, it&amp;rsquo;s not fair,
but please don&amp;rsquo;t be embittered by this fact.
Now without having done a lick of work,
without having spent any time in class,
without once walking into that library
in order to have anything to do
with the graduating class of Harvard,
it&amp;rsquo;s faculty or it&amp;rsquo;s a distinguished alumni,
I make a good living playing someone who did.
(people laughing)
It&amp;rsquo;s the way of the world kids.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Johns Hopkins University - Volodymyr Zelenskyy Makes Surprise Speech at 2023 Johns Hopkins Commencement</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3002800001/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3002800001/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript We could not be prouder that he&amp;rsquo;s joining us today from Ukraine where he is leading the struggle
to keep his country free and Europe safe.
Welcome, President Zelenskyy, to Johns Hopkins.
(audience cheers and applauds)
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Thank you, Mrs. Applebaum,
for such a generous and yet brief introduction.
Mr. President Daniels,
Mr. Chairman of the board of Trustees, Forster,
dear students, faculty, parents, and guests</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Mark Rober Address to MIT Class of 2023</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3002200001/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3002200001/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript [CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
MARK ROBER: All right.
Good afternoon, esteemed faculty, distinguished guests,
relieved parents, bored siblings, confused pets,
and, of course, the 2023 graduating class of MIT.
[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
It is indeed a warm welcome.
It&amp;rsquo;s hot.
And you know what I love to do on a beautiful, sunny,
95-degree summer day?
Where a big black blanket.
[LAUGHTER]
At least I&amp;rsquo;m up here in the shade.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>NAU Social Media - Bill Gates NAU Commencement Address 2023: 5 things I wish I heard at the graduation I never had</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3002400001/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3002400001/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript It is my pleasure to bring before you today an outstanding
individual whose accomplishments and contributions warrant
special recognition from the academic community of Northern
Arizona University. Bill Gates is co-chair of the Bill and
Melinda Gates Foundation, founder of Breakthrough Energy
and cofounder of Microsoft through more than 20 years of
leadership.
At the Gates Foundation, he has worked on a broad spectrum of
global health and development issues, and through his private</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>New York University - 2023 NYU Commencement Speaker Sanna Marin, Prime Minister of Finland</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3002000001/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3002000001/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript I would like to introduce Alina Das, professor of Clinical Law,
and James Weldon Johnson, professor NYU School of Law,
who will present the candidate for Doctor of Humane Letters.
Will trustee and chair designate Evan Chesler
please escort the candidate to the lectern?
(audience cheering and applauding)
Sanna Marin, 46th Prime Minister of Finland. You personify the promise of Finland&amp;rsquo;s robust democracy
and demonstrate-
(audience cheering)
You demonstrate successful humanitarian governance.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>OWN - Oprah&#39;s Compelling Commencement Speech To TSU Class of 2023</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3002300001/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3002300001/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript Friends, faculty, family, and the Tennessee
State University class of 2023.
[CHEERING]
Who says you can&amp;rsquo;t go home again?
Because I&amp;rsquo;m back.
Dr. Glenda Glover is the reason why I&amp;rsquo;m here,
because she is relentless.
You actually&amp;ndash; you don&amp;rsquo;t know the meaning of no.
And she&amp;rsquo;s been here a decade and has
been asking me for a decade.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been to so many graduations since I have 20 daughters</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>University of Pennsylvania - Commencement 2023 - Liz Magill Speech</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3002700001/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3002700001/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript Thank you Reverend Howard. Hello amazing class of 2023.
(audience applauds)
This is my first time up here
and I am so proud that my first commencement
is with your class.
All right, before we go any further,
echoing Reverend Howard,
there&amp;rsquo;s something we&amp;rsquo;re called to do
to start this ceremony.
Today, of course, culminates your individual paths at Penn
but you didn&amp;rsquo;t walk alone.
Sorry, you just sat down, but graduates,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>YaleUniversity - Yale College 2023 Baccalaureate Ceremony</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3002500001/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3002500001/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript Welcome, everybody. Mr. President, Mr. Provost, Madam Secretary, college deans,
colleagues, friends, families, move all, members of the class of 2023.
Welcome to this day and congratulations. [Cheers and Applause]
I call on the University Chaplain. &amp;raquo; SHARON KUGLER: With deep
gratitude to the Quinnipiac ople for this land on ich stand, my beloved Yale Family, I
invite you to join me in the spirit of prayer. Almighty and loving God, you are</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>NVIDIA - NVIDIA Keynote at COMPUTEX 2023</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3001600002/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3001600002/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript (calm music plays)
[Voice Off-Screen] I am a translator, transforming text into creative discovery,
turning movement into animation
and infusing words with emotion.
(speaks foreign language)
[Voice Off-Screen] I am a healer,
exploring the building blocks that make us unique,
discovering new threats before they happen.
And searching for the cures to keep them at bay.
I am a visionary
creating new medical miracles
and unlocking the secrets of our sun</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Microsoft - Full Keynote | Satya Nadella at Microsoft Build 2023</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000900002/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000900002/</guid>
        <description>It&amp;rsquo;s like reading my mind.
It&amp;rsquo;s magic.
We&amp;rsquo;re innovating
at a scale like never before.
It takes what you prompt it with
and just runs with it.
Everything is linked.
Everything is easy to use.
We&amp;rsquo;re accelerating how fast we can deliver
solutions to our fans, to our business.
It takes the hands-on time
that the provider has to spend
with the computer
and puts that time back with the patient.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>C-SPAN - ChatGPT CEO Sam Altman Testifies Before Senate on AI Oversight</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3001300002/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3001300002/</guid>
        <description>OpenAI CEO Sam Altman, whose company created ChatGPT, was one of three artificial intelligence
experts to testify on oversight of the swiftly developing technology at a Senate Judiciary
Subcommittee hearing.
Mr. Altman stated that AI could, quote, cause significant harm to the world.
Here&amp;rsquo;s the rest of that hearing.
Welcome to the hearing of the Privacy, Technology, and the Law Subcommittee.
Thank my partner in this effort, Senator Hawley, Ranking Member, and I particularly</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Google - Google Keynote (Google I/O &#39;23)</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000300002/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000300002/</guid>
        <description>Google I/O &amp;lsquo;23
[Cheers and Applause]. &amp;raquo; Hello.
Hello. Hello.
Hello. Hello.
Hello. Hello.
Hello. Hello, everyone, my name is Dan
deacon. Thanks for coming here early.
It&amp;rsquo;s a real pleasure to be sharing the stage with some of
my all-time favorites, G-mail and Google Calendar.
So we&amp;rsquo;re going to &amp;ndash; I&amp;rsquo;m going to play some songs, and a lot of
the content is going to be made using Fanake and Bard and Music</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>DeepLearningAI - ChatGPT Prompt Engineering for Developers - Conclusion</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3001800009/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3001800009/</guid>
        <description>Congratulations on making it to the end of this short course.
In summary, in this short course you&amp;rsquo;ve
learned about two key principles for prompting. Write
clear and specific instructions, and when it&amp;rsquo;s appropriate, give the
model time to think. You also learned about iterative
prompt development and how having a
process to get to the prompt that&amp;rsquo;s right for
your application is key. And we went through a few capabilities of large</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>DeepLearningAI - ChatGPT Prompt Engineering for Developers - Chatbot</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3001800008/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3001800008/</guid>
        <description>One of the exciting things about a large
language model is you can use it to build a custom chatbot
with only a modest amount of effort. ChatGPT, the web interface,
is a way for you to have a conversational interface,
a conversation via a large language model. But one of the
cool things is you can also use a large language model to
build your custom chatbot to maybe play the role of an AI</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>DeepLearningAI - ChatGPT Prompt Engineering for Developers - Expanding</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3001800007/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3001800007/</guid>
        <description>Expanding is the task of taking a short piece of text,
such as a set of instructions or a list of topics,
and having the large language model generate a
longer piece of text, such as an email or
an essay about some topic. There are some great uses of this,
such as if you use a large language model as a brainstorming partner.
But I just also want to acknowledge that</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>DeepLearningAI - ChatGPT Prompt Engineering for Developers - Transforming</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3001800006/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3001800006/</guid>
        <description>Large language models are very good at transforming its input to a
different format, such as inputting a
piece of text in one language and transforming
it or translating it to a different language,
or helping with spelling and grammar corrections,
so taking as input a piece of text that may not be
fully grammatical and helping you to fix that up a bit,
or even transforming formats such as inputting HTML and</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>DeepLearningAI - ChatGPT Prompt Engineering for Developers - Inferring</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3001800005/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3001800005/</guid>
        <description>This next video is on inferring. I like to think
of these tasks where the model takes a text as input and
performs some kind of analysis. So this could be extracting labels,
extracting names, kind of understanding the
sentiment of a text, that kind of thing.
So if you want to extract a sentiment, positive or negative,
with a piece of text, in the traditional
machine learning workflow, you&amp;rsquo;d have to collect the label data set, train</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>DeepLearningAI - ChatGPT Prompt Engineering for Developers - Summarizing</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3001800004/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3001800004/</guid>
        <description>There&amp;rsquo;s so much text in today&amp;rsquo;s world, pretty much none of us have
enough time to read all the things we wish we had time to. So one
of the most exciting applications I&amp;rsquo;ve seen of
large language models is to use it to
summarise text. And this is something that I&amp;rsquo;m seeing multiple teams
build into multiple software applications. You can do this
in the Chat GPT Web Interface. I do this all</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>DeepLearningAI - ChatGPT Prompt Engineering for Developers - Iterative</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3001800003/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3001800003/</guid>
        <description>When I&amp;rsquo;ve been building applications with
large language models, I don&amp;rsquo;t think I&amp;rsquo;ve ever come to the prompt that
I ended up using in the final application on my first attempt.
And this isn&amp;rsquo;t what matters. As long as you have a good process
to iteratively make your prompt better, then you&amp;rsquo;ll
be able to come to something that works
well for the task you want to achieve.
You may have heard me say that when I train a machine learning model,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>DeepLearningAI - ChatGPT Prompt Engineering for Developers - Guidelines</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3001800002/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3001800002/</guid>
        <description>In this video, Isa will present some guidelines for prompting to
help you get the results that you want.
In particular, she&amp;rsquo;ll go over two key principles for how to write
prompts to prompt engineer effectively. And
a little bit later, when she&amp;rsquo;s going over the Jupyter Notebook examples, I&amp;rsquo;d
also encourage you to feel free to pause the video every
now and then to run the code yourself so you can see</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>DeepLearningAI - ChatGPT Prompt Engineering for Developers - Introduction</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3001800001/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3001800001/</guid>
        <description>Welcome to this course on ChatGPT prompt engineering
for developers. I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to have with
me Isa Fulford to teach this along with me. She
is a member of the technical staff of
OpenAI and had built the popular ChatGPT
retrieval plugin and a large part of the work has been teaching
people how to use LLM or large language
model technology in products. She&amp;rsquo;s also contributed to the
OpenAI cookbook that teaches people prompting.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Adobe - Adobe Summit 2023 Inspiration Keynote</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3001500002/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3001500002/</guid>
        <description>[Music]
I&amp;rsquo;m feeling over there
[Music]
thank you
please welcome president digital experience Anil chakravarthy
[Music] morning everybody good morning hope
everybody is doing great and welcome to day two of Summer it&amp;rsquo;s great to have all
of you back and I really hope yesterday I left you inspired about the
opportunity in front of all of us when it comes to driving growth from
experiences I&amp;rsquo;m really truly excited by The</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Adobe - Adobe Summit 2023 Opening Keynote</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3001500001/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3001500001/</guid>
        <description>[Music]
I&amp;rsquo;m feeling over there
[Music]
thank you [Music]
please welcome president digital experience Anil chakravarti
[Music]
good morning everybody oh look at that that&amp;rsquo;s awesome well welcome to Adobe
Summit everybody it&amp;rsquo;s amazing opening video isn&amp;rsquo;t it give a hand to our
creative team great video to set the stage
is wonderful it&amp;rsquo;s really wonderful to be back in person here after four years in
Las Vegas it&amp;rsquo;s awesome to feel the energy in this room all the leaders in</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>C-SPAN - TikTok CEO Shou Zi Chew testifies before Congress</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3001300001/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3001300001/</guid>
        <description>TIKTOK SIVS TESTIFYING &amp;ndash; ITS RELATIONSHIP TO CHINA.
YOU&amp;rsquo;RE WATCHING LIVE COVERAGE ON C-SPAN 3.
THIS MORNING ON CAPITOL HILL THE CEO OF TIKTOK, SHOU ZI CHEW
IS TESTIFYING ON THE SOCIAL MEDIA COMPANY&amp;rsquo;S DATA SECURITY
PRACTICES AND RELATIONSHIP WITH THE CHINESE GOVERNMENT.
IT IS EXPECTED TO TELL LAWMAKERS THAT BANNING THE APP
IN THE U.S. WOULD HURT AMERICAN BUSINESSES, AND THE ECONOMY.
YOU ARE WATCHING LIVE COVERAGE HERE ON C-SPAN 3.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Canva - Canva Create: Brand New Era</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3001700001/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3001700001/</guid>
        <description>Hello. I&amp;rsquo;m Susan. I&amp;rsquo;m Gurindji Woolwonga
With deep honor and respect
I asked to speak to the male spirits,
I asked to speak to the female spirits for permission for all of us together
on Gadigal land.
Hello, Sydney.
And hello to all
of those who are online
and to all of
those who are online, globally, around the world,
who are tuning in this afternoon.
My name is Susan Moylan Coombs</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>IGN - State of Unreal Livestream: A Glimpse of Next-Gen Gaming</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3001000001/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3001000001/</guid>
        <description>hey everyone it&amp;rsquo;s great to be back at GDC
you know back in 2020 as the pandemic was ramping up we were the last major
company to drop out of GDC we&amp;rsquo;re the first to go all remote and then we
headed into the pandemic it was a completely crazy time with thousands of
people working from around their homes but the company thrived and so I&amp;rsquo;d like
to go through some of the things that we&amp;rsquo;ve done since the since the last GDC</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>NVIDIA - GTC 2023 Keynote with NVIDIA CEO Jensen Huang</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3001600001/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3001600001/</guid>
        <description>For nearly four decades
Moore’s Law has been the governing dynamics of the computer industry
which in turn has impacted every industry.
The exponential performance increase at constant cost and power has slowed.
Yet, computing advance has gone to lightspeed.
The warp drive engine is accelerated computing and the energy source is AI.
The arrival of accelerated computing and AI is timely
as industries tackle powerful dynamics
sustainability
generative AI</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>CNBC - Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang On How His Big Bet On A.I. Is Finally Paying Off - Full Interview</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3001400001/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3001400001/</guid>
        <description>Jensen, thank you so much for being here today.
And I want to get started just with a question that is
really basic, but I think chips have been in the
ecosystem a lot more lately, and there&amp;rsquo;s people
who probably didn&amp;rsquo;t even really know what a
semiconductor was a few years ago.
Can you give me a very basic definition of what
Nvidia is?
Wow, that&amp;rsquo;s an easy question.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>ABC News - OpenAI CEO, CTO on risks and how AI will reshape society</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3001200001/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3001200001/</guid>
        <description>So you are the CEO of OpenAI, 37 years old.
Your company is the maker of ChatGPT,
which has taken the world by storm.
Why do you think it&amp;rsquo;s captured people&amp;rsquo;s imagination?
I think people really have fun with it
and they see the possibility
and they see the ways this can help them,
this can inspire them,
this can help people create,
help people learn,
help people do all of these different tasks.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Microsoft - The Future of Work With AI - Microsoft March 2023 Event</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000900001/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000900001/</guid>
        <description>SATYA NADELLA: Welcome, and thank you for joining us.
We are here today to talk about something that&amp;rsquo;s very
fundamental to the human experience,
the way we work.
Most specifically, the way we work with computers.
In fact, we&amp;rsquo;ve been on this continuous journey
towards human-computer symbiosis for several decades.
Starting with Vannevar Bush&amp;rsquo;s vision that he
outlined in his seminal 1945 essay,
As We May Think.
Bush envisioned of futuristic device</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>OpenAI - GPT-4 Developer Livestream</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000800001/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000800001/</guid>
        <description>To the GPT-4 developer demo live stream.
Honestly, it&amp;rsquo;s kind of hard for me
to believe that this day is here.
OpenAI has been building this technology really
since we started the company.
But for the past two years, we&amp;rsquo;ve
been really focused on delivering GPT-4.
That started with rebuilding our entire training stack,
actually training the model, and then
seeing what it was capable of, trying to figure out</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>SXSW - OpenAI Co-founder on ChatGPT, DALL·E, and the Impact of Generative AI | SXSW 2023</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3001100001/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3001100001/</guid>
        <description>Hi guys. Happy South by. I feel like what a way to kick this off. One of the things I love about South by Southwest is I&amp;rsquo;ve been coming for the last decade, and we&amp;rsquo;re always talking about what&amp;rsquo;s the next big thing in tech, and I would say like artificial intelligence and chat GPT is like couldn&amp;rsquo;t be more relevant. So glad to be sitting here with you. How</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Wolfram - What is ChatGPT doing...and why does it work?</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000500001/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000500001/</guid>
        <description>okay hello everyone well usually in this time slot each week i do a science and technology q a for
kids and others which i&amp;rsquo;ve been doing for about three years now where i try and answer arbitrary
questions about science and technology today i thought i would do something slightly different
i just wrote a piece about chat gpt uh what&amp;rsquo;s it actually doing why does it work i thought i would</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Berkeley Haas - In the halls of power: Berkeley Haas economists on advising world leaders</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000600002/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000600002/</guid>
        <description>So, good afternoon everyone. I&amp;rsquo;m Ann Harrison.
I&amp;rsquo;m the dean of the Haas School of Business.
Welcome to today&amp;rsquo;s Dean&amp;rsquo;s Speaker Series.
As you may know, our flagship dean speaker series
invites preeminent business leaders to share their insights
with our community.
I am so excited today,
I cannot tell you how excited I am
to welcome two exceptional leaders
who are actually members of our very own faculty.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Apple Music - The Official Rihanna Interview</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000700001/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000700001/</guid>
        <description>14 number one songs.
14 number one songs. She has 9 Grammys.
She&amp;rsquo;s Oscar nominated, an entrepreneur, a visionary, and
this Sunday at the Apple Music Super Bowl LVII Halftime Show,
the wait is over!
It&amp;rsquo;s been 2,190 days. Dude.
Rihanna, we waited for you.
You it&amp;rsquo;s been over six years
since the nine-time Grammy winner &amp;ndash;
Rihanna. RiRi, where have you been?
We have been impatiently waiting for &amp;ndash;</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Google - Google presents: Live from Paris</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000300001/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000300001/</guid>
        <description>[MUSIC PLAYING]
PRABHAKAR RAGHAVAN: Hello, everyone.
Bonjour.
Welcome.
Before we start, I&amp;rsquo;d like to join
[? Mack ?] in acknowledging the tragic loss of life
and the widespread destruction from the earthquakes in Turkey
and Syria.
Our hearts are with the people there.
Now, we&amp;rsquo;re here in France, the birthplace
of seven giants of science and mathematics&amp;ndash;
Blaise Pascal, Pierre de Fermat, Joseph Fourier,
to name just a few on whose shoulders computer scientists</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Bing - Introducing your copilot for the web: AI-powered Bing and Microsoft Edge</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000200001/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000200001/</guid>
        <description>[MUSIC]
SATYA NADELLA: Hi, everyone.
Welcome. It&amp;rsquo;s great
to see all of you in Seattle in person.
We have an unbelievable show.
I see Scott Guthrie even wore his red shirt.
We welcome you to
the Azure Kubernetes Container Service 2023 launch.
No, don&amp;rsquo;t worry. We&amp;rsquo;ll have some fun.
Scott is not coming up to show you
code onscreen anytime soon,
but look, it&amp;rsquo;s an exciting time in tech.
The broad contours of</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Berkeley Haas - Dean&#39;s Speaker Series | Jensen Huang Founder, President &amp; CEO, NVIDIA</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000600001/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000600001/</guid>
        <description>Well, good evening, everyone. Good evening.
I&amp;rsquo;m Ann Harrison.
I&amp;rsquo;m the Dean of Berkeley Haas. - Hi, Ann
And I&amp;rsquo;d like to welcome you to tonight&amp;rsquo;s Dean&amp;rsquo;s Speaker Series.
So I have the privilege of introducing you,
our speaker, very well known.
We&amp;rsquo;ve never had this venue as packed as it is tonight.
Jensen Huang.
So Jensen founded Nvidia in 1993.
He served since its inception as president,
chief executive officer,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Berkeley Haas - In the halls of power: Berkeley Haas economists on advising world leaders</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000600003/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000600003/</guid>
        <description>Good evening everyone, I&amp;rsquo;m Ann Harrison. I&amp;rsquo;m the Dean of the Haas School of Business.
Welcome to tonight&amp;rsquo;s event.
We are delighted to have guests
from the Graduate School of Journalism,
as well as distinguished guests
from our Greater Bay Area community.
Today is the third Chris Boskin Dean&amp;rsquo;s Speaker series,
which has been made possible
by a generous donation by Michael Boskin,
in honor of his wife.
Chris, would you like to stand up?</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Berkeley Haas - Dean&#39;s Speaker Series | Afsaneh Beschloss Founder &amp; CEO, RockCreek</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000600004/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000600004/</guid>
        <description>(audience chattering)
Good afternoon and welcome to today&amp;rsquo;s Dean&amp;rsquo;s Speaker Series on Sustainable Futures.
I am Michele de Nevers.
I&amp;rsquo;m the executive director of the Sustainability
and Climate Change Office here at Berkeley Haas,
and I am thrilled to introduce two
of the women leaders whom I most admire.
Today&amp;rsquo;s guest speaker in the Dean&amp;rsquo;s Speaker Series
is Afsaneh Beschloss.
Afsaneh is the founder and the CEO of RockCreek,
which is an investment firm</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Berkeley Haas - Dean&#39;s Speaker Series | Karan Singh, BS/BA 05, COO, Headspace Health/Co-Founder, Ginger</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000600005/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000600005/</guid>
        <description>Good evening, everyone. My name is Michael Martin,
and I am excited that we are kicking off the
Johnny Martin Mental Healthcare Challenge.
I&amp;rsquo;d be remiss if I didn&amp;rsquo;t go and give a shout-out
to the student chairs and team in this room before
we get things kicked off.
So, can I ask you guys to stand up for a brief second,
and get your applause?
(audience applauding)
We have a fantastic evening plan for you,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Berkeley Haas - Dean&#39;s Speaker Series | Mike Smith, MBA 98, General Partner &amp; Co-Founder, Footwork</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000600006/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000600006/</guid>
        <description>Good afternoon, everybody. I&amp;rsquo;m Ann Harrison, I&amp;rsquo;m the Dean
of the Haas School of Business.
Welcome to today&amp;rsquo;s Dean&amp;rsquo;s Speaker Series,
which today is co-sponsored by the Berkeley Culture Center.
I&amp;rsquo;m really truly excited to introduce today&amp;rsquo;s speaker
and a Haas alum, go Bears, Mike Smith.
Mike is a proud graduate of our full-time MBA program.
He currently serves as General Partner and Co-Founder
of Footwork, an early stage venture capital firm.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Berkeley Haas - Dean&#39;s Speaker Series | Kathryn Hall, Founder &amp; Co-Chair, Hall Capital Partners</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000600007/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000600007/</guid>
        <description>(audience chattering indistinctly)
Great. Good afternoon and welcome today&amp;rsquo;s Dean&amp;rsquo;s Speaker Series.
I&amp;rsquo;m Jillian Grennan.
I teach the SIF class here at Haas.
And it&amp;rsquo;s great pleasure today
to be able to introduce today&amp;rsquo;s guest speaker, Katie Hall.
Katie is the founder and co-chair of Hall Capital Partners.
Founded in 1994, HCP manages over 40 billion in investments
for foundations, endowments,
and large pools of family capital.
It&amp;rsquo;s one of the largest woman-led</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Berkeley Haas - Dean&#39;s Speaker Series | Mary Nichols, Vice Chair, California-China Climate Institute</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000600008/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000600008/</guid>
        <description>(people chattering)
Okay. So, good afternoon everyone,
and welcome to today&amp;rsquo;s Dean Speaker Series.
I am really absolutely delighted to welcome today&amp;rsquo;s speaker,
Mary Nichols.
Very exciting.
Mary has been described
as the most influential environmental regulator in history,
and she&amp;rsquo;s known as California&amp;rsquo;s #CleanAir guru.
She pushed forward clean air and decarbonization programs
under four California governors.
And as we know, where California goes,
there goes the United States.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Berkeley Haas - Dean&#39;s Speaker Series | Jen Wong, COO, Reddit</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000600009/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000600009/</guid>
        <description>Good afternoon everybody. I&amp;rsquo;m Anne Harrison.
I&amp;rsquo;m the dean of the Haas School of Business.
Welcome to today&amp;rsquo;s Dean Speaker series co-sponsored
by our MBA Student club,
Q at Haas.
(audience applauds)
So I am really delighted to introduce today&amp;rsquo;s speaker,
Jen Wong,
who is the Chief Operating Officer of Reddit.
In her role since 2018,
she oversees business strategy and related teams.
Jen has been instrumental in transforming Reddit,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Berkeley Haas - Dean&#39;s Speaker Series | Becoming a Changemaker</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000600010/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000600010/</guid>
        <description>(crowd chatters)
Good afternoon, welcome. My name is Erika Walker.
I am the senior assistant dean for instruction here
at the Haas School of Business,
and I&amp;rsquo;d like to welcome you on behalf of Dean Ann Harrison,
who&amp;rsquo;s traveling today, to our Dean Speaker Series.
I&amp;rsquo;m excited for this particular topic today.
It&amp;rsquo;s just really wonderful to be here on this occasion
to reflect on just how much change Alex</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Berkeley Haas - Dean&#39;s Speaker Series: Sustainable Futures | Pierre Breber, Vice President &amp; CFO, Chevron</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000600011/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000600011/</guid>
        <description>Well, good afternoon, everyone. And welcome to the first Dean&amp;rsquo;s Speaker Series
of the academic year.
Our event today is co-sponsored by BERC,
which is the student led
Berkeley Energy and Resources Collaborative.
It&amp;rsquo;s the largest of its kind in the United States.
Anybody here who&amp;rsquo;s a member of BERC raise your hands.
Woohoo, woo.
So it&amp;rsquo;s also co-sponsored by the Energy Institute at Haas,
which brings together the largest concentration</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Berkeley Haas - Haas MBA Commencement Ceremony 2022</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000600012/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000600012/</guid>
        <description>(&amp;ldquo;Pomp and Circumstance&amp;rdquo;)
(&amp;ldquo;Pomp and Circumstance&amp;rdquo; continues)
(crowd chattering)
[Ann] Yeah, I mean, they&amp;rsquo;re down there.
[Students In Crowd] We love you!
(crowd cheering)
(crowd chanting)
Ladies and gentlemen, distinguished guests, family and friends of the graduates,
and members of the graduating class of 2022,
(graduates cheering)
on behalf of our esteemed faculty and staff,
I welcome you
to the Berkeley Haas MBA Commencement Ceremony.
(crowd cheering)
I&amp;rsquo;m Ann Harrison, Dean of the Haas School.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Berkeley Haas - Haas Undergraduate Program: 2022 Commencement</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000600013/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000600013/</guid>
        <description>(graduation music playing)
Members of the faculty and staff, family and friends of the graduates,
and members of the graduating class of 2022.
(audience cheering)
Welcome to the Undergraduate Commencement Ceremony
for the Haas School of Business.
(audience cheering)
I&amp;rsquo;m Ann Harrison, Dean of the Haas School.
It is my great pleasure to officiate at today&amp;rsquo;s ceremony,
the first in-person undergraduate commencement
we have held since 2019.
(audience cheering)
You don&amp;rsquo;t know how happy that makes me.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Berkeley Haas - 2020/2021 FTMBA Commencement</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000600014/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000600014/</guid>
        <description>(upbeat music)
(orchestral music playing)
So, we have waited longer than we ever thought possible to say the following words;
distinguish guests, members of the faculty and staff
and friends of the graduates
and members of the graduating classes of 2020
and 2021, on behalf of our esteemed faculty and staff,
I welcome you to Berkeley Haas
full-time MBA commencement ceremony.
(audience cheering)
I&amp;rsquo;m Ann Harrison, Dean of the Haas School,</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Berkeley Haas - Dean&#39;s Speaker Series | Indra Nooyi, Former Chairwoman and CEO, PepsiCo</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000600015/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000600015/</guid>
        <description>(audience murmuring)
Good afternoon everyone. I&amp;rsquo;m Ann Harrison.
I&amp;rsquo;m the Dean of the Haas School of Business.
Welcome to today&amp;rsquo;s Dean&amp;rsquo;s Speaker Series
cosponsored by the Berkeley Culture Initiative.
This is an incredible honor to introduce today&amp;rsquo;s speaker,
Indra Nooyi.
There is so much that I could say about Indra
as the first woman of color and immigrant
to run a Fortune 50 company,
Nooyi is certainly among
the world&amp;rsquo;s most admired business leaders.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Berkeley Haas - Dean&#39;s Speaker Series | Michael Smith, MBA 86, Chief Marketing Officer, NPR</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000600016/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000600016/</guid>
        <description>(people murmur)
Good afternoon, everyone. Sorry.
I&amp;rsquo;m Ann Harrison.
I&amp;rsquo;m the dean at the Haas School of Business.
Welcome to today&amp;rsquo;s Dean Speaker Series.
I&amp;rsquo;m really excited to introduce and welcome back
today&amp;rsquo;s speaker Michael Smith who&amp;rsquo;s our MBA,
one of our own from 1986.
Michael earned his MBA from Berkeley in marketing
and finance after earning his bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in science,
technology and society from that school
that shall not be named, Stanford University.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Berkeley Haas - Dean&#39;s Speaker Series/AmpEquity Speaker Series | Yamini Rangan, MBA 03, CEO, HubSpot</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000600017/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000600017/</guid>
        <description>All right, good afternoon, everyone. Nice to see you all here.
My name is Courtney Chandler.
I&amp;rsquo;m the senior assistant dean, chief strategy,
and operating officer here at the Haas School of Business
and I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to be here.
On behalf of Dean Ann Harrison,
who is traveling today,
I&amp;rsquo;d like to welcome you to our today&amp;rsquo;s dean speaker series,
which is co-sponsored by the AmpEquity series.
I am really, really thrilled to be introducing today&amp;rsquo;s guest</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Berkeley Haas - Dean&#39;s Speaker Series | Dan Schulman, President &amp; CEO, PayPal</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000600018/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000600018/</guid>
        <description>(audience chatters)
Good afternoon, everyone, and welcome to today&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Dean&amp;rsquo;s Speaker Series.&amp;rdquo;
I am really excited
to introduce today&amp;rsquo;s guest, Dan Schulman.
We are really thrilled that Dan is joining us
and even more thrilled that he is joining us here in person.
Thank you so much, Dan.
(audience applauds)
(Ann claps)
Dan became the president and the CEO of PayPal in 2014.
His current leadership role follows three decades</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Berkeley Haas - Dean&#39;s Speaker Series | General Stanley McChrystal, Founder &amp; CEO, McChrystal Group</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000600019/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000600019/</guid>
        <description>Good afternoon, everybody. I&amp;rsquo;m Ann Harrison.
I&amp;rsquo;m the Dean at the Haas School of Business.
Welcome on this beautiful sunny day.
This is a very special Dean&amp;rsquo;s Speaker Series.
It is co-sponsored by the Haas Veterans Club.
I am deeply honored to introduce General Stanley McChrystal,
who is today&amp;rsquo;s distinguished speaker.
General McChrystal was educated at West Point,
the US Naval War College,
and Harvard&amp;rsquo;s John F. Kennedy School of Government.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Berkeley Haas - Dean&#39;s Speaker Series | Vanessa Morrison, BA, President of Streaming, Walt Disney Studios</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000600020/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000600020/</guid>
        <description>Good afternoon everybody, I&amp;rsquo;m Ann Harrison. I&amp;rsquo;m the Dean at the Haas School of Business.
Welcome everyone to the first Dean&amp;rsquo;s Speaker Series
of our spring semester.
I&amp;rsquo;m really excited and honored to introduce today&amp;rsquo;s speaker
and Berkeley alum, Vanessa Morrison.
Vanessa graduated with a bachelor&amp;rsquo;s in rhetoric
from UC Berkeley class of &amp;lsquo;90.
Today, Vanessa serves as president streaming
for Walt Disney Studios Motion Picture Production.
In this role, she has the responsibility</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Berkeley Haas - Dean&#39;s Speaker Series | Leigh Steinberg, Chairman and Founder of Steinberg Sports and Entertainment</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000600021/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000600021/</guid>
        <description>Good evening, everyone. I&amp;rsquo;m Ann Harrison.
I&amp;rsquo;m the dean at the Haas School of Business.
Welcome to today&amp;rsquo;s Dean&amp;rsquo;s Speaker Series
co-sponsored by the Haas Healthcare Association,
John E. Martin Mental Healthcare Challenge.
I&amp;rsquo;m honored to introduce and welcome back to campus
a double bear in political science and law, Leigh Steinberg.
(audience applauds)
As chairman and founder
of Steinberg Sports and Entertainment,
Leigh is best known for his work building athletes</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Berkeley Haas - EWMBA Commencement 2021</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000600022/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000600022/</guid>
        <description>[Laughter]
distinguished guests members of the faculty and staff
family and friends of the graduates and members of the graduating classes of
2020 and 2021 on
on behalf of our esteemed faculty and staff i welcome you to the berkeley haas
evening and weekend mba commencement ceremony
i&amp;rsquo;m anne harrison dean of the high school it&amp;rsquo;s my duty and great pleasure
to officiate at today&amp;rsquo;s ceremony to our evening and weekend mba graduates</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>MrBeast - I Survived 50 Hours In Antarctica</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/3000100001/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/3000100001/</guid>
        <description>Video Transcript - We just landed in Antarctica,
and we&amp;rsquo;re gonna survive the next 50 hours here.
We&amp;rsquo;re literally at the bottom of the globe,
at the coldest place on Earth. (bell dings)
- Can&amp;rsquo;t wait to freeze to death.
(plane engine hums) - And there goes the plane.
Right, all right, see you later.
And now that that plane has left, boys,
there&amp;rsquo;s no way out for the next 50 hours.</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
