<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Now You're Asking with Marian Keyes and Tara Flynn on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/now-youre-asking-with-marian-keyes-and-tara-flynn/</link><description>Recent content in Now You're Asking with Marian Keyes and Tara Flynn on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 07:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/now-youre-asking-with-marian-keyes-and-tara-flynn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Comb Over Problem | Now You're Asking with Marian Keyes and Tara Flynn</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4393620001/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4393620001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Your close friend is doing a bad job at disguising his baldness – people are noticing and making cruel comments… what should you do? You know your relationship is over but, if you leave, your partner’s life might fall apart… what should you do? You’ve been asked to a party and the hosts are now asking you to help pay for it… what should you do? Modern dilemmas tackled with wisdom, grace and trademark good humour by Marian and Tara.</description></item><item><title>The Good Cup of Tea Problem | Now You're Asking with Marian Keyes and Tara Flynn</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4393620002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4393620002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is my son gay? What does it even mean when you’re told to “be kind to yourself”? Should I have a baby because I am lonely? All this and possibly our most controversial response to date when a listener confesses to losing the knack of brewing a good cup of tea. Marian and Tara sit up straight and set to tackling their in-tray of Asks. Marian Keyes is a multi-award-winning writer, with a total of over 30 million of her books sold to date in 33 languages.</description></item><item><title>The Package Holiday Problem | Now You're Asking with Marian Keyes and Tara Flynn</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4393620003/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 08:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4393620003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Your new boyfriend wants to go on a package holiday by the sea, but you’d rather be hiking in the mountains – is it time to dump him? Your friends are telling you to make more of an effort but you’re happy in your old clothes – is it time to smarten up? And you’re a working mum of a toddler but you find yourself ‘zoning out’ when he’s in your care – is it time to worry?</description></item><item><title>The Squirrel Problem | Now You're Asking with Marian Keyes and Tara Flynn</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4393620004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4393620004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Content warning - this show contains rodents! Squirrels, to be precise. What can you do to keep them away? Marian and Tara also tackle dealing with prejudice around autism and what to do if you'd rather not go to another birthday party.
Marian Keyes is a multi award-winning writer, with a total of over 30 million of her books sold to date in 33 languages. Her close friend Tara Flynn is an actress, comedian and writer.</description></item><item><title>The 'Is He the One?' Problem | Now You're Asking with Marian Keyes and Tara Flynn</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4393620005/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4393620005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is it ever possible to know whether your partner is 'The One'? Can you go to church but avoid drinking the Kool Aid? Should men shave more than the hair on their chin? It's safe to say there is no subject that Marian and Tara won't tackle in their quest to solve their listener's conundrums.
Marian Keyes is a multi award-winning writer, with a total of over 30 million of her books sold to date in 33 languages.</description></item><item><title>Christmas Special | Now You're Asking with Marian Keyes and Tara Flynn</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4393620006/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4393620006/</guid><description>Podcast Description The holiday season is not easy for everyone. Some people love it, some can’t stand it and others want to enjoy some downtime with the family - if only it wasn’t their family, in their house, at this time of the year.
Demanding guests arrive - but whose holiday traditions should you follow? A family member monopolises the season - should you head over to her house - again?</description></item><item><title>The Bully Father-in-Law Problem | Now You're Asking with Marian Keyes and Tara Flynn</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4393620007/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4393620007/</guid><description>Podcast Description A woman bullied by her father-in-Law, a grieving widow and an anxious midwifery student get help from Marian Keyes and Tara Flynn in the popular advice series. As ever, life is addressed from every angle, with trademark wisdom and good humour, by our hosts.
From dilemmas about life, love and grief, to the perils of laundry or knowing what to say at a boring dinner, we’ll find out what Marian and Tara would recommend - which might not solve the problem exactly, but will make us all feel a bit better.</description></item><item><title>The Workplace Crush Problem | Now You're Asking with Marian Keyes and Tara Flynn</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4393620008/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4393620008/</guid><description>Podcast Description So - you fancy your boss but he wants to keep it casual? You've had second thoughts about joining a book club? You're convinced your dog seems to hate you? Life is addressed from every angle, with their trademark wisdom and good humour, by Marian Keyes and Tara Flynn.
From dilemmas about life, love and grief, to the perils of laundry or knowing what to say at a boring dinner, we’ll find out what Marian and Tara would recommend - which might not solve the problem exactly, but will make us all feel a bit better.</description></item><item><title>The Ugly Present Problem | Now You're Asking with Marian Keyes and Tara Flynn</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4393620009/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4393620009/</guid><description>Podcast Description What on earth should you do when your grandparents give you a hideous present? Is my sister subject to controlling behaviour from her new girlfriend? Should our 46-year-old male ‘asker’ get botox? All these questions have been sent in by our listeners and are given the Marian and Tara treatment in the latest instalment of their popular advice podcast.
The first series was welcomed by listeners and critics.
"</description></item><item><title>The Overburdened Listener Problem | Now You're Asking with Marian Keyes and Tara Flynn</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4393620010/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4393620010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do your family and friends always seem to bring their problems to you? Why do men so often need telling? You’re a long way from home - should you stay or should you go? All these subjects have been sent in by our listeners and are given the Marian and Tara treatment in the latest instalment of their popular advice podcast.
The first series was welcomed by listeners and critics.</description></item><item><title>The Invisible Sibling Problem | Now You're Asking with Marian Keyes and Tara Flynn</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4393620011/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4393620011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you reached an age where it seems everything is beginning to annoy you? What should you do if you’re a sibling who is invisible to your family? How do you deal with a one-night stand who’s now ignoring you at the school gates? All these subjects have been sent in by our listeners and are given the Marian and Tara treatment in the latest instalment of their popular advice podcast.</description></item><item><title>The Boring Husband Problem | Now You're Asking with Marian Keyes and Tara Flynn</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4393620012/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 19:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4393620012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Has your husband suddenly become boring? What should you do if you’re invited to a swingers party - or, perhaps more pressingly, if you’ve not been invited? Can holiday romances ever work out – even ones in Switzerland? All these subjects have been sent in by our listeners and are given the Marian and Tara treatment in the latest instalment of their popular advice podcast.
The first series was welcomed by listeners and critics.</description></item><item><title>The Love Language Problem | Now You're Asking with Marian Keyes and Tara Flynn</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4393620013/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 18:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4393620013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do you know what ‘love language’ is – and what’s yours? Do you envy people, the homes, lifestyles and careers? Have you experienced strategic untruths on someone’s dating profile? All these subjects have been sent in by our listeners and are given the Marian and Tara treatment in the latest instalment of their popular advice podcast.
The first series was welcomed by listeners and critics.
"Both are warm and kind enough to not only be funny but also offer genuinely thoughtful, if left-field, advice.</description></item><item><title>The Pockets Problem | Now You're Asking with Marian Keyes and Tara Flynn</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4393620014/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 18:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4393620014/</guid><description>Podcast Description What happens when a neighbour takes your pizza ‘by mistake’? Or you’ve accidentally ended up paying for a friend’s childcare for too long? If your brother brings home an old flame – should you say something? And what should you do if your coat doesn’t have pockets? All these subjects are given the Marian and Tara treatment in the latest instalment of their popular advice podcast.
The first series was welcomed by listeners and critics.</description></item><item><title>The Hot Tub Problem | Now You're Asking with Marian Keyes and Tara Flynn</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4393620015/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 18:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4393620015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Does being shown baby pictures in the supermarket drive you up the wall? Has someone given you unsolicited advice about your weight? What should you do if you’re invited to try out a neighbour’s hot tub but you’d really rather not? All these subjects are given the Marian and Tara treatment in the latest instalment of their popular advice podcast.
The first series was welcomed by listeners and critics.</description></item><item><title>The Thong Problem | Now You're Asking with Marian Keyes and Tara Flynn</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4393620016/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 18:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4393620016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Thongs, personal grooming, rights of way across fields and 'going non-contact' get the Now You're Asking treatment in the first episode of this new series with Marian Keyes and Tara Flynn addressing real life problems sent in by their listeners. The first series was welcomed by listeners and critics. "Both are warm and kind enough to not only be funny but also offer genuinely thoughtful, if left-field, advice." (Miranda Sawyer, The Observer) "</description></item><item><title>The High School Problem | Now You're Asking with Marian Keyes and Tara Flynn</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4393620017/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4393620017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Marian and Tara tackle an over-familiar flatmate, a caustic mother-in-law, love at a distance and high school anxieties with trademark kindness and good humour in the final episode of the series.
Marian Keyes is a multi award-winning writer, with a total of over 30 million of her books sold to date in 33 languages. Her close friend Tara Flynn is an actress, comedian and writer. Together, these two friends have been through a lot, and now want to use their considerable life experience to help solve your biggest - and smallest - problems.</description></item><item><title>The Shoplifter Problem | Now You're Asking with Marian Keyes and Tara Flynn</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4393620018/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4393620018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Marian and Tara tackle front-fastening bras, anxiety, conspiracy theorists and a shoplifting mother with trademark kindness and good humour.
Marian Keyes is a multi award-winning writer, with a total of over 30 million of her books sold to date in 33 languages. Her close friend Tara Flynn is an actress, comedian and writer. Together, these two friends have been through a lot, and now want to use their considerable life experience to help solve your biggest - and smallest - problems.</description></item><item><title>The Co-dependency Problem | Now You're Asking with Marian Keyes and Tara Flynn</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4393620019/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4393620019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Marian and Tara tackle the stresses of IVF, co-dependent relationships, red necks on Zoom and "window shopping" (not the good kind) with trademark kindness and good humour.
Marian Keyes is a multi award-winning writer, with a total of over 30 million of her books sold to date in 33 languages. Her close friend Tara Flynn is an actress, comedian and writer. Together, these two friends have been through a lot, and now want to use their considerable life experience to help solve your biggest - and smallest - problems.</description></item><item><title>The Cardboard Walls Problem | Now You're Asking with Marian Keyes and Tara Flynn</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4393620020/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4393620020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Marian and Tara tackle listeners’ issues with noisy neighbours, an estranged sister and advise on the merits of wedding extravagance with trademark kindness and good humour.
Marian Keyes is a multi award-winning writer, with a total of over 30 million of her books sold to date in 33 languages. Her close friend Tara Flynn is an actress, comedian and writer. Together, these two friends have been through a lot, and now want to use their considerable life experience to help solve your biggest - and smallest - problems.</description></item><item><title>The Bacon Sandwich Problem | Now You're Asking with Marian Keyes and Tara Flynn</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4393620021/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4393620021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Marian and Tara tackle listeners’ issues with the menopause, frisky dreams and a troubling bacon sandwich with trademark good humour.
Marian Keyes is a multi award-winning writer, with a total of over 30 million of her books sold to date in 33 languages. Her close friend Tara Flynn is an actress, comedian and writer. Together, these two friends have been through a lot, and now want to use their considerable life experience to help solve your biggest - and smallest - of problems.</description></item><item><title>The Child Care Problem | Now You're Asking with Marian Keyes and Tara Flynn</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4393620022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4393620022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Marian and Tara tackle jealousy, code switching, frizzy hair and wandering accents and much more.
Marian Keyes is a multi award-winning writer, with a total of over 30 million of her books sold to date in 33 languages. Her close friend Tara Flynn is an actress, comedian and writer. Together, these two friends have been through a lot, and now want to use their considerable life experience to help solve their listeners' biggest - and smallest - problems.</description></item><item><title>The Surprise Party Problem | Now You're Asking with Marian Keyes and Tara Flynn</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4393620023/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4393620023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Marian and Tara tackle awkward in-laws, unrequited love and a surprise party, swipe fatigue, ageing parents and much more.
Marian Keyes is a multi award-winning writer, with a total of over 30 million of her books sold to date in 33 languages. Her close friend Tara Flynn is an actress, comedian and writer. Together, they have been through a lot, and now want to use their considerable life experience to help solve your biggest - and smallest - of problems.</description></item><item><title>The ‘Resting Bitch Face’ Problem | Now You're Asking with Marian Keyes and Tara Flynn</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4393620024/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4393620024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Marian and Tara discuss serial bad-boy dating, what your face says about you, a missing mojo, personal grooming issues and much more.
Marian Keyes is a multi award-winning writer, with a total of over 30 million of her books sold to date in 33 languages. Her close friend Tara Flynn is an actress, comedian and writer. Together, these two friends have been through a lot, and now want to use their considerable life experience to help solve your biggest - and smallest - problems.</description></item><item><title>The Badly-Dressed Boyfriend Problem | Now You're Asking with Marian Keyes and Tara Flynn</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4393620025/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4393620025/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s instalment, Marian and Tara tackle a badly-dressed boyfriend, a weighted blanket, the problem with noisy eaters and much more.
Marian Keyes is a multi award-winning writer, with a total of over 30 million of her books sold to date in 33 languages. Her close friend Tara Flynn is an actress, comedian and writer. Together, these two friends have been through a lot, and now want to use their considerable life experience to help solve your biggest - and smallest - of their listeners' problems.</description></item><item><title>The Pink Flamingo Problem | Now You're Asking with Marian Keyes and Tara Flynn</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4393620026/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4393620026/</guid><description>Podcast Description In their first episode, Marian and Tara tackle a problem pink flamingo, a messy daughter and a contested will.
Marian Keyes is a multi-award-winning writer, with a total of over 30 million of her books sold to date in 33 languages. Her close friend Tara Flynn is an actress, comedian and writer. Together, these two friends have been through a lot, and now want to use their considerable life experience to help solve the biggest - and smallest - of their listeners' problems.</description></item><item><title>Welcome to Now You’re Asking with Marian Keyes and Tara Flynn | Now You're Asking with Marian Keyes and Tara Flynn</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/4393620027/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 12:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/4393620027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Marian Keyes and Tara Flynn want to solve your problems. Or try, at the very least. Join Marian and Tara as they dig into their own life experience to find advice for all of us.
Marian Keyes is a multi award-winning writer, with over 30 million of her books sold to date in 33 languages. Her close friend Tara Flynn is an actress, comedian, and writer. Together, these two friends have been through a lot, and now want to use their own life experience to help solve your biggest - and smallest - problems.</description></item></channel></rss>