<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>If Books Could Kill on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/if-books-could-kill/</link><description>Recent content in If Books Could Kill on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/if-books-could-kill/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Identity Trap | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510001/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;quot;There are two kinds of political scientists: The types who deal with noisy data and post on Twitter with a bunch of caveats. And then there are the types who write books about identity politics.&amp;quot;
Where to find us: TwitterPeter&amp;apos;s other podcast, 5-4Mike&amp;apos;s other podcast, Maintenance PhaseSources:
Sam Huneke&amp;apos;s &amp;quot;Yascha Mounk’s Woke Straw Man&amp;quot;Jacob T. Levy&amp;apos;s &amp;quot;The Defense of Liberty Can’t Do Without Identity Politics&amp;quot;Olúfẹ́mi O. Táíwò&amp;apos;s &amp;quot;Elite Capture&amp;quot;Aaron Huertas&amp;apos;s &amp;quot;We Need to Talk About Reactionary Centrists&amp;quot;Mary Lin Elementary under federal investigationParents refute claims of segregation at Mary Lin Elementary SchoolSchool Segregation in Metropolitan Regions, 1970–200060 Years After BrownSchool choice and racial segregation in US schoolsStudent Population Has Significantly Diversified, But Many Schools Remain Divided Along Racial, Ethnic, and Economic LinesU.</description></item><item><title>Pundit Portraits: Kathleen Parker and Chris Cillizza [TEASER] | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510002/</guid><description>Podcast Description To hear the rest of the episode, support us on Patreon:
https://www.patreon.com/IfBooksPod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510003/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510003/</guid><description>Podcast Description You stare, mouth agape, at the bookstore display. It’s a self-help book, but with curse words in the title?! This must be a revolutionary new framework, not simply the same dull, reactionary ideas repackaged as hip and new.
Support us on Patreon:
https://www.patreon.com/IfBooksPod
Where to find us: TwitterPeter&amp;apos;s other podcast, 5-4Mike&amp;apos;s other podcast, Maintenance PhaseSources:
The Subtle Art of Not Giving a Fuck (Blog Post)Where A is Ordinary: The Evolution of American College and University Grading, 1940-2009We’ve Been Handing Out Participation Trophies for 100 Years</description></item><item><title>The 48 Laws of Power | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510004/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1996, a frustrated screenwriter got a fellowship in Italy. Twenty years later, Beyoncé released &amp;quot;Lemonade.&amp;quot; Content warning: This episode includes a mention of suicide.
Support us on Patreon:
https://www.patreon.com/IfBooksPod
Where to find us: TwitterPeter&amp;apos;s other podcast, 5-4Mike&amp;apos;s other podcast, Maintenance PhaseSources:
Rebecca Solnit’s “A Paradise Built in Hell”Kelly Link&amp;apos;s &amp;quot;White Cat, Black Dog&amp;quot;The Half-Century in Bullshit: On Peter Bogdanovich’s “Paper Moon” and Robert Greene’s “The 48 Laws of Power”A Book of Anecdotes, 1957</description></item><item><title>The "Organized Retail Crime" Panic [TEASER] | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Retailers have been sounding the alarm about a shoplifting epidemic driven by organized criminal syndicates. In a shocking twist, it turns out that their story is mostly made up. Join us as Peter tries to figure out where this panic originated and as Mike finally comes clean about his criminal past.
To hear the rest of the show, support us on Patreon:
https://www.patreon.com/IfBooksPod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>San Fransicko | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510006/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;apos;re tackling &amp;quot;San Fransicko: Why Progressives Ruin Cities,&amp;quot; a book that dares to ask: What if everything that experts think about homelessness is wrong, and everything that one crank on Twitter thinks about homelessness is right?
Thanks to Ned Resnikoff for helping us with the research for this episode!
Support us on Patreon:
https://www.patreon.com/IfBooksPod
Where to find us: TwitterPeter&amp;apos;s other podcast, 5-4Mike&amp;apos;s other podcast, Maintenance PhaseSources:</description></item><item><title>The 4-Hour Workweek | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever wanted to escape the grind and follow your dreams? This week we&amp;apos;re discussing &amp;quot;The 4-Hour Workweek,&amp;quot; which reveals that all you need is a plan, a willingness to take risks and a modestly sized fraud operation built on Third World labor.
Support us on Patreon:
https://www.patreon.com/IfBooksPod
Where to find us: TwitterPeter&amp;apos;s other podcast, 5-4Mike&amp;apos;s other podcast, Maintenance PhaseSources:
The Fraud and the Four-Hour WorkweekRevisiting &amp;quot;The 4-Hour Workweek&amp;quot;New!</description></item><item><title>The Clinton E-Mail Scandal [TEASER] | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510008/</guid><description>Podcast Description But her e-mails! Michael explains the non-scandal that captivated the mainstream media in 2016 while Peter attempts to sow the podcast with anti-Hillary sentiment.
To hear the rest of the show, support us on Patreon:
https://www.patreon.com/IfBooksPod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>God And Man At Yale | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Oops all grievance.
Support us on Patreon:
https://www.patreon.com/IfBooksPod
Where to find us: TwitterPeter&amp;apos;s other podcast, 5-4Mike&amp;apos;s other podcast, Maintenance PhaseSources:
No Ivory Tower : Mccarthyism And The UniversitiesThe Fire Is Upon UsThe Conservative Intellectual Movement in America Since 1945The Passion of William F. Buckley: Academic Freedom, Conspiratorial Conservatism, and the Rise of the Postwar RightWhy Are Professors Liberal and Why Do Conservatives Care?Compromised Campus: The Collaboration of Universities with the Intelligence Community, 1945-1955Debunking a Longstanding Myth About William F.</description></item><item><title>'On Bullsh*t' and the Pundit Industrial Complex [TEASER] | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510010/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510010/</guid><description>Podcast Description For this month&amp;apos;s bonus episode we dissected Harry Frankfurt&amp;apos;s gloriously brief bestseller and applied the concept to our favorite op-ed page. To hear the rest of the show, support us on Patreon:
https://www.patreon.com/IfBooksPod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Liberal Fascism | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who poses the greatest threat to democracy? Is it the movement that openly identifies with the symbols, goals and policies of fascist governments? Or is it the median bureaucrat at the Department of Health and Human Services? In 2008, a National Review nepo-baby attempted to answer this vexing question.
Support us on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IfBooksPod
Where to find us: TwitterPeter&amp;apos;s other podcast, 5-4Mike&amp;apos;s other podcast, Maintenance PhaseSources:
History News Network: A Symposium on Jonah Goldberg’s Liberal FascismThe Nature of FascismHow Fascism Works: The Politics of Us and ThemThe Anatomy of FascismMussolini and Fascism: The View From AmericaThe Return of Old-Fashioned Racism to White Americans’ Partisan Preferences in the Early Obama EraIdentity Crisis: The 2016 Presidential Campaign and the Battle for the Meaning of AmericaWhat Hillary Rodham Clinton Really Said About Children’s Rights and Child PolicyThe Ku Klux Klan in the City, 1915-1930A campus takeover that symbolized an era of change Thanks to Mindseye for our theme song!</description></item><item><title>Are The Straights OK [TEASER] | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510012/</guid><description>Podcast Description In our &amp;quot;Rules&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Game&amp;quot; episodes we didn&amp;apos;t get a chance to dissect the phenomenon of online dating (i.e. describe our worst dates and read cringe profiles out loud to each other), so that is what we are doing on today&amp;apos;s bonus episode. To hear the rest of the show, support us on Patreon:
https://www.patreon.com/IfBooksPod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>BONUS: Conservatives vs. Pride Month | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lots of subscribers asked us to release last month&amp;apos;s bonus episode in full so here it is! Share it with the conservatives, the boomers and the Satanists in your life.
Support us on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IfBooksPod
Where to find us: TwitterPeter&amp;apos;s other podcast, 5-4Mike&amp;apos;s other podcast, Maintenance PhaseThanks to Mindseye for our theme song!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Rules | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510014/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510014/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1995 a bestselling book proposed a simple dating strategy for women: Lose weight, wear bright colors and become a completely different person for the rest of your life.
Thanks to Moira Donegan for helping us with this episode! Support us on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IfBooksPod
Where to find us: TwitterPeter&amp;apos;s other podcast, 5-4Mike&amp;apos;s other podcast, Maintenance PhaseSources:
From Front Porch to Back Seat: Courtship in Twentieth-Century America Taffy Brodesser-Akner’s essay, “Stuff Your ‘Rules’” The More Things Change: The Rules And Late Eighteenth‐Century Conduct Books For Women Shrinking Violets and Caspar Milquetoasts: Shyness and Heterosexuality from the Roles of the Fifties to &amp;quot;The Rules&amp;quot; of the Nineties From Mountain Peak to Total Woman: An Evolutionary History of Pre-feminist Dating Advice The Mating Game: How Gender Still Shapes How We Date by Ellen Lamont So Many Rules, So Little Time Abiding by The Rules: Instructing Women in Relationships What leads to romantic attraction: similarity, reciprocity, security, or beauty?</description></item><item><title>Atomic Habits | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510015/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;apos;re discussing &amp;quot;Atomic Habits,&amp;quot; a book about how to use science (and also some stuff that’s definitely not science) to train yourself to be a more functional person.
Support us on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IfBooksPod
Where to find us: TwitterPeter&amp;apos;s other podcast, 5-4Mike&amp;apos;s other podcast, Maintenance PhaseSources:
How 1% Performance Improvements Led to Olympic GoldFrom paupers to kings: The lottery-funded revolution Habit FormationImplementation Intentions to Reduce Smoking: A Systematic Review of the LiteratureEffectiveness of the use of implementation intentions on reduction of substance use: A meta-analysisWhen Intentions Go PublicEffect of Intensive Handwashing Promotion on Childhood Diarrhea in High-Risk Communities in Pakistan Thanks to Mindseye for our theme song!</description></item><item><title>The World is Flat | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Much has been said about globalization, but perhaps no one has said it worse than Thomas Friedman.
Content Note: Discussions of xenophobic and racist content, especially toward the end of the episode.
Support us on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IfBooksPod
Where to find us: TwitterPeter&amp;apos;s other podcast, 5-4Mike&amp;apos;s other podcast, Maintenance PhaseSources:
Why The World Isn&amp;apos;t FlatThe World Is Still Not FlatDHL Global Connectedness Index 2022The Fallacies of FlatnessThe Sociopathy of Thomas Friedman: A CompendiumThomas Friedman sums up the Iraq War (YouTube) Thanks to Mindseye for our theme song!</description></item><item><title>"Nudge" Part 2: Mr. Nudge Goes to Washington | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510017/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510017/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Nudgening.
Support us on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IfBooksPod
Where to find us: TwitterPeter&amp;apos;s other podcast, 5-4Mike&amp;apos;s other podcast, Maintenance PhaseSources:
David Gal&amp;apos;s &amp;quot;Behavioral Winter&amp;quot;The i-frame and the s-frame: How focusing on individual-level solutions has led behavioral public policy astrayWhy Is Behavioral Economics So Popular?Applying Behavioral Insights To Intimate Partner ViolenceWhat Counts as a Nudge?The Power of Nudges, for Good and BadAllowing Patients to Waive the Right to Sue for Medical Malpractice: A Response to Thaler and SunsteinObama’s ObamaBehavioural Insights Applied to Policy - Country Overviews 2016The opioid crisis and nudge theoryOn the Supposed Evidence for Libertarian PaternalismThe effect of charter schools on charter students and public schoolsRe-election Strategy Is Tied to a Shift on SmogIs the White House delaying too many health and safety rules?</description></item><item><title>The Meme Stock Cult [TEASER] | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510018/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2021, scrappy young investors from across the world joined forces to buy GameStop stock, aiming to take down greedy hedge funds. What came next was tragedy, injustice, and a conspiratorial internet cult so stupid we had to do an episode about it.
To hear the rest of the show, support us on Patreon:
https://www.patreon.com/IfBooksPod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>"Nudge" Part 1: A Simple Solution For Littering, Organ Donations and Climate Change | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510019/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2008, an economist and a law professor proposed a radical new approach to politics: Telling people not to do bad stuff.
Support us on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IfBooksPod
Where to find us: TwitterPeter&amp;apos;s other podcast, 5-4Mike&amp;apos;s other podcast, Maintenance PhaseSources:
Mike&amp;apos;s Maintenance Phase episode on the godfather of the &amp;quot;cafeteria nudge&amp;quot;Nudge: Concept, Effectiveness, and EthicsFrom mechanism to virtue: Evaluating Nudge theoryThe effectiveness of nudging: A meta-analysis of choice architecture interventions across behavioral domainsWhy the Most Important Idea in Behavioral Decision-Making Is a FallacyBehavioral WinterWhy Is Behavioral Economics So Popular?</description></item><item><title>The 5 Love Languages | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510020/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510020/</guid><description>Podcast Description What’s your love language? Is it gifts? Words of affirmation? Or is it podcasts about books with extremely weird, reactionary gender dynamics?
Support us on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IfBooksPod
Where to find us: TwitterPeter&amp;apos;s other podcast, 5-4Mike&amp;apos;s other podcast, Maintenance PhaseSources:
Can Gary Chapman Save Your Marriage?The Sixth Love Language Does Not ExistHow ‘The Five Love Languages’ Gets Misinterpreted The 5 Love Languages Don’t Matter as Much as You ThinkThe Creator Of The 5 Love Languages Is A Homophobe And This Is Why We Can&amp;apos;t Have Nice ThingsFamed Author Gary Chapman Talks Love, Marriage, Sex Evangelicals IncorporatedThanks to Mindseye for our theme song!</description></item><item><title>Ben Shapiro's Plan To End Poverty [TEASER] | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510021/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is it bootstraps? It&amp;apos;s bootstraps.
To hear the rest of the show, support us on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IfBooksPod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Rich Dad Poor Dad | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510022/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1997, Robert Kiyosaki revealed the secret to lifelong success: Deliver grifty seminars and hire child slaves.
Support us on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IfBooksPod
Where to find us: TwitterPeter&amp;apos;s other podcast, 5-4Mike&amp;apos;s other podcast, Maintenance PhaseSources:
Pound Foolish: Exposing the Dark Side of the Personal Finance Industry‘Rich Dad Poor Dad&amp;apos; Robert Kiyosaki ExposedStupid Investment of the WeekRobert Kiyosaki’s Rich Dad Education on Real Estate Investing ReviewThe Ticket to Easy Street? The Financial Consequences of Winning the LotteryWhy the Myth of the Miserable Lottery Winner Just Won’t DieWork Centrality and Post-Award Work Behavior of Lottery Winners&amp;quot;The best way to get even with A-grade students was to make them employees of mine&amp;quot;Ohio real estate investor’s warning statement on Robert Kiyosaki and Bill Gatten’s complex PACtrust for real estate investingAcademic Discipline and Personal Finance Instruction in High SchoolThanks to Mindseye for our theme song!</description></item><item><title>The Dumbest Campus Controversies Of The Last Decade [TEASER] | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get in loser, we&amp;apos;re going to Oberlin.
To hear the rest of the show, support us on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IfBooksPod
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hillbilly Elegy | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510024/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510024/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2016, J.D. Vance informally launched his political career with &amp;quot;Hillbilly Elegy,&amp;quot; a memoir that blames the relative poverty of Appalachian and Rust Belt populations on their own culture. Despite its reactionary premise, mainstream and liberal press outlets were so enamored by the book that they accidentally made Vance a senator.
Support us on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IfBooksPod
Where to find us: TwitterPeter&amp;apos;s other podcast, 5-4Mike&amp;apos;s other podcast, Maintenance PhaseSources:</description></item><item><title>The Coddling Of The American Mind | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510025/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510025/</guid><description>Podcast Description TRIGGER WARNING: if you&amp;apos;re a SNOWFLAKE college professor afraid of how your students are expressing themselves, you might need a SAFE SPACE, because Michael and Peter are discussing &amp;quot;The Coddling of The American Mind,&amp;quot; a book about campus culture that&amp;apos;s light on facts and heavy on cherry-picked anecdotes.
CORRECTION: The Socrates quote mentioned at the end of this episode is apocryphal. We thank the listeners who pointed this out for refusing to coddle our American minds.</description></item><item><title>The New York Times's War On Trans Kids [TEASER] | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510026/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510026/</guid><description>Podcast Description The nation&amp;apos;s most prestigious newspaper insists on asking a very stupid question. So for this month&amp;apos;s bonus episode, we decided to answer it. To hear the rest of the show, support us on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IfBooksPod
As we mentioned at the top of the episode, we&amp;apos;re donating this month&amp;apos;s support to three of our trans journo-friends! They&amp;apos;ve been unbelievably patient with Mike as he&amp;apos;s navigated the science and politics of this issue over the last year.</description></item><item><title>The Clash of Civilizations | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510027/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510027/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;quot;If your thesis doesn&amp;apos;t hold up to obvious criticisms, there&amp;apos;s a chance that your thesis sucks.&amp;quot; Thanks to Paul Musgrave and Alex Cruikshanks for helping us fact-check this episode!
Support us on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IfBooksPod
Where to find us: TwitterPeter&amp;apos;s other podcast, 5-4Mike&amp;apos;s other podcast, Maintenance PhaseLinks!
Huntington’s 1993 articleStatistics on deaths in state-based conflicts The Clash of Civilizations: An Islamicist’s CritiquePaul Musgrave’s Roundtable on Clash of Civilizations “The Hispanic Challenge” The “Arab Street”?</description></item><item><title>The End of History | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510028/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Francis Fukuyama&amp;apos;s &amp;quot;The End of History and the Last Man&amp;quot; changed political discourse forever. Peter and Michael peel back his muddled history and fluffy rhetoric, revealing several more layers of muddled history and fluffy rhetoric.
Support us on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IfBooksPod
Where to find us: TwitterPeter&amp;apos;s other podcast, 5-4Mike&amp;apos;s other podcast, Maintenance PhaseSources:
Reflections on the End of History, Five Years Later (https://www.jstor.org/stable/2505433)More Proof That This Really Is the End of History (https://www.</description></item><item><title>The Lab Leak [TEASER] | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510029/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510029/</guid><description>Podcast Description In December 2019, the coronavirus pandemic began in Wuhan, China. In May 2021, America experienced one of the most cursed weeks of punditry we&amp;apos;ve ever seen. This is a condensed version of the full episode. To hear the rest go to patreon.com/IfBooksPod. See you next week! Transcript</description></item><item><title>Men Are From Mars, Women Are From Venus | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510030/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510030/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1992 a yoga instructor with a distance-learning PhD had the courage to ask: &amp;quot;Are women not getting help around the house because they&amp;apos;re using the wrong modal verb?&amp;quot; Support us on Patreon
Where to find us: TwitterPeter&amp;apos;s other podcast, 5-4Mike&amp;apos;s other podcast, Maintenance PhaseSources:
The Myth of Mars and Venus: Do Men and Women Really Speak Different Languages?A critical response to John Gray&amp;apos;s Mars and Venus portrayals of men and women The Gender Similarities HypothesisThe Rebuttal from UranusComing home upset: Gender, marital satisfaction and the daily spillover of workday experience into couple interactionsFDA warning letter Men are from Mars, Women are from Venus: An Analysis of a Potential MemeWomen, Men and Language Women, Men, and Gender: Ongoing DebatesWomen and Men Talking: Are They World’s Apart?</description></item><item><title>The Secret | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510031/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rhonda Byrne&amp;apos;s &amp;quot;The Secret&amp;quot; sold millions of copies based on a simple premise: All of science is fake and the only reason anything ever happens is because people manifest it by communicating with the universe.
Support us on Patreon
Where to find us: TwitterPeter&amp;apos;s other podcast, 5-4Mike&amp;apos;s other podcast, Maintenance PhaseSources:
Power Lines Oprah&amp;apos;s Ugly Secret The Staggering Bullshit of The SecretDeath by “alternative” medicine: Who’s to blame? For Some Seeking Rebirth, Sweat Lodge Was End A Little Secret About The Secret Thanks to Mindseye for our theme song!</description></item><item><title>The Population Bomb | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510032/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510032/</guid><description>Podcast Description How a Stanford lepidopterist convinced the world to fear the breeding habits of the poor. Again. Support us on Patreon
Where to find us: TwitterPeter&amp;apos;s other podcast, 5-4Mike&amp;apos;s other podcast, Maintenance PhaseSources:
Sonia Shah’s “The Next Great Migration” Barbarian Hordes: The overpopulation scapegoat in international development discourseOptimism and OverpopulationThe Population Bomb RevisitedThe Strange History of Birth ControlBirth Control for OthersHow the World Survived the Population Bomb: Lessons From 50 Years of Extraordinary Demographic HistoryWhy the Population Bomb is a Rockefeller Baby
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A Bari Special Bonus Episode [TEASER] | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510033/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our first premium episode is a deep dive into the blog of the infamously (and dubiously) &amp;quot;canceled&amp;quot; Bari Weiss. To hear the full episode, subscribe on Patreon: https://www.patreon.com/IfBooksPod
More free episodes are on their way! Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Game | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510034/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Neil Strauss&amp;apos;s &amp;quot;The Game&amp;quot; aimed to teach any man how to hook up with beautiful women. All he needed was a little bit of sociopathy, a lot of misogyny and a fanny pack full of props.
Support us on Patreon
Where to find us: TwitterPeter&amp;apos;s other podcast, 5-4Mike&amp;apos;s other podcast, Maintenance PhaseSources:
He&amp;apos;s Simply Resistable Pickup Artists Are Still A Thing. And They Want You To Know They’ve Evolved.</description></item><item><title>David Brooks's "Bobos in Paradise" | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510035/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510035/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Brooks became liberals&amp;apos; famous conservative by telling them what they wanted to hear. But ... why did they want to hear something that was lazy and wrong?
Support us on Patreon
Where to find us: TwitterPeter&amp;apos;s other podcast, 5-4Mike&amp;apos;s other podcast, Maintenance Phase
Sources:
A Reasonable ManDavid Brooks: Boo-Boos in ParadiseA Cartoon EliteDavid Brooks’s Conversion StoryDavid Brooks and the Endless Grift of the Conservative CommentariatHow The Bobos Broke AmericaDeath Of A Yuppie Dream: The Rise And Fall Of The Professional-Managerial ClassStuff the Professional-Managerial Class Likes: &amp;quot;Distinction&amp;quot; for an Egalitarian EliteDavid Brooks’s Search for MeaningThe facts vs.</description></item><item><title>Malcolm Gladwell's "Outliers" | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510036/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510036/</guid><description>Podcast Description In &amp;quot;Outliers,&amp;quot; Malcolm Gladwell posited that it takes 10,000 hours of practice to become an expert in something. Mike and Peter prove him wrong by mastering his dumb book over the span of about 50 minutes.
Support us on Patreon
Links:
Malcolm Gladwell talks about responding to critics, and the perils of ‘Talking to Strangers’Gladwell for Dummies Malcolm Gladwell interview The Role of Deliberate Practice in the Acquisition of Expert Performance The Dangers of Delegating Education To Journalists Good intuition takes years of practice Blinkered How Malcolm Gladwell Tricks You Into Believing Complexity and the Ten-Thousand-Hour Rule Trends in International Mathematics and Science Study
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Freakonomics | If Books Could Kill</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2977510037/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2977510037/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2005, two men named Steven and Stephen published the quintessential airport book. In 2022, two men named Mike and Peter started a whole podcast just to make fun of it. Thanks to Ted Joyce and Ames Grawert for helping with the research for this episode!
Support us on Patreon
Where to find us: TwitterPeter&amp;apos;s other podcast, 5-4Mike&amp;apos;s other podcast, Maintenance Phase
Sources:
The 2003 NYT articleFreakonomics: What Went Wrong?</description></item></channel></rss>