<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Talking Bollox Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/talking-bollox-podcast/</link><description>Recent content in Talking Bollox Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 17:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/talking-bollox-podcast/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Episode 152 - Receding | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320001/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's just the two lads for this week's episode and there are a few juicy confessions to kick off with, including Terence's new favourite drink and Calvin's unusual diet, not to mention his 38 hour fast. There's also chat about Terry’s hair line and the whole new look and haircut he'll be sporting in 2024. There's talk of politics and the importance of voting and having your area be represented, as well as plans for the future - Not just dream guests for next year but funeral songs and soups are also debated.</description></item><item><title>Bonus: Coconut Lattes on Stoneybatter | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320002/</guid><description>Podcast Description The facts and "facts" are flying around this week, with many claims and counter-claims.
We sift through your questions and they lead us to discuss sneaky bath bombs, own brand crisps, the world's loudest animal, and Calvin ageing gracelessly as he struggles to come to grips with life in his 30s.
Terence has a hard time arguing Calvin has gone middle class when he lets slip about his own coconut latte addiction, and quickly deflects by blaming Calvin for him mistakenly buying an air fryer.</description></item><item><title>Episode 151 w/ Olivia O'Toole | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Football legend, and one of Ireland's top international goal scorers, second only to Robbie Keane, Olivia O'Toole joined us this week. She told us about growing up in Sheriff Street during a heroin epidemic that impacted her family directly and how her love of football helped to keep her on the right path. She also spoke about the changing attitudes towards women's football since her days being sent off the pitch when the other team noticed she was a girl.</description></item><item><title>Bonus: A (micro)Nation Once Again | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320004/</guid><description>Podcast Description A listener's question leads to a historic moment, and the founding of a nation created by and for Talking Bollox. The fledgling nation will be located off the coast of Dublin and to start will have just a handful of laws - mostly related to footwear, and some related to getting fresh.
Terence has hired the bodyguard John Lennon should have had, while Calvin wants to raise an issue with Terencea warning about a trans-Atlantic tsunami.</description></item><item><title>Episode 150 w/ Dec Pierce | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dec joins us to talk about everything form growing up being bullied in school to becoming a huge DJ &amp;amp; radio presenter in Ireland. He also tells us how he set up Block Rockin Beats, which is a huge success and is getting bigger and bigger! Dec gets into detail about his health scare at the start of the year. He talks about the trauma that has come with that, how he tries to deal with it now &amp;amp; ow he's grateful to be able t do certain things with his life again.</description></item><item><title>Bonus: Once Upon a Time in Antarctica | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320006/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320006/</guid><description>Podcast Description The best insults, tales of spoiled dogs and planning holidays to Antarctica (without your appendix) - it's a meandering episode this week
Your questions have Terence and Calvin considering if they'd sacrifice the internet to save the chipper (while questioning what became of Dublin's best chippers), and wondering why some people are producing gourmet meals for dogs. Terry is on Sky Scanner pricing up flights to the South Pole, and Calvin is wondering if there are more people in Antarctica or Leitrim.</description></item><item><title>Episode 149 w/ Danny O'Brien | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ahead of Friday's live show, comedian Danny O'Brien joined us to offer some of his own disaster stories from the stage and his tips for putting it all into perspective, like reminding yourself no matter how bad it went 'nobody died'. He told us about performing in the Ringsend flats and the community spirit he felt there, even after the event got broken up by the Guards.
He also spoke about his work in addiction services and why its so personal to him, as well as sharing some gas tales from the workshops he does in prisons and schools.</description></item><item><title>Bonus: Cult Leader for a Day | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320008/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 09:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Would Terence make a good cult leader? Is Calvin on the juice, or has he just been eating a lot of whole cakes?
Terence decides he might skip the cult circuit and go straight for the Aras, if he can turn down his invite to the 27 club and makes it to 35.
The lads give their best shot at inventing a conspiracy theory, Calvin is trying to explain Squirrel Stamps to Terence, and there’s a detailed debate about the world’s soundest animal (besides dogs).</description></item><item><title>Episode 148 w/ Nathan Kelly | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320009/</guid><description>Podcast Description MMA fighter Nathan Kelly joined us this week to tell us how fighting helped him both during his childhood in Finglas and later when he went down the wrong path with drugs and alcohol. He explained how he turned things around, even going on to fight at Madison Square Garden with a headline show in the 3arena coming up on the 8th of December.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonus: The Waterboy | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320010/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320010/</guid><description>Podcast Description From panicking in the shower to swearing by LL Cool J’s “iconic” Deep Blue Sea, Terence is thriving in the water this week. A film recommendation from Calvin sees Terence insisting he can be a world beating free-diver, but not without warning of the dangers of panicking in the shower. And some education on record breaking films leads to him swearing off all fish cinema – except one.</description></item><item><title>Episode 147 w/ PJ Gallagher | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320011/</guid><description>Podcast Description PJ Gallagher has been one of Ireland's most famous faces for the past two decades, and has lived his life in the public eye in that time - but he is only now telling the full story.
He spoke to us about growing up in a house with alcoholic parents and 5 men with schizophrenia; how he got into comedy; the birth of Naked Camera and the inspiration behind Jake Stevens; how he found out he was adopted and contacted his birth parents, and how his struggle with depression very nearly saw him take his own life, but through the help of friends and the proper car he was able to come out the far side.</description></item><item><title>Bonus: The Invention of Running | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320012/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Terence has been conned by a DM of disinformation, while Calvin is outraged by the poor terminology used by one listener around breakfast. There are calls for the banning of hard crisps (to protect Terry's teeth), while Calvin makes a stunning admission about his own ignorance of one popular morning staple.
The lads try to weigh up their chances in a race against Usain Bolt, and also decide on the one form of potatoes to live with for the rest of their days.</description></item><item><title>Episode 146 w/ Marcus Cowzer | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320013/</guid><description>Podcast Description After giving up on his dream of becoming a professional footballer, Marcus Cowzer spent years being unsure of his future, feeling like he had disappointed his father and being unable to deal with the anger and fear of abandonment inside him. While he did eventually rebuild his relationship with his father, it wasn't without a struggle.
He tells us about growing up feeling like nothing he did was ever good enough, and how his father's death sent him on his journey to becoming a psychotherapist.</description></item><item><title>Episode 145 - Ritual | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320014/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320014/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's been a while but we go back to just the two boys this week. We take your questions and talk about everything from suspected hauntings, to the trickier elements of dog ownership, to Terence's shocking New Balance admission.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonus: Terry Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Terence recalls his time spent recently on a strange hospital ward with some unusual, but lovable, neighbours - and Calvin wonders if there might have been more going on that Terry realised.
Terence admits, quite proudly, he wants to cry more, while Calvin has an incredible true tale about the highest non-fatal fall in human history.
A question about eating a bucket of onions make Terence seriously doubt if Calvin has become middle class.</description></item><item><title>Episode 144 w/ Chris Connolly | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320016/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a powerful tale of pulling yourself back from the brink, and escaping even the darkest moments.
Chris found himself trapped in a spiral of drink and drugs that led to extreme paranoia and psychosis - to the point he believed a hitman was chasing him, and his family were aiding the plot to kill him.
Today Chris runs 5km (at least) every day, and he has done that for over 200 days in a row now.</description></item><item><title>Bonus: Murder was the Case | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Terence has been paying extortionate prices for sandwiches and Calvin thinks it's time to strike back against the cost of living crisis, in his own particular way.
Terence wants to get clarity on how murder charges work, and if podcasting can have any bearing on them, while Calvin wonders if the charge for murdering Tupac should be worth the same when it's taken almost three decades to get an arrest.</description></item><item><title>Episode 143 w/ Jordan McCann | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320018/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 15:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jordan McCann has come through many obstacles and battled many demons to become a hugely respected musician. He talks to us about life growing up in Little Hulton, his experiences of prison, and the damage left behind by poverty and addiction.
He talks to us about how everyone can turn their life around, and how he left behind a life on the streets to achieve his success.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonus: Two for a Chew | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320019/</guid><description>Podcast Description What are the most valuable liquids in the world? Terence and Calvin attempt to make their own lists and include some questionable additions like Blue Powerade and Volvic Water.
A listener gets in touch to share another random fact that has the boys wondering what defines a castle, while a different question has them debating the months of the summer season.
And Terence is left to defend himself after being spotted heading to the Busted concert.</description></item><item><title>Episode 142 w/ Kiefer Crosbie Part 2 | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320020/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Since he first spoke to us over 2 years ago, Kiefer Crosbie has gone on to achieve his dream of fighting in the UFC - But he won't stop there. Kiefer told us all about the journey he's been on to get to this point, and what he sees in his future, including a return of the UFC to Dublin. He also talked about the power of martial arts in preventing violence on the streets and Terence called him out for potentially breaking his ribs during training.</description></item><item><title>Bonus: The Mini Pinch Apocalypse | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320021/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320021/</guid><description>Podcast Description If the zombie apocalypse came to Ireland, would Terence and Calvin team up for survival, or each go their own way? One listener's question about their survival plans kicks off a major difference of opinion, and leads to some strange revelations and worrying admissions.
There's a seemingly unanswerable riddle that leads to deep thought on the importance of the element of surprise when it comes to your pain threshold and Terence threatening people with assault by a six-year-old.</description></item><item><title>Episode 141 w/ Keith Barry | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hypnotist, magician and brain hacker Keith Barry joined us this week to explain how he got started with magic and mind reading, his work with some very well known names including Morgan Freeman and Nicole Scherzinger and he even hacks our brains and makes a promise to rid Terence of his smoking habit through hypnosis.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonus: Don't Call it a Comeback | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320023/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a long hiatus we return to the studio for a very special bonus episode. Terence gives an update on what has kept him away for so long and why it's cost him two teeth, so far. Calvin argues he could be a pilot with minimal time spent training, while Terence argues he got the better of Lance Armstrong going up Howth Hill.
There’s also some talk of clapping at funerals and on flights, while Terence admits to breaking out in applause in taxis - and gets thrown a Texas question to welcome him back.</description></item><item><title>Episode 140 - The National Stadium | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320024/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our biggest ever live show! We packed out the National Stadium for our show on the 28th of June and were joined by our most requested guest ever Willa White who had us all in stitches with his stories, illusionist Keith Barry also appeared and did a few tricks with us and we even got Maverick Sabre to sing us all a few songs!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 139 - Electric Picnic w/ Willa White | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320025/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320025/</guid><description>Podcast Description A Talking Bollox first this week, as we have an episode with just one of the lads. Illness meant Terence wasn't able to make it to Electric Picnic this year, so Calvin called on Willa White to share the stage with him. It wasn't quite the show we had all hoped for, but Willa brought some stories and jokes that lifted the roof off the place.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonus: Take the L | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320026/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Calvin has a new theory about the flocks of Spanish students he's been seeing on the bus this past summer, while Terence is too busy getting recognised by bus and Luas drivers to notice - Although it unclear whether this fame is due to the podcast or his shameless disregard for buying tickets. There's also talk of spur of the moment tattoos, surprising ecosystems and survival on coffee alone.</description></item><item><title>Episode 138 w/ Alexandra Ryan | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320027/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ali Ryan joined us to talk to us about her huge success as a showbiz journalist, founding Goss.ie at just 23 and her struggles and determination to keep it afloat in the early years. She also opened up about the sex tape filmed without her consent, the blackmail and rumours around it, and the impact it had&amp;nbsp;on&amp;nbsp;her&amp;nbsp;life.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonus: Amy with a Fada | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320028/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Terence suffers from a bout of sleep paralysis that sends him down a YouTube rabbit hole and has him worried he might be the latest member of the 27 club. Meanwhile, Calvin is reassessing his music playlists in favour of podcasts and choosing who he would bring back from the dead for a headline act at Electric Picnic. There's also an assertion that Howth Head is a harder cycle than the Tour De France and a promise of a big budget guests in the next year.</description></item><item><title>Episode 137 w/ Eddie Mullins Part 2 | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320029/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former Governor of Mountjoy Prison, Eddie Mullins joined us as he moves into a new role where he'll be tackling the issues around the inner city. We chat about the solutions to those issues, including preventative measures and more balanced reporting in the media and online. We also hear about how Dublin, and Mountjoy, has changed over the past 30 years as well as what has stayed the same.</description></item><item><title>Bonus: A Barber Scorned | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320030/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are there more mullets now than there are skin fades? Yes, according to Terence and Calvin, but what they don&amp;rsquo;t know is whether they&amp;rsquo;re by choice or the result of being unfaithful to your barber. They ponder this, along with questions about going back in time, emigrating and sacrificing your sight for your family.
Terence also offers some advice to aspiring runners and while Calvin shares his own fond memories of chasing after a shoplifter.</description></item><item><title>Episode 136 w/ Kiera Dignam | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320031/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kiera Dignam joined us to talk about being bullied in school, getting pregnant at 16 and being a &amp;rsquo;nepo baby'.
In the wake of her father Christy&amp;rsquo;s passing, she also told us about how music has helped her to deal with grief and why he could never be replaced.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonus: Happy as a Sardine | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320032/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Calvin&amp;rsquo;s taste in TV shows is questioned, along with his life philosophy after he is forced to choose between lions and sardines. And Terence tells us why he&amp;rsquo;s getting sick of explaining his &amp;rsquo;embarrassing&amp;rsquo; tattoo.
A listener reaches out with some statistics that reignite the 147, 9 darter, hole in 1 debate and the lads discuss recent cases of antisocial behaviour in Dublin, possible solutions and their own run ins with the law.</description></item><item><title>Episode 135 - Respite | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320033/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Next week&amp;rsquo;s bonus episode comes early after a tooth ache throws off the typical recording schedule but there&amp;rsquo;s still plenty of Talking Bollox with tales of heroic life saving and dramatic plane journeys.
Not to mention the listener questions which have Terence contemplating life as a spy and Calvin reminiscing on some of the stranger &amp;lsquo;facts&amp;rsquo; he learned in college. The lads also debate the best quiz show to win and the explore the strange world of Japanese reality TV.</description></item><item><title>Bonus: TB to the Moon | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320034/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320034/</guid><description>Podcast Description The bonus episodes return with big dreams, from a young Calvin’s childhood dream of becoming an astronaut, to Terry Flower’s mission to become a mogul in 12 months, and a blueprint for success for the Talking Bollox business empire.
Calvin is still fielding a wave of hate over a tweet, while Terence is wondering what he can make his enemies eat for eternity.
They lament the lack of passion shown in sandwich making at times, and remember a story of murder down at the shop, and sketch out plans for the Talking Bollox business empire.</description></item><item><title>Episode 134 - Relief | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320035/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320035/</guid><description>Podcast Description We return after our break and we&amp;rsquo;ve got a few things to talk about - from Terence&amp;rsquo;s discovery that Talking Bollox appears to be huge in Turkey, to some stories from behind the scenes of our recent live shows.
And, as promised, there&amp;rsquo;s the big reveal on the complex, secretive story behind the R episodes.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 133 - Talking Bollox Sports | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320036/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320036/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we bring you our favourite Talking Bollox moments from the world of sport. We’ve got inspirational stories of recovery, the lessons that come with missing out on huge potential but finding peace, and a chat with the world’s biggest boxing promoter – Eddie Hearn.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonus: In the Name of the Father Power | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320037/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Terence is considering a calling from God, but early signs are the priesthood might not be for him.
The coffee and strawberry debates (and listener backlash) continue, while Terence has some &amp;ldquo;facts&amp;rdquo; about beverage temperatures - and Calvin wants a fact check on those &amp;ldquo;facts&amp;rdquo;.
Terence worries his potted memory of the Rocky films is a sign of a serious and concerning memory issue, while the lads weigh up their go-to films and TV shows.</description></item><item><title>Episode 132 - Talking Bollox Live | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320038/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320038/</guid><description>Podcast Description After our shows at the National Stadium we decided to go back to the archives and bring you some of our favourite bits from our live shows, going right back to the start.
We&amp;rsquo;ve put together a mix of moments from when we were joined on stage by Roddy Collins, John Connors, Marc O&amp;rsquo;Neill, Senator Lynn Ruane, Hughie Maughan, Aoife Moore, James Kavanagh, Ciaran Moran and Enya Martin.</description></item><item><title>Bonus: Secret Payments and Alestations | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320039/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Terence is in a rage against a local festival that has ruined his week, and Calvin has some issues with the gentrification of place names in the inner city. Calvin is left baffled by Terence&amp;rsquo;s bizarrely in depth knowledge of animals who have worked as spies, and a story of a pigeon that is too good to be true. There&amp;rsquo;s some discussion of the recent controversy at RTE - and Terence makes the case for refusing nothing in life but a clatter.</description></item><item><title>Episode 131 - Ragamuffin | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320040/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ahead of two of our biggest ever live shows at the National Stadium we sit down to answer your important questions, like would we rather go on Love Island or Big Brother and which is harder a hole in one, a 147, or a nine darter?
And is now the right time to reveal the secret meaning behind the &amp;lsquo;R&amp;rsquo; words?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonus: A rumour always better than the truth | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320041/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320041/</guid><description>Podcast Description The true worth of iced coffee threatens to ignite all out war, with CAlvin and Terence firmly at odds.
Calvin gives Terence has a revelation about coat hooks in his home, and this leads to him making an admission about a very sentimental bottle of cooking oil.
Live show nerves are in the background, but Terence has a new diet of around the clock porridge that is going to see him through.</description></item><item><title>Episode 130 w/ Roddy Collins Part 2 | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320042/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Friend of the podcast, Roddy Collins joins us once again to entertain with stories of singing down the phone to his book publisher, a holiday home that was once a caravan and awards ceremonies gone wrong.
We also suggest a few other career opportunities for him now that his book has been released, including his own podcast or a return to management and he tells us why he has never been happier than he is now.</description></item><item><title>Bonus: Undefeated &amp; Underrated | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320043/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Terence claims to be the world&amp;rsquo;s greatest player at a very particular and parochial game, Calvin wants to whittle down the list of potential narrators to tell the Talking Bollox story. The lads weigh up which celebrity they would live with for a year, and Terence wants to know if we can talk about Adele. There are death row menus and the highly fluid local rules of switch are discussed.</description></item><item><title>Episode 129 w/ Darren Conway Part 2 | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320044/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320044/</guid><description>Podcast Description 100 episodes later, Darren Conway is back in with us for a part 2.
We chat about Darren&amp;rsquo;s work in the couple of years since he was last in, from his TV series to his own podcast, and how he&amp;rsquo;s now fielding frequent calls from Terence - sometimes with strange results.
There&amp;rsquo;s a bit of reminiscing about Terence and Calvin&amp;rsquo;s acting debut on Darren &amp;amp; Joe&amp;rsquo;s Free Gaff, and an explanation of the origins of &amp;ldquo;The Hooley Gooley&amp;rdquo; threat.</description></item><item><title>Bonus: James Bond, muppet | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320045/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Terence practices telepathy while trying to decide on his favourite Irish film of all time; there&amp;rsquo;s an offer to play a life or death game with tempting odds; Calvin rails against the James Bond franchise while he also considers body modifications to secure a one hundred million euro prize.
And we meet the first known Swedish Talking Bollox fan, and Terence stereotypes the life out of the Swedish nation.</description></item><item><title>Episode 128 w/ Deirdre Gogarty | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320046/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ireland&amp;rsquo;s first female world champion boxer, Deirdre Gogarty faced a lot of obstacles in her journey to becoming champion including the attitude towards women boxing in Ireland, dangerous unsanctioned matches, and having to make weight by stuffing her pockets with coins - just to get a chance to fight. She joined us to share her story and to discuss the progress of Katie Taylor from exchanging letters at a young age to sitting ringside at her most recent fight.</description></item><item><title>Bonus: good kid, bAd wheelie | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320047/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320047/</guid><description>Podcast Description The inability to do a wheelie continues to haunt Terence and Calvin, but memories of the thrill of the chase of childhood knick knacks still warms their hearts. Terence has been crank calling Darren Conway, while Calvin shows startlingly quick reactions when asked about a giraffe wearing a tie. There&amp;rsquo;s some more serious discussion about crime and punishment, and a zinger to make your skin crawl.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 127 w/ Katriona O'Sullivan | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320048/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Katriona is a doctor with a PhD in psychology, but she has had to face some incredible obstacles to get where she is today. She told us about growing up in poverty and with parents who were addicts, having a child at 15, and ending up homeless, suffering with her own addiction - and then how she turned it all around. We talk about how teachers can have an incredible, transformative impact on the life of a kid who's struggling - or they an do the opposite.</description></item><item><title>Bonus: Unmasking the TV licence man | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320049/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Listeners have a strange array of questions for us this week - everything from needing answers on blocking the toilet at work; giving your mortal enemy a cash windfall, and the symbolism of strange dreams.
As well as all of that, we look back at Eddie Hearn&amp;rsquo;s visit to the studio, Terence considers boycotting Spotify on moral grounds, and the scammers have been coming for us.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 126 w/ Gerry Hussey | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320050/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 11:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gerry is a performance psychologist and author of ‘Awaken Your Power Within’ and more. He joined us to share his story of struggling with his mental health from a young age and told us how it nearly cost him his life as a child. That experience inspired Gerry to learn more about the brain and how we can train it with the right exercises to reduce anxiety and to live a more fulfilling, rewarding life.</description></item><item><title>Bonus: Teleporting the gaff down | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320051/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Terence sees the vast potential in the powers of teleportation (of others), Calvin has big questions about strange names, a listener challenges the lads to consider which animal they would stand the best chance with in a fight, and the lads weigh up which fictional movie character they&amp;rsquo;d choose to live the rest of their days as.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 125 w/ Eddie Hearn | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320052/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 11:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chairman of Matchroom Sports and arguably the world&amp;rsquo;s most influential boxing promoter, Eddie Hearn joined us ahead of Katie Taylor&amp;rsquo;s homecoming to discuss the legacy of the fight, and how his attitude towards women&amp;rsquo;s sports has changed over the years. He also told us about his upbringing, the origins of his work ethic and his drive to win.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonus: Moonwalking under a ladder | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320053/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 08:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Umbrella theft, superstitions, the size of fridges, chewing gum in the shower and debatable time travel options - it&amp;rsquo;s a weird one, but Terence explaining his problem with switches on plug sockets takes us on a journey into another realm entirely.
Calvin admits to multiple holding on to multiple superstitions, and a strict code of conduct towards magpies, which Terence mocks him for before admitting to one of the strangest habits we&amp;rsquo;re ever likely to hear.</description></item><item><title>Episode 124 w/ Pat Shortt | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320054/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 15:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pat Shortt is one of Ireland&amp;rsquo;s most famous, and most loved, comedians and actors. We talked about his early life growing up, how D&amp;rsquo;Unbelievables got their start, the fame of Father Ted, and how later in his career he has earned respect as an actor - including a big role in the Banshees of Inisherin. And not to forget, knocking Shakira off the top of the charts with &amp;ldquo;Jumbo Breakfast Roll&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Bonus: The Babylonian Fellas | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320055/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 08:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Terence is thrown into a tailspin by questions over who invented time, while Calvin is baffled by how far away Lucan is.
Calvin has lessons for us on the world of pigeon fancying - a world Terence insists he never had the opportunity to enter - and they consider which of the two of them is more difficult to spend time with.
Then there&amp;rsquo;s listener questions, leading us to conversations about hauntings, a missing moon, the daily workload of a modern day exorcist, and musical guilty pleasures.</description></item><item><title>Episode 123 w/ Chris Forrester | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320056/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris comes in to chat with us about the League of Ireland, arriving to play for Bohs in his school uniform and beating the likes of Villa &amp;amp; Leicester in cup games for Peterborough. He names the best and worst players he’s played with in his career so far and goes through some career highs and lows, including struggling with his mental health while playing in the UK after the death of his sister.</description></item><item><title>Bonus: The Texas Connection | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320057/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 08:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320057/</guid><description>Podcast Description You asked for them, so we&amp;rsquo;ve delivered them. The bonus episodes are here.
In our first ever extra episode we take your questions, give some stories that haven&amp;rsquo;t made it into the main episodes, and have all of the details about our next live show.
Terence wonders who invented the English language, Calvin makes the case against dolphins and they debate which ghost they&amp;rsquo;d most want to have as a guest on the podcast.</description></item><item><title>Episode 122 w/ Adam Rowe | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320058/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320058/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a lot of manifesting by Terence, comedian and host of Have A Word podcast, Adam Rowe joined us this week for a chat about everything from flying and counting cards to conspiracies and aliens. He also told us about his life growing up in Liverpool, and how he went from maths whizz-kid to stand up comedian.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 121 - Referendum | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320059/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320059/</guid><description>Podcast Description We chat about the aftermath of last weeks episode with Tánaiste Micheál Martin - from the reaction, good and bad, to some of the more incredible conspiracy theories people came up with around it all.
We also answer your questions, throw out some zingers of our own, and Terence goes down a rabbit hole on his complex, fraught lifelong relationship with bees.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 120 w/ Micheál Martin | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320060/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320060/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;rsquo;re joined by Tánaiste Micheál Martin this week. We talk about his early life growing up in Cork, his start in politics and what it&amp;rsquo;s like to become Taoiseach. And of course we throw him a few zingers.
Beyond that, we get into an in-depth discussion on issues like social inequality, Ireland&amp;rsquo;s drugs policy and the housing crisis.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 119 w/ Owen Roddy | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320061/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Once known as &amp;lsquo;Rowdy&amp;rsquo; Owen Roddy and now known for his coaching expertise, Owen joined us to chat about about his life growing up, his start in MMA &amp;amp; how sports saved his life.
He also told us about some of the lessons it has taught him including how being a Jack of all trades is sometimes better than being a master of one and he revealed why Nate Diaz wouldn’t survive walking down Summerhill.</description></item><item><title>Episode 118 w/ Neil Delamere &amp; Dave Moore | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320062/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320062/</guid><description>Podcast Description We welcome comedian Neil Delamere back to the pod this week and he&amp;rsquo;s brought along his own podcast co-host, Dave Moore, of Today FM, to give us a general knowledge workout. We talked about everything from Mastermind specialist subjects, to collecting runners, the baffling number of molecules in a glass of water, swimming with sharks, and even a quickfire quiz.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 117 - Restless | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320063/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320063/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, the lads sit down together to catch up and run through some of your questions. They offer up their opinions on everything from crows and water slides to rugby fans and the middle class and debate how much money they would need to send their mams to jail for a year. Calvin also shares some advice for new dads and ruins Terence&amp;rsquo;s dream of becoming a father to twins.</description></item><item><title>Episode 116 w/ Eve McDowell | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320064/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eve is a stalking victim, who has used her personal experience to campaign for the introduction of laws against stalking in Ireland. She was followed relentlessly from first thing in the morning to last thing at night by a man with a fixation on her. He was eventually jailed for breaking into her home and attacking her housemate with a hammer and was released earlier this month.
Eve told us about her experience and her ongoing fight for dedicated laws against stalking in Ireland to protect those going through similar situations.</description></item><item><title>Episode 115 w/ Darren O'Connor | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320065/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Darren is a youth worker who has worked in Dublin&amp;rsquo;s inner city for many years, including with Terence as a young man. Darren told us about growing up in Ballymun and how that environment gave him the tools to help young people later in life. He spoke to us about the seismic changes youth workers can quietly do to turn around the lives of people that others might have given up on, why the greatest successes aren&amp;rsquo;t the loudest ones in life, and he also has some cracking stories for us.</description></item><item><title>Episode 114 w/ Tommy Mallet | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320066/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320066/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we talked to one of the biggest names in men&amp;rsquo;s fashion, the one and only Tommy Mallet. We talk about everything from his childhood in London, the earliest days of Mallet clothing, Tommy&amp;rsquo;s new view on life since receiving a diagnosis for ADD, and his Pearse Street roots (and his ma&amp;rsquo;s coddle).
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 113 - Report Card | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320067/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320067/</guid><description>Podcast Description The lads take your questions and try to help out with your requests for advice, and this week there are some strange, disturbing and hilarious submissions from listeners. Everything from bomb disposal on a push bike, to managing Valentine&amp;rsquo;s disasters, to how to unravel the mystery of a suspiciously locked room in a rented house. And to go with that, Terence has found his old school journal, and it offers a glimpse into the chaotic world of teenage Terry.</description></item><item><title>Episode 112 w/ Ray Lane | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320068/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ray Lane is a veteran bomb disposal expert from Dublin. His career began by working to defuse IRA bombs and trying to outsmart and track down the bombers, some of whom he got to know personally. When the NATO forces in Afghanistan were facing a daily onslaught of Taliban bombs, it was Ray who they sent for, as his experience from Ireland gave him an insight unlike anyone else.</description></item><item><title>Episode 111 w/ Conor Moore | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320069/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conor Moore, AKA Conor Sketches, has achieved global fame and success with his comedy and impressions. He tells us the incredible story of how he went from making a video about his local GAA club, just for his close friends, to working with superstars like Tiger Woods and Jose Mourinho - and even having Justin Timberlake steal his punchlines.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 110 w/ Dr Sharon Lambert | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320070/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sharon is a psychologist who has been working on mental health, addiction and trauma throughout her career. She spoke to us about her work, about &amp;lsquo;social capital&amp;rsquo; and how it impacts all of our lives, and why no matter how hard someone works the likelihood is that without social capital you can&amp;rsquo;t beat the system.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 109 - Remembrance | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320071/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320071/</guid><description>Podcast Description The two boys sit down to take your questions and talk about everything from what they&amp;rsquo;d put in a Dublin time capsule, to Terence&amp;rsquo;s chances of outwitting and out-running a silverback gorilla in the Ilac Centre, and the one mystery they would love to know the truth behind.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 108 w/ Aoife Moore | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320072/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Aoife Moore is a journalist covering Irish politics. She was a guest at our last live show and since then we&amp;rsquo;ve been hounded by requests to get her on for a full episode. We talked about everything from how the murder of her uncle on Bloody Sunday inspired Aoife to want to be a journalist, the online abuse she has faced, what it&amp;rsquo;s like covering Irish politics, the protests around refugee centres, the prospects for a united Ireland, and how trauma rooted in The Troubles lives on today.</description></item><item><title>Episode 107 w/ Jason Byrne | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320073/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320073/</guid><description>Podcast Description This one goes as you might expect - a bit of everything and all over the place in the best way possible. We talk a little about men and their health (and why old habits die hard), Jason&amp;rsquo;s heart troubles, Terence&amp;rsquo;s mystery lump, UFOs, the speed of sound, and why it&amp;rsquo;s never a good idea to start a fight with a celebrity.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 106 - Vicar St 3.0 | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320074/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Roddy Collins, Aoife Moore and James Kavanagh were our guests for talking Bollox Live at Vicar Street on the 19th of November&amp;hellip; and this might be our favourite live show so far. There was an incredible atmosphere in the crowd that night and the guests gave us big laughs and powerful conversations.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 105 - The Best of 2022 | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320075/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320075/</guid><description>Podcast Description We take a moment this week to sit down and look back on some of our favourite moments and guests from the past 12 months. It has been an incredible year for Talking Bollox and we wanted to take a bit of time to thank the listeners and give you some insight into the biggest moments of the year, and give you a few stories from behind the scenes.</description></item><item><title>Episode 104 - Reindeer | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320076/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320076/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s a Talking Bollox Christmas special this week, with the two lads sitting down to talk about their Christmas traditions and a few other things that come to mind over the festive season. Plus there&amp;rsquo;s plenty of questions from listeners answered, and Terence reveals his newfound dream to become a star of the big screen.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 103 w/ Kenneth O'Driscoll | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320077/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kenneth was once stuck in the trap of a vicious cycle of drug addiction and crime, which stemmed from trauma in his early years. It was the birth of his daughter that motivated him to change his life, and since then he has gone on an incredible road to recovery ad redemption and now dedicates himself to helping others. This episode brings us back to our roots and it was an inspiring story to hear.</description></item><item><title>Episode 102 w/ Belters Only | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320078/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320078/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week the 2 lads are joined by 2 of the biggest DJs not only in Dublin but in Ireland, Belters Only. They chat about how they came together and found the incredible success they&amp;rsquo;ve had, how dark periods left them stronger and better able to handle the pitfalls of the music industry, and why timing is everything in life.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 101 - The Murder of Charles Self | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320079/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Charles Self, an RTE set designer, was brutally murdered in his own home on an icy night in January 1982. 40 years later the case remains clouded in mystery. The investigation that followed saw 1500 gay men interviewed around Dublin, with many feeling the gardai used the investigation as cover to carry out a witch hunt against the gay community, at a time when homosexual acts were outlawed in Ireland.</description></item><item><title>Episode 100 w/ Versatile &amp; Willa White | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320080/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320080/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s our 100th episode so we&amp;rsquo;re having a bit of party. Dublin rappers Versatile - Casper Walsh and Eskimo Supreme - join us for their first ever in-depth interview. They tell their story for the first time, from breaking new ground in Irish music with the incredible heights of their 3 Arena show, to dark days when they faced calls for their cancellation amid allegations of racism and misogyny.</description></item><item><title>Episode 99 w/ Maverick Sabre | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320081/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Maverick Sabre is one of the most talented and successful Irish artists of recent years and he joins the lads to talk about his rise in the music industry, struggling with identity between his Irish and English roots, and how sage advice and making the right moves at the right times helped him avoid potential pitfalls on the road to fame.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 98 - Reconciliation | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320082/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320082/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week the lads answer your questions. Everything from how to set up your own podcast; the one musical artist they could listen to forever, and what would be your death row meal?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 97 w/ Neil Delamere | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320083/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Neil Delamare is one of Ireland&amp;rsquo;s best known and most successful stand up comedians and he joined us for what turned out to be a hilarious, interesting chat that covered everything from Ireland&amp;rsquo;s greatest moments, to mysteries around the pyramids, Terence&amp;rsquo;s obsession with JFK, and a very tricky zinger about time travel.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 96: Live at Electric Picnic | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320084/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Missed the lads at EP?? No bother as in this episode we hear Talking Bollox live from Electric Picnic. Listen as the lads talk all about being backstage, the artists, the energy and a special guest makes an appearance too.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 95 w/ The Two Norries | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320085/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320085/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week on the podcast, the lads are joined by the stars of The Two Norries Podcast, James Leonard &amp;amp; Timmy Long. They discuss what it was like growing up in Cork City, addiction, crime, mental health and how their podcast is their way of releasing stress and getting things off their chest.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 94 - Vicar St 2.0 | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320086/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320086/</guid><description>Podcast Description With the week that’s in it, after selling out two nights at Vicar St faster than any other podcast in history, we’re putting out our most recent live show at the iconic venue. What a night this was! Recorded in front of a capacity crowd in August 19, 2022, the place was electric as always! We want to say a huge thanks to our guests on the night Marc O&amp;rsquo;Neill, John Connors, Dylan Moran and Ciaran Moran.</description></item><item><title>Episode 93 w/ Enda Murphy | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320087/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320087/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week the lads are joined by Cognitive Behavioural Psychotherapist Enda Murphy. His firsthand experience of having ADHD has given Enda a unique insight into the difficulties children and adolescence face in growing up. This insight has enabled him to translate complex psychodynamics into easily understood programmes for parents, teachers and health professionals. His understanding and ability to communicate is astounding and we learn a few things about Calvin and Terence too.</description></item><item><title>Episode 92 w/ Damien Dempsey | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320088/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320088/</guid><description>Podcast Description One of Ireland&amp;rsquo;s greatest songwriters and one of Dublin&amp;rsquo;s finest ambassadors joins us this week. Damo talks to us about everything from growing up in Donaghmede to making his break into music, his outlook and philosophy on life, his legendary gigs and cult following - and he has a zinger that leaves the lads completely stumped.
And, of course, Damo plays a few tunes for us - and he nearly takes the roof off the place.</description></item><item><title>Episode 91 - Revolut | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320089/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320089/</guid><description>Podcast Description The two lads sit down for a catch up and to take questions from listeners. We cover everything from why the Garth Brooks gigs have Terence living in a state of fear, the potential to run away forever to Sweden, our dream superhero powers, and what advice we would give to our 15-year-old selves.
Plus there is some quiet reflection on addiction and recovery, as a big month passes.</description></item><item><title>Episode 90 w/ John Connors | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320090/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320090/</guid><description>Podcast Description John is one of Ireland&amp;rsquo;s most famous actors and he&amp;rsquo;s never been scared of voicing his opinion, which has often led to controversy. He came in to chat with us and for the first ever he talks about it all - from politics to cancel culture, to suicide, career success and personal breakdowns - and how acting saved his life more than once. Above all though this one was a great laugh, and we made sure to ask what it was like to kill Nidge.</description></item><item><title>Episode 89 w/ Shauna Bannon | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320091/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Shauna Bannon is one of the lading faces of Irish MMA and her personal story is one of incredible determination in pursuing excellence, as she aims to reach the MMA by the age of 30. She joined us to talk through her journey to mixed martial arts, through a career in kickboxing that started age 3 and ended up with world titles. And to go with it all that she talked to us about what it&amp;rsquo;s like chasing that dream while being a single mother, and handling the tough training schedule with raising her son.</description></item><item><title>Episode 88 w/ Willa White Part 3 | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320092/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320092/</guid><description>Podcast Description We make Talking Bollox history this week, as we have the first ever guest hattrick, with Willa White making his third appearance. To mark the occasion we covered everything from Goldilocks going over bank counters for porridge, the greatest Dublin slang, Terence and Calvin&amp;rsquo;s supernatural encounters, and Willa&amp;rsquo;s choice for an alternative to a guide cat.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 87 w/ Stephen Travers | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320093/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320093/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Miami Showband Massacre is one of the most infamous atrocities of The Troubles. In the early hours of the morning The MiamI Showband - then one of Ireland&amp;rsquo;s most famous groups - were stopped at what appeared to be a military checkpoint in County Down. It was in fact an ambush, planned as an attempt to frame the band as terrorists. Three of the band members were killed in the attack.</description></item><item><title>Episode 86 - Live at Vicar Street | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320094/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320094/</guid><description>Podcast Description On June 19th we played Vicar Street for the first time, and it was an incredible night with a sold out crowd lifting the roof off the place. The guests that joined us on stage were comedian Enya Martin, sex educator Jenny Keane, and musician and D1 native Gemma Dunleavy.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 85 w/ Tony Groves | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320095/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tony Groves is the co-founder of the Tortoise Shack podcast publishing platform, a former banker and an active political commentator. In this episode, Tony speaks to us about the number of people who have died while in Garda custody, and some of his grievances with GSOC. He also discusses going viral online after his appearance on Claire Byrne Live, as well as the issues of housing and classism. He offers an insight into his days working in the banking sector before and during the financial crash and how that has impacted on his life now.</description></item><item><title>Episode 84 - Recognition | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320096/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320096/</guid><description>Podcast Description We go back to just the two boys in the studio this week. We want to discuss a few things on our mind and take your questions. You&amp;rsquo;ve given us some very interesting zingers and asked us about everything from how we approach and handle our deeper episodes, to why Terence keeps starting on everyone.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 83 w/ Sarah Grace | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320097/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320097/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2019 Sarah Grace was violently sexually assaulted in her home by a man who broke into her bedroom. She told us the harrowing story of that night and the battle she then had to fight to ensure her attacker was brought to justice. What she went through made her determined to speak out to help others who might have to go through the same thing. It is an eye opening account of how a survivor of sexual violence can emerge on the far side, and the legal hurdles in their way.</description></item><item><title>Episode 82 w/ Keith Treacy | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320098/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Keith Treacy&amp;rsquo;s story is one of great hope, tragedy and ultimately redemption. He was a footballing prodigy from the flats on Dublin&amp;rsquo;s Sheriff Street. Man Utd&amp;rsquo;s assistant manager was calling the family home in Dublin to plead with Keith to sign at just 13 years old, at 15 he was training with Premier League first teams, he played for Ireland and before long he was lining up against the game&amp;rsquo;s greats, like Leo Messi and Cristiano Ronaldo.</description></item><item><title>Episode 81 w/ John Kavanagh | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320099/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320099/</guid><description>Podcast Description John Kavanagh is known for becoming one of the most successful coaches in the MMA game - but his story was already a fascinating one long before he reached the UFC. John tells us about how he started a back alley gym in Dublin when almost nobody knew what MMA was and through years of hard graft turned that into an an international success story. And he tells us about how he turned a moment of adversity and pain into a new beginning, and why the lessons he learned from his own struggle can help anyone to transform their life.</description></item><item><title>Episode 80 w/ Iain Ward (King of Chemo) | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320100/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Iain Ward goes by the online name King of Chemo, and he has set himself the mission of breaking the world record for the most amount of money ever raised for charity by running a marathon. In just a few weeks he has racked up tens of thousands of followers trying to help him achieve his goal. Iain was diagnosed with a terminal brain tumor at the age of 30 but his attitude to his illness, and life in general, is incredibly uplifting and inspiring.</description></item><item><title>Episode 79 w/ Coolio | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320101/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320101/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a year of surreal moments for Talking Bollox, this is up there at the very top. We were joined in the studio by Coolio, the platinum selling, Grammy winning rapper who has created some of the most famous songs in hip hop history.
We talked about his life growing up in Compton and he tells us about some extreme moments of violence he witnessed. We also go back to his early days in the music game, and then of course the massive global success he enjoyed with hits like &amp;ldquo;Gangsta&amp;rsquo;s Paradise&amp;rdquo;, and the legacy he enjoys today.</description></item><item><title>Episode 78 - Relaxed 2.0 | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320102/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320102/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s the two boys this week, enjoying a nice relaxed chat ahead of the live show in Vicar Street on Sunday. We talk about what it&amp;rsquo;s like going to festivals and concerts sober, if going on a date is leading someone on, the many uses of the words bollocks, and our ridiculous demands backstage at live shows.,
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 77 w/ Ciaran Moran | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320103/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ciaran is a singer/songwriter from Dublin&amp;rsquo;s north inner city and a man whose music speaks about where he, and we, came from. He joined us to talk about life growing up in the area, his musical inspirations, what inspires him to make his music, and he has a very questionable zinger. There was plenty more in this episode too, including the biggest viral moment of the week - Terence&amp;rsquo;s very public, and very embarrassing, fall.</description></item><item><title>Episode 76 w/ Lynsey Bennett | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320104/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 15:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lynsey Bennett is our guest this week. She was first diagnosed with cervical cancer in 2017 and endured three and a half years of hell while undergoing chemo
She fills us in about life now after the most challenging 18 months, she updates us on how she has managed to keep her cancer stable using holistic treatments and gives us the results of her most recent trip to Germany.</description></item><item><title>Episode 75 w/ Tony O'Reilly | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320105/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320105/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is one of the most incredible stories we&amp;rsquo;ve heard yet, and the first time we have taken a deep dive into the world of problem gambling. Tony stole €1.75m from his employer to fund a gambling habit that got so out of control he lost of €10m in total, including almost half a million in just 12 hours. This is a great insight into the grip gambling can take on people and how addicts can live a double life with what can be a totally secret addiction.</description></item><item><title>Episode 74 w/ Eddie Mullins | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320106/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eddie Mullins is the Governor of Mountjoy Prison. He came in to us to give us an insight into life in Irish prisons, from the perspective of the prisoners and the prison guards. His views on life, punishment, and rehabilitation are fascinating and it was a pleasure to sit down and get an incredible look into a world that almost everyone has an opinion on, but very few know.</description></item><item><title>Episode 73 w/ Anna Clifford | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320107/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Anna came in to us this week to tell us about her career on stage from Canada to the UK and back home again, to help us with some very tough zingers, and offer some valuable advice on dealing with stage fright ahead of our live show - including some of her own experiences of what it&amp;rsquo;s lime to have a disaster on stage, and just keep going with it.</description></item><item><title>Episode 72 - Revealed | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320108/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320108/</guid><description>Podcast Description We did an Ask Us Anything this week where we took your questions, and they&amp;rsquo;re a mixed bag. We covered everything from choosing between if you would give up crisps or sweets for life, to our biggest influences in life, the growing pressure of social media to show wealth (whether its real or imagined) and misconceptions around ADHD. This one was a lot of fun and also threw us a few curveballs to really think about.</description></item><item><title>Episode 71 w/ Christy Dignam Part 2 | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320109/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Christy Dignam is one of the legends of Irish life, and his experiences have given him an incredible insight into far more than just the music business.
We&amp;rsquo;ve had Christy on the show back in the early days and we felt there was a lot more to talk about so we asked him to join us again. We talked about everything from his battles with addiction, to Aslan&amp;rsquo;s plane crash, to the hoodie v jumper debate, and Christy weighs in on the Beatles V Oasis debate.</description></item><item><title>Episode 70 w/ Karl McManus | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320110/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Karl is one of the boys, he&amp;rsquo;s better known by his online persona Awful Gas. He started out streaming and making videos during the pandemic and has developed a large online community, with big followings on YouTube, TikTok and Twitch. This episode is a prime example of how a Talking Bollox episode can spiral far beyond the guest&amp;rsquo;s story. We cover everything from conspiracy theories to ghosts and aliens.</description></item><item><title>Episode 69 w/ Eric Donovan | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320111/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eric Donovan is a boxer and a person with a story unlike any other. He came in to tell us his incredible life story and talk about plenty besides that, including his favourite podcasts, the problems some kids face when school doesn&amp;rsquo;t work for them, proving the doubters wrong, redemption in life and sport, and of course a bit about boxing! Above all Eric and the lads talk about how recovery is a journey with no destination, but the destination isn&amp;rsquo;t the point.</description></item><item><title>Episode 68 - The Live Show | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320112/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320112/</guid><description>Podcast Description One month ago we took a huge step and brought Talking Bollox out of the studio and to the people, playing our first ever live show at a sold out Liberty Hall. It was an unforgettable night, with guest Senator Lynn Ruane, Hughie Maughan and Al Foran all joining us for an incredible evening with a crazy crowd.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 67 - Reloaded | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320113/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320113/</guid><description>Podcast Description We go back to the two boys this week, and we&amp;rsquo;re running through a few things listeners have asked us to speak about. We&amp;rsquo;re talking about Terence&amp;rsquo;s theory that the TV licence man doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist; Calvin&amp;rsquo;s eventful week on a ski holiday; Ireland&amp;rsquo;s response to the Ukrainian refugee crisis; Terence&amp;rsquo;s latest film reviews (controversial) and then the future of live shows for the pod - plus plenty more.</description></item><item><title>Episode 66 w/ Suzanne Jackson | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320114/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 18:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320114/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we welcome Suzanne Jackson to the Talking Bollox studio. Many of you will know her as SoSueMe, she is one of Ireland&amp;rsquo;s most famous people. What not many will know is how hard she grafted to become one of the most successful businesswomen in the country. A brand builder and entrepreneur she was one of the first bloggers in Ireland, long before anyone knew what an influencer was.</description></item><item><title>Episode 65 w/ Enya Martin | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320115/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 18:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320115/</guid><description>Podcast Description We finally met our match in the Talking Bollox world. We thought we were able to talk some bollox until we met Enya. There’s some great chats in this one and some mad detours including Tinder, American sports, Ronaldo and sign language. Enya also tells us about how she got into comedy from her first sketch to eventually selling out Vicar Street. Selling out Vicar St sounds like good craic doesn&amp;rsquo;t it?</description></item><item><title>Episode 64 w/ Des Bishop | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320116/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Des Bishop has had a fascinating life and he came in to offer us some of the knowledge he&amp;rsquo;s collected along the way - from dealing with imposter syndrome, to handling pressure, to the differences between choices and chances in all our lives.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 63 w/ Dr Brian Pennie Part 2 | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320117/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320117/</guid><description>Podcast Description We all remember Brian from his first appearance in episode 37, but while that chat was about his personal story, this is him bringing his incredible professional knowledge to the table.
He explains to us what happens to the body and brain during periods of addiction and stress, and the scientific tactics that can help us all battle those things. He also explores why we end up in those states in the first place.</description></item><item><title>GoLoud Selects | Talking Bollox on Unusual Suspects | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320118/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320118/</guid><description>Podcast Description A short message from Terence and Calvin about a brand new true crime podcast coming from one of our team here at Talking Bollox. Unusual Suspects is the incredible story of a $7.4m armed heist in New York, and the FBI chasing an Irish priest and an ex-IRA man (turned comic book dealer) in connection with it. This story and the characters in it are incredible, it grips you right from the start and it is absolutely top notch.</description></item><item><title>Episode 62 w/ Roddy Collins | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320119/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 18:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320119/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week it&amp;rsquo;s the one and only Roddy Collins. There&amp;rsquo;s nobody quite like him in football and it was a pleasure to sit down and hear some of the stories from a long career in the game, a lifetime around Dublin city, and watching his younger brother, Steve, rise to the top of the boxing game and become world champion.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 61 w/ Ger &amp; Gavin Power | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320120/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320120/</guid><description>Podcast Description At last we finally managed to get the three Power brothers in the studio together, as Terence&amp;rsquo;s brothers Gavin and Ger join us to talk about life growing up with Terry Flower. You&amp;rsquo;ll have heard Terence&amp;rsquo;s story before, from both him and his ma, but his brothers have their own perspective and we wanted to hear that. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of laughs and funny stories in this one, but on a more serious side the lads talk about how so many kids are written off by society because of their circumstances, but there can be hope for anyone.</description></item><item><title>Episode 60 w/ Jenny Keane | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320121/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 18:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320121/</guid><description>Podcast Description As it&amp;rsquo;s Valentine&amp;rsquo;s week we decided to bring in a sex educator. Absolutely nothing is off limits in this episode! Jenny has made her name talking about sex with an honesty and openness we don&amp;rsquo;t often hear in Irish society. and this week she&amp;rsquo;s taking all of your questions. You definitely don&amp;rsquo;t want to miss this one!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 59 w/ Darren Lalor | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320122/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 18:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320122/</guid><description>Podcast Description Darren Lalor maybe isn&amp;rsquo;t as well known as some of our guests, but his story is no less fascinating or inspirational. Darren grew up in Finglas and left school at 14. He went on to have a career managing many music acts, including Aslan. Later in life he was making a living as a taxi drive, and decided he wanted to train to become a barrister. It was a long, hard road that involved him studying at night while he sat in his car between fares, but he pulled it off.</description></item><item><title>Episode 58 - Riveted | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320123/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 18:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320123/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week it&amp;rsquo;s just the two boys. It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since we sat down with just the two of us, talked bollox and had a laugh - so this week we&amp;rsquo;ve got a lot of zingers, our quiz battle returns and we talk through a few topics listeners asked us to cover.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 57 w/ Pat Divilly | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320124/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pat Divilly is an expert on mental and physical wellness, with a wealth of insight into how we can improve our lives with simple steps. Pat is renowned for his books, seminars and workshops, and he came in to tell us his story about how struggles in his 20s set him on a new path in life, and share some of what he has learned on his journey.</description></item><item><title>Episode 56 w/ Ardal O'Hanlon | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320125/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 18:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320125/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;rsquo;re joined by Irish comedy legend Ardal O&amp;rsquo;Hanlon. Ardal has some brilliant stories and tells us about going from life as a shy kid in County Monaghan, living in the shadow of The Troubles, to becoming one of the most recognisable faces in Irish comedy. We of course talk about being Father Dougal Maguire, but there&amp;rsquo;s a lot more to this than just Father Ted.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 55 w/ Caoimhin Agyarko | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320126/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320126/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;rsquo;re joined by one of the hottest prospects in Irish boxing, WBA International Champion, Caoimhin Agyarko.
Caoimhin talks to us about growing up in Belfast, how he got into boxing, and how he has dealt with racist abuse throughout his life. He also tells us about when he was stabbed on a night out in Belfast a few years ago. It was an attack that very nearly cost him his life and changed his whole perspective on the world.</description></item><item><title>Episode 54 w/ Jim Sheridan | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320127/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 18:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jim Sheridan is a giant of Irish cinema, and one of our own. From Sheriff Street, Jim has made some of Ireland&amp;rsquo;s most famous and powerful films, including &amp;lsquo;In the Name of the Father&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;My Left Foot&amp;rsquo;.
He&amp;rsquo;s worked with some of the greats of cinema and he&amp;rsquo;s been nominated for six Oscars. He tells us how a lad from Dublin 1 conquered the world, and about working with people like 50 Cent and Daniel Day Lewis.</description></item><item><title>Episode 53 w/ Ross Tierney | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320128/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 18:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320128/</guid><description>Podcast Description At just 20 years of age Ross Tierney has achieved a lot, establishing himself as a star of the Bohs first team, playing for Ireland under-21s and earning himself a transfer to Scottish Premiership side Motherwell.
But what he has gone through off the pitch is on another level entirely. He suffered a deep personal tragedy when he lost his best friend to suicide, and faced one of the toughest situations imaginable for any new parent when his newborn son was born with serious complications.</description></item><item><title>Episode 52 w/ Willa White Part 2 | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320129/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320129/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week marks one year of the Talking Bollox Podcast, so it was a time for our birthday celebration. And then Willa White announced the death of the zinger.
But we bounced back for a chat that looked back on an incredible year, the Talking Bollox Awards, and a bumper quiz. On top of all that there were some powerful moments and a lot of laughs, courtesy of Willa.</description></item><item><title>Episode 51 w/ Jack Byrne | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320130/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 18:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320130/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ireland international Jack Byrne comes in to talk to us about his journey in football, going from playing under Patrick Viera at Man City to playing in Holland, the Championship and eventually playing for Ireland. He talks about the personal struggles he faced as he moved between clubs, and why he finally decided he wanted to move home. He also talks to us about how Irish football can move to the next level and he tells us some of the best players he played with and against</description></item><item><title>Episode 50 w/ Miriam Mullins | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320131/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 18:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Miriam is one of the biggest social media content creators in Ireland. She comes in to talk to us about how she built a massive global social media audience in a short space of time and her journey from lockdown to The Late Late Show, with a stop off in South Africa. We also talk about why social media is the new mainstream media, and much more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 49 w/ Adrian Kennedy | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320132/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320132/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adrian Kennedy is the king of talk radio. He comes in off the bat with some very controversial zingers! He comes in to talk to us about growing up, getting in to radio, how big the phoneshow was and the impact it had. He tells us some of his most memorable phone calls it &amp;amp; behind the scenes about the days of the show when it was one of the biggest in the country.</description></item><item><title>Episode 48 w/ Joe McGucken Part 2 | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320133/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320133/</guid><description>Podcast Description We have a serious bit of craic in this one, but then we get in to why we got Joe in for a part 2, because a lot was left unsaid in Part 1. This is a very raw, gripping story about Joe&amp;rsquo;s loss of his brother and father and the miracle birth of his son Ollie ‘Ice’ McGucken.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 47 - Retrograde | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320134/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320134/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week it&amp;rsquo;s just the two boys with a few things to talk about. We talk about how Calvin caused murder with some comments on the law of attraction, and we talk about mindfulness/mindset and how big a role it plays in success and failure in life. We talk about travel and the new experiences it can bring you, and we did a bit of a quiz this week too, with the two boys going head to head.</description></item><item><title>Episode 46 w/ Stall It | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320135/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 17:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320135/</guid><description>Podcast Description We have a very different episode for you this week. We recorded a crossover episode with Darren Conway and Joe McGucken, the lads from the Stall It podcast, and it&amp;rsquo;s a mad listen that gets hectic.This episode is 4 lads talking about anything, letting the conversation go anywhere, causing slaughter and having the craic. There&amp;rsquo;s no structure to this one, but loads of laughs about haircuts and runners and Halloween memories, and plenty of real talk about fame and the work that goes into a podcast.</description></item><item><title>Episode 45 w/ Sinead Kavanagh | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320136/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 17:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320136/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Sinead Kavanagh joins us in the GoLoud Studios. Sinead is on the cusp of becoming world champion with her upcoming fight against Cris Cyborg. Sinead comes in to talk to us about her road to this career defining moment, what life was like growing up, going from being homeless with her child living in B&amp;amp;B&amp;rsquo;s to now preparing for one of the biggest fights in female MMA history.</description></item><item><title>Episode 44 w/ Roddy Doyle | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320137/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320137/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;rsquo;re joined this week by one of Ireland&amp;rsquo;s most famous writers, Roddy Doyle, whose Barrytown books are arguably still Dublin city&amp;rsquo;s favourite novels.Roddy joined us to talk about everything from his inspirations, his work writing novels and films, his life growing up in Kilbarrack, his view on how Dublin city is changing today &amp;amp; so much more.He even criticised how we spell “Talking Bollox”.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 43 w/ Graham Burke | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320138/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320138/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we have our first ever footballer on the pod! Graham Burke plays for Shamrock Rovers and has been capped for Ireland, is a D1 native and someone with a fascinating story about life in professional football. He tells us about achieving every boys dream of securing a move to a Premier League club. We talked about how politics and decisions can hamper your career in football. He also tells us how coming back to Ireland isn’t always a step down in football and why playing football in Ireland is starting to offer big opportunities to young players.</description></item><item><title>Episode 42 w/ Joe McGucken | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320139/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320139/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we talk to one of Ireland&amp;rsquo;s rising stars and D1 native, Joe McGucken. The skinny fella is representing D1 on the comedy scene and as the host of &amp;lsquo;Stall It&amp;rsquo;, his own GoLoud podcast, alongside Darren Conway. We had some buzz with Joe but it’s not all laughs, he&amp;rsquo;s gone through some struggles in his life and he told us about the highs and lows along the way and the life lessons he has taken from the tough times.</description></item><item><title>Episode 41 w/ Glenn 'Sauso' Murray (Part 2) | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320140/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320140/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we welcome back one of our most memorable interviewees, Glenn &amp;lsquo;Sauso&amp;rsquo; Murray. Glenn talks to us about heartbreak, the reason why he hitch hiked around Ireland to raise awareness for mixing alcohol and drugs with your mental health. He touches on ADHD &amp;amp; OCD+ in detail and everything he’s done since he appeared on episode 9 at the start of the year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 40 w/ Wayne Hart | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320141/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wayne Hart is a reformed criminal. We talked to him about his life of crime, he reflects on how the sexual abuse he suffered as a child led to him turning from the victim to the monster, and the pain he caused people during those years.Wayne has spent 17 years in prison but is now dedicating his life to preventing people following in his footsteps. We had Wayne on as part of the @get_themessage_out campaign.</description></item><item><title>Episode 39 w/ Mick Conlan | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320142/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320142/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;rsquo;re joined by one of Ireland&amp;rsquo;s most famous sportspeople - World and European champions and Olympic medalist, Mick Conlan.Mick tells us about what it was like growing up in Belfast, his journey through amateur boxing, the infamous Olympics scandal and his transition to the pro game with his plans for the future. We also talk about the legacy the Troubles left in Mick&amp;rsquo;s hometown, and the work he is doing now to try to combat the scourge of mental health problems there.</description></item><item><title>Episode 38 - Resonate | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320143/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320143/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a few weeks of guests we go back to the two boys. This week we touch on some personal topics in regards to traits associated with ADHD and how this impacts day to day life for Terence, and we also give an insight into the thought process of what goes into an episode of Talking Bollox.We go into detail of the school system and the drain it can have on families, and the two boys talk about their very different lives in education.</description></item><item><title>Episode 37 w/Brian Pennie | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320144/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 17:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320144/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is a powerful episode. Brian went from being at death&amp;rsquo;s door to turning his life around after battling addiction to heroin and other drugs for over 20 years, to now being a published author and studying for his PhD. He tells us about his lowest points and the self destruction of addiction and tells us how anyone in that situation can turn their life around.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 36 w/ Emmet Brennan | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320145/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 17:40:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320145/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Emmet talks to us about his journey to becoming an Olympian, he tells us about suffering with depression, to backing himself, getting credit union loans to pursue his Olympic dream and all the set backs that came with the journey. He gives us an insight into the Olympic village also. Emmet&amp;rsquo;s story is inspirational, he’s one of our own from Dublin&amp;rsquo;s north inner city and he’s an absolute gent.</description></item><item><title>Episode 35 w/Dylan Moran | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320146/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 17:35:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320146/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we have first ever culchie on the show, one of Ireland&amp;rsquo;s most exciting professional boxers, Dylan Moran. In this episode Dylan tells us some mad stories from his days travelling around the world with boxing, from his youth in Waterford, to ending up in scary situations in Tijuana, on to fighting for millionaires in the Alps to training with Conor McGregor in Portugal. His journey has been incredible already and it was brilliant to have him on the show.</description></item><item><title>Episode 34 w/Nicola Tallant | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320147/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 17:35:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320147/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we talk to Ireland&amp;rsquo;s most famous crime journalist, Nicola Tallant.We&amp;rsquo;ve been critical of Nicola on this podcast in the past but we wanted to understand more about her work and why she does what she does. We asked her about her perception of the north inner city and whether it gets a fair shake in the media.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 33 w/ Marty Guilfoyle | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320148/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 17:35:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320148/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Marty tells us about life growing up, how he got into DJing, how tiktok got him a huge record deal, and dealing with social media hate around joining the goat house. And of course we ask him if he pisses in the shower. We had a great laugh and the energy was electric!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 32 - Relaxed | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320149/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 17:30:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320149/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we go with just the 2 of us as we have a good bit to talk about after settling in to the new studio (in our sliders).In this episode we talk about a new venture that we have coming up, we have a good laugh in this one and a few zingers, we talk about our interview with The Journal and a few more important topics that yous have suggested we talk about.</description></item><item><title>Episode 31 w/ Senator Lynn Ruane | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320150/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 17:30:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320150/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Lynn talks to us about life growing up, about taking drugs from as early as 11 years old, robbing cars, and getting pregnant at 15 with her first of 2 daughters.She tells us about her journey through a mad childhood and teenage years to becoming a senator. She proves that anybody can do whatever they want once they put their mind to it!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 30 w/ Hughie Maughan | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320151/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 17:30:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320151/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Hughie talks to us about growing up in Ballymun, life as a Traveller in Ireland, coming out as gay within his community, and his reality TV career. And, of course, we ask him if he pisses in the shower.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 29 w/ Darren Conway | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320152/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 18:00:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320152/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode Darren talks to us about how he got started with his sketches, screaming at crips, and drops a little Talking Bollox exclusive. We had a good bit of laugh in this episode and we hope yous enjoy it, thanks for coming in Darren ya legend!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ready for the big jump | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320153/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 14:38:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320153/</guid><description>Podcast Description The lads record from Calvin’s kitchen one last time to send a short message about the next big step.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 28 w/ Orlagh &amp; Sinead Wheelock | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320154/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 17:19:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320154/</guid><description>Podcast Description Orlagh and Sinead aresisters to the late Terence Wheelock who died due to his injuries he sustained in Garda custody in 2005. They along with the rest of their family have been fighting and campaigning for an independent inquiry into the circumstances surrounding their brothers death and the aftermath that followed.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 27 - Responsibility | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320155/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 17:35:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320155/</guid><description>Podcast Description The lads sit down this week to discuss a wide range of topics from the lottery to the events on South William Street to the responsibility of being a parent and showing maturity for your actions in life. Plenty of bollox talked and even Conor has a mic this week.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 26 w/ Gemma Dunleavy | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320156/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 17:45:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320156/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gemma Dunleavy is a singer/song writer from the heart of Dublin. She joins the lads to talk about life growing up in different flat complexes, her musical journey, inner city life and how the working class people are being priced out of their own area but still maintain their unique characterisitcs.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 25 w/ The WallFella | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320157/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 18:03:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320157/</guid><description>Podcast Description Willo Wall aka The WallFella is an up and coming Irish rapper from the flats. He sits down with the lads to discuss the current climate living in Ireland, what inspired him to get into hip hop and what it was like in the flats growing up towards the current generations upbringing.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 24 w/ Ellie Kelly | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320158/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 17:59:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320158/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ellie Kelly is one of Ireland&amp;rsquo;s leading social media influencers. She joins the lads to talk about the stigma of her role in society, her plans for the future and of course to talk loads of bollox.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 23 w/ Rachel Power (Terence's Ma) | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320159/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 17:53:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320159/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rachel Power is Terence&amp;rsquo;s Ma, she joins the lads to talk about her trauma growing up and her struggles with addictio and how her and her son are breaking the generational cycle.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 22 - Relapse | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320160/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 17:43:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320160/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week the lads discuss a hard hitting topic &amp;ldquo;Relapsing&amp;rdquo; and how unprepared people can be for it. There is many benefits of being sober but the burden of falling off the wagon is always there. There is also plenty of zingers and usua laughs.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 21 w/ Kiefer Crosbie | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320161/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 17:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320161/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kiefer &amp;ldquo;Big Daddy&amp;rdquo; Crosbie is a professional mixed martial artist from the inner city of Dublin currently fighting in the Bellator orgainisation. He joins the lads today to talk about growing up in Dublin, how he got into martial arts, what it takes to become a world champion, Dublin at Halloween time and much more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 20 w/ Willie White | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320162/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 17:15:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320162/</guid><description>Podcast Description Willie White is a stand up comedian, actor, singer and scaffolder from Ballymun. He joins the lads to talk about his struggle with addiction, time in prison and what it&amp;rsquo;s like on stage as a comedian.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 19 w/ Charleen Murphy | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320163/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 16:43:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320163/</guid><description>Podcast Description Charleen Murphy is a n Irish fashion blogger and social media influencer. She joins the lads to talk about online abuse, her experience with school &amp;amp; college and her plans for the future for herself as a brand and other business ventures. There is also a whole load of zingers that have been demanded over the past few weeks that are finally addressed.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 18 w/ Thomas Carty | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320164/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 17:58:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320164/</guid><description>Podcast Description Thomas Carty is a Dublin 7 native who has just signed professional as Irelands hottest prospect in heavyweight boxing. He joins the lads to talk about growing up in Dublin, Easter eggs, spiritual readings and of course boxing!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 17 w/ Christy Dignam | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320165/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 17:59:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320165/</guid><description>Podcast Description Christy Dignam is the lead singer of Aslan. He is a recovered drug addict currently battling cancer. He joins the lads to talk about his journey through life, music, addiction and what it&amp;rsquo;s like living through covid.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 16 w/ Mick The Busker | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320166/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 18:35:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320166/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mick &amp;ldquo;The Busker&amp;rdquo; McLoughlin is a Dublin busker known for performing on Henry street. He joins the lads to talk about his life growing up, his love of music, becoming homeless and how his relationship saved his life. He also performs a series of songs related to different moments of his life.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 15 w/ Ger Redmond | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320167/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 18:38:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320167/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ger Redmond is an Irish professional Triathlete. He joins the lads to talk about his life growing up in Darndale in Dublin, moving to Scotland to become a pro footballer before having to return home to raise his sibilings all at the age of 16. Ger went on to become a criminal and became incarcerated where he decided to turn his life around and set out on his journey which got him to where he is today.</description></item><item><title>Episode 14 w/ Pierce O'Leary | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320168/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 18:22:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320168/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pierce is professional boxer with a current perfect record of 6 wins and no loses. He&amp;rsquo;s born and raised in Dublins inner city and he joins the lads to talk about growing up in sheriff street, his journey to becoming a professional boxer, the sacrifices he has had to make along the way and pyramid schemes!
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 13 - Reflection | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320169/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 18:33:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320169/</guid><description>Podcast Description For this episode the lads go back to how they started, just the two of then talking bollox! They reflect on all things lockdown related and how thats turned the nation against itself as well as one of the most overlooked additions in gambling.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 12 w/ Liam Cunningham | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320170/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 18:43:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320170/</guid><description>Podcast Description Liam Cunningham is an Irish actor best known for his role as &amp;ldquo;Davosn Seaworth&amp;rdquo; in Game of Thrones. He joins the lads via Zoom to tell his story about how he got into acting, being a sparks in Africa and becoming starstruck working with some big names.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 11 w/ Philly McMahon | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320171/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 18:59:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320171/</guid><description>Podcast Description Philly McMahon is an 8 time All Ireland winner with Dublin football. He has countless acolades within the GAA world but it is for his work with drug policies, social change and love of &amp;ldquo;the hip knocker&amp;rdquo; that he joins the lads today.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 10 w/ Yin Yoga Jen | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320172/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 18:57:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320172/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jen Healy btter known as &amp;ldquo;YinYogaJen&amp;rdquo; to her clients is a qualified mental health practitionor and Yin Yoga teacher. She joins the lads to talk about her past traumatic experiences, how finding Yin Yoga has helped heal her mentally and talk loads of bollox about society, sociel media and bouncers being pricks,
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 9 w/ Glen Murray | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320173/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 19:14:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320173/</guid><description>Podcast Description Glen &amp;ldquo;Sauso&amp;rdquo; Murray is a globe trotting sensation from the heart of Dublin. He joins the lads to talk about his journey not only around the globe but his journey to becoming sober as well as an internatinal chef.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 8 w/ Craig O'Brien | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320174/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 18:44:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320174/</guid><description>Podcast Description Craig O&amp;rsquo;Brien is an Irish professional boxer and an Irish champion. He joins the lads to talk about growing up in the flats, addiction, his time in prison and how he turned all of it around by going pro in the Irish boxing scene. The lads also touch on their experience with Covid 19.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 7 w/ Cheryl Lyons | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320175/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 18:26:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320175/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cheryl Lyons is a makeup artist turned entrepreneur. She joined the lads to talk all things from her past, what drives her ambition and running a business throughout mutiple lockdowns.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 6 w/ TheWheloFella | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320176/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 18:21:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320176/</guid><description>Podcast Description TheWheloFella is an Irish rapper and a member of the Irish defence forces. He sat down with the lads to discuss his success in the Irish rap scene, his journey to the army and the best burger in Dublin.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 5 - Recap | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320177/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 18:50:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320177/</guid><description>Podcast Description The lads have a quick recap and reflection of current affairs, how the podcast has taken off and where they see it going in the new year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 4 w/ Conor Ryan | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320178/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 18:28:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320178/</guid><description>Podcast Description Conor is a social media influencer. He joins the lads to talk about red sauce, OnlyFans and the pressure social media can cause on a person and their relationships.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 3 w/ Carly Mahady | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320179/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 21:31:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320179/</guid><description>Podcast Description Carly is a breast cancer survivor at the age of 25 and is advocating for the breast check age in Ireland to be lowered. She joins the lads at the kitchen table to talk cancer, chicken fillet rolls and raves.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 2 - Background | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320180/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 18:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two lads having a chat about their backgrounds, addiction, mental health, physical wellbeing and King or Tayto.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 1 - Intro | Talking Bollox Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1521320181/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 17:33:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1521320181/</guid><description>Podcast Description Just a brief intro into what can be discussed off the cuff sitting at a kitchen table.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>