<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>American English Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/american-english-podcast/</link><description>Recent content in American English Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 13:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/american-english-podcast/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>155 - Decades: The 1980s with Alex | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990172/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990172/</guid><description>Podcast Description Earlier this year, I asked some friends and family members if they could write a short story about their favorite decade. A decade is a ten-year time frame. For example, 1970-1979 is a decade. 1980 -1989 is another decade. I asked some friends and family members if they could write a short story about their favorite decade.
My thought was that it would be interesting to step out of the 2020s and relive a decade in the life of someone else.</description></item><item><title>154.2 - The Boston Tea Party + U.S. Independence from Britain | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990001/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Boston is situated in present-day Massachusetts, right on the northern Atlantic coastline. It’s picturesque, it’s lively and it’s steeped in stories of how the United States gained its independence from Britain. Today you’ll hear those tales of organization, patriotism and madness: This is the Boston Tea Party. I&amp;apos;ve also put together a page to Prepare for the U.S. Citizenship test. Premium Content: Season 4 (Episodes 150 - 200) = Includes quiz, transcript with definitions and mp3.</description></item><item><title>154 - Expression: My Cup of Tea | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990002/</guid><description>Podcast Description This lesson has two parts. In part one, you&amp;apos;ll learn the common English expression &amp;quot;my cup of tea&amp;quot; you&amp;apos;ll hear a joke and you&amp;apos;ll do some pronunciation exercises.
In part two (which will be posted shortly), you&amp;apos;ll learn about one of the most iconic events in U.S. history, the Boston Tea Party. It&amp;apos;s one of the major events that fueled our fight for independence from Britain, and the story is just nuts.</description></item><item><title>153 - 5-Minute English: Shopping for Clothes | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Every year, more and more people buy clothes online, but today, you are heading to the mall with your stylish friend, Katrina. Your mission is to buy a new wardrobe (a whole new set of clothes). Listen and learn the vocabulary, phrases and collocations we use when talking about clothing in English! You&amp;apos;ll learn adjectives to describe the good, the bad and the ugly, expressions to comment on style and so much more.</description></item><item><title>152 - The Legend of Sleepy Hollow (Halloween Special) | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sleepy Hollow is a quaint village nestled in the Hudson Valley, in New York. There, many many years ago a peculiar schoolteacher named Ichabod Crane gets wrapped up in the spooky legend of the Headless Horseman. Today you’ll hear “the Legend of Sleepy Hollow” and learn about the heart-pounding events that took place on one fateful Halloween night. It’s a story of love, rivalry, and the supernatural and I’ve simplified it for intermediate and advanced English learners.</description></item><item><title>151.2 - Moose in the U.S. (Do we live in harmony with our moose?) | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990005/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Moose are majestic creatures and an iconic symbol of wilderness in North America. They inhabit many northern states in the U.S.; the state with the biggest population is Alaska. In this episode, you&amp;apos;ll learn many English words related to nature and animals, but it&amp;apos;s much more than a National Geographic style lesson. You&amp;apos;re about to step into the funny, wild and sometimes tragic tales that emerge as humans and moose try to live harmoniously.</description></item><item><title>151 - Expression: To Steer Clear | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990006/</guid><description>Podcast Description This lesson has two parts. In part one, you&amp;apos;ll learn the common English expression &amp;quot;to steer clear,&amp;quot; you&amp;apos;ll hear a joke and you&amp;apos;ll do some pronunciation exercises.
In part two (which will be posted shortly), we&amp;apos;ll be talking about moose in the US. You know what a moose is, right? It&amp;apos;s a large mammal in the deer family. It has big antlers — these sort of long, pokey branch-like things that stick out of their heads — and they live in many northern states in the United States.</description></item><item><title>150 - Review: Season 3 | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two years ago, I started Season 3 (Episodes 101 - 150) and it&amp;apos;s been a journey. In this episode, you&amp;apos;ll hear about the many cultural topics we covered in the past 50 episodes. You&amp;apos;ll hear which episodes were the most popular among listeners, which stories left me speechless and which ones I found incredibly useful. Get your notebook! Be ready to write down the episode number for the stories that interest you most.</description></item><item><title>149 - 5-Minute English: Injuries and Getting Hurt | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today you&amp;apos;ll hear a short story our recent trip to Brazil, during which I ended up going to the hospital and getting stitches. Throughout this story you&amp;apos;ll hear 20+ words related to injuries and getting hurt. Although I hope you don&amp;apos;t get hurt anytime soon, I hope this lesson prepares you to talk about the times when you did in English.
We all have a getting hurt story, whether it&amp;apos;s our own or someone else&amp;apos;s.</description></item><item><title>148 - Language Learning with Ben Whately (Co-founder of Memrise) | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we have a special guest named Ben Whatley. Maybe you know him! He&amp;apos;s the Co-founder and Chief Strategy Officer at Memrise, one of the most celebrated language apps there is. Ben received his master&amp;apos;s in experimental psychology from Oxford University and has since been working with language acquisition. In fact, he&amp;apos;s a pioneer in the field; Ben helped create the first AI language partner using GPT3 technology. It&amp;apos;s called the MemBot.</description></item><item><title>147.2 - 10 Words a Day: German Words in English (11-20) | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990010/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990010/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is part two of a very special story about my dear friend, Nina, who is from Germany. In the story of our friendship, which I&amp;apos;ll wrap up in the this episode, you&amp;apos;ll learn 10+ German loanwords in English. A loanword is a words borrowed from a foreign language.
American English has many German words; how do we pronounce them? Well, I know a lot of you are saying we butcher them, that&amp;apos;s okay (I don&amp;apos;t disagree with you!</description></item><item><title>147 - 10 Words a Day: German Words in English (1-10) | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990011/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;apos;s story time! Welcome to a true story about my friend, Nina, who is from Berlin, Germany. In the story of our friendship you&amp;apos;ll learn 10+ German loanwords in English. A loanword is a words borrowed from a foreign language.
American English has many German words; how do we pronounce them? Well, I know a lot of you are saying we butcher them, that&amp;apos;s okay (I don&amp;apos;t disagree with you!</description></item><item><title>146.2 - The Incredible Flight of "Lawn Chair" Larry (Larry Walters) | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990012/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today&amp;apos;s episode, you’ll hear the incredible story of a man named Larry Walters, or &amp;quot;Lawn Chair&amp;quot; Larry, who bought over 40 weather balloons, attached them to a lawn chair in his backyard and flew 16,000 feet up in the air.
The story is weird and funny, and it gives way to a larger discussion about “Cluster Ballooning.” I’ll explain challenging words and phrases as I go along!</description></item><item><title>146 - Expression: Up in the Air | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990013/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990013/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today&amp;apos;s episode, you&amp;apos;ll learn all about the common English expression &amp;quot;up in the air.&amp;quot; You&amp;apos;ll learn the expression&amp;apos;s origin, how to use it in a multitude of situations and you&amp;apos;ll do pronunciation exercises with it. The second part of this episode, is all about Larry &amp;quot;Lawnchair,&amp;quot; a man who gave birth to cluster ballooning as an activity. Stay tuned, that episode will be posted shortly.
Big shoutout to Guilherme Krause for supporting the podcast this month, I really appreciate it!</description></item><item><title>145 - Discover Maine with Brent Watson | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990014/</guid><description>Podcast Description The for this episode was recorded on March 22, so keep that in mind when listening to our discussion about the weather and daylight hours.
***ABOUT***
Maine is the easternmost and northernmost state in the contiguous United States, and it’s known for its expansive forests, breathtaking coastlines, and its unique New England culture.
Today, we&amp;apos;re going to talk to Brent (Speak English with This Guy), who is a middle school English teacher from Maine.</description></item><item><title>144.2 - The Kentucky Derby | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990015/</guid><description>Podcast Description At the beginning of May every year, horse racing season begins. In the U.S., it starts off with The Kentucky Derby, a horse race that is often referred to as “the most exciting two minutes of sports.” 🐎 Since 1875, eager spectators have been pouring into Churchill Downs in Louisville, Kentucky to watch the ca. 20 racers make their way to the finish line. Just given how long the event has been around, you can probably imagine how many traditions there are at the event.</description></item><item><title>144 - Expression: To Jump the Gun | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990016/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you&amp;apos;ll learn how to use the common English expression &amp;quot;To Jump the Gun.&amp;quot; Be sure to stay tuned until part 2 to learn all about the Kentucky Derby, &amp;quot;the most exciting two minutes of sports.&amp;quot;
*****
Premium Content: This episode is part of Season 3. By purchasing Season 3 transcripts, you&amp;apos;ll be able to access the full episodes, the full PDF transcripts for episodes 101 - 150, an Mp3 download and the premium podcast player to work on your pronunciation.</description></item><item><title>143 - 5-Minute English: Grocery Shopping | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today you’ll hear about a trip to the grocery store. Imagine yourself as the main character of this story; visualize the interior of the store and that you are walking down the aisles. Picture everything from the moment you grab your cart or basket at the entrance, to the moment you check out at the register and head home.
As usual with 5-Minute English episodes, I try to keep the audio part of this lesson to 5 minutes.</description></item><item><title>142 - Discover Connecticut with Natalie Sawicki | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990018/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today&amp;apos;s episode, we&amp;apos;re talking to Natalie Sawicki, a songwriter from Los Angeles, who spent most of her life in Connecticut! She shares so much about this charming small state; you’ll hear about the fall foliage, New England fashion, local delicacies and much more!
Let&amp;apos;s Discover “The Nutmeg State&amp;quot; with a local!
Follow Natalie&amp;apos;s work on Instagram @natsawicki. *****
Connecticut is a small state. In fact, it&amp;apos;s the third smallest state in the United States after Rhode Island and Delaware.</description></item><item><title>141 - Chats with Shana: Parties and Poopers | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990019/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this 3-part episode, you&amp;apos;ll hear a casual discussion about one of life&amp;apos;s most mundane topics: peeing and pooping. It&amp;apos;s taboo to talk about, which is strange given how it&amp;apos;s one of the most common things in the world. In part 1, you’ll hear about potty training, you’ll hear a joke and learn some fun things. If you&amp;apos;re interested, here&amp;apos;s the Potty Training book I was talking about! (The E-book is FREE.</description></item><item><title>140.2. - The Story of Dr. Seuss ("The Father of Children's Literature") | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990020/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you don&amp;apos;t know who Dr. Seuss is, you should!
He was a cartoonist and author that brought us The Cat in the Hat, The Grinch, Green Eggs and Ham and over 40 other incredible books for children and adults around the world. He&amp;apos;s been called &amp;quot;the father of contemporary children&amp;apos;s literature.&amp;quot; One out of four children in the US receive a Dr. Seuss book as their first book in life, and there&amp;apos;s a good reason for it: they&amp;apos;re playful and clever, with quirky images and rhymes, and there&amp;apos;s a lot of repetition, so it&amp;apos;s ideal for beginner readers.</description></item><item><title>140 - Expression: Cat Got Your Tongue? | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990021/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990021/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;apos;s a ridiculous visual, is it not?! If the cat&amp;apos;s got your tongue, you can&amp;apos;t talk, you&amp;apos;re speechless! And that&amp;apos;s pretty much how we use it in English conversation. We often ask someone &amp;quot;Cat got your tongue?&amp;quot; in situations when they can&amp;apos;t respond, or they don&amp;apos;t respond. Listen to this episode to hear a joke, learn this expression and practice your pronunciation. This is Part 1. Stay tuned for Part 2, where we&amp;apos;ll talk about Dr.</description></item><item><title>139.2 - Mardi Gras in New Orleans | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990022/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Every year in New Orleans, Louisiana, a million visitors come to experience the biggest Mardi Gras party in the United States. Learn about the history of this event and the traditions and culture surrounding it.
If you plan on visiting, be sure to stay tuned until the very end; you&amp;apos;ll learn how to make the most of it as a tourist!
This is Part 2. In Part 1 of this episode, Episode 139, you&amp;apos;ll learn how to use the very common expression up one&amp;apos;s alley, you&amp;apos;ll heard a joke and practice your pronunciation!</description></item><item><title>139 - Expression: (To Be) Up One's Alley | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Isn&amp;apos;t it nice when you learn an English expression that you can use a million times a day, every single day that you speak English? Well, listen to this episode. In today&amp;apos;s episode, you&amp;apos;ll learn how to use the very common expression up one&amp;apos;s alley, you&amp;apos;ll hear a joke and you&amp;apos;ll practice your pronunciation! This is Part 1. Stay tuned for Part 2, where we&amp;apos;ll talk about the massive Mardi Gras celebration in New Orleans, Louisiana, and how you can take part in it!</description></item><item><title>138 - 5-Minute English: How to Order a Cocktail in English | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990024/</guid><description>Podcast Description You walk into a restaurant and head towards the bar. Behind it, a lighted mosaic of colorful liquors spread from the ceiling to the floor. It&amp;apos;s fancy on another level. Some people may describe it as resplendent; it feels like you&amp;apos;re looking into a Queen&amp;apos;s jewelry box.
A long counter separates you from the skilled bartender behind it, who shakes, stirs and strains with ease. As you approach, you consider how you&amp;apos;ll place your order in English and suddenly you feel out of your element.</description></item><item><title>137 - 10 Words a Day: French Words in English | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990025/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;apos;s story time! Welcome to a French coffee shop and fancy restaurant where you&amp;apos;ll be introduced to a number of common French loanwords in English. A loanword is a words borrowed from a foreign language.
American English is packed with French words; how do we pronounce them? Well, I know a lot of you are saying we butcher them, that&amp;apos;s okay (I don&amp;apos;t disagree with you!) In general, the pronunciation of a words depends on how popular / common a word is.</description></item><item><title>136 - Discover Michigan with Camille Hanson | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990026/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990026/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today&amp;apos;s episode, we&amp;apos;re talking to Camille Hanson, an ESL teacher and social media influencer who grew up in the U.P. - the Upper Peninsula of Michigan. Buckle up! You&amp;apos;re about to be immersed in an adventure; one that includes snow, lake life, deer flies, girls hunting with bows and arrows and so much more. Learn from a local how you can take advantage of &amp;quot;The Mitten State.&amp;quot;</description></item><item><title>135.2 - The Story of "Jingle Bells" | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990027/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990027/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s lesson you’re going to hear the story of the creator of Jingle Bells, his questionable character and we’ll go through the lyrics of the song so if you want to sing it in English, you can. This is Part 2. In Part 1, we spoke about the common English expression Bells and Whistles.
*****
In December of 1965, a spacecraft called Gemini 6 was flying in outer space, looking back down at earth.</description></item><item><title>135 - Expression: Bells and Whistles | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990028/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990028/</guid><description>Podcast Description The holiday season is here and I bet some of you are skimming the internet for new gadgets. Do you like gadgets with a bunch of bells and whistles (fancy features) or do you prefer simplicity? In this episode, you&amp;apos;ll learn how to use the common expression bells and whistles, you&amp;apos;ll hear a joke and you&amp;apos;ll practice your pronunciation! This is Part 1. Stay tuned for Part 2, where we&amp;apos;ll talk about the popular Christmas song Jingle Bells.</description></item><item><title>134.2 - The Story of Starbucks Coffee | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990029/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990029/</guid><description>Podcast Description You know Starbucks, right? The coffee company? Born in Seattle, Washington and brewed around the world? I bet you do; they have over 33 thousand stores in over 80 countries. In today&amp;apos;s episode, we&amp;apos;re going to talk about those guys, the beans and more! Why is it called Starbucks? Who&amp;apos;s that woman on their cups?
There are a lot of Starbucks haters and a lot of lovers out there, but all of you will find this episode fascinating because 1.</description></item><item><title>134 - Expression: To Blow Off Steam | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990030/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990030/</guid><description>Podcast Description The expression To Blow Off Steam is a common one in the United States. In today&amp;apos;s episode, you&amp;apos;ll learn how to use it in everyday contexts, you&amp;apos;ll hear a joke and also practice your pronunciation! :) Thanks again to my amazing supporters who have contributed to this podcast either by purchasing Premium Contentor buying me coffee!Thank you to Paulo, Picante, Stefan, Ortiz and the other anonymous contributors from this month.</description></item><item><title>133.2 - Common Similes with Liz (16 - 30) | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990031/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990031/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is PART 2 of episode 133. In today’s lesson, Liz and I will be going through 15 common similes that you’ll hear in everyday conversation. Some are literal, so they’ll sound normal, others are quite random so you may want to write these down in your notebook. If you would the full list of words, with examples and a quiz to make sure you’ve understood them, be sure to sign up to Premium Content at americanenglishpodcast.</description></item><item><title>133 - Common Similes with Liz (1-15) | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990032/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990032/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s lesson, Liz and I will be going through 15 common similes that you’ll hear in everyday conversation. Some are literal, so they’ll sound normal, others are quite random so you may want to write these down in your notebook. If you would the full list of words, with examples and a quiz to make sure you’ve understood them, be sure to sign up to Premium Content at americanenglishpodcast.</description></item><item><title>132 - Discover Colorado with Lindsay McMahon | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990033/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990033/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today&amp;apos;s episode, Lindsay, host of the All Ears English Podcast, will take us on a journey to Colorado, one of the most stunning mountainous states in the western United States.
On our 3-day trip to Colorado, via audio, we&amp;apos;ll not only get a taste of what it&amp;apos;s like to be a tourist there, but hear from a local&amp;apos;s standpoint what culture, beauty and adventures awaits us.
Be sure to check out the episode webpage for links to the places we talked about in this episode!</description></item><item><title>131 - 13 Common Superstitions in the U.S. and their Origins | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990034/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990034/</guid><description>Podcast Description We live in a day and age that is driven by science and technology, yet people are still superstitious. According to a study I read by YouGov, 9% of Americans claim to be superstitious, while another 35% admit to not being very superstitious, but somewhat. That makes over 40% of individuals in the United States somewhat superstitious.
So what does it mean to be superstitious? According to Cambridge Dictionary, it is to have beliefs that are not based on human reason or scientific knowledge, but are connected with old ideas about magic.</description></item><item><title>130 - Music: "Sunday Toasted" by Zinn | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990035/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990035/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;quot;Sunday Toasted&amp;quot; is a song that was recently released by a new artist named Zinn, and it&amp;apos;s jam-packed with American slang and vocabulary which we&amp;apos;ll go through in this episode. This song is also full of cultural references about working and partying :).
All in all, I can&amp;apos;t think of a more fitting song to be the first &amp;quot;music&amp;quot; episode on this podcast. By the end, you&amp;apos;ll have a beautiful picture in your mind of a typical summer&amp;apos;s day in the South and understand why lake culture is so big there!</description></item><item><title>129.2 - The Monster Study | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990036/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990036/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Monster Study (aka Tudor Study) is an unethical psychology experiment that was conducted in 1939 on 22 orphans in Davenport, Iowa. The goal was to a test the theory that by deeply worrying about starting to stutter, one may develop the speech disorder. Mary Tudor, a graduate student, attempted to induce stuttering - to create the behavior - in fluent speakers with the assistance of her advisor Wendell Johnson.</description></item><item><title>129 - Expression: Off the Record | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990037/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990037/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, there are two parts. In Part 1, you&amp;apos;ll hear a joke, practice your pronunciation and learn the expression &amp;quot;Off the Record&amp;quot;. In Part 2 of today&amp;apos;s lesson, we’re going to talk about The Monster Study, a wildly unethical study (by today&amp;apos;s standards) that is about orphans and language development, specifically stuttering.
To amp up the learning experience in episode 129, I explain challenging words and phrases as I go along.</description></item><item><title>128 - 5-Minute English: Birthday Parties | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990038/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990038/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today&amp;apos;s episode, you&amp;apos;ll learn vocabulary, phrasal verbs and expressions related to Birthday Parties. This episode was created with a goal in mind: to help you think about the birthday parties in your life. I hope that by the end of this lesson you feel like you can describe your special days with more detail in English.
This is an advanced listening exercise so it&amp;apos;s ok if you don&amp;apos;t understand everything!</description></item><item><title>127 - Discover Washington with Philip Clem | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990039/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990039/</guid><description>Podcast Description About
Philip Clem is a talented singer and songwriter from Seattle, Washington who has lived in San Francisco, Spain and now Los Angeles, California. Today, Philip is going to tell us about what it&amp;apos;s like to be a local from Seattle. In this episode, you&amp;apos;ll learn about the state, its stereotypes (and whether or not they&amp;apos;re true!), you’ll learn about the culture, food, weather and, of course, about our special guest!</description></item><item><title>126 - 5-Minute English: A Day At The Beach | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990040/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990040/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today&amp;apos;s 5-Minute English episode, you&amp;apos;ll learn vocabulary, phrasal verbs and collocations needed to describe A Day At The Beach.
Beach Recommendations
U.S. Beaches where you can drinkNude Beaches in the U.S.My favorite beaches in California: Pacific Beach - San DiegoPismo Beach - near San Luis ObispoLa Jolla - near San Diego (go kayaking + look at the lion sharks below!)Zuma Beach - Malibu (this is our go-to beach)Santa Cruz (go to the Boardwalk boardwalk, SO fun!</description></item><item><title>125.2 - Doughnuts (or Donuts!) | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990041/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we&amp;apos;re going to be talking about doughnuts (or donuts; both spellings are acceptable in American English). You&amp;apos;ll learn the history, the stories behind the most famous doughnut brands and all about the most popular doughnuts in the display case. After all, if you&amp;apos;re going to be the one who brings doughnuts to the office, you got to do it right.
Premium Content
This episode is part of Season 3.</description></item><item><title>125 - Expression: To Sugarcoat Something | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990042/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990042/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, there are two parts. In Part 1, you&amp;apos;ll hear a joke, practice your pronunciation and learn the expression &amp;quot;To Sugarcoat Something&amp;quot;. In Part 2 of today&amp;apos;s lesson (available on Saturday, July 23), we’re going to talk about donuts. You’ll learn the history, the stories behind the most famous brands and all about the most popular donuts in the display case. Afterall, if you’re going to be the one who brings donuts, you gotta do it right!</description></item><item><title>124 - 3 Must-Know Expressions for IELTS Speaking and Daily Life with Aubrey Carter | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990043/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990043/</guid><description>Podcast Description The decision to move overseas is a big one and it requires preparation. The first step for non-native English speakers who want to live, study or work in the U.S. is taking an English exam as proof of English ability. The IELTS exam is one of the most popular. Today, I had the pleasure of speaking with Aubrey Carter, who shared three expressions that you can use on the IELTS exam and in daily life.</description></item><item><title>123 - Goldilocks and The Three Bears (Phrasal Verb Fairy Tale) | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990044/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Goldilocks and The Three Bears is one of the most popular children&amp;apos;s books ever written in English and it is my daughter&amp;apos;s favorite. Today, you&amp;apos;ll hear a modernISH American English version of the classic tale and I&amp;apos;ve carefully selected a number of phrasal verbs, expressions and collocations and inserted them seamlessly into the story to amp up (improve, increase) the listening experience. If you&amp;apos;re trying to improve your use of more challenging tenses in English, listening to stories is a natural way to start mastering them!</description></item><item><title>122.1 Rosa Parks and The Freedom Movement (from Slavery to Civil Rights) | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990045/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990045/</guid><description>Podcast Description In honor of Juneteenth, we will be talking about &amp;quot;The Mother of the Freedom Movement&amp;quot; - Rosa Parks. Rosa made history when she politely refused to give her seat to a white passenger on a public bus in Alabama when institutionalized racial segregation existed in the South (Jim Crow Laws). Her story is one of courage; she&amp;apos;ll make you want to stand up for what&amp;apos;s right. Note: Juneteenth is on June 19th, and it&amp;apos;s been a federal holiday in the United States since 2021.</description></item><item><title>122 - Expression: Once in a Blue Moon | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990046/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990046/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you&amp;apos;ll learn how to use the common expression Once in a Blue Moon. In Part 2, which will be posted shortly, you&amp;apos;ll learn all about Rosa Parks and The Freedom Movement. Premium Content
This episode is part of Season 3. By purchasing Season 3 transcripts, you&amp;apos;ll be able to access the full episodes, the full PDF transcripts for episodes 101 - 150, an Mp3 download and the premium podcast player to work on your pronunciation.</description></item><item><title>121 - Chats with Shana: 5 Surprising Things About Los Angeles | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990047/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990047/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;apos;ve lived in Los Angeles for about 5 months and spend a lot of time exploring. I&amp;apos;m happy to say that the city is growing on us - we LOVE the restaurant scene here and checking out the stunning mansions, beautiful beaches and fun neighborhoods.
There are a few stereotypes about Los Angeles that you may have been exposed to if you watch films made in Hollywood. Up until this point, I&amp;apos;ve been pleasantly surprised to disagree with most of them.</description></item><item><title>120 - 5-Minute English: U.S. Geography | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990048/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today you&amp;apos;re going to learn so many fun facts about the US, all of which have to do with geography. You&amp;apos;ll hear about the topography, so the physical features of the land that make it visually unique. And you&amp;apos;ll also learn about the population - so where residents are distributed throughout the country.
By the end of this episode, you should have a solid geographical overview of the United States and be able to talk about geography in English.</description></item><item><title>119 - The Tale of Peter Rabbit by Beatrix Potter | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990049/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990049/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Tale of Peter Rabbit was published in 1902 by the British author and illustrator Beatrix Potter. Today I&amp;apos;ll read the story to you. What&amp;apos;s the moral of this story? Let us know via Instagram!
Premium Content
This episode is part of Season 3. By purchasing Season 3 transcripts, you&amp;apos;ll be able to access the full episodes, the full PDF transcripts for episodes 101 - 150, an Mp3 download and the premium podcast player to work on your pronunciation.</description></item><item><title>118 - Expression: Out of the Blue | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990050/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990050/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of the American English Podcast, you&amp;apos;ll learn how to use the common English expression OUT OF THE BLUE. In Part 2 (Episode 118.2), you&amp;apos;ll hear the story of the BLUE PEOPLE OF KENTUCKY.
Premium Content
This episode is part of Season 3. By purchasing Season 3 transcripts, you&amp;apos;ll be able to access the full episodes, the full PDF transcripts for episodes 101 - 150, an Mp3 download and the premium podcast player to work on your pronunciation.</description></item><item><title>118.2 - The Blue People of Kentucky | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990051/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Martin ended up falling in love with a redheaded American woman named Elizabeth Smith, and eventually the couple decided to have a family. Never in their wildest dreams could they have imagined what would come next: Four out of their seven children were born with blue skin.
In this episode of the American English Podcast, you&amp;apos;ll learn about THE BLUE PEOPLE OF KENTUCKY. In the first part of the episode, you&amp;apos;ll learn how to use the common English expression OUT OF THE BLUE.</description></item><item><title>117.2 - The Survival Story of Aron Ralston | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990052/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990052/</guid><description>Podcast Description We all love survival stories, do we not? Watching men and women find food and water, seeing them build shelters out of sticks, stones and leaves. It’s a common theme on reality television. Occasionally though, in real life, we hear real survival stories. People who were confronted with death and managed to escape it. Today you’ll hear the incredible story of Aron Ralston. You may know his story already if you’ve seen the movie 127 hours.</description></item><item><title>117 - Expression: Between a Rock and a Hard Place | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990053/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990053/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today&amp;apos;s episode you&amp;apos;ll learn how to use the common English expression BETWEEN A ROCK AND A HARD PLACE.
Premium Content
This episode is part of Season 3. By purchasing Season 3 transcripts, you&amp;apos;ll be able to access the full episodes, the full PDF transcripts for episodes 101 - 150, an Mp3 download and the premium podcast player to work on your pronunciation.
Follow along with the Season 3 audio (episodes 101-150) as episodes are released.</description></item><item><title>116 - 5-Minute English: Colds, Flus and Sickness | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990054/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990054/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this 5-Minute English episode, you&amp;apos;ll hear a lot of vocabulary and phrases related to Cold, Flus and Sickness.
This episode type is extra challenging, but short. Listen to it multiple times and consider transcribing the audio as a listening exercise. You can also dive deeper into this lesson by purchasing Premium Content. *****
IF YOU WANT TO SUPPORT REFUGEES IN EUROPE - CHECK BACK SOON! I WILL BE POSTING LINKS FOR HOW YOU CAN HELP (IF YOU WANT :)).</description></item><item><title>115 - 5-Minute English: Winter | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990055/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990055/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this 5-Minute English episode, you&amp;apos;ll hear a lot of vocabulary and phrases related to winter and the cold. You&amp;apos;ll also learn about the typical experience at a Colorado ski resort. This episode type is extra challenging, but short. Listen to it multiple times and consider transcribing the audio as a listening exercise. You can also dive deeper into this lesson by purchasing Premium Content. *****
Premium Content</description></item><item><title>114 - Dream House with Mara (Napa Valley Wine Country!) | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990056/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990056/</guid><description>Podcast Description After my last conversation with Pete about his &amp;quot;Dream House&amp;quot; in Australia (Ep. 109), I decided to ask my friends and family members about their dream home. My mom was the first to respond and this episode is her response. My mom&amp;apos;s dream house would be in Napa Valley in California, which is wine country here. As you can tell, she loves this topic - she uses all of the right terminology for stuff, some of it might be challenging to understand and that&amp;apos;s ok.</description></item><item><title>113 - Chats with Shana: We're Moving to Los Angeles! | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990057/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990057/</guid><description>Podcast Description We&amp;apos;re moving to Los Angeles, L.A. - the City of Angels. This is a Chats with Shana episode, what I&amp;apos;m thinking comes out of my mouth. Hear about the big adventure we&amp;apos;re about to embark on. I&amp;apos;m going to take you on this journey with us, WISH US LUCK!
Premium Content
This episode is part of Season 3. By purchasing Season 3 transcripts, you&amp;apos;ll be able to access the full episodes, the full PDF transcripts for episodes 101 - 150, an Mp3 download and the premium podcast player to work on your pronunciation.</description></item><item><title>112 - Embarrassing Stories with Charlie (British and American English) | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990058/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990058/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Charlie and I discuss all things embarrassing. This is your chance to hear some funny embarrassing stories, practice listening to British and American English and learn some amazing vocabulary (hear how we compare terms like &amp;quot; your fly is down,&amp;quot; &amp;quot;to let one slide&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;to eat shit&amp;quot;!)
Charlie also teaches us how to act appropriately if the Queen rips one (farts) at a fancy feast.</description></item><item><title>111.2 Is it IN Hawaii or ON Hawaii? (Prepositions with Locations) | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990059/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990059/</guid><description>Podcast Description The preposition in and on can be a nightmare, but in this short recording I hope to clarify some of the confusion when it comes to speaking about islands.
Yes, there will be a few exceptions to the rules here, but honestly this topic can get so convoluted, simplifying it the way I have will enable you to speak correctly about islands 99% of the time. The one exception probably worth mentioning is Rhode Island - Rhode Island is a state and when I visit, I&amp;apos;m IN Rhode Island.</description></item><item><title>111 - Chats with Shana: A Vacation in Hawaii | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990060/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Want to go on a vacation to Hawaii? In this episode, I speak about our recent trip to Oahu - the most visited and populous island in the archipelago. Hawaii was the 50th state to join the union and in this episode I give you a general overview of the islands and what you can do as a tourist there. Why do people from other states go there so often?</description></item><item><title>110 - 5-Minute English: Skincare and Makeup | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990061/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990061/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this 5-Minute English episode, you&amp;apos;ll hear a lot of vocabulary and phrases related to skincare and makeup. This episode type is extra challenging, but short. Listen to it multiple times and consider transcribing the audio as a listening exercise. You can also dive deeper into this lesson by purchasing Premium Content. *****
Premium Content
This episode is part of Season 3. By purchasing Season 3 transcripts, you&amp;apos;ll be able to access the full episodes, the full PDF transcripts for episodes 101 - 150, an Mp3 download and the premium podcast player to work on your pronunciation.</description></item><item><title>109 - Dream Houses with Pete | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990062/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990062/</guid><description>Podcast Description I&amp;apos;ve always loved talking about Dream Houses. It&amp;apos;s sort of a magical topic that everyone can relate to and yet for every person the response is going to be different. How we answer / describe our space largely depends on our life experience to date and perception of places we&amp;apos;ve been and have not been to. In this conversation I talk to Pete (my Australian friend and host of the Aussie English Podcast) about his dream home and we compare our previous living environments to where we&amp;apos;d like to be.</description></item><item><title>108.2 - Sharks and Shark Attacks in U.S. Waters | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990063/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Oct 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990063/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today&amp;apos;s episode, you&amp;apos;ll learn about Sharks and Shark Attacks in U.S. waters and how to avoid a shark if you&amp;apos;re visiting the U.S. coast!
Premium Content
This episode is part of Season 3. By purchasing Season 3 transcripts, you&amp;apos;ll be able to access the full episodes, the full PDF transcripts for episodes 101 - 150, an Mp3 download and the premium podcast player to work on your pronunciation.</description></item><item><title>108 - Expression: To Rock the Boat | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990064/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990064/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today&amp;apos;s episode, you&amp;apos;ll learn how to use the common expression: To Rock the Boat. You&amp;apos;ll get to practice pronunciation and hear a joke as well. Premium Content
This episode is part of Season 3. By purchasing Season 3 transcripts, you&amp;apos;ll be able to access the full episodes, the full PDF transcripts for episodes 101 - 150, an Mp3 download and the premium podcast player to work on your pronunciation.</description></item><item><title>107 - Expression: The Coast is Clear / The Great Escape from Alcatraz | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990065/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990065/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today&amp;apos;s episode, you&amp;apos;ll learn how to use the common expression: The Coast Is Clear. You&amp;apos;ll get to practice pronunciation and hear a joke as well. The fun fact in this episode is all about Alcatraz, an island or prison, I should say - former prison - off the coast of San Francisco, which housed some of the United States&amp;apos;s most infamous criminals from 1934 until 1963.
One former resident you may know of is Al Capone, the American gangster / mobster, you can say, also known by the nicknames Public Enemy #1 and, of course, Scarface.</description></item><item><title>106 - Off the Beaten Track with Charlie ("A Dream Trip to the Maldives") | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990066/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Charlie, our good friend from The British English Podcast, came up with an incredibly entertaining podcast format: &amp;quot;Off the Beaten Track.&amp;quot; In short, it&amp;apos;s all about asking someone detailed questions about their ideal itinerary for a DREAM vacation. I emphasize DREAM because this episode is packed with HYPOTHETICALS! You&amp;apos;ve hit the hypothetical jackpot... and it&amp;apos;s real! In today&amp;apos;s episode, we heard all about his crazy trip up to space and then to the Maldives; he would go skydiving and scuba-diving with sharks among some other legit (very cool) activities.</description></item><item><title>105 - Chats with Shana: Animals and Nature in Brazil (+10 Common Collective Nouns!) | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990067/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990067/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is part of Season 3. In this episode of the podcast, you&amp;apos;ll hear about our recent month-long stay in Brazil. Other than spending time with family and friends, the highlights of the trip were with animals and nature. Tune in and hear learn a lot of animal vocabulary! In this story, you&amp;apos;ll also be exposed to the 10 most common collective nouns for animals. A collective noun is a word used to describe a group.</description></item><item><title>104 - Study or Work Abroad: The IELTS Exam with Jessica Beck | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990068/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990068/</guid><description>Podcast Description The decision to move overseas is a big one and it requires preparation. The first step for non-native English speakers who want to live, study or work in the U.S. is taking an English exam as proof of English ability. The IELTS exam is one of the most popular. Today, I had the pleasure of speaking with Jessica Beck all about IELTS. She shared many reasons why you should consider taking this exam over the TOEFL or TOEIC, she gave some tricks on how to get a higher score, how to deal with anxiety of speaking in English in an interview setting and much much more.</description></item><item><title>103 - Expression: To Push Someone's Buttons / The Milgram Experiment | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990069/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990069/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is part of Season 3. In this episode of the podcast, you&amp;apos;ll learn how to use the common expression TO PUSH SOMEONE&amp;apos;S BUTTONS. For the fun fact about American History and Culture, you&amp;apos;ll learn about THE MILGRAM EXPERIMENT.
Premium Content
This episode is the first episode in Season 3. By purchasing Season 3 transcripts, you&amp;apos;ll be able to access the full episodes, the full PDF transcripts for episodes 101 - 150, an Mp3 download and the premium podcast player to work on your pronunciation.</description></item><item><title>102 - 5-Minute English: Toddlers | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990070/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990070/</guid><description>Podcast Description The term &amp;quot;toddler&amp;quot; is typically used to describe a child that is between the ages of one and three, although some people consider a three-year-old up until four, also a toddler. It&amp;apos;s the stage in a human&amp;apos;s life when they&amp;apos;re no longer a newborn, they&amp;apos;re no longer an infant, so a baby, but they&amp;apos;re also not really a kid.
The term toddler comes from the verb toddle, which means to walk with short and unsteady steps, according to Oxford Languages.</description></item><item><title>101 - Welcome to Season 3! | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990071/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to Season 3!! In this episode, I share some news going on here in California and then we talk about what you can expect from Season 3. Premium Content This episode is the first episode in Season 3. By purchasing Season 3 transcripts, you&amp;apos;ll be able to access the full episodes, the full PDF transcripts for episodes 101 - 150, an Mp3 download and the premium podcast player to work on your pronunciation.</description></item><item><title>100 - 100 Commonly Mispronounced Words in American English | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990072/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 11:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990072/</guid><description>Podcast Description After 5 years of teaching intermediate to advanced level English online, I found trends in the words that my students mispronounced. In today&amp;apos;s episode, I consolidated the common mispronounced words in my language classes into one episode with example sentences so that you can work on your pronunciation.
Premium Content (formerly called the Classroom)
This episode is part of Season 2. By purchasing Season 2, you&amp;apos;ll be able to access the full transcript, a comprehension quiz and the premium podcast player to work on your pronunciation.</description></item><item><title>099 - 10 Words a Day: Alex's Dating Disasters (Verbs 11-20) | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990073/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 01:00:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990073/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of the American English Podcast, you&amp;apos;ll gain maximum exposure to 10 common verbs. You&amp;apos;ll hear a story, get the definitions and new example sentences to better your pronunciation and amp up your vocabulary!The 10 words are:
To pick one&amp;apos;s noseTo growlTo zip upTo slam on the brakesTo splashTo wet oneself To flip someone offTo swearTo take a sipTo wavePremium Content (formerly called the Classroom)
This episode is part of Season 2.</description></item><item><title>098 - 10 Words a Day: Alex's Dating Disasters (Verbs with Sound 1-10) | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990074/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 16:20:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990074/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of the American English Podcast, you&amp;apos;ll gain maximum exposure to 10 common verbs that produce sound. You&amp;apos;ll hear a story, get the definitions and new example sentences to better your pronunciation and amp up your vocabulary! The 10 words are:
to spitto snoreto gargleto yawnto sniffleto cough to sneezeto snap your fingersto slurpto burpPremium Content (formerly called the Classroom)
This episode is part of Season 2.</description></item><item><title>097 - Expression: Bottoms Up! / Cinco de Mayo | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990075/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 12:16:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990075/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of the American English Podcast, you&amp;apos;ll learn how to use the expression BOTTOMS UP! and all about CINCO DE MAYO.
Premium Content (formerly called the Classroom)
This episode is part of Season 2. By purchasing Season 2, you&amp;apos;ll be able to access the full transcript, a comprehension quiz and the premium podcast player to work on your pronunciation.
Season 2 contains bonus material for episodes 051 - 100.</description></item><item><title>096 - Expression: Bent Out Of Shape / Tornadoes in the U.S. | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990076/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 14:45:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990076/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of the American English Podcast, you&amp;apos;ll learn how to use the expression BENT OUT OF SHAPE and all about TORNADOES IN THE U.S..
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Get Season 2 Premium Content OR Get ALL PREMIUM CONTENT FOR SEASONS 1-3 (including transcripts + mp3s)Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level.</description></item><item><title>095 - Chats with Shana: 10 Must-Know Expressions to Survive English Conversations | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990077/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 10:45:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990077/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Chats with Shana episode, you&amp;apos;ll hear about some of the language mistakes I&amp;apos;ve made in foreign languages. You&amp;apos;ll learn how to get yourself out of awkward situations in English by using common expressions!
Premium Content (formerly called the Classroom)
This episode is part of Season 2. By purchasing Season 2, you&amp;apos;ll be able to access the full transcript, a comprehension quiz and the premium podcast player to work on your pronunciation.</description></item><item><title>094 - Expression: To Ring a Bell / The Liberty Bell | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990078/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 12:10:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990078/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of the American English Podcast, you&amp;apos;ll learn how to use the expression TO RING A BELL and all about the LIBERTY BELL, a symbol of freedom in the United States.
Premium Content (formerly called the Classroom)
This episode is part of Season 2. By purchasing Season 2, you&amp;apos;ll be able to access the full transcript, a comprehension quiz, shadowing exercise and the premium podcast player to work on your pronunciation.</description></item><item><title>093 - Chats with Shana: The Story of My Previous Language Company | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990079/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 15:45:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990079/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Episode #93, you&amp;apos;ll hear my adventure starting a business in NYC and traveling overseas as a digital nomad. You&amp;apos;ll also hear the lessons learned from this experience using the third conditional.
Premium Content (formerly called the Classroom)
This episode is part of Season 2. By purchasing Season 2, you&amp;apos;ll be able to access the full transcript, a comprehension quiz, shadowing exercise and the premium podcast player to work on your pronunciation.</description></item><item><title>092 - Expression: To Pull Some Strings / The Great Iditarod Dogsledding Race | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990080/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 15:20:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990080/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of the American English Podcast, you&amp;apos;ll learn how to use the expression TO PULL SOME STRINGS and all about the GREAT IDITAROD RACE, the largest annual sporting event in Alaska. Spoiler alert: It&amp;apos;s all about dogsledding!
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Get Season 2 Premium Content ORGet ALL PREMIUM CONTENT FOR SEASONS 1-3 (including transcripts + mp3s)Each episode is much more than just the audio.</description></item><item><title>091 - 5-Minute English: Babies | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990081/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2021 15:25:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990081/</guid><description>Podcast Description How many vocabulary words, phrases and collocations can you think of within the topic of Babies? I bet a lot. Now, do you know the translations for them in English?
This episode introduces everything you&amp;apos;ll need to know about the topic in order to navigate a conversation with a native speaker, other than the two obvious terms I&amp;apos;ve left out &amp;quot;crying&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;baby bottle,&amp;quot; but you know these already ;)This episode is long overdue and I hope you enjoy it.</description></item><item><title>090 - Chats with Shana: Yearly Review | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990082/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 22:15:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990082/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the first of many (hopefully) yearly reviews. There&amp;apos;s nothing better than reflecting on the highlights in one&amp;apos;s year, especially with the help of images. I&amp;apos;ve done this partially for myself and also to help you listeners. I&amp;apos;ve talked about some of the events I&amp;apos;ve spoken about the podcast to &amp;quot;jog your memory&amp;quot; (episode #1) and used a number of other expressions from the expression episodes to talk about my 2020.</description></item><item><title>089 - Dessert Adjectives with Charlie | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990083/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 19:15:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi Everyone! Christmas is just a few days away and what better way to prepare than by learning how to describe desserts in English. Whether you celebrate Christmas or not, the holiday season tends to be a time of indulgence; if you&amp;apos;re not diving into calorie-filled desserts with your family members (even just on Zoom this year), what are you doing?!? In English the four tastes are sweet, salty, sour and bitter (some also mention umami).</description></item><item><title>088 - The Night Before Christmas (A Visit From Santa Claus) | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990084/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 16:05:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi Everyone! Welcome back to Episode #088. Today we will be talking about a poem, a very famous poem. In fact it may be one of the most read and referenced poems in English. Don&amp;apos;t quote me on that, but it&amp;apos;s a poem that you&amp;apos;ll hear on the radio in the U.S. as December 25th approaches, you&amp;apos;ll see lines from it on Christmas cards, in advertisements and in many many movies.</description></item><item><title>087 - 5-Minute English: Strengths and Weaknesses | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990085/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 02:50:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990085/</guid><description>Podcast Description For today we&amp;apos;re back with another 5-Minute English episode and it&amp;apos;s all about Strengths and Weaknesses, one of the most challenging questions you&amp;apos;ll run into at a job interview. In the 5-Minute discussion we&amp;apos;ll dive into an individual&amp;apos;s head on the day of a job interview and see how they decide on their strength. As usual, 5-minute episodes are intensive listening exercises so it should be a challenge! If you&amp;apos;re struggling to understand and feel overwhelmed by the complexity of advanced vocab words, I highly recommend signing up to Season 2 or the 5 Minute-English Course.</description></item><item><title>086 - Expression: In the Red / Black Friday | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990086/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 13:10:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990086/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today&amp;apos;s episode you&amp;apos;ll learn how to use the expression IN THE RED and we&amp;apos;ll talk about how BLACK FRIDAY got started, how it grew in popularity and what it&amp;apos;s like in case you want to take advantage of sales on your next trip to the US.
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Get Season 2 Premium Content ORGet ALL PREMIUM CONTENT FOR SEASONS 1-3 (including transcripts + mp3s)Each episode is much more than just the audio.</description></item><item><title>085 - British Tea Time and Baking Vocabulary with Charlie | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990087/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 12:25:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990087/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, we have a special guest. His name is Charlie Baxter and he&amp;apos;s the host of the British English Podcast. We talk about the British Bake Off and he helps me understand the terminology used in it.
To gain access to the full episode, transcript, podcast player, quizzes and more, be sure to sign up to Season 2 (see below)
Charlie&amp;apos;s Info
The British English Podcast WebsiteThe British English Podcast Charlie&amp;apos;s Youtube channelPremium Content (formerly called the Classroom)</description></item><item><title>084 - College Life with Jessica Buenaventura | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990088/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 15:28:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Listen to Jessica (my college roomie) and I talk about our college experiences at UC Santa Barbara!
To gain access to the full episode, transcript, podcast player, quizzes and more, be sure to sign up to Season 2.
Premium Content (formerly called the Classroom)
Season 2 - Premium Content for episodes 051 - 100 ORGet ALL PREMIUM CONTENT FOR SEASONS 1-3 (including transcripts + mp3s)Other Content
Get the Free E-Book: 101 American English Slang WordsConnect on Instagram</description></item><item><title>083 - Chats with Shana: October Days | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990089/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 11:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990089/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you&amp;apos;ll hear about what my family has been doing in the month of October. You&amp;apos;ll hear the Present Perfect Continuous tense used over and over again.
To gain access to the full episode, transcript, podcast player, quizzes and more, be sure to sign up to Season 2.
Premium Content (formerly called the Classroom)
Season 2 - Premium Content for episodes 051 - 100 ORGet ALL PREMIUM CONTENT FOR SEASONS 1-3 (including transcripts + mp3s)Other Content</description></item><item><title>082 - Halloween Story: The Red Spot (Lower Intermediate) | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990090/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 12:02:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990090/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you&amp;apos;ll hear a lower intermediate story for Halloween called the Red Spot. It&amp;apos;s disgusting. Don&amp;apos;t say I didn&amp;apos;t warn you, so either skip it or listen all the way to the end because you&amp;apos;ll be less disturbed if you make it to the last few minutes! To gain access to the full episode, transcript, podcast player, quizzes and more, be sure to sign up to Season 2.</description></item><item><title>081 - 5-Minute English: Fall | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990091/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 13:54:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990091/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you&amp;apos;ll hear a 5-Minute English episode about FALL (AKA AUTUMN) in the United States. By the end, you&amp;apos;ll learn vocabulary, phrasal verbs and collocations needed to talk about this topic with a native speaker.
Like most 5-Minute Episodes, the listening is short and more challenging. You might need to listen to an episode at least three times in order to fully comprehend it. There are 40+ vocabulary words and phrases in this lesson.</description></item><item><title>080 - Expression: Hit the Spot / Ben and Jerry's Ice Cream | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990092/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 12:45:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi Everyone! In today&amp;apos;s episode, you&amp;apos;ll learn how to use the expression HIT THE SPOT like a native speaker. You&amp;apos;ll also learn about Ben and Jerry&amp;apos;s, one of the most socially and environmentally conscious companies in the U.S..
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Get Season 2 Premium Content ORGet ALL PREMIUM CONTENT FOR SEASONS 1-3 (including transcripts + mp3s)Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level.</description></item><item><title>079 - The Faces On Our Money | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990093/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 17:50:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi everyone! In today&amp;apos;s episode we&amp;apos;ll be talking about THE FACES ON OUR MONEY. By money, I&amp;apos;m referring to the United States Dollar, which is commonly written as USD. The faces I&amp;apos;m referring to are the portraits of influential Americans you&amp;apos;ll see if you look at the front of our bills and coins. According to the U.S. treasury, these portraits are &amp;quot;of deceased persons whose places in history the American people know well.</description></item><item><title>078 - 5-Minute English: Elections and Voting | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990094/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 05:51:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990094/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you&amp;apos;ll hear a 5-Minute English episode about ELECTIONS AND VOTING in the United States. By the end, you&amp;apos;ll learn vocabulary, phrasal verbs and collocations needed to talk about this topic with a native speaker.Like most 5-Minute Episodes, the listening is short and more challenging. You might need to listen to an episode at least three times in order to fully comprehend it. There are 40+ vocabulary words and phrases in this lesson.</description></item><item><title>077 - 5-Minute English: Labor and Delivery | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990095/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 05:26:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990095/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you&amp;apos;ll hear a 5-Minute English episode about LABOR AND DELIVERY, as well as facts and statistics about GIVING BIRTH in the United States. By the end, you&amp;apos;ll learn vocabulary, phrasal verbs and collocations needed to talk about this topic with a native speaker.Like most 5-Minute Episodes, the listening is short and more challenging. You might need to listen to an episode at least three times in order to fully comprehend it.</description></item><item><title>076 - Portmanteaus with Liz Johnson! | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990096/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 12:54:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi Everyone! In today&amp;apos;s episode, Liz is back on the show! We have a very fun / funny episode for you which is about Portmanteaus. Don&amp;apos;t be afraid of the word, I don&amp;apos;t think most Americans know what a portmanteau is. What&amp;apos;s important is we USE them ALL THE TIME! For example, instead of saying &amp;quot;I&amp;apos;m going out to grab some frozen yogurt,&amp;quot; we might say &amp;quot;I&amp;apos;m going out to get some froyo.</description></item><item><title>075 - 5-Minute English: Wildfires in the U.S. | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990097/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 13:18:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi Everyone! In today&amp;apos;s episode, I talk about WILDFIRES, which is a devastating issue many Americans face every summer (including myself!). Since this is a 5-Minute Episode it&amp;apos;s topic-specific and MORE CHALLENGING than regular episodes. In it, you&amp;apos;ll learn vocabulary, phrasal verbs, and collocations needed to talk about this topic in depth in English. Like most 5-Minute Episodes, the listening is short and more challenging. You might need to listen to an episode at least three times in order to fully comprehend it.</description></item><item><title>074 - Fairy Tale: Hansel and Gretel | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990098/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 11:11:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi Everyone! In this week&amp;apos;s episode, I retell the very famous Brothers&amp;apos; Grimm fairy tale, Hansel and Gretel. I&amp;apos;ve made a few changes to the original text. First of all, I&amp;apos;ve intentionally added phrasal verbs and prepositional phrases throughout the text so that you can learn them in a context. Secondly, I&amp;apos;ve modernized some of the language a bit, since the original texts were written in German in the 1800s.</description></item><item><title>073 - Expression: On the Edge of One's Seat / The Life of Stan Lee | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990099/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 01:21:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi Everyone! In today&amp;apos;s episode, you&amp;apos;ll learn how to use the expression ON THE EDGE OF ONE&amp;apos;S SEAT like a native speaker. You&amp;apos;ll also learn about the life of STAN LEE, the brain behind some of the world&amp;apos;s most beloved and despised superheroes and villains. You&amp;apos;ll also get some insight into comic book history! :)
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Get Season 2 Premium ContentOR Get ALL PREMIUM CONTENT FOR SEASONS 1-3 (including transcripts + mp3s)Each episode is much more than just the audio.</description></item><item><title>072 - 5-Minute English: Cleaning | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990100/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 11:00:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi Everyone! In today&amp;apos;s episode, I talk about CLEANING, which is an activity that most of us dread. The thing is, the topic often pops up in conversation so the vocabulary, phrasal verbs, collocations and expressions in this episode are very useful! Like most 5-Minute Episodes, the listening is short and more challenging. You might need to listen to an episode at least three times in order to fully comprehend it.</description></item><item><title>071 - Expression: Through Thick and Thin / Parental Leave in the U.S. | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990101/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 09:59:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi Everyone! In today&amp;apos;s episode, you&amp;apos;ll learn how to use the expression THROUGH THICK AND THIN like a native speaker. You&amp;apos;ll also learn about MATERNITY LEAVE / PARENTAL LEAVE IN THE US.
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Get Season 2 Premium Content OR Get ALL PREMIUM CONTENT FOR SEASONS 1-3 (including transcripts + mp3s)Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level.</description></item><item><title>070 - Expression: Music to One's Ears / The Life of Elvis Presley | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990102/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 06:05:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi Everyone! In today&amp;apos;s episode, you&amp;apos;ll learn how to use the expression MUSIC TO ONE&amp;apos;S EARS like a native speaker. You&amp;apos;ll also learn about the fascinating life of ELVIS PRESLEY.
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Get Season 2 Premium ContentOR Get ALL PREMIUM CONTENT FOR SEASONS 1-3 (including transcripts + mp3s)Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level.</description></item><item><title>069 - 5-Minute English: Summer in the U.S. | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990103/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 14:29:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi Everyone! In today&amp;apos;s episode, I talk about Summer in the US. For many Americans, summertime brings back a sense of nostalgia. Today, we&amp;apos;ll talk about the common activities kids do outdoors during the summer months, how families spend summer break (road trips!) and about temperature. Like most 5-Minute Episodes, the listening is short and more challenging. You might need to listen to an episode at least three times in order to fully comprehend it.</description></item><item><title>068 - Initialisms in Conversation: Party Culture in the U.S. | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990104/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 10:13:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990104/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of the American English Podcast, we will talk about initialisms which are a type of abbreviation. The initialisms discussed are used in PRE-PARTY and PARTY situations. In the first part of the discussion I explain the difference between initialism and acronym. I also explain a list of party initialisms (such as RSVP, BYOB, etc.). In the second part, you will hear a conversation with my mom using them all in a discussion about PARTY CULTURE IN THE U.</description></item><item><title>067 - Expression: A Lot On One's Plate / Competitive Eating in the U.S. | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990105/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 12:27:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990105/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this American English Podcast Episode you&amp;apos;ll learn how to use the expression A LOT ON ONE&amp;apos;S PLATE and hear about COMPETITIVE EATING in the U.S.. The topic arouses mixed feelings probably in you and in many Americans because of world hunger, domestic hunger issues and obesity. We&amp;apos;ll touch on such criticisms during the discussion.
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Get Season 2 Premium ContentOR Get ALL PREMIUM CONTENT FOR SEASONS 1-3 (including transcripts + mp3s)Each episode is much more than just the audio.</description></item><item><title>066 - 5-Minute English: American Barbecue | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990106/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 14:27:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi Everyone! In today&amp;apos;s episode, I start by talking about our recent trip to an RV park, a chat with some boys I had about hunting and eating bear and then dive into a 5-minute discussion about AMERICAN BARBECUE. (For you people who hate &amp;quot;American&amp;quot; as an adjective, I&amp;apos;m sorry, but that&amp;apos;s the adjective that exists for the United States). If you&amp;apos;re interested in hearing casual chat and a lot of useful and different vocabulary words, listen in!</description></item><item><title>065 - Chats with Shana: Nesting | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990107/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 10:08:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi Everyone! In today&amp;apos;s episode, we talk casually about NESTING which is a phenomenon that occurs with pregnant women (some men!) and animals before childbirth. It&amp;apos;s characterized by preparing the environment, cleaning, organizing and more. If you&amp;apos;re interested in hearing casual chat and a lot of useful and different vocabulary words, listen in!
Premium Content (formerly called the Classroom)
This episode is part of Season 2. By purchasing Season 2, you&amp;apos;ll be able to access the full transcript, a comprehension quiz and the premium podcast player to work on your pronunciation.</description></item><item><title>064 - Pronunciation: 50 U.S. States | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990108/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 09:45:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi Everyone! In today&amp;apos;s episode, I teach how to pronounce the 50 U.S. States. In this lesson, you&amp;apos;ll also learn about unstressed syllables and the importance of listening. The American English Accent Course
Nobody needs to change their accent; it&amp;apos;s a personal decision! If your accent bugs you - if it screws with your confidence, makes it difficult to be understood, or is the reason why natives speak slower to you - I&amp;apos;ve made a course to help you out.</description></item><item><title>063 - Expression: Take a Hike / Yellowstone National Park | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990109/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 17:02:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi Everyone! In today&amp;apos;s episode, I teach how to use the expression TAKE A HIKE like a native speaker. For the fun fact, we go over YELLOWSTONE NATIONAL PARK and places to visit in the surrounding area.
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Get Season 2 Premium ContentOR Get ALL PREMIUM CONTENT FOR SEASONS 1-3 (including transcripts + mp3s)Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level.</description></item><item><title>062 - Baseball Culture and Expressions with Liz Johnson (PART 2) | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990110/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 11:58:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Episode #62 is part 2 of a long conversation with my good friend Liz Johnson about BASEBALL and BASEBALL EXPRESSIONS we use in everyday life. The examples shared in the audio are real and personal and we hope that you will learn how you can insert them into your everyday life. Premium Content (formerly called the Classroom)
This episode is part of Season 2. By purchasing Season 2, you&amp;apos;ll be able to access the full transcript, a comprehension quiz and the premium podcast player to work on your pronunciation.</description></item><item><title>061 - Baseball Culture and Expressions with Liz Johnson (PART 1) | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990111/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 13:36:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990111/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Episode #61, my good friend Liz Johnson and I talk about BASEBALL CULTURE IN THE U.S. and we teach COMMON BASEBALL EXPRESSIONS we use in everyday life. This is PART 1 of a longer recording. PART 2 will be posted soon. The examples shared in the audio are real and personal and we hope that you will learn how you can insert them into your everyday life. Premium Content (formerly called the Classroom)</description></item><item><title>060 - Expression: Out Of This World / The Life of Walt Disney | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990112/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 16:58:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi Everyone! In today&amp;apos;s episode, I teach how to use the expression OUT OF THIS WORLD like a native speaker. For the fun fact, we go over THE LIFE STORY OF WALT DISNEY.At the beginning of the episode, you will learn many alternative adjectives for the word &amp;quot; amazing.&amp;quot; During the fun fact section, you&amp;apos;ll hear a number of expressions in context.
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)</description></item><item><title>059 - 5-Minute English: Springtime in the U.S. | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990113/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 12:41:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi Everyone! Today you&amp;apos;ll hear another 5-Minute English episode and it&amp;apos;s all about Springtime.5-Minute English episodes are designed to teach &amp;quot;fluency one topic at a time.&amp;quot;In them, you&amp;apos;ll learn phrasal verbs, collocations and vocabulary in specific topics. Learning all of the terms well will help prepare you for conversations with native speakers.
Like most 5-Minute Episodes, the listening is short and more challenging. You might need to listen to an episode at least three times in order to fully comprehend it.</description></item><item><title>058 - Expression: A Method to Madness / Exotic Animals as Pets | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990114/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:46:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi Everyone! In today&amp;apos;s episode, I teach how to use the expression A METHOD TO MADNESS like a native speaker. For the fun fact, we go over EXOTIC ANIMALS AS PETS in the U.S. In discussing exotic animals as pets, you&amp;apos;ll learn about laws that exist in the United States as a whole and how different states differ in terms of what exotic animals you can have. Can you keep a lion or tiger in your backyard?</description></item><item><title>057 - Gender Prediction and Old Wives' Tales | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990115/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 16:57:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi Everyone!I&amp;apos;m very excited about this week&amp;apos;s episode which is about a topic that is not often discussed: Gender Prediction.In the episode, I&amp;apos;ll share 10 very common Old Wives&amp;apos; Tales for predicting gender (or sex, as some prefer to say). You&amp;apos;ll learn vocabulary related to the characteristics of pregnancy such as mood swings, break outs, cravings and I&amp;apos;ll also share our results to these tests within the episode.</description></item><item><title>056 - Expression: On a Roll / Philly Cheesesteaks | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990116/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 11:47:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi Everyone! In this week&amp;apos;s episode I&amp;apos;ll teach you the expression ON A ROLL and all about the famous PHILLY CHEESESTEAK. You&amp;apos;ll also learn many adjectives to describe good vs. bad sandwiches (bread, meat, cheese and onions).
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Get Season 2 Premium Content OR Get ALL PREMIUM CONTENT FOR SEASONS 1-3 (including transcripts + mp3s)Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level.</description></item><item><title>055 - 5-Minute English: 3 Trending Diets To Lose Winter Weight | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990117/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 11:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi Everyone! Today you&amp;apos;ll hear another 5-Minute English episode and it&amp;apos;s all about 3 Trending Diets to Lose Winter Weight.5-Minute English episodes are designed to teach &amp;quot;fluency one topic at a time.&amp;quot;In them, you&amp;apos;ll learn phrasal verbs, collocations and vocabulary in specific topics. Learning all of the terms well will help prepare you for conversations with native speakers.
Like most 5-Minute Episodes, the listening is short and more challenging.</description></item><item><title>054 - Expression: To Pull Someone's Leg / Best April Fool's Jokes in History | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990118/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 10:59:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990118/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi Everyone! This week&amp;apos;s episode is about the expression TO PULL SOMEONE&amp;apos;S LEG and popular APRIL FOOL&amp;apos;S JOKES that went down in history.
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Get Season 2 Premium Content OR Get ALL PREMIUM CONTENT FOR SEASONS 1-3 (including transcripts + mp3s)Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level.</description></item><item><title>053 - Chats with Shana: Brazil Trip and Coronavirus | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990119/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 09:36:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990119/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week’s episode is all about my family’s TRIP TO BRAZIL and how “the shit has hit the fan” during the past two weeks because of the CORONAVIRUS. This episode uses a lot of perfect tenses. If you need to practice the present perfect, past perfect or even the passive forms for either of these I highly recommend listening!
Premium Content (formerly called the Classroom)
This episode is part of Season 2.</description></item><item><title>052 - Expression: A Bun In The Oven / The "Octomom" | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990120/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 15:02:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990120/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi Everyone! This week’s episode is all about pregnancy! The expression is A BUN IN THE OVEN and the fun fact is about THE WOMAN WHO GAVE BIRTH TO OCTUPLETS, FORMERLY KNOWN AS OCTOMOM.
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Get Season 2 Premium ContentOR
Get ALL PREMIUM CONTENT FOR SEASONS 1-3 (including transcripts + mp3s)Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level.</description></item><item><title>051 - Expression: That's The Way The Cookie Crumbles / Girl Scout Cookies | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990121/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 13:03:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi Everyone! This week’s episode is all about cookies! The joke is about cookies, the expression is THAT’S THE WAY THE COOKIE CRUMBLES and the fun fact is about GIRL SCOUT COOKIES.
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Get Season 2 Premium ContentOR
Get ALL PREMIUM CONTENT FOR SEASONS 1-3 (including transcripts + mp3s)Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level.</description></item><item><title>050 - Chats with Shana: Snow Trip and Snow Vocabulary! | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990122/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 16:55:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990122/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week’s episode is all about my family’s trip to the snow last week. In it, I share tips on skiing and snowboarding in the US as well as plenty of essential vocabulary words you’ll need to talk about the snow, skiing and snowboarding!
Get Premium Content (formerly called &amp;quot;the Classroom&amp;quot;) Season 1 - Bonus Material for Episodes 001 - 050 OR
Get ALL PREMIUM CONTENT FOR SEASONS 1-3 (including transcripts + mp3s)Connect on Instagram</description></item><item><title>049 - Expression: When Hell Freezes Over / Ice Castles of Utah | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990123/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 15:17:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990123/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi Everyone! In this week&amp;apos;s episode, I teach the common English expression: When Hell Freezes Over. We also talk all about the very famous ICE CASTLES, which were created by the entrepreneur, Brent Christensen, in 2011.
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Get Season 1 Premium Content OR
Get ALL PREMIUM CONTENT FOR SEASONS 1-3 (including transcripts + mp3s)Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level.</description></item><item><title>048 - Interview with Lauren: Sororities and Fraternities | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990124/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 13:35:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi Everyone! This week&amp;apos;s episode is all about SORORITIES AND FRATERNITIES. I introduce the history of Greek Life and talk about the famous people were part of sororities and fraternities. As a special guest, we talk to my cousin Lauren about what it was like to be in a sorority. Hopefully you&amp;apos;ll learn a little bit more than the stereotypes! There are many takeaways from this very unique college experience.</description></item><item><title>047 - Expression: Hit Or Miss / The National Anthem ("The Star-Spangled Banner") | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990125/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 13:11:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi Everyone! This week&amp;apos;s episode is all about THE NATIONAL ANTHEM of the United States which is called THE STAR-SPANGLED BANNER. We will go through the expression &amp;quot;HIT OR MISS&amp;quot; as well.
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Get Season 1 Premium Content ORGet ALL PREMIUM CONTENT FOR SEASONS 1-3 (including transcripts + mp3s)Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level.</description></item><item><title>046 - Chats with Shana: A Cultural Trip Through Florida | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990126/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 12:35:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990126/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week&amp;apos;s episode, I talk to you from Miami, Florida where we have spent the past 2.5 weeks enjoying the warm weather, tropical fruit and latin culture. Within the episode, I talk to you about our time in Orlando and Miami and share many facts and figures about the state and its people.
Premium Content (formerly called &amp;quot;The Classroom&amp;quot;) Season 1 - Bonus Material for Episodes 001 - 050 Get ALL PREMIUM CONTENT FOR SEASONS 1-3 (including transcripts + mp3s)Get the Free E-Book: 101 American English Slang WordsConnect on Instagram</description></item><item><title>045 - Expression: To Put Someone On A Pedestal / Groundhog's Day | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990127/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 10:16:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990127/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Episode #45, I teach you how to use the expression TO PUT SOMEONE ON A PEDESTAL like a native speaker from the States. I also talk about GROUNDHOG&amp;apos;S DAY, which is a goofy holiday on February 2nd every year in the U.S. and Canada.
Hi Everyone! This week&amp;apos;s episode is all about Driving in the U.S. and it&amp;apos;s a little bit longer this week because there&amp;apos;s simply so much information to share.</description></item><item><title>044 - Driving in the U.S.: Vocabulary and Rules (with special guests Joe and Mara) | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990128/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 15:23:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990128/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi Everyone! This week&amp;apos;s episode is all about Driving in the U.S. and it&amp;apos;s a little bit longer this week because there&amp;apos;s simply so much information to share.I highly recommend listening to this episode twice. The vocabulary words will be incredibly useful if you ever talk to somebody in English about driving or cars.
For the full 44 minute episode and transcript, Mp3 and more, check out Season 1 - Bonus Material for Episodes 001 - 050 (formerly called &amp;quot;the Classroom&amp;quot;).</description></item><item><title>043 - Interview with My Dad: Living and Working in Alaska | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990129/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 10:31:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990129/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Episode 43, we talk to my dad about what it&amp;apos;s like to live and work in Alaska. During the conversation we talk about wildlife, outdoor sports and his long days finding oil. You will learn a lot about Alaska by listening to this one! Enjoy :)
Premium Content (formerly called &amp;quot;the Classroom&amp;quot;)
Season 1 - Bonus Material for Episodes 001 - 050 Get ALL PREMIUM CONTENT FOR SEASONS 1-3 (including transcripts + mp3s)Connect on Instagram</description></item><item><title>042 - Expression: To Drop the Ball / Why do we drop a ball at Times Square on New Years? | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990130/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 13:11:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990130/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of the podcast, I&amp;apos;ll teach you how to use the expression TO DROP THE BALL like a native speaker from the United States. The fun fact of the day answers the question WHY DO WE DROP A BALL AT TIMES SQUARE ON NEW YEARS?
Season 1 - Bonus Material for Episodes 001 - 050 (formerly called &amp;quot;the Classroom&amp;quot;)
Premium Content:
Get ALL PREMIUM CONTENT FOR SEASONS 1-3 (including transcripts + mp3s)Get ONLY the Transcripts for Episodes 001 - 100Get the Free E-Book: 101 American English Slang WordsThe American English Accent Course **Connect on Instagram**</description></item><item><title>041 - American English Slang with Liz Johnson | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990131/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 21:25:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990131/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Episode #41, my good friend Liz Johnson and I planned on talking about 10 AMERICAN ENGLISH SLANG WORDS that we use on a daily basis. After all is said and done, we ended up sharing about 20 very common words and phrases! That&amp;apos;s a lot of slang. Notice how I didn&amp;apos;t write slang with an &amp;quot;s&amp;quot;. Slang with an &amp;quot;s&amp;quot; doesn&amp;apos;t exist. It is uncountable. Learn slang. Learn slang words.</description></item><item><title>040 - Chats with Shana: December Days | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990132/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 19:16:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990132/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of the podcast, I speak casually to you about our first week in December. Within the multiple mini stories, you&amp;apos;ll hear irregular past tense verbs, learn Christmas vocabulary and get a feel for some of the pre-Christmas activities that are celebrated in California.
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level.</description></item><item><title>039 - Expression: A Blessing in Disguise / SantaCon | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990133/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 11:34:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990133/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode of the podcast, I&amp;apos;ll teach you how to use the expression A BLESSING IN DISGUISE like a native speaker from the United States. The fun fact of the day is about SANTACON, which takes place during the first few weekends of December in over 100 cities in the US.
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level.</description></item><item><title>038 - The Green Card: Our Experience, Tips and More | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990134/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 16:30:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990134/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Episode of the American English Podcast, Lucas and I talk about our experience getting his GREEN CARD. Yes, it was approved, finally! We go through some of the following points:
What is a Green Card?What&amp;apos;s the difference between Permanent Residency and Citizenship?What are the benefits of Citizenship?Tips for the Official InterviewQuestions they ask at the Interview How to Prepare Our Mistakes and friends&amp;apos; mistakesLawyer (cost &amp;amp; their role)+ so much more.</description></item><item><title>037 - Expression: To Quit Cold Turkey / Thanksgiving in the U.S. | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990135/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 16:01:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990135/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you will learn about THANKSGIVING IN THE US and how to use the English Expression TO QUIT COLD TURKEY like a native speaker. Friends Episodes (available on Netflix in the U.S.) - Season 3, Episode 9 (The Football Game)- Season 5, Episode 8 (Flashbacks to Previous Thanksgivings)- Season 6, Episode 9 (Rachel&amp;apos;s Trifle).
Thank you to all of my premium subscribers! **Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)</description></item><item><title>036 - Our Story: Dating, Engagement and Marriage | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990136/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 15:46:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990136/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Wednesday, November 13th, Lucas (my husband) and I will have his green card interview. A green card, is a physical card you receive from the U.S. government that permits you to reside in the U.S. and work.Since we will need to tell our story to the judge / immigration official, including specifics about dating, engagement and marriage, I figured why not tell our story to you. I&amp;apos;ve added tons of vocabulary, collocations, slang and more to this to make it a well-rounded learning experience.</description></item><item><title>035 - Expression: The Last Straw / The Story of Coca-Cola | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990137/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 20:15:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990137/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you will learn about THE STORY OF COCA-COLA and how to use the English Expression THE LAST STRAW like a native speaker. **Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level. This includes:
PDF and Mp3 downloadsExercises + quizzesShadowing exercises Challenges</description></item><item><title>034 - Expression: To Have A Few Screws Loose / The Winchester Mystery House | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990138/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 12:47:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990138/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you will learn about THE WINCHESTER MYSTERY HOUSE and how to use the English Expression TO HAVE A FEW SCREWS LOOSE like a native speaker. You can access premium content for this episode by joining The Classroom. **Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level.</description></item><item><title>033 - A Classic Scary Story For Halloween | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990139/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 02:31:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990139/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Episode 33, I tell two more interesting facts I&amp;apos;ve learned about Halloween since Episode 31 (which was the Halloween Special) AND I tell you a scary story that&amp;apos;s jam-packed with the Past Perfect tense!
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level.</description></item><item><title>032 - Expression: To Wing It / Bald Eagles (Our National Emblem) | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990140/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 11:52:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990140/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode you will learn about BALD EAGLES and how to use the English Expression TO WING IT like a native speaker. **Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level. This includes:
PDF and Mp3 downloadsExercises + quizzesShadowing exercises Challenges</description></item><item><title>031 - Halloween Special: Interview with Liz Johnson | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990141/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 15:00:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990141/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode you will learn a brief history of Halloween and about HALLOWEEN CULTURE IN THE UNITED STATES leading up to the 31st of October and on Halloween day.In this episode, we talk about pumpkin patches, carving pumpkins, horror movies, haunted houses and our experiences as kids, teenagers and adults.
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level.</description></item><item><title>030 - Expression: In the Loop / The Hyperloop | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990142/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 11:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990142/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn American English in this episode of the American English Podcast where I talk about THE HYPERLOOP (new type of transportation) and teach you to use the expression IN THE LOOP and OUT OF THE LOOP like a native speaker.
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level.</description></item><item><title>029 - Expression: To Carve in Stone / Mount Rushmore and The Crazy Horse Memorial | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990143/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2019 13:10:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990143/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn American English in this episode of the American English Podcast where I talk about MOUNT RUSHMORE and THE CRAZY HORSE MEMORIAL and teach you to use the expression TO CARVE IN STONE like a native speaker. If you haven&amp;apos;t already, follow me on instagram @americanenglishpodcast and let me know where you&amp;apos;re from! :)
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Each episode is much more than just the audio.</description></item><item><title>028 - Expression: To Give Your Two Cents / Tipping Culture in the U.S. | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990144/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 12:13:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990144/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn American English in this episode of the American English Podcast where I talk about TIPPING CULTURE IN THE U.S. and WHERE IT CAME FROM and teach you to use the expression TO GIVE YOUR TWO CENTS like a native speaker.
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level.</description></item><item><title>027 - Expression: To Bite Off More Than You Can Chew / The Donner Party | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990145/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 11:57:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990145/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn American English in this episode of the American English Podcast where I talk about THE DONNER PARTY and teach you to use the expression TO BITE OFF MORE THAN YOU CAN CHEW like a native speaker. To see photos of where the Donner Party was trapped in the Sierra Nevada Mountains check out my Instagram @americanenglishpodcast.
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Each episode is much more than just the audio.</description></item><item><title>026 - Interview with Dana: 25 Facts About Canada | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990146/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 16:46:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990146/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn American English in this episode of the American English Podcast where I talk with Dana from the Can Learn English Podcast about CANADA. We discuss 25 FACTS ABOUT CANADA and hear her take (opinion) on them!
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level.</description></item><item><title>025 - Chats with Shana: The County Fair | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990147/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 10:20:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990147/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn American English in this episode of the American English Podcast where I talk about COUNTY FAIRS and teach you about THE DEMOLITION DERBY at my county fair.Check out the images on Instagram @americanenglishpodcast
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level.</description></item><item><title>024 - Expression: Spill the Beans / 3 Major Oil Spills off of U.S. Coasts | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990148/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 12:30:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990148/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn American English in this episode of the American English Podcast where I talk about OIL SPILLS OFF THE COAST OF THE U.S. and teach you to use the expression SPILL THE BEANS like a native speaker. Pete&amp;apos;s &amp;quot;Spill the Beans&amp;quot; Episode for Australian English can be found here: https://aussieenglish.com.au/589Dana&amp;apos;s &amp;quot;Spill the Beans&amp;quot; Episode for Canadian Episode will be posted today on the Can Learn English Podcast.**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)</description></item><item><title>023 - Interview with a Hairstylist: Sonia Murray | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990149/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 15:24:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990149/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, you&amp;apos;ll learn all about hair, haircuts and hairstyles with my aunt, Sonia Murray. She is a hairstylist. See the YouTube video that corresponds with this episode here: https://youtu.be/pXJOFWZRk6U
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level.</description></item><item><title>022 - Expression: By the Book / Project Gutenberg | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990150/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 14:54:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990150/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn American English in this episode of the American English Podcast where I talk about PROJECT GUTENBERG and teach you to use the expression BY THE BOOK like a native speaker.
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level.</description></item><item><title>021: Chats with Shana: Trip to the Avenue of the Giants | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990151/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2019 12:45:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990151/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is about my trip to the AVENUE OF THE GIANTS, the area of the massive COASTAL REDWOOD TREES in California. **Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level. This includes:
Transcript + Mp3
The premium content for this episode can be found in Season 1, which also contains bonus material for episodes 001 - 050.</description></item><item><title>020 - Expression: To Play With Fire / Burning Man Festival | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990152/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 12:30:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990152/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn American English in this episode of the American English Podcast where I teach you to use the expression TO PLAY WITH FIRE like a native speaker. In the second part, you&amp;apos;ll learn all about the Burning Man Festival in Nevada.
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level.</description></item><item><title>019 - Expression: To Have Foot-In-Mouth Disease / The Discovery of Bigfoot | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990153/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 19:51:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990153/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn American English in this episode of the American English Podcast where I teach you to use the expression TO HAVE FOOT-IN-MOUTH DISEASE like a native speaker. For the fun fact, you&amp;apos;ll learn about BIGFOOT.
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level.</description></item><item><title>018 - Expression: Take a Rain Check / How to use Fahrenheit and WHY? | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990154/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 14:38:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990154/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn American English in this episode of the American English Podcast where I teach you to use the expression TAKE A RAIN CHECK like a native speaker. You&amp;apos;ll also learn the story WHY THE U.S. USES FAHRENHEIT.
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level.</description></item><item><title>017 - Chats with Shana: About Me, the Podcast and Gardening | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990155/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2019 15:12:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990155/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the first of some bonus episodes I&amp;apos;ve decided to add about me, my thoughts and plans for the podcast.
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level. This includes:
PDF and Mp3 downloadsExercises + quizzesShadowing exercises Challenges</description></item><item><title>016 - Expression: Give an Inch, Take a Mile / The Metric System in the U.S. | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990156/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 11:45:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990156/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn American English in this episode of the American English Podcast where I teach you to use the expression GIVE AN INCH, TAKE A MILE like a native speaker. For the fun fact, we&amp;apos;ll talk about the METRIC SYSTEM IN THE U.S..
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level.</description></item><item><title>015 - Expression: Piece of Cake / The Happy Birthday Song | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990157/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 12:07:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990157/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn American English in this episode of the American English Podcast where I teach you to use the expression PIECE OF CAKE like a native speaker. For the fun fact, we&amp;apos;ll talk about THE HAPPY BIRTHDAY SONG.
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level.</description></item><item><title>013 - Expression: To Get The Hang of It / The Salem Witch Trials | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990158/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 17:48:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990158/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn American English in this episode of the American English Podcast where I teach you to use the expression TO GET THE HANG OF IT like a native speaker. You&amp;apos;ll also learn all about THE SALEM WITCH TRIALS.
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level.</description></item><item><title>012 - Expression: It's Not Rocket Science / NASA Space Exploration | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990159/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 12:49:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990159/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn American English in this episode of the American English Podcast where I teach you to use the expression IT&amp;apos;S NOT ROCKET SCIENCE like a native speaker. You&amp;apos;ll also learn all about NASA.
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level.</description></item><item><title>011 - Expression: To Show Your True Colors / The American Flag | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990160/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 14:31:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990160/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn American English in this episode of the American English Podcast where I teach you to use the expression SHOW YOUR TRUE COLORS like a native speaker. The fun fact for this episode is THE HISTORY OF THE AMERICAN FLAG.
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level.</description></item><item><title>010 - Expression: Bear With Me / Bears in the U.S. | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990161/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 18:38:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990161/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn American English in this episode of the American English Podcast where I teach you to use the expression BEAR WITH ME like a native speaker. You&amp;apos;ll also learn all about BEARS IN THE U.S.
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level.</description></item><item><title>009 - Expression: From Rags to Riches / The California Gold Rush | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990162/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 06:20:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990162/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn American English in this episode of the American English Podcast where I teach you to use the expression FROM RAGS TO RICHES like a native speaker. You&amp;apos;ll also learn all about THE CALIFORNIA GOLD RUSH.
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level.</description></item><item><title>008 - Expression: Hit The Hay / The Amish Communities | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990163/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 13:27:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990163/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn American English in this episode of the American English Podcast where I teach you to use the expression HIT THE HAY like a native speaker. The fun fact for this episode is all about THE AMISH COMMUNITIES. **Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level.</description></item><item><title>007 - Expression: Walk All Over You / Internships in the U.S. | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990164/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 12:37:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990164/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn American English in this episode of the American English Podcast where I teach you to use the expression WALK ALL OVER YOU like a native speaker. You&amp;apos;ll also learn all about GETTING INTERNSHIPS IN THE U.S.. The fun fact for this episode is about INTERNSHIPS IN THE UNITED STATES.
**Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Each episode is much more than just the audio. For many episodes, like this one, there is premium content that will push you to improve your language level from an intermediate to advanced level.</description></item><item><title>006 - Expression: A Taste of Your Own Medicine / Henrietta Lacks | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990165/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 23:37:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990165/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn American English in this episode of the American English Podcast where I teach you to use the expression A TASTE OF YOUR OWN MEDICINE like a native speaker. You&amp;apos;ll also learn all about HENRIETTA LACKS, a woman who drastically impacted modern science. **Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Want to improve your English while listening? &amp;quot;Premium content&amp;quot; is supplementary learning material for episodes on the American English Podcast.</description></item><item><title>005 - Expression: Cut Corners / University Admissions Scandal | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990166/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 19:15:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990166/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn American English in this episode of the American English Podcast where I teach you to use the expression CUT CORNERS like a native speaker. The fun fact for this episode is about UNIVERSITY ADMISSIONS and THE UNIVERSITY ADMISSIONS SCANDAL.
The premium content for this episode can be found in Season 1, which also contains bonus material for episodes 001 - 050. **Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)</description></item><item><title>004 - Expression: Get Over It / Yosemite + Hiking Half Dome | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990167/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 22:22:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990167/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn American English in this episode of the American English Podcast where I teach you to use the expression GET OVER IT like a native speaker. The fun fact for this episode is about YOSEMITE NATIONAL PARK.
The premium content for this episode can be found in Season 1, which also contains bonus material for episodes 001 - 050. **Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Want to improve your English while listening?</description></item><item><title>003 - Expression: Cut the Cheese / Pizza + Italian Immigration | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990168/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 22:18:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990168/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn American English in this episode of the American English Podcast where I teach you to use the expression CUT THE CHEESE like a native speaker. The fun fact for this episode is ITALIAN IMMIGRATION and PIZZA IN THE U.S.!
The premium content for this episode can be found in Season 1, which also contains bonus material for episodes 001 - 050. **Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)</description></item><item><title>002 - Expression: Blow Your Mind / Amazon Go Stores | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990169/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 22:12:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990169/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn American English in this episode of the American English Podcast where I teach you to use the expression BLOW YOUR MIND like a native speaker. You&amp;apos;ll also learn all about THE AMAZON GO STORES.
The premium content for this episode can be found in Season 1, which also contains bonus material for episodes 001 - 050. **Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Want to improve your English while listening?</description></item><item><title>001 - Expression: Jog Your Memory / The Barkley Marathons | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990170/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 22:08:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990170/</guid><description>Podcast Description Learn American English in this episode of the American English Podcast where I teach you to use the expression JOG YOUR MEMORY like a native speaker. The fun fact for this episode is about the BARKLEY MARATHONS.
The premium content for this episode can be found in Season 1, which also contains bonus material for episodes 001 - 050. **Premium Content** (formerly called the Classroom)
Want to improve your English while listening?</description></item><item><title>Trailer: American English Podcast | American English Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8189990171/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8189990171/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hi! My name is Shana and I&amp;apos;m a native English speaker from California. Over the past 10 years, I&amp;apos;ve been teaching American English to learners like you. On this show, I teach intermediate to advanced English through stories. You&amp;apos;ll dive into the lives of fascinating Americans like Walt Disney and Stan Lee, you&amp;apos;ll hear about big events and holidays, the birth of businesses and tech and even wild stories like the Discovery of Bigfoot or the Blue People of Kentucky.</description></item></channel></rss>