<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>When the Facts Change on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/when-the-facts-change/</link><description>Recent content in When the Facts Change on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 16:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/when-the-facts-change/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Spinoff presents SUPERPOD 2023 | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130156/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130156/</guid><description>Podcast Description SUPERPOD is back! Hosted by Gone By Lunchtime&amp;rsquo;s Toby Manhire and featuring Jane Yee and Alex Casey from The Real Pod, Duncan Greive from The Fold, Gone By Lunchtime&amp;rsquo;s Annabelle Lee-Mather, Simon Pound from Business Is Boring, Bernard Hickey from When The Facts Change and The Spinoff Podcast Network&amp;rsquo;s Te Aihe Butler and Samuel Robinson, SUPERPOD 2023 is the crossover to end all crossovers. From intense discussion of government policy to figuring out what the heck a skibidi toilet is, we celebrate the best and worst of what has been a rollercoaster year.</description></item><item><title>The economic impact of record-high migration | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130001/</guid><description>Podcast Description 2023 has seen record-high net migration after a large dip during the height of Covid. Bernard Hickey talks with Kiwibank economist Mary-Jo Vergara about the economic effects of high migration on rents, inflation, interest rates and house prices.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The real cost of the smoking excise tax | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130002/</guid><description>Podcast Description To replace $700 million a year of revenues lost from a foreign buyers tax, the new coalition government is dumping the previous government&amp;rsquo;s smoke free 2025 goal. This relaxing of policies will keep more people smoking for longer, costing thousands of lives per year and at least $10 billion is extra health costs and lost working hours. Bernard Hickey speaks with University of Otago public health researcher Andrew Waa about his analysis of the changes to smoke free, and finds out the true costs of reversing them.</description></item><item><title>When can we expect mortgage rates to drop? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130003/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Reserve Bank surprised everyone this week by warning it may have to raise interest rates again to force inflation down, effectively eliminating the prospect of major mortgage rate cuts over the coming summer. Kiwibank Chief Economist Jarrod Kerr joins Bernard Hickey to dig in to the RBNZ’s unexpected hawkish outlook heading into 2024. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The budget benefits of going electric | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Could a South Island cherry farm set the standard for an electric future? Mike Casey from Rewiring Aotearoa joins Bernard Hickey to discuss what it took to make the switch from running his cherry farm on fossil fuels to renewable electricity. He also explains the ways in which going electric will save our homes, farms and small businesses thousands each year. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.</description></item><item><title>The state of the economy in Aotearoa with Steve Jurkovich | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130005/</guid><description>Podcast Description With cost of living forefront on people&amp;rsquo;s minds, what are banks doing to alleviate pressure on the consumer? Bernard Hickey sits down with Kiwibank chief executive Steve Jurkovich to discuss how the economy is travelling, the pressures consumers are dealing with, and the regulatory adjustments he hopes to see in 2024. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A new solution to the first-home deposit problem? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130006/</guid><description>Podcast Description New fintech startup Aera says first-home buyers would need to save for an infinite number of years to secure a house deposit. Founder Derek Handley joins Bernard Hickey to discuss Aera&amp;rsquo;s plan to help first-home buyers to get onto the property ladder, with a new take on the bank of mum and dad.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How leaders can learn from their mistakes | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130007/</guid><description>Podcast Description After leaving the CEO position at Z Energy, Mike Bennetts became an executive coach and has just published his own book: Being Extraordinary by confronting your ordinary. Mike talks to Bernard Hickey about how leadership is different from management, and how leaders can learn from their mistakes.
You can find Mike&amp;rsquo;s book at: https://www.taumataadvisory.com/beingextraordinary Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to defend yourself from tech-savvy scammers | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130008/</guid><description>Podcast Description In April and June of 2023, online scammers stole $4.2 million from New Zealanders. Bernard Hickey speaks to Kiwibank senior external fraud investigator Sareta Fraser about how bank customers and banks are in an arms race against increasingly ingenious and awful scammers. She lays out the tricks and schemes used by the scammers and offers tips and techniques that customers can use to protect themselves. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>The wind power revolution energising Aotearoa | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130009/</guid><description>Podcast Description What makes New Zealand one of the most geographically perfect places to harness the power of Tāwhirimātea? This week, Bernard Hickey talks with Giacomo Caleffi from Copenhagen Infrastructure Partners about how the NZ Super Fund could bolster their plan to build a massive offshore wind farm off the coast of South Taranaki. They discuss why offshore wind is so necessary in the transition to 100% renewable energy, and how renewable energy differs from renewable power.</description></item><item><title>Powering down to keep your savings up | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130010/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are we using our energy networks as efficiently as possible? Bernard Hickey interviews Octopus Energy’s UK-based head of systems change, Marcia Poletti, about innovative ways power companies can adapt their current system to better support the energy grid. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Using LinkedIn to build your business better | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130011/</guid><description>Podcast Description All around the globe, business owners are struggling to launch, manage, and sustain their companies&amp;rsquo; increasingly necessary online presence in an impactful way. Bernard Hickey speaks to the marketing director at Smarketing Lab, Assia Salikhova, for some free consulting on how to build his podcasting empire in the social space. She explains the simple ways you can let nosy folks know that you and your business are alive and thriving.</description></item><item><title>The post-pandemic office experience | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130012/</guid><description>Podcast Description It turns out many offices are empty now, particularly on Mondays and Fridays, and workers aren’t there to sit at their open-plan desks. They’re there to join Zoom or Teams calls in quiet spaces, or to meet each other in conference rooms. Bernard Hickey talks to XYSense co-founder and CEO Alex Birch about how building managers, planners and bean counters can understand the best way to run an office of the future.</description></item><item><title>Melbourne City's carbon neutral apartment building | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Liam Wallis, is the founder of HIP V HYPE, a design agency in Melbourne that helped design, fund and build the first Nightingale project apartments in Melbourne’s Brunswick. These apartments are designed from the start to be carbon neutral, healthier, and cheaper places to heat. He talks to Bernard Hickey about the number of times the air changes every hour in a normal house (20), and how often the air changes in a home like the ones built in the Nightingale projects.</description></item><item><title>Is an economic summer on the horizon? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130014/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kiwibank chief economist Jarrod Kerr tells Bernard Hickey why there are early signs of a rebound in confidence and hope for the summer to come, and into next year, despite the interest rate hikes. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Chris Hipkins on leading a conservative left-wing government | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130015/</guid><description>Podcast Description The prime minister seems to be moving forward with his plan to ignore the infrastructure deficit by ruling out wealth and capital gains taxes. He joins Bernard Hickey to defend his stance as a steady, status quo government and tries to win the vote of Bernard in the process. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Reconnecting the regions with better public transit | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bernard Hickey discusses the need for much better bus and train connections within and between our smaller provincial cities with public transport advocate and award-winning singer-songwriter Anthonie Tonnon. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Shining a light on our solar industry | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why is Aotearoa&amp;rsquo;s solar panel industry lagging so far behind the rest of the world? SolarZero CEO Matt Ward joins Bernard Hickey to talk about how using batteries to complement rooftop solar is changing the game and how he believes that the number of solar panels in Aotearoa are about to go through the roof.
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The company transitioning businesses to a low carbon economy | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130018/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bernard Hickey talks with CoGo founder Ben Gleisner about the potential to use bank data on spending to help businesses and consumers monitor and tweak their climate emissions. Gleisner talks about Aotearoa’s rocky and long pathway to open banking and the options for a type of ‘nudge’ economy towards decarbonisation. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to construct an affordable and eco-friendly home | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are we building our houses as smart as we possibly can? GEOBIND co-founder Alice Hosted says that Aotearoa could help solve its housing cost and carbon problems by using hempcrete walls. They discuss the pros to using hemp in building construction, and the current logistical frameworks that restrict its use in New Zealand. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The renewable energy source beneath our feet | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130020/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bernard Hickey drills down into the future of geothermal electricity production in this week’s interview with Isabelle Chambefort from GNS Science. She’s excited about the potential for deep drilling to uncover ‘supercritical’ heat that supercharges geothermal power output, helping solve the dry year problem bedevilling or hydro dominated power system. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>This is Kiwi: Kiri Nathan on building community through creativity | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130021/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kiri Nathan isn’t just a leading figure in the Aotearoa fashion industry, she’s a true inspiration – a remarkable artist and guiding mentor to young indigenous designers. Kiri stands apart from her peers in the world of fashion, with her commitment to incorporating her whakapapa in her creations by using Māori patterns, textiles and weaving techniques. In this kōrero we discover what motivates Kiri and the obstacles she’s conquered to achieve respect and success in this notoriously tough industry.</description></item><item><title>What is the future of our banking system? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130022/</guid><description>Podcast Description As the world globalises, open banking is becoming an increasingly attractive prospect to customers, so why aren&amp;rsquo;t our banks onboard yet? Bernard Hickey talks with Josh Daniell at FinTech firm Akahu about what’s being done in Aotearoa to accelerate the move to open banking, something already well advanced in Europe, the UK, and Australia. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>This is Kiwi: Robbie Van Dam on finding innovation everywhere | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130023/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Meet Robbie van Dam, a visionary entrepreneur and finalist for the Kiwibank New Zealander of the Year Spark Innovator Award for 2023. Through his company GoodNature, Robbie’s passion and commitment has helped revolutionise the pest control industry thanks to a groundbreaking trap that humanely kills pests with remarkable efficiency. With over 22 million pests killed worldwide and huge monetary savings in conservation efforts, Robbie’s inspiring story of challenging the status quo, making meaningful change and turning innovation into a global success is not to be missed.</description></item><item><title>Breaking the financial barriers for Māori | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130024/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130024/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Māori economy is one of the fastest growing in the country, yet many tangata whenua still face major barriers when borrowing from banks to kickstart businesses. Kiwibank&amp;rsquo;s head of Māori advisory Teaho Pihama sits down with Bernard Hickey to discuss the issues facing Māori when it comes to accessing capital and what practical solutions his team at Kiwibank are doing to give Māori greater access to lending. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>This is Kiwi: Dr Ellen Joan Nelson on embracing a better way of working | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130025/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr Ellen Nelson is a military veteran, esteemed academic, and Kiwibank local hero of the year for 2023. For this special kōrero we delve into Ellen’s passion for improving working conditions for parents and her campaigns advocating for flexible and inclusive workplaces.
We find out what drives Ellen, covering her bold approach to leadership, mammoth volunteer effort leading the evacuation of Afghan refugees to Aotearoa and academic achievements focusing on women’s empowerment.</description></item><item><title>Making climate adaptation as fair as possible | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130026/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130026/</guid><description>Podcast Description University of Auckland academic Troy Baisden and Catherine Leining from Motu Research talk to Benard Hickey about their new guide that gives a unique insight into how we can adapt fairly to a myriad of problems facing Aotearoa in the coming decades. They discuss what this research means, what the next steps are and what keeps them optimistic that we can achieve a just transition. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>This is Kiwi: Dr Rangi Mātāmua on finding wisdom in the stars | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130027/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Esteemed Matariki expert Dr Rangi Mātāmua brings a wealth of wisdom and expertise that extends beyond the stars, encompassing topics such as living by the Maramataka and food sovereignty.
With Matariki, the Māori new year, on the horizon, there&amp;rsquo;s no better time to delve into the significance of this celestial celebration with someone who played a pivotal role in its recognition on the public holiday calendar. As a renowned expert in indigenous knowledge and the Professor of Mātauranga Māori at Massey University, Dr Rangi Mātāmua is Kiwibank&amp;rsquo;s New Zealander of the Year for 2023.</description></item><item><title>When house price sustainability doesn’t mean affordability | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130028/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130028/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2021, the Reserve Bank told us that house prices were unsustainably high and would likely fall by around 15%. That has proven to be the case and the market is now considered sustainable. Yet, house price-to-income ratios are still two to three times higher than they were 20 years ago, and most people with regular incomes still struggle to buy homes. In this episode, Bernard Hickey talks to Reserve Bank researcher Dr Andrew Coleman about his research measuring house price sustainability and why house prices remain unaffordable, despite hitting sustainable levels.</description></item><item><title>This is Kiwi: Simran Kaur on planning for future wealth | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130029/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130029/</guid><description>Podcast Description As founder of Girls That Invest, Simran Kaur wears multiple hats: financial columnist, best-selling author, TEDx speaker, and financial literacy advocate. Her highly acclaimed podcast has garnered over four million downloads and topped the business podcast charts worldwide. At just 26 years old, Simran’s remarkable achievements, including speaking at the UK House of Parliament, defy her age.
In this conversation Jane Yee gets to know the woman behind the success story, revealing Simran’s humility, generosity and determination to empower others.</description></item><item><title>The future runs on electric power | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130030/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130030/</guid><description>Podcast Description A groundbreaking transformation is underway in the United States, as they embark on an industrial revolution that aims to replace a staggering one billion fossil-fueled machines with clean, electric alternatives fueled by the forces of nature—wind, sun, and water. This remarkable shift, ignited by a masterful manoeuvre within the world&amp;rsquo;s largest and most complex political economy, has set the stage for an inspiring journey. Bernard Hickey sits down with climate tech entrepreneur and activist Saul Griffith to unravel the story of how Saul and his fellow activists collaborated with Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s White House to successfully take control of the climate debate.</description></item><item><title>This is Kiwi: Dave Letele on beating the odds | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130031/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130031/</guid><description>Podcast Description While you wait for the next episode of When the Facts Change, we thought you might enjoy This is Kiwi – a new series about inspiring New Zealanders brought to you by our friends at Kiwibank. Beyond his triumphs in professional sport, Dave Letele has always maintained an unwavering commitment to his community. Through the establishment of the BBM Motivation foundation, Dave has emerged as a beacon of hope, establishing free fitness classes, nutritional guidance, and smarter food banks to help those eager to reclaim their health.</description></item><item><title>How to ensure fairer infrastructure costs for all | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130032/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130032/</guid><description>Podcast Description For decades, the wealthiest New Zealanders have been reaping enormous private gains from public infrastructure investments. While those who benefit consider the game fair, the less fortunate bear the overwhelming burden of infrastructure costs. Bernard Hickey talks with Geoff Cooper, the head of strategy at the Infrastructure Commission, as they delve into groundbreaking policy ideas aimed at transforming the existing landscape. Together, they explore strategies to achieve better distribution of infrastructure costs and envision a society where all individuals contribute their fair share towards a brighter future.</description></item><item><title>Redefining carbon farming in Aotearoa | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130033/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Both farmers and environmentalists fear Aotearoa becoming a sea-to-sea swathe of permanent Pinus radiata plantations that collect billions of dollars of carbon sequestration credits for investors, but few create long-term jobs and become deserts for native flora and fauna to thrive. But it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be that way. There are plenty of redwood, eucalypt, and other fast-growing carbon sinks that foster native regrowth and birds, and which would keep billions of emissions credits in Aotearoa, rather than going overseas.</description></item><item><title>Is AI enhancing efficiency or encroaching on humanity? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130034/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130034/</guid><description>Podcast Description AI is gearing to be as much of a cultural revolution as the birth of the iPhone, but it’s still yet to be seen how its implementation in the workplace will impact everything from efficiency to recruitment. In this week’s episode of When the Facts Change, Bernard Hickey talks to CK Lee, founder of receipt scanning app Taggun, about how he uses AI in his business and as a tool to improve his thinking.</description></item><item><title>How big does Chris Bishop want us to be? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130035/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 18:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130035/</guid><description>Podcast Description National&amp;rsquo;s housing spokesman Chris Bishop wants councils to zone enough land with enough pipes and roads to house 30 years worth of population growth, but not all through densification. In this week&amp;rsquo;s episode of When The Facts Change, Bernard Hickey asks Bishop just how big he wants Aotearoa to be, and who will pay for all the extra infrastructure needed when that growth is on green fields. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>How we budget is costing us dearly | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130036/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 19:56:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Aotearoa has been penny-wise and pound-foolish with its investments in maintaining and building public infrastructure and services. This week Bernard Hickey talks with wellbeing economist Katherine Trebeck about how the machinery of government, politicians and voters can think and plan differently to avoid that same pound-foolishness again Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Budget special: Bernard Hickey and Toby Manhire binge on bread and butter | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130037/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 06:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130037/</guid><description>Podcast Description With the political and economic gravities pulling in various directions, the finance minister was tasked with providing support for the hardest hit by the cost-of-living crisis without heaping sugar in an already high-inflation sauce. And on top of that, it&amp;rsquo;s an election year. To assess whether Grant Robertson managed to thread that needle, Gone By Lunchtime’s Toby Manhire sits down with When the Facts Change’s Bernard Hickey to discuss their Budget 2023 reactions.</description></item><item><title>Could standardising housing drive down the prices? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130038/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Most new homes in Aotearoa are still designed with bespoke elements and a multitude of building materials. It feels a lot like the early days of cars, when there were thousands of manufacturers with many more thousands of models of cars. Then along came Henry Ford and Toyota to standardise and mass produce cars, driving prices down and quality up. This week Bernard Hickey talks with Simplicity Living MD Shane Brealey about how to build the Toyota Corolla of homes at two thirds the cost of other homes.</description></item><item><title>The pathway to homeownership for solo buyers | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130039/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Buying a home with a partner you&amp;rsquo;re romantically involved with has always been the norm, but what if you&amp;rsquo;re not in a relationship or prefer to go solo? Bernard Hickey talks to Kiwibank&amp;rsquo;s Philippa Scott and Pip Maxwell about their new Co-own mortgages, which allow flatmates, brothers, sisters, cousins, and groups of friends to save, borrow and own houses together in ways that fit around modern family structures. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>How do we fix New Zealand's tax inequity? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130040/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130040/</guid><description>Podcast Description An IRD investigation into the wealth of New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s richest 311 families found they paid an effective tax rate of just 9.5%, less than a third the 30% effective rate being paid by single PAYE-taxpaying renter on $80,000 a year. This week Bernard Hickey talks to the report’s commissioner, revenue minister David Parker, to break down what the report says and discuss the fairness New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s current tax system.</description></item><item><title>How hiring autistic people benefits your workplace | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130041/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130041/</guid><description>Podcast Description As companies struggle to replace staff of all skill levels, is there a group of potential workers being overlooked by employers because they don&amp;rsquo;t fit the traditional mold? Bernard Hickey talks with Autism NZ CEO Dane Dougan about the benefits that come with hiring autistic people and what employers can do to make their workplace safer for autistic staff members. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices</description></item><item><title>What we need to do to meet our climate goals | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130042/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Aotearoa needs to double the size of its electricity industry over the next 30 years to meet our emissions reductions targets. We&amp;rsquo;ve done it before in 1945 to 1985 but can we do it again? With a myriad of privately and publicly owned companies waiting for market and regulatory signals, it seems unlikely. Bernard Hickey talks with electricity expert John Hancock about the prospects of doubling our power industry again and explains how we can get it done.</description></item><item><title>Is your employer watching you work from home? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130043/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130043/</guid><description>Podcast Description The surge in working from home looks here to stay, unleashing a whole new class of software tools for bosses to keep an eye on workers — and not always in a good way. Bernard Hickey talks to Multitudes.co founder and CEO Lauren Peate about the risks of employer surveillance, and how software can be made more ethical, more productive and less stressful. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Will climate change wipe out your insurance? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130044/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Since the devastation of Cyclone Gabrielle, insurers have begun rapidly repricing the land beneath homes for flood risk, which is creating a Wild West for home owners impatient to find out if their lands are going to continue to be insurable. Bernard Hickey talks to insurance and banking academic Dr. Michael Naylor from Massey University to explore what home owners can do to protect their housing insurance in a warming climate.</description></item><item><title>How Labour just hurt the Emissions Trading Scheme | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130045/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris Hipkins&amp;rsquo; dump of Ardern-era policy has potentially jeopardised a major part of the government&amp;rsquo;s climate change response. Bernard Hickey talks to climate policy expert Christina Hood from Climate Compass to find out why this month’s Emissions Trading Scheme auction failed and how she feels cabinet have destroyed confidence in the market by accident. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode: Are the Greens willing to work with National? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130046/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 21:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130046/</guid><description>Podcast Description With Chris Hipkins transitioning into a new era of policy, what does that mean for the Green Party&amp;rsquo;s agreement with Labour? Green MP Julie Anne Genter joins Bernard to discuss the Green Party&amp;rsquo;s position on Labour&amp;rsquo;s policy dump, who they&amp;rsquo;re willing to go into government with, and her hopes for the upcoming election. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Why Auckland Council should just borrow | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130047/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 20:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Auckland mayor Wayne Brown has embarked on a money saving scheme to plug a $295 million &amp;ldquo;fiscal black hole&amp;rdquo; in the council&amp;rsquo;s finances, but is it true? A Better Budget for Auckland&amp;rsquo;s India Logan-Riley talks with Bernard Hickey about the flaws in Brown&amp;rsquo;s logic and suggests an alternative to the mayor&amp;rsquo;s belt tightening that doesn&amp;rsquo;t involve slashing social services. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The future of sustainable farmlands | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130048/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is the environment changing faster than we can adapt to? The emissions trading scheme incentivised livestock farmers to rid their land of animals in favour of converting it for pine forestry. However, the silt and leftover slash used to make those forests are the same things that wrecked havoc on horticultural lands during Cyclone Gabrielle. Alison Dewes and John Burke are two farmers who feel they&amp;rsquo;ve adopted a much better, and more sustainable farming practice - converting some of their grass paddocks back into native forest and wetlands.</description></item><item><title>Is corporate greed the real culprit behind inflation? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130049/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who is really winning from skyrocketing inflation? National Party finance spokesperson Nicola Willis went head to head with Reserve Bank governor Adrian Orr this week, blaming him and the government for being an active contributor to inflation by printing mass amounts of money during the COVID response. However, another factor may be to blame - corporate price gouging. Bernard Hickey explores how widening company profit margins may be the real reason behind the countries inflation issues.</description></item><item><title>Will we change in the aftermath of Cyclone Gabrielle? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130050/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amongst the tragedy of Aotearoa&amp;rsquo;s recent climate disasters is an opportunity to enact lasting legislation to prevent it happening again. Climate policy academic David Hall is tasked with finding the economically and politically sensible ways that we can adapt to the climate crisis. He talks with Bernard Hickey about gnarly politicking and the changes we need to make to avoid environmental disaster. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.</description></item><item><title>How Cyclone Gabrielle will forever change the housing industry | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130051/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130051/</guid><description>Podcast Description The effects of climate change are beginning to pool at the feet of New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s coastal home owners. Climate Sigma managing director Belinda Storey says most beachfront properties will either need to be moved or demolished in the next 30 years. She and Bernard discuss the morally hazardous world of climate finance, the future cost of repairing mega-mansions, and how the taxpayer can avoid footing the full bill. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Will RMA reform actually solve our water woes? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130052/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130052/</guid><description>Podcast Description A replacement to the Resource Management Act of 1991 is currently going through the motions of parliament with hopes to create more resource and eco friendly industries in Aotearoa. However, Irrigation NZ CEO Vanessa Winning is worried the new version of the RMA could create perverse and unintended consequences. Bernards talks to her about how the government&amp;rsquo;s good intentions could negatively impact our produce production. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>How venture capitalism can fund a greener economy | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130053/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130053/</guid><description>Podcast Description How does Aotearoa stop relying so heavily on agriculture to prop up our economy? Online tax and accounting service Hnry just raised $35m to grow its software on-demand service across the globe. Bernard Hickey talks with AirTree partner Jackie Vullinghs about how venture capitalists are funding Aotearoa’s fastest growing, least-polluting and highest-wage export growth sector. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Is Wellington at risk of a slow, painful death? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130054/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Parts of the nation&amp;rsquo;s capital have turned into a wasteland of red stickers, and &amp;lsquo;for lease&amp;rsquo; signs. WellingtonNZ CEO John Allen has been given the challenge of breathing new life into the city&amp;rsquo;s economy, businesses, and image. He talks to Bernard about housing and hotel shortages, sewerage on the streets, a movie industry on the brink of collapse, and all the other challenges facing Te Whanganui-a-Tara in the coming decade.</description></item><item><title>Tory Whanau's plan for transport, housing, and the future of Wellington City | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130055/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wellington has a new mayor determined to shake things up. At the beginning of the year, Tory Whanau was a mayoral candidate pitching her ambitious vision for the future of Wellington city. Now, she sits in the top spot and is tasked with turning that vision into a reality. She talks with Bernard, exactly one year on from when they last spoke on the podcast, to discuss economics, housing, and who she would be nervous about becoming the next transport minister.</description></item><item><title>Mini-pod: "Let that sink in" | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130056/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130056/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a three-episode miniseries over summer Bernard breaks down the quotes from 2022 that changed everything&amp;hellip; This episode, Elon Musk confidently strides into Twitter HQ to claim his new seat as CEO holding&amp;hellip; A sink? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mini-pod: "Wicked perfect storm" | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130057/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130057/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a three-episode miniseries over summer Bernard breaks down the quotes from 2022 that changed everything&amp;hellip; This episode, Jacinda Ardern blames a &amp;ldquo;wicked perfect storm&amp;rdquo; for the cost of living crisis that swept over the entire country. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mini-pod: "Cool the jets" | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130058/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130058/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a three-episode miniseries over summer Bernard breaks down the quotes from 2022 that changed everything&amp;hellip; This episode, Adrian Orr tells New Zealanders to &amp;ldquo;cool their jets&amp;rdquo;, signalling a dark storm cloud set to loom over the economy. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>So the economy's a mess... What now? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130059/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Well that took a turn, didn&amp;rsquo;t it? With a war in Ukraine, supply chain mayhem and a deadly disease tearing through the workforce, this year was one for the history books. Bernard is joined by Kiwibank chief economist Jarrod Kerr to discuss the previous year, increasing interest rates and what it all means for 2023. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mind the pay gap | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130060/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 22:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why is it that women still earn less than men across many industries in New Zealand? Economist Isabelle Sim is using groundbreaking research to uncover why the stubbornly high pay gap really exists. She talks with Bernard about how other countries achieve pay equity, working mums, and why transparency is the best way forward. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Turning the nation's happiness into data | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130061/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130061/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Treasury has just published a government mandated report on the overall wellbeing of our country. Typically, a country&amp;rsquo;s success would be measured by GDP, employment rates, and net debt, but this report aims to redefine how New Zealand measures growth. Tim Ng from the Treasury talks with Bernard about how this shifting of the goalposts might affect the future of political investment. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Pensioner poverty has changed the retirement debate | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130062/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130062/</guid><description>Podcast Description We hear a lot about young people struggling with housing affordability, but much less is spoken of how the housing crisis will impact pensioners. A new report shows we&amp;rsquo;re at serious risk of doubling the number of retirees facing rent and mortgage stress by 2048. While the debate around who should get NZ Superannuation and how much they should get has been mostly frozen in time since the late 1990s, the current landscape means the debate has now changed.</description></item><item><title>How to share your capital gains | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130063/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130063/</guid><description>Podcast Description While billionaires build their bunkers in Queenstown, Julie Scott, CEO of the Community Housing Trust is building affordable homes with profits made by new suburb developers. She tells Bernard all about how inclusionary rezoning can be used to make the rapidly expanding region affordable for locals again Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How do we solve our emissions issue? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130064/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130064/</guid><description>Podcast Description Methane and nitrous oxide produced by cows and sheep remain the biggest barrier to Aotearoa meeting its emissions reduction goal. Science writer Melanie Newfield talks with Bernard to break down The Government&amp;rsquo;s recent policy announcement and discuss why gassy livestock is so crucial to the country&amp;rsquo;s climate solution. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nicola Willis is breaking from tradition | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130065/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130065/</guid><description>Podcast Description The National Party&amp;rsquo;s Deputy Leader has spoken out against The Reserve Bank Governor Adrian Orr, calling for an independent review if National are elected in 2023. Skyrocketing house prices and record-high inflation are being blamed on The Government&amp;rsquo;s money printing scheme during the COVID-19 pandemic. Willis says an external review would answer the question - how can this be avoided in the future? Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Another broken relationship with the Crown | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130066/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130066/</guid><description>Podcast Description As central and local government battle for asset control, the lack of investment in infrastructure becomes an ever-growing issue. Bernard talks to former Auckland Deputy Mayor Penny Hulse about the tension between these forms of government and how it can be mended - what has ruptured in these relationships and why does it matter? Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How effective is our environmental spending? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130067/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Aotearoa’s Government spends $2b a year on the environment, but where does that money go? Backed by his recently published report on our tracking of emissions, Parliamentary Commissioner for the Environment Simon Upton dives into discussion with Bernard Hickey on the importance of collective clarity and knowledge in the measurement of our environmental spending. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How green is your building? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130068/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Building developers and funders are scrambling to work out how much carbon dioxide is emitted or captured in a building’s construction and operation over its lifetime. Jasmax’s Carbon Research Lead, Paul Jurasovich, joins Bernard to map out the new world of carbon budgeting for buildings (such as the five star green-rated Kiwibank corporate office in Auckland). Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Using NFTs and engineered wood to solve housing problems | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130069/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Professor Anthony Hoete is trying to solve some of the biggest housing problems in Te Ao Māori with new tools and technology. He talks with Bernard Hickey on This weeks When the Facts Change about using NFTs to bring together dispersed iwi land titles and engineered timber to turn iwi forests into homes that are carbon sinks. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to mark a B Corp | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130070/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kiwibank has just produced its first sustainability report as a B Corp, paving the way for big organisations joining the ESG reporting movement. But what does a pass mark look like? How can the marking process be used to do better? CEO Steve Jurkovich joins Bernard in conversation to korero about what Kiwibank did to its climate emissions, how it measured pay equity and what can be done to help fund Māori housing.</description></item><item><title>The build-to-rent solution | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130071/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Private rentals owned by ‘Mum and Dad’ landlords are expensive and unstable, making it difficult for tenants and their tamariki to settle into their communities and schools. As renting becomes a long-term reality for more and more of us, is there a better way? In this episode, Bernard is joined by Helen O’Sullivan, CEO of Crockers Property Group, to talk about one possible solution, and what policy tweaks the government needs to make to help it grow.</description></item><item><title>The three horsemen of our housing apocalypse | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130072/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130072/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s evident to those living in Aotearoa that doing so does not come cheap, but did you know our housing and rental affordability is the worst in the world? Treasury Chief Economist Dominick Stephens went hunting with a team of Government experts for the reasons why. Revealing the three key factors driving our housing market, Stephens deep dives into conversation with Bernard Hickey on how the combination of lower interest rates, land use restrictions and our tax system has caused such an explosion.</description></item><item><title>So who 'owns' the car parks? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130073/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130073/</guid><description>Podcast Description The great battle for walkable cities that prioritise cyclists and pedestrians over cars has only just begun. In this battle, Waka Kotahi is a key player in deciding how this battle plays out. In this week&amp;rsquo;s episode, Bernard Hickey talks to Waka Kotahi&amp;rsquo;s urban mobile manager Kathryn King to find out how mode shift might be allowed, or made to happen. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.</description></item><item><title>Economics 101 for housing supply | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130074/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bernard Hickey dives deep into the demand and supply factors behind our endemic housing shortages with Kiwibank economist Jeremy Couchman, including what they might mean for house prices. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>What Adrian Orr just learned about the global economy | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130075/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130075/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Reserve Bank Governor has just returned from the hottest and most important annual get together of central bankers at Jackson Hole in Wyoming. He found a bunch of Governors hunkered down and under attack because inflation blew past their targets this year. He talks exclusively to Bernard Hickey about what has changed permanently in the workings of the global economy that is slowing growth and increasing inflation, and why we should care here in Aotearoa.</description></item><item><title>Two epic tax fails | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130076/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 01:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Revenue Minister David Parker steered the government into a political minefield this week with his extension of GST to all KiwiSaver fees that was gone by lunchtime within a day. Bernard Hickey talks with tax expert and historian Terry Baucher about why this epic fail pales in comparison to another from 33 years ago when Labour’s David Caygill failed to introduce a Capital Gains Tax to match our ‘perfect’ GST and income tax systems.</description></item><item><title>The finger of blame for high house prices | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130077/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130077/</guid><description>Podcast Description The &amp;ldquo;official&amp;rdquo; economists in Wellington went hunting for the true culprit behind Aotearoa’s house prices and rents being the most expensive in the world – but perhaps the biggest culprit is the government itself. With Wellington gaslighting the councils, now the finger of blame may be turning back in its direction. In this week&amp;rsquo;s episode, Bernard Hickey talks to Hamilton mayor Paula Southgate about the funding infrastructure and challenges, as well as why not enough land was opened up, to then be sold.</description></item><item><title>Aotearoa's future of low battery anxiety | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130078/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Electricity is something we can&amp;rsquo;t live without at this stage in global growth – but with expensive renewable supply, how do users and the industry match the demand? In this week&amp;rsquo;s episode, Bernard Hickey speaks with Octopus Energy&amp;rsquo;s Margaret Cooney about possible solutions to shift away from expensive peaks, and how an obscure law change might unleash a surge of retail competition, all in the hopes of calming our collective low battery anxiety.</description></item><item><title>Is your property a climate change hot potato? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130079/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130079/</guid><description>Podcast Description If climate change projections make their way to Land Information Memorandums, owners of coastal properties may find themselves struggling to stay afloat long before waves start lapping at their door. Vulnerable properties will become uninsurable causing banks to withhold lending – suddenly passing on that slice of hot potato paradise will be near impossible. This week James Shaw joins Bernard Hickey to talk about the real meaning of climate change adaptation and who&amp;rsquo;s responsible for funding infrastructure that will mitigate the effects of climate change.</description></item><item><title>Finally, more women in construction | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130080/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130080/</guid><description>Podcast Description With unemployment now having climbed to 3.3% within the industry, builders are now crying out for workers. With this ascent and historically driven as a mostly male-dominated field, they’re getting serious about hiring the other half of the population. Bernard Hickey talks with Kiwibank economist Mary Jo Vergara about a surprise rise in employment growth for women in construction. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Could full transparency solve our pay equity problems? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130081/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Imagine living in a society where details about everyone’s earnings and taxes are publicly available. With a gender pay gap of just 4%, Norway has operated under this system of pay transparency since the 1800s and some argue it’s time for a similar approach in Aotearoa. Join Bernard Hickey as he talks to AUT Professor Gail Pacheco, who heads the NZ Work Research Institute, about whether pay transparency is the answer to help address our pay equity gaps for women, Māori and Pasifika.</description></item><item><title>The reality of free fares | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130082/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Half-price bus and train fares are good, but wouldn’t completely free fares be even better? Bernard Hickey talks to transport and urban planning academic Jen McArthur about the economics and the politics of free public transport. He even discovers some positives that make the idea more attractive to the usual opponents. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Time to pull the migration lever? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130083/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Businesses, hospitals and the opposition are pleading for a loosening of migrant worker restrictions to ease the intense labour shortages that are forcing cancellations and jury-rigged services up and down the motu. Bernard Hickey sits down to interview Productivity Commission chair Ganesh Nana to find out if a migration surge would solve our productivity problem, and why any decision to pull the migration lever must also look to pull the infrastructure investment lever.</description></item><item><title>Is the housing market’s tide really turning? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130084/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130084/</guid><description>Podcast Description For decades we&amp;rsquo;ve been warned of major slumps that never happened, but the Reserve Bank&amp;rsquo;s new chief economist says this time, it&amp;rsquo;s different. With a history of central bank governors and finance ministers making similar predictions that never came to pass, listen as Bernard Hickey challenges Paul Conway&amp;rsquo;s view that the housing market’s ever-upward tide may be turning. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Shy small businesses are holding the nation back | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130085/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why do so few of our small businesses make the leap to become bigger, faster-growing engine rooms for economic growth and higher wages? Curiously, Aotearoa also has a long tail of older business owners that are comfortable bumbling along with sub-scale firms that would do better with bigger and more ambitious owners. This week Bernard Hickey talks to ABC Business Sales MD Chris Small about why so many business owners won’t jump up, or out, and why it’s holding back the nation as a whole.</description></item><item><title>The great resignation hits Aotearoa | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130086/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130086/</guid><description>Podcast Description The employment landscape currently favours workers, yet we’re still reluctant to ask for a pay rise and fear being sacked. Bernard Hickey is joined by AUT professor Jarrod Harr to examine how work culture, pay, conditions and the power relationships between employers and employees have been transformed by the pandemic and try to figure out why workers still feel insecure and what employers can do to combat the great resignation.</description></item><item><title>Inflation everywhere, except the housing market | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130087/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130087/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s hitting food, petrol, rent, shipping and wages, but inflation hasn’t touched the housing market. Bernard is joined by Kiwibank economist Mary-Jo Vergara to unpack the surprisingly big and long spike of inflation that is cascading into every aspect of our day-to-day lives. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Budget 2022: Reaction special | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130088/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 04:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bernard Hickey (When The Facts Change; parliament studio) and Toby Manhire (Gone By Lunchtime; Auckland studio) join forces for a budget reaction crossover special. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The rise of the inflation robots | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130089/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Inflation has become the thief in our wallets for the first time in a generation and there are plenty of culprits to blame. The Ukraine War, supply chain disruptions and US$10t of money printing are the first and most obvious cabs off the rank, but there&amp;rsquo;s a new and more insidious source of inflation developing: automatic inflation. These annual CPI-linked price increases from a range of companies, utilities, government departments and regulated services are fine when inflation is &amp;ldquo;normal&amp;rdquo; and stable around 2%, but this year’s 6% increases are turning into a nasty feedback loop of inflationary pressure that will hurt those on the lowest disposable incomes the hardest.</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode: What the new lending rules mean for mortgages | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130090/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130090/</guid><description>Podcast Description In December 2021 the government made changes to the Credit Contracts and Consumer Finance Act that were designed to protect borrowers – but had consequences that saw reports of people being rejected for lending because they had takeaways too often, had too many streaming subscriptions, and even because they made regular investments. Earlier this month, the Minister for Commerce and Consumer Affairs, David Parker announced that the Government plans to make further changes to the CCCFA to help avoid these unintended outcomes.</description></item><item><title>Petrol prices and our lizard brains | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130091/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130091/</guid><description>Podcast Description The government’s decision to cut fuel taxes this week highlights just how hard it is for politicians and voters to deal with short sharp shocks to the system. The ‘lizard brain’ part of our body politic has evolved to recoil from a petrol price shock, but this type of ‘thinking fast’ will need to be replaced with ‘thinking slow’ if we are to engineer a just transition to carbon zero.</description></item><item><title>Unpacking our supermarkets’ superprofits | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130092/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Back in 2002, supermarket chains Foodtown and Woolworths were allowed to combine into the group now known as Countdown. That consolidated the market down to a duopoly of the Australian-owned Countdown and the local cooperative of Foodstuffs, which owns Pak’nSave, New World and Four Square. A new report published by the Commerce Commission this week found the duopoly has used its market power to suck profits from either side of them in the grocery supply chain to make an estimated $430m a year in superprofits.</description></item><item><title>What strawberries can teach us about NZ’s economy | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130093/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130093/</guid><description>Podcast Description New Zealand has a lot of small businesses, but relatively few of them expand into larger, more productive operations. Strawberry farms are a good example of this – many don’t invest in technology or systems to grow scale or profits, because it’s more profitable to simply wait for the farm’s land value to rise instead. But there are some interesting exceptions out there too. This week, Bernard talks to strawberry scientist Geoff Langford and Kiwibank business banking manager Wayne McEntee about the sorts of choices small businesses face around going up, going out, or just remaining stagnant.</description></item><item><title>What the Reserve Bank's latest decision means | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130094/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130094/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Reserve Bank made its first big set piece decision of the year this week, releasing its monetary policy statement and raising the Official Cash Rate to 1.0%. So what does that mean for interest rates and house prices? In this week’s episode, Bernard Hickey asks Reserve Bank governor Adrian Orr about the property price boom and wage inflation, and talks through the implications of the Reserve Bank’s decisions and outlook with Kiwibank chief economist Jarrod Kerr.</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode: The power of diversity and inclusion | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130095/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130095/</guid><description>Podcast Description This year marks 50 years of the gay liberation movement in New Zealand – 50 years of fight, advocacy, celebration, progress and frustration in the Rainbow community’s struggle for equality and equity. In recognition of the Pride festival this month, Liz Knight, chief risk officer at Kiwibank and a proud member of the Rainbow community, and Jess Segal, senior manager of Leadership, and Diversity, Equity and Inclusion at Kiwibank, joined The Spinoff&amp;rsquo;s Simon Day to discuss how far New Zealand has come – and the work that still needs to be done.</description></item><item><title>Aluminium prices vs our climate plans | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130096/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130096/</guid><description>Podcast Description The price of aluminium has exploded in the last six months – so much so that Rio Tinto now wants to delay the closure of the aluminium smelter it owns at Tiwai Point beyond the planned end date of 2024. But this decision has thrown a big spanner into the works of climate change planners, investors and politicians, who had been working under the assumption that, come 2024, the 13% of the nation’s power supply that Tiwai Point uses would become available to help cities decarbonise their transport fleets.</description></item><item><title>Light rail’s heavy carbon footprint | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130097/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Building a light rail line between Auckland’s CBD and the airport sounds like a good thing for the climate and reducing transport emissions. But the new plan to dig a long tunnel and lay a new railway line will actually generate an extra 400,000 tonnes of carbon emissions in its first 10 years, and take until 2040 before it starts being carbon negative. Still sound like a good idea?</description></item><item><title>Why is everything getting more expensive? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130098/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who or what is responsible for all the price inflation we’ve been seeing lately? And how do we know when we’re paying too much? Bernard Hickey talks to economic consultant Donal Curtin (previously of the New Zealand Commerce Commission) and Kiwibank chief economist Jarrod Kerr. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>A big year for local politics | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130099/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130099/</guid><description>Podcast Description All the political roads in housing and climate change lead to council chambers rather than parliament these days. This week, we look ahead to the high stakes local elections in October, which will decide whether much progress is made in the next decade to deal with our twin emergencies. Bernard talks to Wellington mayoral candidate Tory Whanau about how tough 2021 was in local politics, and the massive year ahead.</description></item><item><title>A big year for the economy | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130100/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Against all expectations a year ago, the global economy ended 2021 wracked by inflation and a debate about whether it’s transitory (and so can be ignored by central banks) or bedding in (and should be beaten down with higher interest rates). Bernard talks with Kiwibank’s Jarrod Kerr about what’s happening in our housing market and how well our exporters have done to offset the collapses of international tourism and education exports.</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode: The dangers of debt | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130101/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Natalie Vincent is the chief executive of Ngā Tangata Microfinance Trust, which works with New Zealanders experiencing financial hardship to provide them with small, safe, interest-free loans and mentorship to help them get – and stay – out of debt. The last two years have been the busiest in the organisation’s history, and December 2021 brought the most referrals for support yet. Natalie tells Simon Day how easy it can be for people to get into financial difficulty when one crisis puts them into debt, how hard it can be to get out and the importance of building financial capability and wellbeing.</description></item><item><title>A big year for housing | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130102/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bernard Hickey is joined by Ockham founder Mark Todd to dig through a massive year for housing. They talk about the record high number of houses being built despite all sorts of supply chain grief and skills shortages, plus whether the ‘Townhouse Nation’ law changes rammed through Parliament will actually make a difference, or leave us regretting the prescriptive legislation in years to come. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Summer reissue: An epic intergenerational wealth transfer | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130103/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130103/</guid><description>Podcast Description When the Facts Change is taking a short break over summer. We&amp;rsquo;ll be back with new episodes soon, but until then here&amp;rsquo;s one of our most popular episodes of 2021. From July: Over the last 30 years, a generation of voters and politicians made a decision to stop investing in infrastructure – it’s expensive, and it means you can’t cut taxes or keep rates low. Now we’re seeing the collective catastrophe of this underinvestment landing on our heads in the form of labour shortages and massive housing affordability problems.</description></item><item><title>Summer reissue: The impossible dream of home ownership | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130104/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130104/</guid><description>Podcast Description When the Facts Change is taking a short break over summer. We&amp;rsquo;ll be back with new episodes soon, but until then here&amp;rsquo;s one of our most popular episodes of 2021. From June: For a growing number of Wellingtonians, the dream of owning a home in the city is all but dead. And it&amp;rsquo;s the same story in other parts of the country too – successive governments have sat on their hands afraid that doing anything to create more housing might drive down prices, and as a result median rents and house prices have skyrocketed out of reach.</description></item><item><title>Eight years to carbon zero | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130105/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130105/</guid><description>Podcast Description The UN Climate Change Conference in Glasgow earlier this year removed all doubt about how fast we need to cut climate emissions. If we’re to keep warming below 1.5 degrees, we need to make big changes by 2030 – two or three decades to build rail lines and wait for Tiwai Point to close won’t cut it any more. So what needs to be done to rapidly engineer a just transition to zero carbon in less than a decade?</description></item><item><title>Our discounted future | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130106/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130106/</guid><description>Podcast Description The social discount rate is one of the tools the government uses to calculate the cost benefit analysis on long-term investments. And according to a report released earlier this week, our social discount rate has been too high for more than 30 years. In this episode, Bernard Hickey looks at the way the government makes decisions around intergenerational issues like climate change, child poverty and housing affordability, and how things like discount rates have disadvantaged future generations.</description></item><item><title>The shipping forecast | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130107/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Like the rest of the world, Aotearoa’s ports are clogged with containers, trucks, ships and growing shipping bills. But it’s not all because of Covid worker shortages and lockdowns. In this episode, Bernard Hickey looks at how the many weird economic effects of Covid are playing out through the world’s logistics chains, from frantic factories to empty store shelves and even Adele’s new album. Guests: Chris Edwards, president of the Custom Brokers and Freight Forwarders Federation, and professor Tava Olsen, director of the Centre of Supply Chain Management at the University of Auckland Business School.</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode: A new way of banking, with Steve Jurkovich | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130108/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Steve Jurkovich has been CEO of Kiwibank for three years, during which time he has introduced a raft of changes – from embracing te ao Māori to registering as a B Corp. He tells The Spinoff&amp;rsquo;s Duncan Greive what&amp;rsquo;s driven this reimagining of the organisation. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Can we make housing affordable without crashing the market? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130109/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130109/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week new National leader Chris Luxon was asked a question that was posed to Jacinda Ardern and Judith Collins before last year’s election: Do you want house prices to fall? It’s a curly one for politicians to answer – how do they make housing more affordable while at the same time preventing the market from collapsing? In this episode Bernard Hickey attempts to figure out how it could be done, and how long it might take to happen.</description></item><item><title>You deserve a raise | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130110/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130110/</guid><description>Podcast Description New Zealand’s Labour Cost Index showed a 2.4% wage increase last year. But when you set that against an inflation increase of 4.9% over the same period, in real terms the average New Zealander took a 2.5% pay cut. In a tight labour market, we should in theory all be marching into our boss’s office and asking for a raise – so why isn’t this happening? To find out, Bernard Hickey talks to CTU chief economist Craig Renney and Kiwibank economist Mary Jo Vergara.</description></item><item><title>What’s behind the booming art market? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130111/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Back in March, a virtually unheard-of digital artist called Mike Winkelmann, aka Beeple, made a collage of 5,000 pieces of his digital art into an NFT and sold it via auction house Christie’s. When the hammer finally fell, bids had reached over US$69million. In just the last couple of weeks, some similarly eye-watering prices have been fetched in New Zealand’s fine art market, with Michael Parekowhai’s sculpture &amp;lsquo;A Peak In Darien&amp;rsquo; selling at auction for a record-breaking NZ$2.</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode: The rise and rise of cyber fraud | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130112/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Recorded during Fraud Awareness Week, Simon Day speaks to Neil Hallett, the New Zealand Operations Manager for IDCARE Australia and New Zealand’s national identity and cyber support service. Kiwibank is a key partner of IDCARE, and the bank refers its customers who have been victims of cyber crime to the charity’s support services. IDCARE offers victims a trained case management officer to guide them through the practical steps for what they need to do to respond to the fraud.</description></item><item><title>The KiwiSaver provider and developer teaming up on housing | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130113/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Back in 2008 New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s property development sector went bust, and it scarred people for over a decade. How do we move past that now that we’ve got all this KiwiSaver money which could be used to build houses much more affordably? Simplicity managing director Sam Stubbs and NZ Living director Shane Brealey join Bernard Hickey to talk about their big plans. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.</description></item><item><title>Climate change and house prices | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130114/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last month the Reserve Bank of New Zealand released its 2021 Climate Change Report, the first significant report it has released on the topic since launching its Climate Change Strategy in 2018. In this episode, Bernard takes a deep dive into what climate change means for monetary policy, and the one thing that dominates not just New Zealand’s economy but our society in general – house prices. With Reserve Bank governor Adrian Orr and Victoria University economist Belinda Storey.</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode: Covid and our economy | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130115/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kiwibank economist Mary Jo Vergara joins Simon Day to talk about how Covid-19 has affected the local economy over the last two years. What has the pandemic revealed about the country’s economic strengths and weaknesses, and what does the forecast for the future look like? Mary Jo also speaks to the financial position of women in Aotearoa and how they have been among the worst affected by the economic fallout from the pandemic.</description></item><item><title>How would a central bank digital currency work? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130116/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Central banks all over the world have been looking at building their own digital currencies – and in the last couple of months, the Reserve Bank of New Zealand has issued a discussion paper about how one might work here. To find out more, Bernard talks to Ian Woolford, the head of money and cash at the RBNZ, and Janine Grainger, the CEO of NZ-based exchange Easy Crypto. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Three storeys high and rising | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130117/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130117/</guid><description>Podcast Description A big new bipartisan deal on housing was announced this week that could change the face of our cities and allow more medium-density housing to be built. But is there a piece of the puzzle missing? To discuss the new RMA changes and the issues they raise, Bernard is joined by Wellington City Councillor Tamatha Paul, Wellington Regional Councillor Thomas Nash, National Party housing spokesperson Nicola Willis and Kiwibank economist Jeremy Couchman.</description></item><item><title>Joining the dots to solve the housing crisis | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130118/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130118/</guid><description>Podcast Description There’s no shortage of cash piled up in New Zealand’s banks and pension funds – but what we do have a shortage of is affordable housing. So how do we connect all the money in the institutional funding sector with the housing projects that would begin to solve the housing crisis? To find out more, Bernard talks to Community Finance GM Paul Gilberd, Forever Affordable Housing founder Imogen Schoots and Community Housing Aotearoa CEO Victoria Crockford.</description></item><item><title>What we've learned about working from home | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130119/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over the last 18 months Covid-19 has changed the way many of us work and put real pressures on how we organise our lives. To find out more about how the culture of work has changed, the rise of burnout and the inequities the pandemic has exposed, Bernard Hickey talks to tech leader Rowan Simpson and clinical psychologist Jacqui Maguire. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices</description></item><item><title>The B Corp moment | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130120/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130120/</guid><description>Podcast Description More and more companies are committing to doing sustainable and ethical business by becoming B Corporation accredited. Bernard Hickey talks to Kiwibank CEO Steve Jurkovich about what B Corp certification means and why they’ve done it, and B Corp ambassador Tim Jones from Grow Good explains what companies have to do to become accredited. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How sustainable is your supply chain? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130121/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over the last 30 years, we’ve built an incredibly complex supply chain to give us stuff really cheap. But is it really? Or have the costs just been pushed onto the environment and other workers? How do we find out which products are produced cleanly and don’t impose those unseen costs? On this week’s episode, Bernard speaks to John Holt, who’s launching All Things Considered – a global directory that collates, organises and fact checks the sustainability claims of companies and organisations.</description></item><item><title>Cleaning up capitalism from the inside out | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130122/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130122/</guid><description>Podcast Description ESG (Environmental, Social, Governance) investing is a movement that has arisen over the last decade or so, where big fund managers invest only in companies with sustainable, socially responsible policies. It turns out this is often also the most profitable approach in the long run. One of the leading players in this movement has been the New Zealand Superannuation Fund, and its CEO Matt Whineray joins Bernard Hickey in this episode to talk about how the fund operates its ESG policy.</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode: Why Kiwibank is embracing te ao Māori | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130123/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130123/</guid><description>Podcast Description In recognition of Te Wiki o Te Reo Māori and what the language means to the fabric of Aotearoa, The Spinoff’s commercial editorial director Simon Day speaks to Teahooterangi Pihama, head of Māori advisory, and Keita Te Ngoungou, Kiwibank Māori advisor. They’ve been given a mandate to steer the Kiwibank waka on it’s journey into te ao Māori, and talk about why te reo Māori is important for all New Zealanders, and how lifting the cultural competency at Kiwibank can improve outcomes for Māori staff and customers, support the growth of the Māori economy and raise the financial capabilities of Māori.</description></item><item><title>The future of capitalism, with Luigi Zingales | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130124/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gordon Gekko’s “Greed is Good” era of shareholder-driven global capitalism is ending, but what and who will replace it? Bernard Hickey interviews renowned Chicago School economist, author and podcaster Luigi Zingales (Capitalisn&amp;rsquo;t) about what went wrong with corporate capitalism and how it could be fixed. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The case for mandatory vaccines in the workplace | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130125/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Businesses face a big task and some big decisions in the months ahead. They need to ensure as many staff as possible get vaccinated, without breaking the law or alienating their workforces. They’ll have to look at their own vaccination programmes, their own testing policies and their employment policies. Should they adopt a “no jab no job” policy? Can they? To discuss where these lines will be drawn and who should be doing that drawing – businesses or government – Bernard Hickey talks to BusinessNZ CEO Kirk Hope and Frances Hughes from Oceania Healthcare.</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode: How businesses are responding to the return of Covid-19 | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130126/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130126/</guid><description>Podcast Description When New Zealand’s second national level four lockdown was announced in August, it was a situation many New Zealand business owners were already familiar with and prepared for. The Spinoff’s commercial editorial director Simon Day speaks to Quentin Quin, chief customer officer – business banking at Kiwibank, about what businesses have learned from the last 18 months and how that’s changed their response to the most recent outbreak. Before joining Kiwibank, Quentin worked in ​​a number of post conflict countries, emerging economies and unregulated unstable business environments, and he compares that experience to the economic uncertainty of Covid-19.</description></item><item><title>Who's taking advantage of the wage subsidy scheme? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130127/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last year the government paid out $14 billion in wage subsidies to businesses as part of the Covid-19 response. This included a number of large companies who went on to deliver big annual profits and dividends to shareholders – and very few of those companies have repaid it. In this week’s episode, Bernard Hickey looks at the ethics of the wage subsidy scheme and asks: where is the accountability?</description></item><item><title>How should we plan our population? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130128/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130128/</guid><description>Podcast Description How big do we want Aotearoa to be? How fast do we want it to grow, and where? And are we still a classless society, or are we becoming a country of owners and servants? In this episode, Bernard Hickey looks at the need for an actual population policy alongside new migration settings. To find out more he talks to demographers Paul Spoonley and Tahu Kukutai, the New Zealand Infrastructure Commission&amp;rsquo;s Geoff Cooper and geographer Francis Collins.</description></item><item><title>The political economy of the climate crisis | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130129/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130129/</guid><description>Podcast Description How is it that democracies can only make big, politically difficult changes when faced with an emergency? We did it last year with Covid-19 – so could we do it again with the climate emergency that is in our faces right now? New reports released this week all point to the fact we can’t really afford to wait any longer – we need to take some political and economic pain to reduce emissions, and do it fast.</description></item><item><title>How do we fix our unkind migration system? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130130/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130130/</guid><description>Podcast Description What does the way we treat our migrant population say about who we are as a country? With around 200,000 people living and working in New Zealand on temporary visas, pressure is mounting on the government to make sweeping policy changes to address the limbo these migrants are being left in – an already Kafkaesque situation which has only been exacerbated by Covid. To look at how we ended up in this situation and what needs to be done to tackle the problems that have arisen as a result, Bernard talks to National’s immigration spokesperson Erica Stanford, The New Zealand Initiative&amp;rsquo;s Eric Crampton and Dr Oliver Hartwich, along with immigration lawyer Alistair McClymont.</description></item><item><title>Back to the future of public transport | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130131/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bernard Hickey goes on a journey to find out how New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s fascinating public transport history can inform our future, meeting musician, historian and public transport advocate Anthonie Tonnon at Whanganui’s historic Durie Hill underground elevator. Built in 1919, the elevator was once part of an extensive and heavily used public transport network in the city – how were these networks built, why did they die off and what can they tell us about the future of public transport in this country?</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode: SMEs with Kiwibank’s Joanna Greaves | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130132/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130132/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Spinoff business editor Michael Andrew speaks to Joanna Greaves, head of the small and medium enterprise team at Kiwibank. As an award-winning dairy farmer, accountant, agricultural ambassador and small business owner, Joanna has a wonderful insight into the value and the realities of SMEs in New Zealand. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How do we get a vaccination rate over 80%? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130133/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Around the world, countries are seeing Covid-19 vaccination rates plateauing at around 50-60% – and it&amp;rsquo;s hurting them badly. So how will we get our Covid-19 vaccination rates up to the 80%-90% required for herd immunity? In this episode, Bernard Hickey explains how we can nudge our way to that target using behavioural economics and behavioural finance to get there. To find out more, he speaks to Māori health advocate Rawiri McKree Jansen and vaccinologist Helen Petousis-Harris.</description></item><item><title>A big money-saving solar power idea | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130134/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130134/</guid><description>Podcast Description New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s electricity market isn&amp;rsquo;t working to produce enough renewable power to get to carbon zero by 2050 – but maybe there’s a solution in solar power and batteries in everyone’s homes. In this episode, Bernard Hickey explores an idea for how the government could shake up the electricity sector and return the big taxpayer-built power schemes to public ownership. Guests: Flick Electric Co CEO Steve O’Connor and Eric Pyle, the director of public affairs and policy at solarZero.</description></item><item><title>An epic intergenerational wealth transfer | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130135/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over the last 30 years, a generation of voters and politicians made a decision to stop investing in infrastructure – it’s expensive, and it means you can’t cut taxes or keep rates low. Now we’re seeing the collective catastrophe of this underinvestment landing on our heads in the form of labour shortages and massive housing affordability problems. In this episode, Bernard Hickey reveals an intergenerational wealth transfer worth $1 trillion, and how it could be atoned for and reversed – if only to ensure the culprits can enjoy watching their grandchildren grow up healthy, warm and in person.</description></item><item><title>Looking for hope in our housing crisis | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130136/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130136/</guid><description>Podcast Description In last week’s episode, Bernard Hickey talked about how he had given up hope for affordable housing. This week, he talks to some people who still have hope to hear their ideas on how to solve New Zealand’s housing crisis. Kay Saville-Smith is a longtime researcher and policy advisor on housing who still believes there are ways through – in fact, she’s more hopeful now than she has been for years.</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode: Digital innovation with Kiwibank's Ranjit Jayanandhan | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130137/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130137/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this month&amp;rsquo;s bonus episode, The Spinoff’s business editor Michael Andrew is joined by Ranjit Jayanandhan, general manager of Kiwibank’s foundation tech experience hub. As the person leading Kiwibank’s digital innovation journey, Ranjit has a unique perspective into how banking and fintech will change in New Zealand and the increasing role technology plays in the customer experience. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How home ownership became the impossible dream | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130138/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130138/</guid><description>Podcast Description For a growing number of Wellingtonians, the dream of owning a home in the city is all but dead. And it&amp;rsquo;s the same story in other parts of the country too – successive governments have sat on their hands afraid that doing anything to create more housing might drive down prices, and as a result median rents and house prices have skyrocketed out of reach. To find out more about the costs of this housing inaction and if Wellington&amp;rsquo;s Spatial Plan can change anything, Bernard talks to Ashok Jacob from Renters United, Alison Anitawaru Cole from Victoria University, director of the Growing Up in New Zealand study Susan Morton and Kiwibank senior economist Jeremy Couchman.</description></item><item><title>Why is New Zealand’s housing stock so bad? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130139/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130139/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Climate Change Commission report released last week made it clear that we need to start building new houses that are warmer, drier and produce less carbon. Not only that, we need to retrofit all the houses we’ve already built. How do we do this, and how are we going to finance it? To find out more, Bernard talks to healthy housing expert Philippa Howden-Chapman and Kiwibank head of sustainability Julia Jackson.</description></item><item><title>New Zealand's path to carbon zero | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130140/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130140/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Bernard Hickey takes a deep dive into the new Climate Commission report and finds an unrealistic and inadequate prescription to get to carbon zero. To find out more, he speaks to asset manager Paul Winton about how reconfiguring motorways for cycling, walking and buses could be quicker and more effective than building new rail networks, and associate professor Sara Walton from the University of Otago business school explains how insurers and banks are being pushed to force businesses to reduce their emissions and plan for a lower-carbon future.</description></item><item><title>The future of currency | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130141/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever thought about what money really is, and what it might look like in the future? With central banks now considering launching digital currencies to take on the rise of big tech and cryptocurrency, our currency systems could be in for some big changes – so who should we trust to create and run the digital currency or currencies that will define the world’s financial and economic landscapes for decades to come?</description></item><item><title>Designing a social insurance scheme that works | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130142/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130142/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’ve been hearing the phrase “social insurance” a lot since the government released the 2021 budget last week. It’s an idea designed to deal with unemployment we’re going to see a lot more of in the years to come, but it also brings up issues of inequality and fairness. Would introducing unemployment insurance just help embed a two-tier system in which the rich stay rich and the poor stay poor?</description></item><item><title>Budget 2021: Reversing the mother of all budgets | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130143/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130143/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week’s episode is coming to you from parliament, where Bernard Hickey has been up to his elbows in the budget just released by finance minister Grant Robertson. This year’s budget is a big one – it’s the first one after Covid, and with a parliamentary majority, a very popular prime minister at the helm, a strong economy and low public debt, it was a huge opportunity for the government to do some things… so what did they do?</description></item><item><title>What have we got to lose by standing up to China? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130144/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130144/</guid><description>Podcast Description New Zealand has made international headlines in recent weeks for deciding to take the word “genocide” out of a parliamentary motion criticising China for its treatment of Uyghurs in the Xinjiang province. Basically, we were afraid it would hurt our trade relationship. In this episode, Bernard Hickey wants to change our minds on how New Zealand deals with China, and explain why we should follow Australia&amp;rsquo;s lead and stop worrying so much about trade and start standing up for our views on human rights.</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode: Sustainability with Kiwibank's Julia Jackson | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130145/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130145/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Spinoff business editor Michael Andrew is joined by Kiwibank sustainability lead Julia Jackson to talk about the evolving concept of sustainability, its growing influence on businesses and how New Zealanders can better integrate it into their lives. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.fm/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The value of investing in health and happiness | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130146/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130146/</guid><description>Podcast Description How does a government work out the best way to spend money to maximise not just GDP but the long-term health and happiness of its population? This is something our government is trying to do, or says it’s trying to do – but when it comes to the wellbeing side of the equation, is it doing a good enough job? In this episode, Bernard Hickey talks to Girol Karacaoglu, head of the school of government at Victoria University and one of the architects of the way New Zealand analyses happiness.</description></item><item><title>What will the Reserve Bank’s decisions mean for house prices? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130147/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130147/</guid><description>Podcast Description Imagine if the value of your house doubled overnight. Could that actually happen? In this week’s episode, Bernard Hickey explains how it could – and how the Reserve Bank and government are doing things in the next couple of weeks to make sure it doesn’t. To find out more about how banks, lending and the housing market all operate, Bernard talks to Carmen Vicelich, CEO of Valocity Global. She knows exactly how banks decide who to lend to, when to lend to them and how much the property under the loan is worth.</description></item><item><title>New Zealand’s temporary migration scandal | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130148/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130148/</guid><description>Podcast Description A new report on temporary migration in New Zealand suggests the current settings are letting down migrants and contributing to a low wage, low productivity and low wellbeing society. To find out more, in this episode Bernard talks to Julie Fry, the economist who wrote the report, and asks Anu Kaloti from the Migrant Workers’ Association about the scale of temporary migrant exploitation in New Zealand and what needs to change.</description></item><item><title>The real fight for climate and housing action is at council level | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130149/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130149/</guid><description>Podcast Description You may think the big decisions around housing affordability and climate change are being made in the Beehive, and that these are national policies. But in this week’s episode, Bernard suggests these issues are actually manifesting in a series of house-to-house and street-by-street fights at council level. To find out more, he speaks to Tamatha Paul from the Wellington City Council and Auckland city councillor Efeso Collins about how young renters and activists wanting higher density housing and more pedestrian and cycling friendly transport routes will have to fight the battle of their lives in next year’s local elections.</description></item><item><title>Bonus episode: Shannon Te Huia, Kiwibank Local Hero of the Year | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130150/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130150/</guid><description>Podcast Description For the last 12 years, Kiwibank has supported the Local Hero Award, acknowledging the people making a difference to New Zealand communities. In this bonus episode of When the Facts Change, The Spinoff’s business editor Michael Andrew talks with Shannon Te Huia, the 2021 Kiwibank Local Hero of the Year. Shannon established Pūniu River Care in 2015, a marae-based initiative designed to improve water quality and biodiversity by planting trees along the banks of the Pūniu river in the Waikato.</description></item><item><title>Global capitalism’s 'doom loop' and how to stop it | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130151/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130151/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we’re talking about global capitalism, and how it&amp;rsquo;s in danger of destroying itself from the inside out. The concept is known as a “doom loop”: as the economy grows, those who own all the assets get more and more, those who don’t get poorer and poorer, and as a result growth slows as the machine grinds to a halt. And the key to stopping this doom loop lies in addressing inequality and productivity.</description></item><item><title>The rise of the work from home economy | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130152/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130152/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we&amp;rsquo;re looking at the rise of the work from home economy that has grown out of global lockdowns. Bernard talks to Dr Paula O’Kane of Otago University about the encouraging evidence around productivity and flexibility as well as the negative effects of disconnection, Zoom fatigue and the blurring of work and home boundaries. He also speaks with Kiwibank’s Chief People Officer Charlotte Ward about how large organisations managed sudden remote working conditions and the long term changes being made as a result.</description></item><item><title>Unpacking Labour’s new housing package | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130153/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130153/</guid><description>Podcast Description The facts changed earlier this week when the government announced a major new housing package. In this episode, we’ll work out what it all means for buyers and renters with Kiwibank chief economist Jarrod Kerr, before talking to architectural designer, writer and housing advocate Jade Kake (Ngāti Hau, Te Parawhau, Ngāpuhi, Te Whakatōhea, Te Arawa) about a part of the market that didn’t get a lot of attention. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Can NZ's housing affordability problem ever be solved? | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130154/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130154/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to When the Facts Change, a new podcast from The Spinoff together with Kiwibank. Each week host Bernard Hickey and guests will be peeling back the layers of New Zealand’s economy to reveal how it’s changing our lives and our society. This week, we’re talking about housing. Bernard is joined by Kiwibank chief economist Jarrod Kerr to discuss what’s going on with interest rates and whether more high-density housing will help solve our affordability issues.</description></item><item><title>Coming soon – When the Facts Change with Bernard Hickey | When the Facts Change</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5710130155/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 04:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5710130155/</guid><description>Podcast Description Created by The Spinoff together with Kiwibank, When the Facts Change with Bernard Hickey is your essential weekly guide to the intersection of economics, business and politics in Aotearoa. Every Friday, Bernard will be joined by expert and industry-leading guests, including a range of Kiwibank specialists, to peel back the layers of our economy and reveal how it’s changing our lives and our society. This series is for anyone curious about what changes in technology, the global economy, finance, housing and politics will mean for them, their jobs, lives, communities and futures.</description></item></channel></rss>