<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Stick to Football on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/stick-to-football/</link><description>Recent content in Stick to Football on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/stick-to-football/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Jaap Stam on Leaving United, Losing In Istanbul &amp; Ten Hag | Stick to Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8722310001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8722310001/</guid><description>Podcast Description On our latest episode of Stick to Football, brought to you by Sky Bet, we are joined by footballing legend Jaap Stam.
Gary and Roy’s former Manchester United team-mate talks about how the move to Old Trafford came about after establishing himself in the Netherlands.
Once the world’s most expensive defender, Stam chats about the highs of winning the Treble with the Red Devils and reveals all on his infamous exit.</description></item><item><title>It's Now Or Never For England! | Euro 2024 Special | Stick to Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8722310002/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 17:00:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8722310002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to a special Euro’s 2024 preview episode on Stick To Football with Gary Neville, Jamie Carragher, Ian Wright and Roy Keane – the original show from the award-winning The Overlap, brought to you by EA Sports FC 24 on PlayStation 5.
Following the Euro draw the panel talk through the best of the group stages which kick-off in June 2024 in Germany.
&amp;nbsp;
Gary, Jamie, Ian and Roy all chat about England’s chances after losing the last Euro’s tournament on penalties and who should start for Gareth Southgate’s team.</description></item><item><title>United’s Press Leaks, Pep Lashes Out &amp; Being Late! | Stick to Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8722310003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 05:00:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8722310003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome back to Stick To Football with Gary Neville, Jamie Carragher, Ian Wright and Roy Keane – the original show from the award-winning The Overlap, brought to you by Sky Bet.
The panel kick-off the show with a Secret Santa draw. With Jill Scott already making her pick and absent from the episode, the five will return in a special Christmas episode with their secret gifts.
Gary and Jamie respond to Manchester City manager Pep Guardiola’s press conference quotes following Gary’s suggestion that City have become complacent and talk about how Arsenal are hitting the right form as they head into the festive fixtures.</description></item><item><title>Ronnie O'Sullivan On World Titles, Personal Struggles &amp; New Doc | Stick to Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8722310004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 05:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8722310004/</guid><description>Podcast Description On our latest episode of Stick to Football, brought to you by Sky Bet, we are joined by the greatest snooker player of all time Ronnie O’Sullivan. With his documentary The Edge of Everything out on Amazon Prime, Ronnie chats about his life that has seen him become the face of snooker whilst battling addictions and substance abuse.
A Seven-time World Champion, the Rocket reveals how he dealt with stage fright on the table and doesn’t hold back on the ongoing issues in the sport.</description></item><item><title>Everton Fans Should Be Furious! | Stick to Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8722310005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 05:00:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8722310005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome back to Stick To Football with Gary Neville, Jamie Carragher, Ian Wright and Roy Keane – the original show from the award winning The Overlap, brought to you by Sky Bet.
With Jill Scott away on A League of Their Own duty, sports journalist David Ornstein joins the show to explain how Everton breached the Profit and Sustainability rules and why the independent commission came to the decision to dock them the most ever Premier League points.</description></item><item><title>Gazza's Meltdown &amp; Getting Back From Saipan | Stick to Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8722310006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 05:00:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8722310006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome back to Stick To Football with Gary Neville, Ian Wright, Jill Scott and Roy Keane – the original show from The Overlap brought to you by Sky Bet. As we reach the international break, today’s episode is all about our panels stories from playing for their country.
Listen to Roy’s tales of the Republic of Ireland squad at the 1994 World Cup and the build-up to the infamous fall out at the 2002 World Cup.</description></item><item><title>Roy Keane's Red Cards &amp; Wrighty's Rage! | Stick to Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8722310007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 05:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8722310007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome back to Stick To Football with Gary Neville, Ian Wright, Jill Scott and Roy Keane – the new original show from The Overlap brought to you by Sky Bet.&amp;nbsp;
&amp;nbsp;
With the absence of Jamie Carragher due to Champions League commitments, former professional referee Mark Halsey makes an appearance to chat about the latest refereeing and VAR controversies.
&amp;nbsp;
Listen to Roy reliving his red card career record and why Wrighty kicked a referee’s door down.</description></item><item><title>Craig Bellamy On Golf Club Incident &amp; Newcastle Fall-Out | The Overlap Preview | Stick to Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8722310008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 08:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8722310008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Here's a preview of the latest episode of The Overlap where we are joined by former Wales captain and Premier League footballer turned coach Craig Bellamy.
Craig takes on Gary at the Cube in Manchester before a fascinating sit-down interview.
Having clocked up over 500 professional appearances and represented nine clubs over a career that spanned almost 20 years, Bellamy does not lack in stories to tell.
Listen here to this amazing episode if you like - https://linktr.</description></item><item><title>Eddie Hearn: Rooney vs Jake Paul at Old Trafford? | Stick to Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8722310009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 04:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8722310009/</guid><description>Podcast Description On our latest episode of Stick to Football, brought to you by Sky Bet, we are joined by one of the world’s leading sports promoters Eddie Hearn.
Chairman of Matchroom Sport, a sporting promotion company founded by his father Barry, Eddie has a renowned status around the globe having played a major role behind some of boxing’s biggest success stories.
Listen to incredible anecdotes from past promotions, what boxing is like as a business and how Eddie wants to see boxing develop and grow into the community.</description></item><item><title>Arsenal Beat City, Onana's Shaky Start &amp; Rooney Returns | Stick to Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8722310010/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 04:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8722310010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome back to Stick To Football with Gary Neville, Jamie Carragher, Ian Wright, Jill Scott and Roy Keane – the new original show from The Overlap brought to you by Sky Bet.
Join us as we chat about what Arsenal’s win over Champions Manchester City means to the title race and what Roy, Gary and Jamie have to say about Manchester United’s goalkeeping situation.
Find out what one thing Jill hates the most in football and why Ian does not see himself going into football management.</description></item><item><title>Beckham Reveals All on Messi &amp; Netflix Doc | Stick to Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8722310011/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 04:00:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8722310011/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the latest episode of Stick to Football, brought to you by Sky Bet, we are joined by footballing legend David Beckham.
With Netflix’s four-part Beckham documentary released, David relives his glittering career with former Manchester United team-mates Gary Neville and Roy Keane alongside compatriots Ian Wright, Jamie Carragher and Jill Scott.
An England captain for six years, Beckham won a Champions League, six Premier League titles and two FA Cup’s with his boyhood side Manchester United before he moved to Real Madrid, LA Galaxy, AC Milan then retired at PSG.</description></item><item><title>The Sancho Saga at Manchester United | Stick to Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8722310012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 06:51:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8722310012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join Gary Neville, Jamie Carragher, Ian Wright, Jill Scott and Roy Keane as we celebrate the first episode of Stick to Football - the new original show from The Overlap brought to you by Sky Bet.
&amp;nbsp;
We kick off the series with plenty of discussion and debate from the football world, including the latest on Jadon Sancho at Manchester United, whether Arsenal have a leadership problem and why have Chelsea faulted under Mauricio Pochettino so far.</description></item><item><title>Stick to Football Trailer | Stick to Football</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8722310013/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 15:22:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8722310013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to "Stick to Football," a new original show from The Overlap, brought to you by Sky Bet.
I'll be joined by my good friends Jamie Carragher, Roy Keane, Jill Scott, and Ian Wright as we delve deep into the game we're all so passionate about like you've never heard us before.
Each week will be action-packed with plenty of in-depth discussions on current football news and some truly entertaining football stories from each of our careers!</description></item></channel></rss>