<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>RedHanded on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/redhanded/</link><description>Recent content in RedHanded on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 07:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/redhanded/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Episode 328 - The Staircase: Michael Peterson - Part 1 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400001/</guid><description>Podcast Description From the outside the Petersons had it all; the perfect family, a beautiful mansion and more money than they could spend. But on 9th December 2001 all that changed, when Michael Peterson claimed to have found his wife, Kathleen, dead at the bottom of their stairs.
What followed would become a bizarre tale of strange family secrets, shocking revelations and a true crime case obsessed over like nothing before, or since.</description></item><item><title>Episode 327 - Murder in Ulvila | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400002/</guid><description>Podcast Description At 3 am on the 1st of December 2006, Anneli Auer phoned Finnish emergency services – to tell them an intruder was stabbing her husband to death as she spoke.
Police arrived on the scene in less than 10 minutes, but it was too late, and the mysterious killer had seemingly vanished into thin air.&amp;nbsp;
Judicial madness, police fuck-ups, greed, undercover lovers, Satanic child abuse rituals, DNA mix-ups, a family torn apart, and a murder mystery that divided a nation: this is the murder of Jukka Lahti, one of the most notorious cases in Finnish criminal history.</description></item><item><title>Episode 326 - Sarah Payne: Into Thin Air | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vanishing in seconds when her older brother turned away, 8-year-old Sarah Payne’s high-profile disappearance gripped the nation. But as mother and father begged for answers and hoped to see their little girl again, sadly it would leave a very different legacy.
This truly heartbreaking case would change the British legal system forever – not before Rebekah Brooks and ‘News of The World’ brought the British media into absolute chaos.</description></item><item><title>Episode 325 - The Vanishing of Lynette Dawson - Part 2 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400004/</guid><description>Podcast Description The evidence against Chris Dawson was overwhelming from the start - so why did it take several investigations, 2 coronial enquiries and 40 years of agony for Lyon’s family for New South Wales police to even make an arrest?
In our final episode on the murder of Lynette Dawson we discuss the day of her disappearance and the unfathomable lack of effort put into finding her. Not to mention why the police were so unwilling to investigate a man several officers referred to lovingly as ‘Dawso’.</description></item><item><title>Episode 324 - The Vanishing of Lynette Dawson - Part 1 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400005/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Lynette Dawson vanished without a trace in January 1982, her husband played the heartbroken victim. He was an abandoned father of two, with no choice but to move a 16-year-old student into the family home to help him out…
This is part 1 of the strange Australian tale. Expect shocking police corruption; rampant sex abuse running wild in the high schools of Sydney’s Northern Beaches; a man who thought he could get away with anything; and his strangely close relationship with his identical twin brother.</description></item><item><title>Bonus - Israel Keyes: Plan of Attack | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400006/</guid><description>Podcast Description You asked for it – to say a huge final THANK YOU to all of you who brought us Gold in the Listeners' Choice category in this year’s BPAs, we promised you a bonus episode of your choice. And you voted in your thousands, for an episode on horrifying serial-killer scumbag, Israel Keyes.
Keyes didn’t earn his place among America’s most terrifying serial killers only for his brutality, or coldness.</description></item><item><title>Episode 323 - The Murder of Marvin Gaye ft. Disgraceland | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400007/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 1984 murder of one of Motown’s biggest stars – at the hands of his abusive, alcoholic, cross-dressing Pentecostal-preacher father – stunned the industry. But despite the media frenzy, almost no justice was served…
In this episode we look at Gaye’s life story, drawing a line from his early traumas to the whirlwind of violence, drugs and sex that seemed to follow him everywhere.
And to tell the whole story, we’re joined this week by Jake Brennan – host of the most-downloaded music podcast EVER: Disgraceland – who dropped in to give us all the essential context behind one of the most notorious crimes in musical history.</description></item><item><title>Episode 322 - The Body, the P.I. &amp; the Hole in the Wall | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400008/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2010, the body of a man was discovered in a locked hotel room in Beaumont, Texas. Apart from some minor bruising on his groin, the man didn’t have a mark on him – yet he had the internal damage of a severe car crash victim.&amp;nbsp;
There was no sign of forced entry or a struggle. He had no enemies, and nobody in the hotel had seen or heard a thing.</description></item><item><title>RedHaunted Special: Ghost Hunting at The Ancient Ram Inn – Audio Preview | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400009/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Halloween Spooky B*tches! To celebrate our favourite time of year - and for getting GOLD at the British Podcast Awards - we took on one of the most demonic locations in the UK… The Ancient Ram Inn.
In this audio preview of our full-length special (which is on YouTube NOW), the owner of The Ram, Caroline Humphries, tells all on the building’s dark past; we get some creepy contact through our ghost-hunting equipment; and we wind down with some creepy RedHaunted stories - sent in by our lovely listeners!</description></item><item><title>Episode 321 - LIVE: Halloween Special Part 2 – Corpsewood Manor and Burke &amp; Hare | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400010/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400010/</guid><description>Podcast Description ’Tis the season, the SpOoKy season… And that means part two of our annual Halloween story swap, this time LIVE from Dallas, Texas!!!&amp;nbsp;
Listen up as Suruthi tells you all about the aptly named Corpsewood Manor and Hannah discusses the murderous Victorian antics of Burke &amp;amp; Hare.&amp;nbsp;
WATCH THIS EPISODE LIVE WITH THE SLIDES AT: https://youtu.be/3dnlbuxf8f8
Follow us on social media:
Instagram
Twitter
Visit our website:
Website
Sources available on&amp;nbsp;redhandedpodcast.</description></item><item><title>Episode 320 - Halloween Special Part 1: The Vampiress of Barcelona &amp; The Dardeen Family Massacre | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Spooky season is upon us once again, and that can only mean one thing: another instalment of RedHanded’s Halloween story swap! For the first of two story-swaps this year, Hannah takes us back to pasto-times Barcelona where an Epstein-esque vampiress stalks the city’s children, and Suruthi regales us with the blood-chilling mystery of the Dardeen family killings…
Follow us on social media:
Instagram
Twitter
Visit our website:
Website</description></item><item><title>Episode 319 - Lam Kor-wan: The Rainy Night Butcher | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400012/</guid><description>Podcast Description In August 1982, a Kodak technician was processing some photos when he saw the image of a naked young woman appear. He took a closer look, and any excitement he may have felt quickly disappeared when he realised she had been severely mutilated…
The ensuing investigation led to the conviction of Hong Kong’s first ever serial killer: Lam Kor-wan, known as the ‘Rainy Night Butcher’, or ‘Jars Killer’. Lam had been conducting sick dissections in a tiny bedroom he shared with his unwitting brother – and keeping specimens, suspended in rice wine, in a grim collection of Tupperware containers under his bed.</description></item><item><title>Episode 318 - The 67 Exorcisms of Anneliese Michel | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400013/</guid><description>Podcast Description With fractured knees and savage bruises – weighing just thirty kilos – 23-year-old Anneliese Michel died in 1976 under some of the strangest circumstances imaginable. But despite looking like she’d been held and tortured against her will, she consented to all sixty-seven of the exorcisms she was subjected to.
Why?
Because Anneliese, her parents, and two-priests all believed she’d been possessed by a demon, and had become the mouthpiece of Adolf Hitler, Judas Iscariot, and even Lucifer himself</description></item><item><title>Episode 317 - Reverend Willie Maxwell: Harper Lee &amp; The Killer Voodoo Preacher | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400014/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400014/</guid><description>Podcast Description In summer 1977, in Alexander City, Alabama, a man stood up in front of 300 mourners at the funeral of a 16-year-old girl – and shot a reverend three times in the head.
When the shooter’s murder trial began, it caught the attention of the renowned author, Harper Lee, who went on to spend years researching the story for her next book.
But it wasn’t the shooting that had piqued her interest.</description></item><item><title>Delphi Update: Odinism &amp; Accusations of Ritual Sacrifice | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400015/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400015/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Richard Allen’s defence team dropped a 136-page document challenging the warrant that police used to search his house.
But it’s not as boring as it sounds – because the bulk of this filing consists of claims that Abby and Libby were in fact killed by an Odinite, white-suprematist cult. And in doing so the defence team has revealed a lot of new information regarding the crime scene.</description></item><item><title>Episode 316 - Seth Rich: Murder in the Age of Conspiracy | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400016/</guid><description>Podcast Description If Seth Rich had had any other job – or if it had been any other year – his tragic death would likely have joined the 65 other unsolved murders in his part of Washington DC that year. But Seth worked for the Democratic Party – and this was the summer of 2016.
And while his family tried to grieve, Seth’s story was co-opted by every side. Through social media echo-chambering and shameless self-promotion, it grew to include accusations of bloodthirsty politicians; allegations of foreign powers destabilising US elections; and a secretive, high-powered paedophile ring that went all the way to the top.</description></item><item><title>Episode 315 - Christian Gerhartstreiter: The Talented Mr Mountbatten | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400017/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1994, in the back garden of a house on Lorain Road, San Marino, California – workers accidentally unearthed a shallow grave containing dismembered human remains.&amp;nbsp;
Investigators were convinced that the discovery had something to do with a charming British man who’d lived at the property a decade before. Not only had he been a member of the British royal family, a celebrated actor, a director, an art collector, a physicist and a naval captain… but he was also a member of the Rockefeller family – with the same social security number as serial killer David Berkowitz…</description></item><item><title>Episode 314 - The Gilgo Beach Killings - Part 2 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400018/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400018/</guid><description>Podcast Description On 13 July 2023 - after decades of corruption and inaction - police arrested 59-year-old New York architect Rex Heuermann, on suspicion of being the LISK.
In this episode, we’ll look at Heuermann’s family life, his background - and delve into the 33-page bail document&amp;nbsp;that offers us an in-depth look at how investigators finally caught this notorious, modern American serial killer.
To vote for us at the British Podcast Awards, click here: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Episode 313 - The Gilgo Beach Killings - Part 1 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400019/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2010, Shannan Gilbert made a series of frantic 911 calls as she ran through the streets of Oak Beach, Long Island, screaming: “They’re trying to kill me”.
Then she vanished.&amp;nbsp;
A few months later a body was found near where Shannan, vanished - but it wasn’t her.&amp;nbsp;
And neither were the next 9 sets of human remains they found along Ocean Parkway.&amp;nbsp;
Now, over a decade later, with the arrest of Rex Heuermann - the police believe they’ve found the elusive Long Island Serial Killer.</description></item><item><title>Episode 312 - Lucy Letby: “Trust me, I’m a nurse” | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400020/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 10:08:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400020/</guid><description>Podcast Description On 21 August 2023, 33-year-old nurse Lucy Letby was handed a whole-of-life order for the murder of seven babies, and the attempted murder of six more. She is only the fourth woman in British history to receive the sentence.&amp;nbsp;
And now this seemingly young, meek, slightly goofy, “vanilla” girl – whose bedroom was filled with stuffed animals – is now Britain’s most prolific child serial killer.&amp;nbsp;
So what really happened?</description></item><item><title>Episode 311 - Bhagwan Rajneesh: The Rolls-Royce Driving Sex Guru | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400021/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400021/</guid><description>Podcast Description In July 1981, the 40 residents of Antelope, Oregon watched on in bemusement as their rural village was descended upon by an Indian guru and thousands of his followers.&amp;nbsp;
Little did they know at the time, that these maroon-robed chanting hippies and their money-loving spiritual leader would go on to overthrow the local government, attempt wide-scale voter fraud, plot to fill a plane with explosives and eventually, carry out the most significant act of bioterrorism in US history.</description></item><item><title>Episode 310 - Brenda Spencer: ‘I Don’t Like Mondays’ | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400022/</guid><description>Podcast Description School shootings are now tragically commonplace in the US. But in 1979, when Brenda Spencer opened fire on Cleveland Elementary School, it took everyone by surprise.&amp;nbsp;
Killing two adults and injuring nine children – allegedly just because she didn’t like Mondays – Brenda has lived on in infamy as one of America’s first school shooters, immortalised by Bob Geldof and The Boomtown Rats.
Follow us on social media:</description></item><item><title>Episode 309 - Thabo Bester: Twisted Firestarter | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400023/</guid><description>Podcast Description At 2am, on the 3rd of May last year – inmates at Mangaung prison in Bloemfontein, South Africa, were woken up by an explosion. Word spread that Thabo Bester, the infamous “Facebook Rapist”, had set himself and his cell on fire. And all that remained after the dramatic blaze were a lighter, and a body, burnt beyond recognition. But that’s far from the end of the story.&amp;nbsp;
With daily revelations from the trial still hitting headlines, expect a farcical morgue-robbing scheme, a massive-scale web of fraud conducted from inside a prison cell, and a glamorous celebrity doctor who’s not quite what she seems.</description></item><item><title>Episode 308 - Christine 'Chris Chan' Chandler: Lifelong Lolcow | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400024/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Graphic Sonic fanfiction, a botched DIY sex change, incest and relentless psychosexual trolling are just some of the hallmarks of Christine Weston Chandler's story. As one of the most documented people in history – with 2,500 Wiki articles covering everything from school reports to her parents’ friends – her almost biblical tale leaves little to the imagination. Yet most people have never heard of her.&amp;nbsp;
Despite decades of online abuse, manipulation, and even extortion, the majority of those who do know about the infamous ‘Chis Chan’ see her as little more than an internet joke.</description></item><item><title>Episode 307 - Warren Jeffs: Bleeding the Beast - Part 2 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400025/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last week, we looked at the formation of the ultra-obedient, bigamist Mormon cult, the FLDS – in which plural marriage to pregnant preteen girls is just the tip of the fundamentalist iceberg. In this second part, we look at how its new prophet, Warren Jeffs, took his so-called religion to ever stricter and more terrifying depths.&amp;nbsp;
With followers so beaten down that they were banned from even laughing; the prophet on the lam, living it up at Disneyland; and a team of ex-faithfuls and dogged investigators closing in – something had to give.</description></item><item><title>Episode 306 - Warren Jeffs: God’s Chosen People - Part 1 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400026/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400026/</guid><description>Podcast Description According to Warren Jeffs’ thousands of followers, he was the leader of a secretive but devoted religion – their prophet, and the representative of God on Earth. But according to US law, he was a dangerous, totalitarian, child-molesting horror with over 80 wives – some married off as young as 12. Still, according to the church, Earthly laws are no match for the voice of God.
In this episode, we explore the story behind the Fundamentalist Church of Jesus Christ of Latter Day Saints: how the visions of a charismatic, seventeen-year-old farmhand grew to become a major world religion; how plural marriage caused a major rift in the church; and how its teachings were warped into a systematic cult of child abuse, underage sex, and absolute power.</description></item><item><title>Episode 305 - Natalia Grace: The Orphan | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400027/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400027/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2009, the horror film ‘Orphan’ told the tale of a couple who unwittingly adopted a 9-year-old girl, who (spoilers) turned out to be a murderous, adult woman.
Sometimes though, reality is stranger than fiction. A year after the film’s release, the Barnetts, a wealthy picture-perfect American family, adopted 6-year-old Natalia Grace from Ukraine. But within just 3 years, they’d abandoned her and fled to Canada.&amp;nbsp;
Why? According to the Barnetts, Natalia – who had a rare form of dwarfism – wasn’t a little girl at all.</description></item><item><title>Episode 304 - Jasmine Richardson &amp; Jeremy Steinke: Natural Born Killers | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400028/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Violently stabbed to death in their own home, the bodies of Debra and Marc Richardson showed the signs of an almighty struggle.
The body of their eight-year-old son Tyler Jacob was upstairs, and their twelve-year-old daughter Jasmine was missing. It all suggested a brutal home invasion, with Jasmine’s abduction as the motive. Yet the narrative the police unwound was more confusing, disturbing – and downright cringe-worthy – than anything they could have imagined.</description></item><item><title>Episode 303 - Anthony Gignac: Prince of Fraud | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400029/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400029/</guid><description>Podcast Description How did an orphan from Bogotá, Colombia, become one of the most audacious white-collar criminals in the US during early 2000s?&amp;nbsp;
Starting his con career in Michigan at the age of just 12, Anthony Gignac transformed himself into a Saudi prince and spent three decades conning society’s elite out of millions – until one day his royal façade cracked, when he ordered the wrong entrée at a restaurant…</description></item><item><title>Episode 302 - Grenfell Tower | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400030/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400030/</guid><description>Podcast Description On 14th June 2017, a fire engulfed Grenfell Tower, a high-rise residential building in West London.&amp;nbsp;
74 people died, and the tragedy became one of the darkest days in recent British history.
But worst of all, the incident was completely avoidable. This is the story of how decades of government corruption and unbelievable corporate greed killed so many innocent people.
As part of our coverage of the Grenfell case, and to support those still affected today - we’re going to be donating a portion of our ad revenue from this episode to the Grenfell Foundation.</description></item><item><title>Episode 301 - Tupac &amp; Biggie: 'Ready to Die' - Part 2 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400031/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400031/</guid><description>Podcast Description In our second instalment, Hannah &amp;amp; Suruthi turn to Christopher George Latore Wallace – better known as the Notorious B.I.G. – and his side of the Biggie/Tupac saga. Lyrically gifted, privately educated and no stranger to a little crack dealing, Biggie became the face the East Coast rap scene in one of the genre's most volatile and dangerous eras.&amp;nbsp;
So what happened to Tupac Shakur and Biggie Smalls? As H&amp;amp;S find out, sometimes the simplest explanation is the most likely.</description></item><item><title>REUPLOAD: Episode 257 - Genes &amp; Justice: Kathleen Folbigg &amp; Patricia Stallings | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400032/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 15:29:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400032/</guid><description>Podcast Description With the news that Kathleen Folbigg has finally been pardoned, we wanted to help you revisit this case, and Kathleen's incredibly tragic story by re-uploading our episode from August 2022.
“One sudden infant death is a tragedy, two is suspicious and three is murder”; this theory has pervaded criminal investigations for decades. So when Kathleen Folbigg’s daughter, Laura, became her fourth child to die mysteriously - Kathleen found herself labeled “Australia’s Worst Female Serial Killer”.</description></item><item><title>Episode 300 - Tupac &amp; Biggie: ‘2 Of Amerikaz Most Wanted’ - Part 1 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400033/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stories of death, drugs, and gang violence were inextricably linked, in the 90s media, to the nation’s biggest rap stars.&amp;nbsp;
Tupac Shakur was one of the decade’s biggest and most admired music icons – until his life was cut tragically short in 1996. By the time he died, he’d been involved in three high-profile shootings, done time for sexual assault, and been associated with serious career criminals. So what happened?</description></item><item><title>Episode 299 - La Maison de L'Horreur: The Dupont de Ligonnès Family Murder | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400034/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400034/</guid><description>Podcast Description When five members of the cheery, churchgoing Dupont de Ligonnès family were found dead at their home in Nantes – buried in the garden with small Catholic relics – a million questions erupted from neighbours, family and friends.
But for the police, only one question mattered: where was the sixth? Xavier Dupont de Ligonnès was nowhere to be found. And as they dug into his past, they uncovered a story that’s obsessed the nation of France for years: one of an ancient aristocratic dynasty, of international espionage, and a crime scene that, decades later, still refuses to add up…</description></item><item><title>TRIAL UPDATE &amp; REUPLOAD: Episode 180 - Lori Vallow: Doomsday | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400035/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400035/</guid><description>Podcast Description To make sure that none of you miss out we've updated our episode on Lori Vallow to include an update on her trial! Listen to this episode and this week's episode of ShortHand for the full scoop.
47-year-old mum of 3, Lori Vallow was convinced of two things; she was a god and the world was ending. Her job was to prepare her people for the second coming of Christ, in July 2020.</description></item><item><title>Episode 298 - Papa Doc: Haiti’s Vodou Dictator | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400036/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400036/</guid><description>Podcast Description What kind of leader would say of his own people that they are “meant to suffer”? Well, maybe a savage despot who claimed to be the master of the dead – a powerful sorcerer who could use vodou to raise murderous zombies at will, read minds, and even assassinate a US president…
Francois Duvalier, known as ‘Papa Doc’, is one of the most ruthless dictators of the 20th Century, responsible for the deaths of an estimated 60,000 people, and a reign of terror that tragically reverberates through Haiti to this day.</description></item><item><title>Episode 297 - Martha Moxley: Death &amp; Dynasty | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400037/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400037/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Halloween morning, 1975, in one of the most exclusive gated communities in the USA, the bludgeoned body of 15-year-old Martha Moxley was discovered on her own front lawn. The shattered pieces of the murder weapon, a six-iron golf club, were found nearby.
The police had the body, they had the weapon, and they had a strong indication of who took her life. But this was going to be anything but an open and shut-case.</description></item><item><title>Episode 296 - Evil Genius: The ‘Pizza Bomber’ | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400038/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400038/</guid><description>Podcast Description When delivery driver Brian Wells wound up with a bomb strapped to his neck after trying to fulfill a seemingly normal order of 2 pepperoni pizzas, local police thought their strange day had come to a dramatic end. In reality, it was the start…
By the end of their investigation they’d have to solve a scavenger hunt, track down a woman known as “crazy Marge”, and defrost the body of a mystery man tossed inside a freezer.</description></item><item><title>Episode 295 - The Christchurch Massacre | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400039/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400039/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the 15th of March, 2019, a 28-year-old man walked into a mosque in Christchurch, New Zealand, holding a shotgun and semi-automatic rifle – and opened fire.&amp;nbsp;
And what set this story apart was not just its brutality, but also the way it was staged – from the internet, for the internet. The gunman had strapped a GoPro to his helmet, and was streaming every second of the Christchurch shooting over Facebook Live.</description></item><item><title>Filthy Ritual: A Brand New Podcast by Suruthi &amp; Hannah | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400040/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 16:35:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to Filthy Ritual - our brand new 6-part series on the Hoax Healer of Hampstead 💸🐒
There's voodoo, shamanism, black magic, a tree of life in the Surinamese jungle, and so much more...
Episode 1 is out now wherever you get your podcasts, but if you can't wait all episodes are available for free on&amp;nbsp;Global Player&amp;nbsp;today!
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.</description></item><item><title>Episode 294 - Roderick Newall: Death in Paradise | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400041/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400041/</guid><description>Podcast Description The sleepy island of Jersey is a safe haven for wealthy Brits to live out their retirement with favourable weather, and an even more favourable tax rate. So when Nicholas and Elizabeth Newall were found bludgeoned to death in their home, the local police were a little out of their depth. What followed was a three-year investigation involving nunchucks, covert surveillance, and ending in a chase upon the high seas.</description></item><item><title>Morbid Caught RedHanded: The Witches of Long Compton | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400042/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400042/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s finally happening – the Morbid X RedHanded collab! And to get everyone’s witchy juices flowing, we took a trip to the sleepy Cotswold village of Long Compton.
Long Compton looks every bit the bucolic British fairytale. But for hundreds of years, stories of black magic, sorcery, necromancy and brutal murder have haunted its villagers. It’s said that in Long Compton, “The influence of witches goes and comes like the full moon.</description></item><item><title>Episode 293 - Gabby Petito: Isolated | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400043/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400043/</guid><description>Podcast Description In December 2020 Gabby Petito and her fiance Brian Laundrie set off on a once-in-a-lifetime journey across the USA in their tiny little van. The trip was set to be packed full of starry nights and stunning vistas for countless happy memories, and also all the beautiful views needed to kickstart Gabby’s dream career as a travel vlogger.
But when Brian returned to his family home in August 2021 without Gabby, things went from living daydream to living nightmare.</description></item><item><title>Episode 292 - Griekwastad: The Steenkamp Family Massacre | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400044/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400044/</guid><description>Podcast Description The sleepy town of Griekwastad South Africa woke up to absolute horror on Good Friday 2012. Three members of the local Steenkamp family had been brutally murdered, leaving their 17-year-old son Don as the only survivor. As the dust settled people blamed everything from a so-called ‘white genocide farm attack’ to a Satanic Cult. However, the reality and the family secrets that emerged were far darker than anything cooked up by the press.</description></item><item><title>Episode 291 - The Silk Road: Drugs, Data &amp; The Dread Pirate Roberts | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400045/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400045/</guid><description>Podcast Description For some, the end of the world&amp;rsquo;s most infamous online marketplace was a major victory in the never ending war on drugs. But for others, the global, multi-agency investigation into the Silk Road set a dangerous precedent for law enforcement – who rifled through the personal data of countless innocent users in their hunt for the elusive online drug-lord/revolutionary: Dread Pirate Roberts.
So prepare for a trip on the Silk Road, and find out how a tax inspector hanging out on a hallucinogenic mushroom forum caught one of the most slippery criminals we’ve ever covered.</description></item><item><title>Episode 290 - Jack Parsons: The Occultist Sex-Crazed Father of Modern Rocketry | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400046/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 23:10:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400046/</guid><description>Podcast Description From Copernicus to Newton, the greatest minds in history have had a crater named after them on the moon. But one name you may not know is Jack Parsons, a pioneer of rocket science whose contributions were so monumental that man wouldn’t have set foot on the moon without him.
However, his sex-crazed occultism and bromance with L. Ron Hubbard made it hard for the scientific community to embrace him, leading to his eponymous crater being placed on the dark side of the moon.</description></item><item><title>Episode 289 - David vs Robin: The Bain Family Killings - Part 2 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400047/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last week we left off with the absolutely batshit-craziness of Margaret’s “Bel”-filled diaries and the rumoured accusations of incest made by Laniet Bain against her father Robin.
And we’ll come back to all of that later in this episode, part 2 of our series on the Bain family murders, but not before we re-join David, as he’s being interviewed for the first time by the police, just hours after the killings…</description></item><item><title>Episode 288 - Black Magic, Incest &amp; Murder: The Bain Family Killings - Part 1 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400048/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400048/</guid><description>Podcast Description On 29 June 1994 the entire Bain family, except for eldest son David, were found murdered in their house in Dunedin.
The investigation that followed would go on to become New Zealand’s most controversial, as allegations of black magic, incest and police corruption exploded…
LAST CHANCE TO GET YOUR NORTH AMERICAN TOUR TICKETS: https://redhandedpodcast.com/
Become a patron:
Patreon
Order a copy of the book here (US &amp;amp; Canada):</description></item><item><title>Episode 287 – The Murdaugh Family Murders | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400049/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400049/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Murdaugh murders are not one story; they are a seemingly endless web of lies, entitlement, and confusion. At the centre of the web are the bodies of Paul and Maggie Murdaugh, found at their hunting lodge. But tangled in it are the tragic deaths of three other completely innocent people, dragged in by the most powerful family in South Carolina. This week Hannah and Suruthi make sense of one of the most sprawling true crime cases out there…</description></item><item><title>Episode 286 - Emanuela Orlandi: The Vatican’s Only Missing Citizen | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400050/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Organised crime, sex scandals, terror plots, hundreds of millions of missing dollars, a gangster known as ‘God’s Banker’ found hanging from a bridge in London, a 100-year-old apocalyptic prophecy, an anonymous tip-off that sounds like it comes from Dan Brown’s never-released Godfather sequel, and messages hidden in crypts…this is the story of Emanuela Orlandi, the only missing citizen of the smallest country in the world. And though she disappeared more than 40 years ago, Emanuela’s story remains, to this day, one of the biggest mysteries in Italian criminal history.</description></item><item><title>Episode 285 - The Murder of Rachel Nickell | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400051/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rachel Nickell’s brutalised body was found on Wimbledon Common with her two-year-old son Alex wiping her bloodied face and begging her to &amp;lsquo;wake up&amp;rsquo;. The nature of the broad daylight attack and the horrific injuries put enormous pressure on the Met to get the case solved and fast. However, none of that justifies the shoddy police work, cut corners, and tunnel vision that allowed a serial rapist to go unchecked for years.</description></item><item><title>Episode 284 - Dorothea Puente: The Boarding House of Death | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400052/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dorothea Puente may have looked every bit the placid old lady she played. In reality, she was in her early fifties, and was using her self-made status as a ‘pillar of the community’ to divert attention away from what was buried and rotting in her garden. Whether her victims had a few hundred thousand dollars, a nice pick-up truck, or even just a meagre social security cheque – they all risked the wrath of the ‘Death House Landlady’.</description></item><item><title>Episode 283 - Rasputin: Russia’s Greatest Love Machine | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400053/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400053/</guid><description>Podcast Description The much-told legend of Rasputin – the giant, wild-eyed, well-hung, wandering Siberian monk who seduced the Tsarina herself – is mostly a bunch of absolute borscht. But the real story is just as wild. H&amp;amp;S look at the life of a peasant who infiltrated Russian nobility, embodying the tensions of a nation – a charismatic zealot who mysteriously healed the Romanovs’ sickly heir. So join us to find out how Russia went from Romanovs to Revolution; the possible MI6 ties to Rasputin’s death; and a classic, quick-fire RedHanded rundown of…the entire First World War.</description></item><item><title>Episode 282 - Jeffrey Epstein: Foul Play - Part 2 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400054/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400054/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2009, having served just 13 months of the cushiest jail sentence this side of Scandinavia, Jeffrey Epstein was free – and legally protected from any future punishment. But there were hundreds of people that knew what he really was: a dangerous, influential and insatiable child rapist with a sophisticated network of fixers. They knew he had to be stopped.
In this second episode of our two-parter, H&amp;amp;S look at the tireless legal and journalistic efforts to bring him down; go deeper into the involvement of Ghislaine Maxwell and Prince Andrew; and find out what kind of justice – if any – was served.</description></item><item><title>Episode 281 - Jeffrey Epstein: Along Came a Spider - Part 1 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400055/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400055/</guid><description>Podcast Description The story of Jeffrey Epstein – the billionaire financier with an industrial-scale web of child abuse implicating some of the most powerful people in the world – sounds like some half-baked conspiracy theory. But it’s all true. And to answer the question of how he went from humble origins to sex-trafficking minors over to his private island, we have to start at the very beginning. So, who exactly was Jeffrey Epstein?</description></item><item><title>Episode 280 - The Idaho Student Murders | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400056/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400056/</guid><description>Podcast Description On 13 November 2022, four University of Idaho students were found stabbed to death in their beds. Six weeks later, the police (under the glare of immense public scrutiny) arrested a PhD student, Bryan Christopher Kohberger, 2,500 miles away in Pennsylvania.
Last week, the probable cause affidavit was released, revealing jaw-dropping evidence against the 28 year old.
In this episode Suruthi and Hannah work their way through the timeline of events, how the investigation unfolded and what we know so far about Kohberger…</description></item><item><title>Bonus Patreon Upcycle - Joe Metheny: Hate, Heroin &amp; Human Hog Roasts | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400057/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400057/</guid><description>Podcast Description There aren&amp;rsquo;t many true crime figures bigger than Joe Metheny. The 450-pound killer cook, who rampaged his way through south Baltimore&amp;rsquo;s homeless community in the early 90s, claimed to have taken the lives of at least 10 victims&amp;hellip; But how does someone go from a quiet, high-achieving young boy to a homeless crack addict with a taste for murder?
New merch at percivalclo.com!
Code: REDHANDED10 for 10% off</description></item><item><title>Bonus Patreon Upcycle - Lobotomies: Piece of Mind | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400058/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Modern medicine’s come a long way since the days of old where doctors would drill a hole in your head for a cold, prescribe you a tobacco-smoke enema, suggest you brush your teeth with urine, or give you heroin as cough medicine.
But things really did get a whole hell of a lot worse before they got better… Lobotomies were performed on tens of thousands of psychiatric patients, misbehaving children, “hysterical” women, JFK’s sister, and the former First Lady of Argentina – all just in the last 80 years.</description></item><item><title>Episode 279 - Scott Peterson: Trial by Media? - Part 2 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400059/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400059/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the concluding part of our deep dive into this murky case, Suruthi and Hannah explore the high drama of the trial that everyone was talking about.
And examine the evidence for and against Scott Peterson, including a dissection of those infamous tapes…
Tour Tickets: redhandedpodcast.com Merch: Percivalclo.com now for brand new, premium merch!
Code: REDHANDED10 for 10% off
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Delphi Update: Patreon Round-Up - December 2022 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400060/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400060/</guid><description>Podcast Description There have been some very interesting developments in the Delphi case (including the release of Richard Allen’s probable cause affidavit!)
And the girls did a deep dive into the ins and outs of the latest bombshell news on Under the Duvet this earlier month…
Here’s your chance to catch up! Press play now to hear the Delphi update from RedHanded’s weekly Patreon-exclusive show, Under the Duvet!
To find out more about Patreon and the hundreds of hours of bonus RedHanded content waiting for you, head over to Patreon.</description></item><item><title>Episode 278 - Scott Peterson: Sex, Lies &amp; Fishing Boats - Part 1 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400061/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400061/</guid><description>Podcast Description When beautiful, eight-and-a-half-month-pregnant Laci Peterson vanished without a trace on Christmas Eve 2002, headlines across the US exploded.
As much as the media and the public obsessed over the case, and the seemingly odd behaviour of her husband Scott, no one was prepared for the shocking revelations that were to come…
Leaving people asking: did Scott Peterson kill his wife, or is he just the unluckiest man alive?</description></item><item><title>Episode 277 - Joyce McKinney: Mormon Sex in Chains | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400062/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kirk Anderson was abducted from an LDS meeting house in Surrey by his ex-partner – and ex-beauty queen – Joyce McKinney. He said he was taken to a small rural cottage, tied to a bed, and sexually assaulted for three days. According to McKinney, everything was above board – Kirk just liked things kinky. But the British tabloids only cared about one thing: the wisecracking Southern belle Joyce McKinney made for great headlines.</description></item><item><title>Episode 276 - Alison Botha: Left for Dead | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400063/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kidnapped, attacked and left disembowelled in the desert by two men who claimed to have been possessed by demons, Alison Botha suffered one of the most torturous ordeals we’ve ever covered.
The men responsible met through a shared love of cheap drinks, sexual assault and the occult, but nothing can explain the brutality of their crimes. Welcome to a case we’ve been avoiding for years… and for good reason.</description></item><item><title>Episode 275 - The Assassination of Olof Palme | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400064/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400064/</guid><description>Podcast Description In February 1986, the prime minister of Sweden was walking home from the cinema, when a man stepped out of a shop doorway and shot him in the neck with a .357 Magnum. The killer ran down a side street – and disappeared without a trace.
The mystery surrounding Olof Palme’s death is a Swedish national obsession that&amp;rsquo;s barely left the headlines in the decades since. Hundreds of theories, from international hitmen to lone gunmen and police conspiracies, have swirled around one of the most extensive murder investigations in history.</description></item><item><title>Bonus - Patreon Round-Up: October 2022 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400065/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you the kind of financially savvy Spooky Bitch who wants to try before you buy? Then why don&amp;rsquo;t you have a listen to all of the very best BONUS CONTENT that we put out on Patreon last month?
This month we&amp;rsquo;ve got some great clips of our on tour shenanigans, plus us watching some of the goriest horror movie moments as voted by you!
If you like what you hear, head on over to Patreon.</description></item><item><title>Episode 274 - Larry Hillblom: Who’s Your Daddy? | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400066/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400066/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1995, the billionaire founder of DHL disappeared off of the face of the planet and left behind a closet full of skeletons. The aftermath stirred up one of the most colossal, convoluted shit storms you’ve never heard of. Two plane crashes, underage sex trafficking, missing DNA, cover-ups, private detectives, and a billion dollars of inheritance left in the air – this is the story of Larry Hillblom.</description></item><item><title>Episode 273 - The Delphi Murders: The Man in the Woods - Part 2 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400067/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400067/</guid><description>Podcast Description On 28 October 2022, in a move that shocked absolutely everyone, investigators in Indiana arrested 50 year old Richard Allen for the murders of Abby Williams and Libby German.
In this episode (that underwent a frantic rewrite in light of these recent developments), Suruthi and Hannah discuss the arrest of Allen, the personality profile of the Delphi killer and what we do know about the crime scene - plus the unbelievable catfishing twist that threw us all…</description></item><item><title>Episode 272 - The Delphi Murders: In Plain Sight - Part 1 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400068/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400068/</guid><description>Podcast Description On 14 February 2017, the bodies of 13-year-old Abby Williams and 14-year-old Libby German were found in the woods in Delphi, Indiana.
Libby’s phone was discovered not far from the crime scene, and the videos she had recorded on it quickly made this case one of the most infamous of recent decades…
Sources: redhandedpodcast.com See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 271 - LIVE: Halloween Special Part 2 – Stalin’s Cannibal Island &amp; Marcel Petiot | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400069/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Recorded live in Columbus, Ohio, at Obsessed Fest 2022, H&amp;amp;S bring you a historical Halloween special. The girls look back at the horrors of Stalin’s cannibal island, and at one of the world’s most prolific serial killers, who terrorised Nazi-occupied Paris.
Episode with slideshow: https://youtu.be/vDarJBeELEY
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 270 - Halloween Special Part 1: The Liske Family Murders &amp; Suzy Lamplugh | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400070/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lock your doors and shut your windows – it’s that time of year again! H&amp;amp;S are back with their annual Halloween story swap. In part one, the girls bring you the tragic case of the Liske family, followed by the chilling, unsolved disappearance of estate agent Suzy Lamplugh. 2022 LIVE SHOW TICKET LINKS:
https://redhandedpodcast.com
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 269 - Devil’s Dorp | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400071/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400071/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the story of a godly rivalry that spun out of control – taking in vampires, werewolves and the murders of eleven people. And behind it all, a 48th-generational satanic witch with 1,000 multiple personalities and a score to settle.
Krugersdorp, a town northwest of Johannesburg, has always had high levels of violent crime. But when South Africa’s own satanic panic kicked into full force in the early 90s, its citizens had an altogether more unholy threat on their hands&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Episode 268 - Blake Leibel: A Blueprint for Evil | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400072/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400072/</guid><description>Podcast Description This case takes the notion of life imitating art to a newly macabre extreme. In 2010, Blake Leibel released his graphic novel, Syndrome. Described as The Truman Show meets Se7en, the story follows a rogue neuropathologist as he attempts to find a cure for evil, using a condemned serial killer as his guinea pig.
Initially met with a lukewarm response, the novel garnered international attention in 2015 after Leibel seemed to use its most violent scenes to commit what&amp;rsquo;s been described as &amp;ldquo;the most brutal murder in LA&amp;rsquo;s history&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Episode 267 – The Unbelievable Saga of Thomas Quick | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400073/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400073/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the early 1990s, a patient at Säter mental institution was undergoing the facility’s revolutionary memory-recovery therapy, when he revealed a shocking incident from his past. Back in 1980, he had killed an 11-year-old boy.
As the therapy continued, more and more brutal confessions came, until he was linked to 39 of Sweden’s most infamous murders. He became known as the nation’s answer to Hannibal Lecter – a sadistic, cannibalistic serial-killer paedophile.</description></item><item><title>Episode 266 - The Burari Deaths: Ritual Slaughter | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400074/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400074/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the early morning of 1 July 2018, Gurcharan Singh went to check on his neighbours in the Burari district of Delhi. When he got there, he found a crime scene so chilling that the whole city was thrown into a frenzy. Ten members of the Chundawat family were hanging from the ceiling. Another, the 80-year-old grandmother, was found strangled in the next room. And the police, the public, and the national media were stumped – it seemed too complex for suicide; too organised for murder.</description></item><item><title>Episode 265 - Susan Cox Powell: Mormon Murder Mystery - Part 2 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400075/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400075/</guid><description>Podcast Description With a 28-year-old Mormon mum still missing – and her husband and father-in-law behaving increasingly erratically – police edged ever closer to finding their culprit.
And a string of shocking discoveries, including hard drives full of hentai, a collection of tampons and a suspicious car accident, only helped their case. What they didn’t know was that before it was all over, in a shocking final act, another four people would end up dead.</description></item><item><title>Killers, Cults and Queens - A Sneak Peek! | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400076/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 13:50:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400076/</guid><description>Podcast Description SURPRISE!!! We&amp;rsquo;ve got an exclusive sneak peek of a brand new show called Killers, Cults and Queens!
From Audioboom Studios, Cheryl Hole and Nikki Druce are on a whistle stop tour of the weirdest corners of the universe. They’ll be stopping to learn about the craziest true crime cases in history, spooky paranormal activities, truly bonkers internet mythology, very convincing cults and much much more. So buckle in… it’s going to be a wild ride!</description></item><item><title>Episode 264 - Susan Cox Powell: Mormon Murder Mystery - Part 1 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400077/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400077/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the 6th of December, 2009, when Susan Cox Powell disappeared while her husband Josh was away on a “spontaneous camping trip”, their community was sent reeling. This Mormon family had long had its issues, but with the revelation of major debts, rampant psychological abuse, and an obsessive and disturbing father-in-law who filmed Susan’s every move, everyone suspected the worst. Yet a decade later, nobody is behind bars…</description></item><item><title>Episode 263 - Larry Nassar: Mental Gymnastics | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400078/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400078/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the gruelling world of elite gymnastics, Larry Nassar was seen by a lot of young athletes as a friendly face in tough times. As the USA Gymnastics National Medical Coordinator, he performed treatments on children as young as ten, for almost 30 years. And under cover of those treatments, he was routinely molesting hundreds of young girls for decades – sometimes multiple times a day, often with their parents sitting just metres away.</description></item><item><title>Episode 262 - West Memphis 3 - Part 2 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400079/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 09:50:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400079/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the second and final installment of our two-part episode, we enter the courtroom to hear some flimsy evidence and absolutely bizarre testimony. Get ready for witchcraft, covens, and satanism that convicted three teenagers of triple child murder.
Damien, Jessie, and Jason would spend the next 18 years in prison. And as the rusty cogs of the US justice system slowly turned, a final bitter pill of injustice was forced upon the West Memphis 3.</description></item><item><title>Episode 261 - West Memphis 3 - Part 1 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400080/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400080/</guid><description>Podcast Description This infamous case is part Stranger Things, part courtroom drama. When the bodies of 3 young boys were found, battered, sexually mutilated and hogtied with their own shoelaces in a local creek, the finger was pointed in the most 80s direction of all… Satan. Or more specifically, at three teenagers accused of being in a witches’ coven, and in league with the devil himself&amp;hellip;
2022 LIVE SHOW TICKET LINKS:</description></item><item><title>Episode 260 - Hotel K &amp; The Bali 9 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400081/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400081/</guid><description>Podcast Description What do Gordon Ramsey’s brother, drug traffickers, rapists, gangsters, terrorists, thieves, and some of the unluckiest tourists in the world have in common?
They’ve all spent time in Bali’s infamous Kerobokan prison, otherwise known as Hotel K. Built around 40 years ago to house 300 inmates, Hotel K is now home to over 1400, over three-quarters of whom are in for drug charges, in a country with some of the most draconian drug laws on the planet.</description></item><item><title>Bonus - Patreon Round-Up: July 2022 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400082/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hello beautiful listeners! Have you been considering becoming an official Spooky Bitch and joining RedHanded&amp;rsquo;s Patreon? Well, here&amp;rsquo;s a tasty sample of just some of the content from the past month that your ear-holes have been missing out on. In this month&amp;rsquo;s Patreon Round-Up we bring you clips from two episodes of our weekly Patreon show, Under the Duvet, and a snippet from this month&amp;rsquo;s bonus episode: Lobotomies: Piece of Mind&amp;hellip; If you like what you hear, head on over to Patreon.</description></item><item><title>Episode 259 - Richard Huckle: Britain's Worst Paedophile | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400083/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400083/</guid><description>Podcast Description In October of 2019, prison officers at HMP Full Sutton in West Yorkshire discovered the body of a prisoner who&amp;rsquo;d been subjected to 89 minutes of torture before being strangled to death by another inmate. The victim was 33-year-old Richard Huckle. Dubbed by the media as &amp;ldquo;The Gap Year Paedophile&amp;rdquo;, Huckle was serving a life sentence for carrying out a 9-year-long, systematic campaign of abuse against some of the world&amp;rsquo;s poorest children.</description></item><item><title>Episode 258 - Alex Skeel: Two Years of Torture | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400084/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Described by the first officer to arrive as “the worst domestic scene” they’d ever witnessed, the brutality of what Alex Skeel endured was shocking. Alex had deep gashes on his arms, burns upon burns, and according to his family, he smelt like he was dead. But his years of isolation and abuse weren’t the work of a kidnapper – they came from the woman he loved.
Become a patron:</description></item><item><title>Episode 257 - Genes &amp; Justice: Kathleen Folbigg &amp; Patricia Stallings | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400085/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400085/</guid><description>Podcast Description “1 sudden infant death is a tragedy, 2 is suspicious and 3 is murder”; this theory has pervaded criminal investigations for decades. And so when Kathleen Folbigg’s daughter, Laura, became her fourth child to die mysteriously - Kathleen found herself labeled “Australia’s Worst Female Serial Killer”.
Today the girls delve into 2 unbelievable cases which highlight the immense challenges of the intersection between science and justice in the courtroom.</description></item><item><title>Episode 256 – Norwegian Black Metal: Pure F**king Armageddon | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400086/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400086/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Norwegian black metal scene of the early 90s started with pigs’ heads impaled on spikes, buried clothes wrapped around dead birds, and other notorious onstage antics. In three years, it spiralled into dozens of ancient churches going up in flames, violent bigotry – and the gruesome deaths of three people.
In this week’s episode, the girls chart the bloody origins of one band, Mayhem, and how they fostered the most feared music scene in history…</description></item><item><title>Episode 255 - Who Killed the Harrisons? | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400087/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400087/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2013, paramedics were called to a home in Mississauga, Ontario.
There they found the body of 40-year-old Caleb Harrison lying in bed, with red marks around his neck.
But this wasn’t the first time that the paramedics had found a dead body at the Harrison family home.
In fact, in the space of just five years, three members of the Harrison family had died in separate and bizarre incidents in the same house…</description></item><item><title>Episode 254 - Jennifer Pan: Tiger Blood | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400088/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400088/</guid><description>Podcast Description When three masked men entered the Pan family home, it seemed like an opportunistic home break-in. But on closer inspection, things just didn&amp;rsquo;t add up. Why would the would-be robbers shoot Hann and Bich Pan in cold blood, but leave their 24-year-old daughter Jennifer relatively unharmed? Why didn’t they drive off in the expensive Lexus that was parked in the drive? And why would Hann Pan run from the house, leaving his daughter tied to a bannister?</description></item><item><title>Episode 253 - Victoria Cilliers: Terminal Velocity | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400089/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Speeding towards the ground at over 60 miles per hour, former soldier and parachute instructor Victoria Cilliers was about to make history. She would be the first person in over a decade to experience a double parachute failure. Miraculously, she survived the impact. But when Victoria’s equipment was examined, it became clear there was more to this “freak accident” than met the eye. There were gas leaks, gaslights and grounds to divorce.</description></item><item><title>Bonus - Patreon Round-Up: June 2022 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400090/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hello beautiful listeners! Have you been considering becoming an official Spooky Bitch and joining RedHanded&amp;rsquo;s Patreon? Well, here&amp;rsquo;s a tasty sample of just some of the content from the past month that your ear-holes have been missing out on. In this month&amp;rsquo;s Patreon Round-Up we bring you clips from our weekly Patreon show, Under the Duvet, and a snippet from this month&amp;rsquo;s bonus episode: Martin MacNeill: Botox in the Bathtub&amp;hellip; If you like what you hear, head on over to Patreon.</description></item><item><title>Episode 252 - The Murder of Sophie Lionnet: Boyzone, Babies &amp; Broken Bones | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400091/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Boyzone obsessions and black magic paedophile rings consumed the mind of Sabrina Koudier. And her neighbours turned a blind eye to the strange woman&amp;rsquo;s violent outbursts and vile treatment of her au pair. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t their place to get involved.
But even the well-to-do residents of Southfields couldn&amp;rsquo;t ignore a billowing plume of black smoke and the unmistakable smell of burning hair and flesh.
Click here to vote for RedHanded in the British Podcast Awards Listeners&amp;rsquo; Choice Award!</description></item><item><title>Episode 251 - Andrei Chikatilo: Doomed from the Womb - Part 2 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400092/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400092/</guid><description>Podcast Description With nothing but a vague suspect profile to go on, and with mutilated bodies piling up around the USSR, Soviet police were battling to bring the Rostov Ripper&amp;rsquo;s reign of terror to an end. All the while Andre Chikatilo tore through his victims, constantly changing who he went after. The police were stumped. But with a dogged detective hot on his tail, Chikatilo made a costly mistake.
In this second and final instalment of the story of Andrei Chikatilo, we take you through the events that led to his downfall.</description></item><item><title>Episode 250 - Andrei Chikatilo: Impotent Rage - Part 1 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400093/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400093/</guid><description>Podcast Description For over thirty years, Andrei Romanovich Chikatilo eluded law enforcement as he slaughtered more than 50 women and children across the USSR. In the first of this two-part episode, we take you through Chikatilo’s early years, the horrors he lived through in Nazi-occupied Ukraine, and how the surrounding chaos turned him into one of the most prolific serial killers in history.
Classic merch is out now:
redhandedshop.com
Become a patron:</description></item><item><title>Episode 249 - RedHanded LIVE: The Amityville Horror | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400094/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400094/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join Hannah and Suruthi live on stage at a packed out Islington Assembly Hall as they describe the demonic possessions, bouncing beds, ghostly green goo and red-eyed pig-monsters linked to 112 Ocean Avenue in Amityville, New York. The six brutal murders and explosive demonic haunting depicted in ‘The Amityville Horror’ are now a part of horror folklore. But what really happened? Did something malignant take over in that three-storey Dutch-colonial house on the south shore of Long Island?</description></item><item><title>Bonus - Patreon Round-Up: May 2022 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400095/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 12:23:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400095/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s that time of year again! We&amp;rsquo;ve cranked the discount slider on Patreon as far as it will go!
For the next 7 days (until June 15th) you can get 12 months of amazing Patreon content for the price of 10!! That&amp;rsquo;s eight Under the Duvets, two episodes of In the News, and two full-length bonus episodes FOR FREE!!!
All you need to do is head on over to patreon.</description></item><item><title>Episode 248 - R Kelly: The Pied Piper of R&amp;B | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400096/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400096/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2021, a 51-year-old man referred to as “Daddy” by the followers of his alleged sex cult, was found guilty of 8 counts of sex trafficking. Breaking any of Daddy’s rules would result in brutal punishment; including beatings, solitary confinement, and starvation. “Daddy” kept his victims – most of them teenagers – locked up in his mansion. And all the while, he was topping music charts across the world with his era-defining R&amp;amp;B hits…</description></item><item><title>Episode 247 – The 2017 Manchester Bombing | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400097/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400097/</guid><description>Podcast Description On 22 May 2017, as Ariana Grande hit the high notes of her final song to a sold-out Manchester Arena, Salman Abedi hit the button on a homemade bomb. The resulting explosion killed Abedi and 22 other innocent people, and left over 1,000 more injured. The country mourned, millions of pounds were raised, and we all promised not to let hate win.
But as the dust settled, a worrying question started being asked: how did a known terrorist sympathiser who had fought alongside an ISIL militia slip through the UK’s counterterrorism net?</description></item><item><title>Episode 246 - The Osage Reign of Terror | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400098/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cowboys, private eyes, poisonings, bomb plots, shootings, and the birth of the FBI.
This is the story of how in the 1920s, one Native American tribe became the richest human beings per capita in the world and the diabolical conspiracy that led to hundreds of their people being murdered in cold blood.
Classic merch is out now:
redhandedshop.com Become a patron:
Patreon
Order a copy of the book here (US &amp;amp; Canada):</description></item><item><title>Episode 245 - ‘The Satanic Verses’: Fatwas &amp; Faux Pas | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400099/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400099/</guid><description>Podcast Description If the contents of a 546-page book can get one man murdered, two more seriously injured and its author forced into hiding for nine years, you can be confident of its subject: religion. But despite its reputation, ‘The Satanic Verses’ isn’t a page-by-page deconstruction of Islam. It’s a work of fiction; one that prompted the leader of Iran to call for a worldwide manhunt of anyone involved in its publication.</description></item><item><title>Episode 244 - The Van Breda Family Axe Murders | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400100/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400100/</guid><description>Podcast Description When police rushed to respond to a triple murder in one of South Africa’s most exclusive gated communities, it seemed as though Henri van Breda had had a lucky escape. They found him standing on his family lawn, dead-eyed and covered in blood and urine. According to the neighbours, he had been eerily waving to them while he waited for the police. All understandable, when three of your loved ones have been hacked to death by an axe-wielding maniac.</description></item><item><title>Episode 243 - The Sackler Family: An American Cartel | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400101/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400101/</guid><description>Podcast Description What if we told you that there was a family out there, who are still free to this day, whose actions are responsible for over half a million American deaths over the past 22 years?
We are, of course, talking about infamous scumbags the Sackler family, whose greed unleashed a plague on the people of North America.
Sources: redhandedpodcast.com See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Episode 242 - Tonya Harding: Cold as Ice | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400102/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400102/</guid><description>Podcast Description What would you do if you put in all the hard work, pushing yourself to the pinnacle of your sport, and you still didn’t get the recognition you deserved?
Would you give up? Would you take matters into your own hands and get a bitch kneecapped as she walked back to her changing room?
Or would your ex-husband do it and throw you under the bus?
Sources:
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uS7023l3QBw</description></item><item><title>Episode 241 - Mel Ignatow: Karma's Glass Table | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400103/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400103/</guid><description>Podcast Description When pulling up the carpets in your new dream home, you&amp;rsquo;ll probably be hoping to find beautiful shiny hardwood floors. What you won&amp;rsquo;t be hoping to find, however, is the former homeowner&amp;rsquo;s secret stash spot of camera rolls. Especially when the said former homeowner was a sexual sadist who'd just been acquitted of murdering his girlfriend. As for what was on those camera rolls&amp;hellip; well, you&amp;rsquo;ll just have to press play to find out&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Bonus - Patreon Round-Up: March 2022 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400104/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400104/</guid><description>Podcast Description What do Will Smith, Sherri Papini, and an antarctic research station have in common? They all featured in this month&amp;rsquo;s Patreon round-up, where we take some of the best bits from our month on Patreon and give you lot a cheeky taster!
Have a listen on the RedHanded feed anywhere you listen to podcasts, and if you like what you hear consider becoming a patron of RedHanded. If you do decide to take the plunge you&amp;rsquo;ll have access to a whole host of bonus content (depending on your tier) including Under the Duvet, In the News, and even a whole bonus episode!</description></item><item><title>Episode 240 - Kim Jong Nam: Prank Show Assassination | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400105/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400105/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the 13th of February 2017, two young women - believing that they were taking part in a bizarre Japanese game show - smeared baby oil across the face of a stranger at Kuala Lumpur Airport in Malaysia. The truth, however, was that there was no Japanese game show; the baby oil wasn&amp;rsquo;t baby oil; and these two women had just unknowingly assassinated the estranged half-brother of North Korea&amp;rsquo;s one and only, Supreme Leader, Kim Jong Un.</description></item><item><title>Episode 239 - The D.C. Snipers | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400106/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400106/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the space of 3 weeks in October 2002, Washington D.C was terrorised by a pair of spree killers carrying out a spate of deadly sniper-style attacks. They killed 10 people and injured 3 others.
Their choice of victims was shockingly random; they crossed racial, gender, age and socioeconomic lines - ensuring that everyone was absolutely terrified. And when the pair were finally apprehended, authorities realised that they had been wrong about almost everything from motive to profile…</description></item><item><title>Episode 238 - The Satanic Panic: QAnon and the Case of Matthew Taylor Coleman | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400107/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400107/</guid><description>Podcast Description What could drag a seemingly normal man, from being a fun-loving Christian surf instructor to killing his own children in fear of their &amp;ldquo;serpent DNA&amp;rdquo;? In part two of our deep-dive into the evolution of the Satanic Panic, we talk bout how anonymous messages left on 4chan became a global cult and started a chain of events that has led to real-world violence including the 2021 Capitol riots, and the deaths of two children.</description></item><item><title>Episode 237 - The Satanic Panic: The Murder of Betty Ann Sullivan - Part 1 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400108/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 09:46:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400108/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Betty Anne Sullivan’s body was found - with her face carved up and eyes missing, lying in a burning house filled with books on the occult - the police of Jefferson Township knew this would be a case that would change everything. And the unbelievably gruesome discovery made the next day, left the people of America shaken to their Christian cores…
Sources: redhandedpodcast.com See Privacy Policy at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Episode 236 - The Kerry Babies | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400109/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400109/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the 14th of April 1984, the body of a baby boy was found on Cahersiveen Beach, County Kerry in Ireland. The baby had been stabbed 28 times and its neck was broken. The Garda quickly found a suspect; Joanne Hayes. And soon, this police investigation became a medieval witch hunt and a dissection of motherhood itself. May 27th London Live Show Tickets: Tickets through DICE! Become a patron:</description></item><item><title>Bonus - Patreon Round-Up: February 2022 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400110/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 13:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you the try before you buy kind Spooky Bitch? Well great! Because here&amp;rsquo;s a big old taster of everything we did on Patreon last month!
We&amp;rsquo;ve got a clip from our casual catch up show Under the Duvet, a snippet from our topical crime news show In the News, and a tasty morsel of this month&amp;rsquo;s bonus episode of RedHanded all about hybristophilia.
If you like it (which you will&amp;hellip;) you can head on over to patreon.</description></item><item><title>Episode 235 - Breck Bednar: Playing Games | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400111/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Every parent's worst fear is that their child is taken away from them. Some imagine that if they relax for a second their child could be snatched from their grasp. But what if you did everything right? What if you identified the danger?
What if you told the police?
What if your child was tricked and manipulated right in front of your eyes?
That is the living hell experienced by Lorin LaFave and Barry Bednar, and that is the story of Breck Bednar and Lewis Daynes.</description></item><item><title>Bonus - Devils in The Dark: Ed Gein, The Butcher of Plainfield | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400112/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 12:14:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400112/</guid><description>Podcast Description From Audioboom Studios, it&amp;rsquo;s a brand new podcast from Helen Anderson. Alongside her hilarious best friend Danni Howard they&amp;rsquo;ll be exploring some of the wildest, most gruesome and totally shocking killers the world has ever seen. You&amp;rsquo;ll hear from psychologists and criminal experts whilst Helen and Danni tell you all the gory details&amp;hellip; but somewhere in the dark they&amp;rsquo;ll find the laughs and the light. Devils In The Dark is available from 28th February with new episodes out every Monday, so search Devils in The Dark and click follow so you never miss an episode.</description></item><item><title>Episode 234 - The Hillsborough Disaster | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400113/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400113/</guid><description>Podcast Description The deadliest event in UK sporting history took place on the 15th of April, 1989. In the starting minutes of the F.A. Cup semi-finals between Liverpool F.C. and Nottingham Forest, a disaster unfolded which to date has claimed the lives of 97 people. and left 766 others injured on the day. These innocent people were the victims of the complacency, ineptitude, and sheer incompetence of those whose very jobs were to ensure their safety.</description></item><item><title>Episode 233 - Peter Kürten: The Vampire of Düsseldorf | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400114/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400114/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the world of true crime, the media is often accused of inaccuracy, dramatisation, and sensational headline writing, but there&amp;rsquo;s an exception to every rule. Never has a killer fitted their moniker more than Peter Kürten, &amp;lsquo;The Vampire of Düsseldorf&amp;rsquo;&amp;hellip;
Kürten may well have had a reflection and he may not have hung from the ceiling like a bat, but in one very key aspect, he was every bit Deutschland's Dracula.</description></item><item><title>Episode 232 - Novichok Eau de Toilette: Sergei &amp; Yulia | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400115/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400115/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the 4th of March, 2018, the residents of Salisbury, England, watched on in horror as British soldiers flooded their streets, and people in hazmat suits cordoned off their roads.
Earlier that day, a man and a woman had collapsed on the high street; both were convulsing and foaming from the mouth.
The people of Salisbury had no idea that their sleepy little town was ground zero for the first chemical weapon attack, using a deadly nerve agent, in Western Europe since WW2.</description></item><item><title>Bonus - Patreon Round-Up: January 2022 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400116/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you been on the fence about becoming a patron of RedHanded for a while? Hopefully, this round-up of some of our best exclusive patron-only content from January will help you make up your mind.
We&amp;rsquo;ve got a snippet from our bonus episode on &amp;ldquo;The Doodler&amp;rdquo; an artistic pick-up specialist turned murderer in 70&amp;rsquo;s San Fransisco, a case of modern slavery from this month&amp;rsquo;s In the News, and some creepy scam stories from Under the Duvet.</description></item><item><title>Episode 231 - A Storm in a Teacup: The Murder of Alexander Litvinenko | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400117/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400117/</guid><description>Podcast Description If a man in his mid-forties crashed into your local hospital being violently sick and claiming to have been poisoned by the Russian State, you&amp;rsquo;d be forgiven for thinking he was just another drunk member of the public. However, what Alexander Litvinenko had ingested was a little bit stronger than anything available at your local pub.
Pop on your ushankas and buy a first-class ticket to Moscow, it&amp;rsquo;s time for round one of RedHanded vs The Kremlin.</description></item><item><title>Episode 230 - Peter Manuel: The Beast of Birkenshaw | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400118/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400118/</guid><description>Podcast Description In early January of 1956, Glasgow police received a phone call about a break-in at the home of the Smart family. The scene they walked in on however was something far more sinister. Peter Smart, his wife, Doris, and their 10-year-old son Michael had all been shot dead at point-blank range in their beds. It was clear to detectives that the Smarts had been dead for almost a week, but if that was true, it didn’t explain who’d been feeding their cat…</description></item><item><title>Episode 229 - Scientology - Part 2: How to Make Celebrity Friends and Influence People | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400119/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400119/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Hannah and Suruthi finish their two-part attempt to unravel the mysteries of Scientology (and get themselves fair-gamed) by discussing Scientology&amp;rsquo;s most important questions like: &amp;ldquo;what is the current structure of The Church of Scientology?&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;where does Tom Cruise fit in?&amp;rdquo; and most importantly &amp;ldquo;where on Xenu&amp;rsquo;s green earth is dead-eyed Dave&amp;rsquo;s wife Shelly Miscavige?&amp;quot;
Become a patron:
Patreon
Order a copy of the book here (US &amp;amp; Canada):</description></item><item><title>Episode 228 - Scientology - Part 1: The Maternity Ward of Questionable Religious Sects | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400120/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400120/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part 1 of this 2 part series, Hannah and Suruthi peer under the slippery stone of Scientology’s sinister origins. They track the life of founder L. Ron Hubbard, from the birth of Dianetics, to the constantly shifting goalposts of engrams, and of course the conception of the Sea Org.
Sources: redhandedpodcast.com See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 227 - The Slenderman Stabbing | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400121/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400121/</guid><description>Podcast Description On May 31, 2014, in Waukesha, Wisconsin, two 12-year-old girls, Anissa Weier and Morgan Geyser, lured their best friend Payton Leutner into the woods and stabbed her 19 times.
They claimed it was in an attempt to become proxies of the fictional character Slender Man.
It was a case that gained the attention of the press internationally, bringing children's internet usage and "creepypastas" to the forefront of public attention.</description></item><item><title>Episode 226 - Casey Anthony: Web of Lies - Part 2 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400122/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400122/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, in the concluding part of our Casey Anthony series - Hannah and Suruthi head into a courtroom full to the brim with bulldog lawyers, yet more lies, accusations of incest and forensic fuck-ups.
In a case that just gets stranger and stranger, the shocks really do come right at the end...
Sources: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vNh3RbxU8v
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ePs5TjFmk4c
https://eu.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2012/11/25/casey-anthony-suffocation-google/1725253/
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.</description></item><item><title>Bonus - December Patreon Round-Up: Best of 2021 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400123/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400123/</guid><description>Podcast Description To celebrate the end of another amazing year on Patreon and our whopping 16% off Patreon annual membership FLASH SALE (details below), we&amp;rsquo;re bringing you some of our highlights from this years Patreon bonus content! We have clips from our bonus episode on Flat Earth &amp;ldquo;Theory&amp;rdquo;, an In the News segment about a very lifelike manikin, and of course some EmyptyHanded caller woes from Under the Duvet. So tuck in, and think about becoming a Patron of the show at patreon.</description></item><item><title>Episode 225 - Casey Anthony: Web of Lies - Part 1 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400124/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400124/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 22-year-old Casey Anthony was arrested on 16 July 2008, her two-year-old daughter Caylee hadn&amp;rsquo;t been seen for over a month. Casey&amp;rsquo;s history of lying and manipulation, as well as her strangely distant attitude towards her missing child, was setting off all kinds of alarm bells&amp;hellip; and the smell of death coming from the boot of her car didn&amp;rsquo;t help either.
Prepare for bizarre phone calls, fascinating police interviews, and generally some of the strangest behaviour we&amp;rsquo;ve ever witnessed, as we cover one of the most infamous true-crime cases of all time.</description></item><item><title>Episode 224 - The Guildford Four &amp; The Maguire Seven | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400125/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400125/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the 5th of October 1974, the Provisional Irish Republican Army blew up a military pub in Guildford, killing four soldiers, one civilian and injuring sixty-five others.
The responsibility for the heinous act of terror was quickly thrown at three young Irish men and a seventeen-year-old English girl. On top of this, accusations of running a &amp;ldquo;bomb factory&amp;rdquo; was soon being shouldered by a middle-aged Irish woman who&amp;rsquo;d lived in England for twenty years.</description></item><item><title>Episode 223 - Village of the Damned: The Nithari Child Murders | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400126/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Every couple of weeks like clockwork, another child would vanish from Nithari, Delhi. The police didn&amp;rsquo;t seem concerned, and no one wanted to take a closer look at the &amp;ldquo;black hole&amp;rdquo; – the alleyway from where all the kids had disappeared.
What the locals would eventually find in the sewers surrounding bungalow D5 would expose a terrifying paedophile, necrophile and cannibal – in a case that would change India forever.</description></item><item><title>Episode 222 - Natalee Holloway | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400127/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400127/</guid><description>Podcast Description In May 2005, 18-year-old Natalee Holloway and her friends flew from Alabama to Aruba to celebrate their graduation.
Just five days later, when the group were set to fly back to the States, Natalee was nowhere to be found. The investigation that followed uncovered sex-trafficking gangs, potential police cover-ups and a terrifying teenage psychopath, all turning this case into America’s favourite reality show…
Become a patron:
Patreon
Order a copy of the book here (US &amp;amp; Canada):</description></item><item><title>Episode 221 - Koh Tao: Murder Island | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400128/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400128/</guid><description>Podcast Description In September 2015 the brutalised bodies of British backpackers Hannah Witheridge and David Miller were found on the tropical island paradise of Koh Tao. The island off the coast of mainland Thailand, has long been a hotspot for partygoers lured in by the cheap alcohol, stunning beaches, and of course its infamous full moon parties.
With the whole world watching, two suspects for the brutal murders were quickly found, but with 20% of the country&amp;rsquo;s income at stake and a background of political unrest, the investigation was far from faultless.</description></item><item><title>Episode 220 - The Murder of Dylan Redwine | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400129/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400129/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the 18th of November, 13 year old Dylan Redwine boarded a plane to visit his dad, Mark. Dylan really didn’t want to go - Mark lived in the middle of nowhere and the relationship between the 2 had been strained since the Redwine’s divorce. But no one could have expected the nightmare that was about to unfold, and the unbelievably shocking family secrets that would be spilled…</description></item><item><title>Episode 219 - Halloween Special Part 2 - The Boogyman and the Boy in the Attic | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400130/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400130/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week we're bringing you part two of our annual Halloween story-swap. We've got two terrifying tales of true crime Halloween-horror including Thailand's real-life answer to The Boogyman, and the infamous case of Ireland's "Boy in the Attic". Become a patron:
Patreon
Order a copy of the book here (US &amp;amp; Canada):
Order on Wellesley Books
Order on Amazon.com
Order a copy of the book here (UK, Ireland, Europe, NZ, Aus):</description></item><item><title>Bonus - Sinister Societies: A Sneak Peek | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400131/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400131/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a bit of a treat for you, our dedicated Spooky Bitches, we&amp;rsquo;ve decided to give you a little sneak peek of our new show Sinister Societies, which debuted last week exclusively on Spotify.
The show comes out every Tuesday and features the same RedHanded flavour you love but covers the world of faith followings, dodgy clandestine organisations, and of course, sinister societies (basically cults).
So have a listen to this sneak peek, and then follow the link below for new episodes every Tuesday exclusively on Spotify.</description></item><item><title>Episode 218 - Halloween Special Part 1: How Would You Make a Human Vagina? | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400132/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400132/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s Halloween time, that means at RedHanded - it&amp;rsquo;s story swap time!
This week Suruthi takes us to a TB ward in the 1930s for some &amp;ldquo;sexy&amp;rdquo; body-stealing, while Hannah shares the tale of the Kurim cult that was cracked thanks to a terrifying baby monitor&amp;hellip;
UK TOUR 2021 - new dates added! Get your tickets here: https://linktr.ee/RedHandedthepod
Become a patron:
Patreon
UK TOUR 2021 - new dates added!</description></item><item><title>Bonus - October Patreon Round-Up | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400133/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400133/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s that time again, where we give you a sneak peek of what goes on over at the glorious RedHanded Patreon page, so we&amp;rsquo;re giving you some of the juiciest highlights from the previous month of bonus content. This time you get to hear all about Raoul Moat from our Patreon exclusive episode Raoul Moat: Terror of Tyneside. On top of that, there&amp;rsquo;s our latest segment on Under the Duvet called &amp;ldquo;EmptyHanded&amp;rdquo; where we listen to the relationship woes of our wonderful patrons, and then try our best to offer some advice.</description></item><item><title>Episode 217 - Stephen McDaniel: The Killer with the Key | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400134/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lauren Giddings had a strange feeling; she couldn’t shake the sense that someone had been coming into her apartment. But nothing was ever out of place and nothing was ever missing, so she tried to put the scary thought out of her head.
Less than a month later Lauren’s torso was found wrapped in a plastic sheet in the bins behind her building.
UK TOUR 2021 - new dates added!</description></item><item><title>Episode 216 - Issei Segawa: The Kobe Cannibal | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400135/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 06:47:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over 30 years ago, Issei Sagawa murdered, raped and ate a young woman named Renée Hartevelt. Despite his guilt never having been in question, Sagawa would not stand trial or spend any significant amount of time behind bars.
And today, in the sleepy Tokyo district of Yurioka, this known murderer, necrophile and cannibal walks the streets not only as a free man - but as a twisted celebrity…</description></item><item><title>Episode 215 - Robert Bales: The Kandahar Massacre | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400136/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400136/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Panjwai, a district in the Kandahar Province of Afghanistan, on the 11th of March 2012, U.S Army Staff Sergeant Robert Bales committed what is considered to be the deadliest war crime blamed on a single member of the U.S Armed Forces since the Vietnam War.
During this brutal massacre, Robert Bales took the lives of 16 innocent Afghan civilians – 9 of them were children. In this week's episode, Hannah and Suruthi explore the various and disturbing factors that led to this unbelievable atrocity.</description></item><item><title>American Vigilante: Interview with Sam Walker | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400137/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 10:01:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400137/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this very special bonus episode of RedHanded, we sit down with former BBC journalist Sam Walker to discuss her latest investigation into the terrifying world of real-life violent vigilantes. Over the course of months, Sam interviewed a mysterious man known only as “KC”. He told her all about his brutal exploits as he and his gang roam the country dishing out their own brand of savage justice. The brand new podcast series - American Vigilante - is out now wherever you listen to your podcasts, with new episodes dropping every Monday.</description></item><item><title>Episode 214: Jodi Jones: Murder in Midlothian | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400138/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400138/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the 3rd of June 2003, 14-year-old Jodi Jones ran home from school and begged her mum Judith to let her go out. Eventually, mum relented and Jodi rushed out saying she was off to meet her boyfriend, a local 14-year-old boy Luke Mitchell.
6 hours later Jodi&amp;rsquo;s naked, mutilated body was found in the woods just a mile from her house, by the very same boy. UK TOUR 2021 - new dates added!</description></item><item><title>Episode 213: We Need to Talk About Paris Bennett | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400139/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400139/</guid><description>Podcast Description As she sat with her two children in Abilene Texas one January morning in 2007, Charity Lee pondered, that she may not be a perfect mother, but she did live in a safe neighbourhood, so her children wouldn't be killed in their beds.
She was wrong. Join the girls for an in-depth exploration of inter-sibling homicide, a crash course in psychopathy, and a cameo from Piers Morgan.
Follow us on social media:</description></item><item><title>Bonus - August Patreon Round-Up | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400140/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400140/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this month&amp;rsquo;s juicy sneak-peek behind the Patreon curtain, we have our In the News coverage of a Doctor tuned Exorcist, our Under the Duvet coverage of the tragedy in Plymouth, and a snippet from our full-length Patreon bonus episode of Georgia Williams and her snuff film-loving murderer. If you want to listen to any of these episodes in full or listen to our entire Patreon back catalogue, head over to: patreon.</description></item><item><title>Episode 212 – 3 Guys, 1 Hammer: The Dnepropetrovsk Maniacs | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400141/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400141/</guid><description>Podcast Description In July 2007, a blurry 8-minute long video shot on a mobile phone, titled “3 guys, 1 Hammer”, was uploaded to a shock video website. The video showed two men using a hammer and a screwdriver to brutally murder a terrified man.
Once they finished, the two killers even posed next to the man&amp;rsquo;s body doing a sieg heil; just another shot to add to their growing photo album of murder…See Privacy Policy at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Episode 211 - Lorena Bobbitt &amp; The 8-Inch Carving Knife | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400142/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400142/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lorena Bobbitt, the penis severing incident and the resulting Frankenpenis porn star hit the front pages almost 30 years ago. And since then, this is a case that has never left the public consciousness.
&amp;nbsp;However, there is a lot more to Lorena Bobbitt's story than a man's member and a hotdog box. There's a story with two sides and a perfect case study on how society treats survivors.</description></item><item><title>Bonus - Georgia Williams: The Snuff Film Maker Down the Street | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400143/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400143/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this second instalment of our promise to deliver two bonus episodes after we won GOLD at the British Podcast Awards, we cover the heartbreaking case of Georgia Williams. Georgia was a high-achieving and kind teenager who was always willing to help those who asked, and her killer knew this. 23-year-old Jamie Reynolds had an obsession with violent pornography and snuff movies. In May 2013 he used Georgia&amp;rsquo;s good nature against her and eventually guilted the 16-year-old into coming over to his parents&amp;rsquo; house to take part in a &amp;ldquo;fake murder&amp;rdquo; photoshoot, that soon turned out to be all too real.</description></item><item><title>Episode 210 - Shamima Begum: ISIS &amp; The Bethnal Green 3 - Part 2 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400144/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400144/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Suruthi and Hannah head into a place widely regarded as one of the most dangerous places in the Middle East right now - the notorious al-Hawl camp. It's where, in 2019, a British journalist found an 18-year-old, 9-month pregnant Shamima Begum. Soon after this discovery, Shamima Begum would have her British citizenship revoked, leaving her stateless in the desert hell-hole.
In the concluding episode of this series, the girls discuss how ISIS used religion to justify sex slavery, the fall of the so-called caliphate and what should be done with individuals like Shamima Begum.</description></item><item><title>Episode 209 - Shamima Begum: ISIS &amp; The Bethnal Green 3 - Part 1 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400145/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400145/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Sunday the 22nd of February 2015, three London schoolgirls aged between 15 and 16 boarded a Turkish Airlines plane from Gatwick – they were headed to Syria, to join ISIS.
In part one of this two-part series, Suruthi and Hannah explore the rise of ISIS, their recruitment tactics, and the motivations of those who willingly enter a warzone to join a death cult.
Sources: redhandedpodcast.com See Privacy Policy at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Episode 208 - Pedro Rodrigues Filho: Serial Killer Superstar | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400146/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400146/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pedro Rodrigues Filho, aka Pedhrino Matador, Killer Petey or The Brazilian Dexter, is a bit of an anomaly as far as serial killers go. He brutally killed at least 71 people, including his own father, but still many people in Brazil revere and applaud him for his "work"...
So much so in fact that today, unbelievably, Filho is free and living his best life as a YouTube sensation with hundreds of thousands of followers, and millions of views.</description></item><item><title>Bonus: The Columbine High School Massacre | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400147/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 17:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400147/</guid><description>Podcast Description Earlier this year we promised that if we won gold in the BPA Listeners&amp;rsquo; Choice category, we would deliver two bonus episodes chosen by the Spooky Bitches. This is the first of those episodes - The Columbine High School Massacre.
The months leading up to the 20th of April 1999 - and the mindsets of both Eric Harris and Dylan Klebold - have been very well documented. And yet the story of The Columbine High School Massacre is still full of misreporting, misunderstanding, and miscommunication.</description></item><item><title>Bonus - June Patreon Round-Up | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400148/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 17:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400148/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hello you lovely listeners! We’ve cut together some snippets of what we’ve been up to on Patreon this month… With highlights from In the News, our monthly true crime news round-up, Under the Duvet our post-show after-party where we discuss everything from current affairs to our latest empty-handed news, and our monthly exclusive bonus episode which, this month, was on the utterly terrifying ’Slenderman Stabbings’. If you like what you hear then head on over to patreon.</description></item><item><title>Episode 207 - Searching the Sounds: The Disappearance of Ben Smart &amp; Olivia Hope | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400149/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400149/</guid><description>Podcast Description Award winning champions of the people RedHanded bring you a boat themed mystery for the ages. In the early hours of New Years Day 1998 Ben Smart and Olivia Hope boarded a mystery yacht and vanished without a trace. Their bodies have never been found, yet one man has been imprisoned for the double murder. He has always maintained his innocence, but the question is can we believe Scott Watson?</description></item><item><title>Episode 206 - Fritz Haarmann: The Butcher of Hannover | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400150/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400150/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the early 1900s Germany was a nation ravaged by the horrors of war, debt and death. For years, as they struggled with stagflation and starvation, all manner of depravity began to emerge; there had even been rumours of human meat being sold on Germany’s black markets.
And it was during this time, that a dangerous man roamed the streets committing a series of gruesome murders so diabolical that he terrified people who had survived the nightmares of WW1.</description></item><item><title>Episode 205 - Anton LaVey &amp; The Church of Satan | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400151/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400151/</guid><description>Podcast Description Anton LaVey, founder and head priest of the Church of Satan, led a controversial life; he was linked to the deaths of a famous Hollywood starlet and a Kennedy brother. Join Hannah and Suruthi for a deep dive into America&amp;rsquo;s satanic panic, the origins of Satanism and how it has evolved over the decades. They explore LaVey&amp;rsquo;s early life, from burlesque organ player, to occultist, to becoming considered by some to be &amp;ldquo;the most evil man in the world&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>RedHaunted: Some Say This Baby Video Is Haunted, Do You Hear It? | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400152/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400152/</guid><description>Podcast Description Watch the full episode here: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b5EQGk3H77w&amp;amp;t=49s&amp;amp;ab_channel=RedHanded
Calling all Spooky Bitches!
Did you know that RedHaunted is back and better than ever on the RedHanded YouTube channel?! 👻
In case you missed it, we’ve decided to upload this little audio highlight for you to feast your ears on…
If you like what you hear then be sure to head on over to the RedHanded YouTube channel for the full, hour-long, extra-special, video extravaganza of spookiness!</description></item><item><title>Episode 204 - Dennis Nilsen: The North London Necrophile | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400153/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400153/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1983, in an unassuming suburb of North London, some plumbers were called out to fix an un-flushable toilet. This already unpleasant job was made much worse by the distinctly hand-shaped bones mixed in with lumps of human flesh blocking the drains. This discovery would lead to the arrest of Britain's most notorious necrophile, Dennis Nilsen. The body Nilsen had chopped up, diligently flushed down the toilet and blocked with was his last victim, but it was nowhere near his first.</description></item><item><title>Bonus - July Patreon Round-Up | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400154/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400154/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s July, we’re RedHanded and football is (maybe) coming home! So, to celebrate, we’re delivering some of our Patreon exclusive best bits straight to your ear holes.
With highlights from In the News, our monthly true crime news round-up, Under the Duvet our post-show after-party where we discuss everything from current affairs to our latest empty-handed news, and our monthly exclusive bonus episode which, this month, was on the utterly horrific ‘Dunblane Massacre’.</description></item><item><title>Episode 203 - The Miyazawa Family Massacre | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400155/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400155/</guid><description>Podcast Description 30th December 2000, in Setagaya&amp;nbsp;Japan, the Miyazawa family were preparing for the upcoming festivities. Tragically, however, the family wouldn't live to see the new year because that night they were all brutally murdered in their own home. A plethora of evidence was left behind at the scene, including DNA, fingerprints, half-eaten food and even an entire outfit, but still to this day this case remains one of Japan's most notorious unsolved murders.</description></item><item><title>Episode 202 - The Haunting Murder of Matthew Shepard | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400156/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400156/</guid><description>Podcast Description Content Warning - this episode contains quotes pertaining to homophobic and discriminatory language which some listeners may find upsetting.
Listener discretion is advised.
On the 7th of October 1998, 21-year old Matthew Shepard was found tied to a prairie fence at the end of a remote dirt track in Laramie, Wyoming. The young gay man had been pistol-whipped in the head over 20 times, and his brain stem had been crushed.</description></item><item><title>Episode 201 - Jimmy Savile: Predator in Plain Sight - Part 2 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400157/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400157/</guid><description>Podcast Description The concluding part of this series explores Savile’s strange relationship with his mother, God and the BBC. The girls examine the mountains of evidence that piled up long before Savile’s death and ask how everyone turned a blind eye to child abuse, rape and necrophilia…&amp;nbsp;
Follow us on social media:
Instagram
Twitter
Facebook
&amp;nbsp;
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 200 - Jimmy Savile: Predator in Plain Sight - Part 1 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400158/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400158/</guid><description>Podcast Description For decades, TV presenter Jimmy Savile was idolised as a national treasure in Britain. But the power and adoration Savile enjoyed was matched only by his perversions and depravity&amp;hellip;
He was knighted, awarded an OBE, he rubbed shoulders with royalty, prime ministers and he ruled the roost at the BBC. Savile also raised millions for charity, for which he was rewarded with the literal keys to hospitals and children&amp;rsquo;s homes across the country.</description></item><item><title>Bonus - Kate Webster: The Real Life Sweeney Todd | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400159/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 11:51:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400159/</guid><description>Podcast Description Thanks to ‘NOW’, and the new show ‘The Nevers’, we’re taking all you spooky bitches on a trip to Victorian London for an extra special bonus episode. And it’s a wild one...in fact, today’s episode resulted in one of the most sensational trials of the time - so big, that the future King of Sweden made the trip all the way to The Old Bailey just to watch!</description></item><item><title>Bonus - June Patreon Round-Up | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400160/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 07:00:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400160/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hello, all you non-Patron pals! Boy, do we have a treat for you... We've cut together some of our Patreon exclusive best bits from the month of May - you know, to give you a taste of what we get up to over here. This round-up includes highlights from 'In The News' our monthly show that gets stuck into the headlines of all things true crime, 'Under The Duvet' our aftershow discussion in which we catch up with one another about our lives and interesting things we've seen, and finally a segment from our latest Bonus Episode which this time involves a Nazi Cult based in Chile.</description></item><item><title>Episode 199 - Cindy James: Invisible Torment | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400161/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400161/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Cindy James' decomposing body was found bound and dumped outside an abandoned house, those who knew her best were horrified - but not entirely shocked.
Cindy had been harassed and attacked by a seemingly all-knowing and malevolent stalker for almost a decade. But, in all those years, despite the thousands of hours of police work spent trying to find Cindy's tormentor, detectives had nothing more than a bizarre phone message to show for it.</description></item><item><title>Episode 198 - The Death of Max Spiers | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400162/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 May 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400162/</guid><description>Podcast Description In July 2016 Max Spiers, a British conspiracy theorist, sent his mother a series of bizarre texts about how he was terrified for his life. Days later Max was found dead, after having vomited up 2 litres of black liquid. Things only became stranger when people realised that Max was meant to speak at a conference the following day about a high power paedophile ring he’d been investigating...</description></item><item><title>Bonus - May Patreon Round-Up | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400163/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400163/</guid><description>Podcast Description The pubs are re-opening indoors! And to celebrate, this week we have a gift for all of you soon-to-be spooky bitch patrons. We’ve cut together a handful of the absolute best bits from this month's exclusive RedHanded Patreon content.
With highlights from In the News, our monthly true crime news round-up, Under the Duvet our post-show after-party where we discuss everything from current affairs to our latest empty-handed news, and our monthly exclusive bonus episode which, this month, was on the utterly horrific ‘Broken Arrow Massacre’.</description></item><item><title>Episode 197 - Ezra McCandless: Killer Girlfriend | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400164/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400164/</guid><description>Podcast Description On 22 March 2018, 19 year old Ezra McCandless stood barefoot, covered in blood banging on the door of a remote Wisconsin farmhouse. She was hysterical and claimed that she’d been attacked by her ex-boyfriend, but the scene police found in the woods told a very different story...
Book! (Including limited signed copies): https://linktr.ee/RedHanded_Book
Subscribe to our YouTube channel: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC7dovjXDB69lhDjASbAgnwA Patreon: patreon.com/redhanded
Sources: redhandedpodcast.com
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description></item><item><title>In Conversation with Clair McGowan: Ireland's Vanishing Triangle | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400165/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400165/</guid><description>Podcast Description Between 1993 and 1998, eight women went missing from an area around Dublin that became known as the ‘Vanishing Triangle’. Was there a link? Speculation abounded. There were whispers of a serial killer, responsible for some, if not all, of these cases. But nobody was ever brought to justice.
Twenty years later, the brutal murder of Jastine Valdez disturbs crime novelist Claire McGowan into action. Reminded, like many in Ireland, of those previous missing women, McGowan brought her skills as a novelist to the real world, setting out to uncover the truth of the vanishing triangle.</description></item><item><title>Episode 196 - General Butt Naked: Liberia’s Cannibal Warlord | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400166/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 08:58:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400166/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Liberia&amp;rsquo;s first bloody civil war, a feared warlord known as &amp;ldquo;General Butt Naked&amp;rdquo; believed that human sacrifice and cannibalism would give his army of child soldiers “divine” strength. Raping and ravaging his way through Liberia, Joshua Milton Blahyi is estimated to be responsible for the deaths of at least 20,000 people. In this episode, Suruthi and Hannah follow the trail of destruction created by Blahyi, and ask can a man once dubbed “the most evil man in the world” really change?</description></item><item><title>Episode 195 - Chris Benoit: The Canadian Crippler | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400167/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400167/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2007 Chris Benoit was one of the biggest stars of the WWE. And he was known for his almost masochistic dedication to his craft, so when he didn’t show up to work one day his colleagues quickly called the police. At the Benoit home, officers discovered a nightmarish scene that would change the face of professional wrestling forever...
BOOK! Pre-order your RedHanded book here: https://linktr.ee/RedHanded_Book
For tonnes of bonus content: patreon.</description></item><item><title>RedHaunted #8 - That Child Looks Scared! | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400168/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400168/</guid><description>Podcast Description RedHaunted is back, and in video form (for all $10+ Patrons)! This time we learn three key things:
Pennsylvania is the land of civil war ghosts. Don’t steal from haunted attics.
If your child starts chatting with a ghost in the basement, don’t keep digging.
If you have a spooky story of your own, send it to redhandedpatreon@gmail.com
BOOK! Pre-order your RedHanded book here: https://linktr.ee/RedHanded_Book
If you’d like to watch this episode of RedHaunted or get your hands on any of the masses of RedHanded bonus content available visit: patreon.</description></item><item><title>Episode 194 - Ivan Milat: The Real Wolf Creek | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400169/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400169/</guid><description>Podcast Description Between September 1992 and November 1993 the remains of seven backpackers were found dotted around Australia’s Belanglo State Forest. The long putrefied bodies had all been shot multiple times by the same .22 calibre rifle, some had snapped spines, others had been used as target practice. Despite all signs pointing to the Milat family, the real challenge for police was finding which of the ten Milat brothers to point the finger at.</description></item><item><title>Episode 193 - Ireland's "Scissor Sisters" | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400170/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400170/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the 30th of March 2005, passers-by began to notice something odd floating down Dublin's Royal Canal. At first they told themselves it was just a mannequin, but when a leg soon popped up - complete with a sock clinging to a putrefying foot - the dismembered limbs became harder to ignore...
BOOK! Pre-order your RedHanded book here: https://linktr.ee/RedHanded_Book For tonnes of bonus content: patreon.com/redhanded
Sources: redhandedpodcast.com
See acast.</description></item><item><title>In Conversation With Emily Kenway: The Truth About Modern Slavery | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400171/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 10:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400171/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily Kenway is a writer and activist. As a former advisor to the UK's first Anti-Slavery Commissioner she was at the heart of modern slavery action. She has written for a variety of publications including the Guardian and TLS.
In 2019, over 10,000 possible victims of slavery were found in the UK. From men working in Sports Direct warehouses for barely any pay, to teenaged Vietnamese girls trafficked into small town nail bars, we're told that modern slavery is all around us, operating in plain sight.</description></item><item><title>Episode 192 - Operation Fort &amp; The Truth about Modern Slavery | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400172/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 07:00:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400172/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2019 a few hungry men went looking for food at a local soup kitchen in Birmingham; here they met an aid worker who was horrified to discover the suffering they had endured at the hands of a notorious Polish crime family. Following this encounter Operation Fort - the biggest modern slavery investigation in the history of the UK - was sparked. In this episode Hannah and Suruthi explore what people trafficking really is as they delve into the UK's prolific slavery network.</description></item><item><title>Episode 191 - "Bride of Christ": Swedish Sects &amp; Sex Slaves | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400173/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400173/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the late 90s Pastor Åsa Waldau became the leader of the Knutby Pentecostal church. She had already been sacked from such a post in Uppsala after having "inappropriate relationships'' with the teenage boys in her congregation, but that wasn't about to stop Åsa. In Knutby she doubled the size of the sect and soon decided that she was in fact the bride of none other than Jesus Christ.</description></item><item><title>Episode 190 - Sylvia Likens: The Girl in the Basement | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400174/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 08:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400174/</guid><description>Podcast Description On 26 October 1965, in the basement of a house in Indianapolis, the police found the body of 16 year old Sylvia Likens. Her remains were covered in over 150 wounds consistent with unspeakable cruelty, torture and sexual abuse.
As the truth came out behind just who had been responsible, the nation looked on in disbelief...
MERCH out now: redhandedshop.com Check out our Patreon: patreon.com/redhanded
Sources: redhandedpodcast.com
See acast.</description></item><item><title>Episode 189 - Castration, Cults and Cauterisation: The Ant Hill Kids | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400175/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400175/</guid><description>Podcast Description As the secret project deadline hangs ominously over us, we have dug up an absolute stonker from the Patreon vaults to keep you all going! In the early 1980s, in a small hamlet in Central Ontario, there was a cult leader with a messiah complex so big he thought he could operate as a surgeon on the living and use his genitals to bring back the dead. Roch Thériault held a vice-like grip over his loyal followers, so tight that they would abandon their children to his surgical madness, and so firm they would abandon their partners for his harem.</description></item><item><title>In Conversation with Sonia Faleiro: The Good Girls | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400176/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400176/</guid><description>Podcast Description In May 2014, the bodies of 2 teenage girls were found hanging from a tree in the Budaun district of Uttar Pradesh in Northern India. It was reported that the girls had been victims of a gang rape.
This story sparked scandal and rage across the nation - but there were serious questions raised about the truth of what had occurred - author and journalist Sonia Faleiro spent four long years investigating the case, talking to relatives, the police, and even the accused.</description></item><item><title>Drunk Women Caught RedHanded | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400177/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400177/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to our Acast Red Nose Day Mashup podcast for Comic Relief For Red Nose day two of the UK’s finest crime podcasts have mashed up for an episode unlike any other. Join Hannah Maguire and Suruthi Bala from RedHanded alongside Hannah George, Catie Wilkins, and Taylor Glenn from Drunk Women Solving Crime to bring us 'Drunk Women Caught Redhanded'. This powerhouse of super-sleuths leaves no stone unturned in solving a true crime from history, whilst imbibing their favorite adult beverages and inviting us to play along too.</description></item><item><title>Episode 188 - Michael Alig: Confessions of a Club Kid Killer | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400178/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400178/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a world where drug use was rampant and controversy was currency, confessions of murder weren't even enough to raise heavily painted eyebrows. This is the story of how one of New York's hottest promoters fell from grace to cause the death of a man and the death of New York's club scene.
In this week's episode of RedHanded, we discuss the killing of Angel Melendez and how Michael Alig went from making TV appearances at the forefront of the groundbreaking Club Kid movement, to killing a man, and then chopping him up in exchange for ten bags of heroin.</description></item><item><title>RedHaunted #7 Stay Away From Small Boys With Red Balls | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400179/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400179/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alien encounters in the Australian outback, the Irish folk horror story of Half-Hanged McNaughton, the man behind the curtain in a haunted theatre, and a blood chilling tale about the ghost of a little boy named Timothy....
These are your spooky stories, and real life experiences of the paranormal and we can't get enough. Brace yourselves!
Send your stories to - redhandedpatreon@gmail.com See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description></item><item><title>Episode 187 - Leonarda Cianciulli: The Soap-Maker of Correggio - Part 2 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400180/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400180/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the concluding part of this grisly series Leonarda Cianciulli sinks deeper into depravity. The fear reaches boiling point as her continued experiments, making human soap from the fat of her victims, fail to deliver. And with Leonarda's beloved son Giuseppe about to head to war - she knows she has just one last shot left to save him - and for that another woman must die...
Merch: www.</description></item><item><title>Episode 186 - Leonarda Cianciulli: The Soap-Maker of Correggio - Part 1 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400181/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400181/</guid><description>Podcast Description Leonarda Cianciulli was consumed by fear thanks to a curse her mother had placed on her. She had learned all she could about black magic from the Romani travellers who passed through her little Italian town, but still the deadly effects of the hex persisted - at least in Leonarda's mind.
As she grew desperate, and immersed herself further into the occult, Leonarda realised it was all about the 'law of equivalent exchange'; to save a life, she'd have to take a life.</description></item><item><title>In Conversation with Ryan White: The Prank Show Murder of Kim Jong-nam | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400182/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400182/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the 13th of February 2017, the world witnessed the most high profile political assassination in decades when Kim Jong-nam was exposed to a deadly nerve agent known as VX in the centre of Kuala Lumpur International Airport. The two women who killed the exiled half-brother of Kim Jon-un, claimed they had been tricked and that they thought they were taking part in a Japanese YouTube prank show.</description></item><item><title>Episode 185 - The Cartels Killing Women | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400183/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400183/</guid><description>Podcast Description On 9 February 2020, 25 year old Ingrid Escamilla was found murdered in her home. She had been stabbed to death by her partner, and then horrifically mutilated. It was just the beginning of one of Mexico's bloodiest years ever.
Femicide in Mexico is at epidemic levels - and the link between the rampant murder of women, corruption and cartels is undeinable. In this episode we explore the horror, the violence and the impunity of what is happening across the nation - and particularly in Ciudad Juarez.</description></item><item><title>Bonus - EmptyHanded: The Supercut | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400184/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400184/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Valentine's Day! (Whatever that means...) This week as a special gift for all of you, we’ve cut together all of the best bits of a segment we do on our after show Under the Duvet called “EmptyHanded”. EmptyHanded is the everlasting discussion of the occasional highs and inevitable lows of our dating lives. We’ve got Japanese Horror Porn, we’ve got Kermit GIFs, we’ve even got blue ticks. It’s a dumpster fire, and we wouldn’t have it any other way (or perhaps we would…).</description></item><item><title>Episode 184 - The Execution of Jamal Khashoggi | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400185/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400185/</guid><description>Podcast Description At 1:14pm on 2 October 2018, Washington Post journalist Jamal Khashoggi walked into the Saudi consulate in Istanbul. Within minutes he was killed and dismembered by a 15 man hit squad sent from Riyadh.
To this day Jamal’s remains have never been found. And aside from a secretive trial conducted by the Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman - the man who according to the CIA and Turkish intelligence ordered the hit - Jamal has had no justice.</description></item><item><title>Episode 183 - Anders Breivik: Norway's Nightmare | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400186/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400186/</guid><description>Podcast Description On 22 July 2011, Anders Breivik sent out thousands of the same email. The subject line read: "The Islamisation of Western Europe and the State of the European Resistance Movements", and attached was his 1500 page manifesto. He then detonated a bomb in the government quarter of Oslo, before heading to the island of Utøya, where he would become Norway's worst mass murderer - after taking the lives of 77 people, mainly teenagers.</description></item><item><title>Episode 182 - Adrian Lim: Singapore's "Ritual" Child Killings - Part 2 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400187/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400187/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode explores the aftermath of the arrests, the strange confessions of ritual black magic and child sacrifice, and the bizarre death penalty trial that followed.
Singapore reeled as it soon became apparent that Adrian Lim and his "holy wives" had been targetting children long before their first murder... Sources:
Book - Unholy Trinity by Alan John www.redhandedpodcast.com
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>RedHaunted #6 Don't Name Your Ghosts | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400188/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400188/</guid><description>Podcast Description A civil war ghost named Toby, tribal curses, granddad's ghost, and Banshees in Ireland....
These are your spooky stories, and real life experiences of the paranormal and we can't get enough. Strap in!
Send yours in to - redhandedpatreon@gmail.com See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 181 - Adrian Lim: Singapore's "Ritual" Child Killings - Part 1 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400189/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400189/</guid><description>Podcast Description Adrian Lim's fascination with the occult, and his obsession with power, drove him to transform himself into a black magic "bomoh". He promised his followers whatever they desired, but in exchange he would need from them, everything that he desired...
Lim's depravity quickly escalated; he became increasingly violent, turned his attention to younger and younger victims, revelled in torture, rape and eventually murder.
Sources:
Book - Unholy Trinity by Alan John www.</description></item><item><title>Update on the Tuam 796 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400190/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400190/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1975 the skull of a child was discovered on the site of an old mother and baby home in Tuam, Ireland. It lead to the discovery of hundreds more children's remains that had been disguarded by nuns who ran the home. Years later fearless campaigner and historian Catherine Corless made sure everyone knew about it and enough pressure was put on the Irish government that an investigation commission was formed.</description></item><item><title>Episode 180 - Lori Vallow: Doomsday | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400191/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400191/</guid><description>Podcast Description 47 year old mum of 3, Lori Vallow was convinced of two things; she was a god and the world was ending. Her job was to prepare her people for the second coming of Christ, in July 2020...
But even as her behaviour became increasingly erratic, and even as those around her started to die in mysterious ways, and even when 2 of her kids - J.J. and Tylee - vanished, it took a shockingly long time for the alarm to be raised.</description></item><item><title>Episode 179 - The Reykjavík Confessions: Memories of Murder | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400192/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400192/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the bizarre story of 2 mysterious disappearances, 1 strange dream and 6 people who ended up confessing to murders they couldn't even remember...What happened on the treacherous lava fields of Iceland back in 1974 that ruined the lives of so many, and crept its way so deep into the Icelandic culture, that this story still makes headlines today?
Book: Out of Thin Air by Anthony Adeane</description></item><item><title>Bonus: 2020 Patreon Upcycle - When Your Child Displays Psychopathic Traits... | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400193/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 10:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400193/</guid><description>Podcast Description We wanted to celebrate and share some of our top picks from our 2020 Patreon releases, so here is possibly our most requested episode from the $10+ Patreon archives!
In this bonus episode we released last summer, we talked with long time Spooky Bitches, Cassie and Mike as they told us about the challenges and difficulties that their family have faced in the midst of their son Arthur’s serious behavioural issues.</description></item><item><title>#6 BLM - Elijah McClain | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400194/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400194/</guid><description>Podcast Description In August 2019, 23 year old Elijah McClain was walking home with some ice tea he had bought for his cousin. On the way he was stopped by police; within minutes Elijah was being restrained and placed in a chokehold. Things escalted further when the police had the young man, who by this point was slipping in and out of consciouness, injected with ketamine.
Elijah died 3 days later in hospital, this is his story.</description></item><item><title>RedHaunted #5 You See Those 2 Pillars? Look In Between Them... | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400195/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400195/</guid><description>Podcast Description 2020 has been absolutely terrifying, so how better to wrap up this shit show than with a very special episode of RedHaunted! Hopefully these bizarre tales of a rattling doorknob, a haunted asylum and a creepy kennel, will help you get you through whatever nightmare awaits us next...
(We're guessing we will all need more spooky tales, and more laughs, next year so send your ghostly encounter stories to: redhandedpatreon@gmail.</description></item><item><title>In The News: The 2020 Round-Up | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400196/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400196/</guid><description>Podcast Description Merry Christmas Spooky Bitches! This year as a present for all the incredible things you guys have achieved (The Listener's Choice and Spotify No:1) we've decided to give you all some bonus content Christmas Presents. We've scoured through the hours of extra content we put up on Patreon to bring you 2020's greatest hits.
This episode is In The News, our monthly episode on the cases that have been hitting the headlines but haven't progressed far enough for a full-length episode.</description></item><item><title>Under The Duvet: The 2020 Round-Up | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400197/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400197/</guid><description>Podcast Description Merry Christmas Spooky Bitches! This year as a present for all the incredible things you guys have achieved (The Listener's Choice and Spotify No:1) we've decided to give you all some bonus content Christmas Presents. We've scoured through the hours of extra content we put up on Patreon to bring you 2020's greatest hits.
This episode is Under The Duvet, the after-show where we discuss the week's goings-on, whether it's politics, TV, or even our personal tales of woe.</description></item><item><title>Episode 178 - Josef Fritzl &amp; His Cellar of Horror - Part 3 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400198/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400198/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the concluding part of this terrifying series, we learn how Josef Fritzl's terrible secret was finally discovered, how his bizarre trial unfolded and what became of Elisabeth and her children.
Sources: www.redhandedpodcast.com Merch: www.redhandedshop.com See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 177 - Josef Fritzl &amp; His Cellar of Horror - Part 2 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400199/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400199/</guid><description>Podcast Description Elisabeth Fritzl had spent her childhood being relentlessly sexually tormented by her father, Josef. But on 29th of August 1984 things escalated to a level of horror she could never have imagined, when she woke up chained to a bed in the cellar of his house...
Merch: www.redhandedshop.com
Sources: www.redhandedthepodcast.com
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.</description></item><item><title>Episode 176 - Josef Fritzl &amp; His Cellar of Horror - Part 1 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400200/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400200/</guid><description>Podcast Description On 19th April 2008, the world discovered the nightmare world Josef Fritzl had created in the labyrinthian cellar of his home in Amstetten, Austria. It seemed like too much to believe. This week in part 1 of this 3 part series, the girls explore Fritzl&amp;rsquo;s fraught childhood - that was peppered with violence, abandonment and spillover trauma from Nazi concentration camps. Merch: www.redhandedshop.com Sources: www.redhandedpodcast.com See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description></item><item><title>Episode 175 - Annie Le &amp; Room G22 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400201/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400201/</guid><description>Podcast Description Annie had it all; she was happily engaged, she was studying for her doctorate at Yale and she had huge ambitions for herself, that seemed well within reach. So when one day she vanished from her lab on campus, no one could believe it. But within days the true horrors of what had happened to Annie surfaced...
20% of all merch (plus new colour sweatshirts and hoodies!) for 72 hours using promo code 'BLACKFRIDAY'</description></item><item><title>#5 BLM - Sheku Bayoh | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400202/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400202/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this month's episode of our Black Lives Matter series, we discuss the death of Sheku Bayoh in the Scottish town of Kirkcaldy. Sheku died after he was pepper-sprayed and restrained by 4 police officers in 2015. The police cover-up, scandal and public inquiry that followed has made Sheku's death one of Scotland's most notorious cases.
This is Sheku's story.
Sources:
Death in Custody: https://www.bbc.co.uk/iplayer/episode/b0bw8f21/disclosure-series-1-3-dead-in-police-custody
https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-scotland-53076269
https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-scotland-edinburgh-east-fife-52754957
https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2019/nov/16/sheku-bayoh-brother-shouldnt-have-died-like-this-inquiry-family\</description></item><item><title>Episode 174 - Keli Lane: What Happened to Baby Tegan? Pt 2 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400203/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400203/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s episode the girls delve into the aftermath of John Borovnik's discovery, the police investigation that followed, and the subsequent trial that saw Keli Lane charged with murder - more than 13 years after her baby vanished.
But even after all this, major questions around what drove Keli's behaviour, and of course what happened to baby Tegan, still remain...
Merch: www.redhandedshop.com
Sources and recommendations:
Documentaries: Exposed: The Case of Keli Lane (Amazon Prime or Netflix - depending on region)</description></item><item><title>Episode 173 - Keli Lane: What Happened to Baby Tegan? Pt 1 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400204/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400204/</guid><description>Podcast Description Between the ages of 17 and 21 Keli Lane, an elite Australian water polo player, got pregnant 5 times - and somehow managed to keep each pregnancy a total secret for years...
But her lies, inconsistencies and cryptic pregnancies all came spilling out in 2001, when a social worker finally noticed that one of her daughters had vanished at just 2 days old. So, what happened to baby Tegan?</description></item><item><title>Episode 172 - Je Suis Prof: The Murder of Samuel Paty &amp; Charlie Hebdo | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400205/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400205/</guid><description>Podcast Description On 16 October 2020, 37 year old teacher Samuel Paty was beheaded on a suburban street in France by an Islamist terrorist. Samuel had become the target of an online hate campaign after he showed his students cartoons from the satirical magazine, Charlie Hebdo, depicting Muhammad. In this episode we discuss the 2015 Charlie Hebdo massacre, the murder of Samuel Paty and the rise of terrorism in Europe.</description></item><item><title>Episode 171 - Halloween Special Part 2: Black Magic Saliva &amp; A Toilet Full of Guts | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400206/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400206/</guid><description>Podcast Description If there's a spiritualist spit hoover and a child's hand boiling away on the stove, it can only be part two of RedHanded's traditional Halloween story swap.
This round, Hannah tells us about a murderous Indonesian sorcerer, while Suruthi racks up our air miles with a trip back to Germany to meet a barbaric Bavarian butcher.
72 FLASH SALE on all Spooky Bitch merch! For 20% off all Spooky Bitch items from 29 Oct until midnight on Halloween use promo code: spooky20off at www.</description></item><item><title>#4 BLM - Ms Dhu | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400207/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400207/</guid><description>Podcast Description This month in our Black Lives Matter series, we discuss the death of Ms Dhu. During the two day's Ms Dhu spent in police custody in Western Australia, she was dropped to the floor, lifted by her hands and feet, and another prisoner was dragged into her cell to stare at her. She went through all of this while being verbally abused and suffering from sepsis. She died of preventable causes aged just twenty-two, while a white officer stood over her saying she was "</description></item><item><title>Episode 170 - Halloween Special Pt 1: Whiskey Cannibals &amp; Blanket Hags | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400208/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400208/</guid><description>Podcast Description As is Halloween tradition at RedHanded - we bring you a story swap! This year, Suruthi goes rogue with a story of colonial cannibalism, while Hannah takes us to Germany for a stomach-churning, true house of horrors...
Merch: http://www.redhandedshop.com/
Sources: www.redhandedpodcast.com
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 169 - The Toolbox Killers: Lawrence Bittaker &amp; Roy Norris | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400209/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400209/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Halloween night 1979, 16 year old Lynette Ledford was on her way home from a party when she vanished. The discovery of her body the next day set in motion a disturbing investigation into a pair of brutal serial killers who had raped, tortured and murdered their way across the state for months. John E Douglas - the FBI profiler who assessed the likes of Manson, BTK, Bundy, John Wayne Gacy, David Berkowitz and Richard Speck - said of one of this pair: “He was the most disturbing man I’ve profiled”.</description></item><item><title>Episode 168 - The Kansas City Butcher: Robert Berdella | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400210/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400210/</guid><description>Podcast Description One April afternoon in 1988 a man named Chris Bryson jumped from the top floor window of 4315 Charlotte St in Kansas City, Missouri.
He was battered, bruised and completely naked - except for a dog collar and lead hanging from his neck. He had been held captive for days, tied to a bed and brutally tortured by Bob Berdella (aka The Kansas City Butcher) - and Chris was not his first victim.</description></item><item><title>Episode 167 - Live from The 2020 London Podcast Festival | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400211/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400211/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week's episode Hannah and Suruthi story swap the on vaguely train related cases of 'The Brighton Trunk Murders' and the killings of Kieran Kelly - one of the UK's most prolific serial killers...
Spooky Bitch MERCH out now! www.redhandedshop.com Check out the visuals for this episode here! OR follow us on social media: @redhandedthepod on insta, and The RedHanded Podcast Group on Facebook for the accompanying visuals.</description></item><item><title>Episode 166 - The Noida Double Murders: Aarushi &amp; Hemraj | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400212/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400212/</guid><description>Podcast Description London Podcast Festival Live Stream Tickets
When 13 year old Aarushi Talwar was found dead with her throat slit in her own bedroom, it sparked the beginning of what would become one of India’s most notorious cases. A story of immeasurable corruption, incompetence, sex, scandals and secrets.
References
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonus - Tamám Shud: The Mysterious Case of the Somerton Man | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400213/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400213/</guid><description>Podcast Description On 1 December 1948 a fully clothed man was found dead on Somerton beach, South Australia. The bizarre discoveries that followed - including a couple of genetic abnormalities, a rare book of Persian poetry and a mysterious code - led to this becoming one of the strangest and most obsessed over mysteries in history...
This is as weird as it gets.
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description></item><item><title>Episode 165 - Did Dai Morris Do It? | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400214/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400214/</guid><description>Podcast Description In June 1999 a fire broke out at 9 Kelvin Road in Clydach, Wales. By the time emergency services arrived the residents: Mandy Power, her 80 year old mother Doris and Mandy’s 2 daughters Katie, 10 and Emily, 8 were all dead. But the cause of death wasn’t the fire; they had all been savagely beaten to death. All of the evidence, including a discovery made inside Mandy, pointed at a possibly grotesquely sexual motive and a potential police cover up.</description></item><item><title>Episode 164 - "Command Rape": Vanessa Guillen &amp; LaVena Johnson | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400215/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400215/</guid><description>Podcast Description The US military has a rape problem; 20% of women who enlist are sexually assaulted or harrassed. The US military also appears to have a murder problem, because a distrubing number of women who have been victims of 'command rape' are dying in mysterious circumstances.
Vanessa Guillen was a 20 year old solider stationed at Fort Hood, Texas and on 22 April 2020 she vanished. 6 weeks later her burned, dismembered and concrete encased remains were found.</description></item><item><title>#3 BLM - Darren Cumberbatch | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400216/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400216/</guid><description>Podcast Description This month in our Black Lives Matter series, we discuss the death of Darren Cumberbatch. Darren was a quick-witted and friendly electrician who was punched, kicked, pepper-sprayed, and tased by British Police while suffering from Acute Behavioral Disturbance in the toilet of a bail hostel in Nuneaton. This is Darren’s story. The Justice4Daz campaign Facebook page:https://www.facebook.com/Justice4Daz/
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Episode 163 - Show &amp; Tell: The Murder of Rachel O'Reilly | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400217/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400217/</guid><description>Podcast Description LONDON PODCAST FESTIVAL TICKETS
When Rachel O'Reilly was brutally murdered in her own home in County Dublin, her family were told that it was a home invasion gone horribly wrong. Her devastated parents thought they'd never set foot in her house ever again; that was until Rachel's husband Joe invited them over. But to their horror Joe insisted on showing them the grisly blood-stained walls and made them watch as he re-enacted how he thought Rachel had been killed.</description></item><item><title>Episode 162: The Many Faces of Franklin Delano Floyd | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400218/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400218/</guid><description>Podcast Description In March 1995 a Kansas mechanic bought an old truck at auction; as he started to fix it up he discovered a manila envelope taped to the gas tank. To his horror, inside were 97 photos - most of them were of children being sexually abused. There was also a series of photos of a badly beaten, naked young woman. He called the police, and this harrowing discovery unbelievably solved multiple, decades-long unsolved mysteries…</description></item><item><title>Bonus - Holly and Jessica: The Soham Murders | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400219/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 06:10:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400219/</guid><description>Podcast Description On 4 August 2002, 10 year old best friends Holly Wells and Jessica Chapman vanished from a family barbeque in Soham, Cambridgeshire. This sparked one of the biggest police hunts in UK history and when a series of grim discoveries were made, it changed the country forever.
References
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 161 - Naomi Oni &amp; The Acid Attack Epidemic | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400220/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400220/</guid><description>Podcast Description It was after midnight on the 29th of December 2012 when 20 year old Naomi Oni was walking home in East London. Suddenly out of the darkness she saw a figure appear and a splash of liquid hit her face. The excruiating burning pain was immediate, and the horrors that followed would only be topped when she discovered just who had carried out this brutal revenge acid attack.</description></item><item><title>Episode 160 - The Most Hated Woman in America | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400221/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400221/</guid><description>Podcast Description Madalyn Murray O’Hair, was a woman very not of her time. In buttoned-up 50s America she called herself a militant feminist, a thinker and a drinker and - perhaps most heinous of all: an atheist. Her provocative ways quickly gained her the illustrious title of "the most hated woman in America". She was so hated in fact that in 1995 when she, her son and her granddaughter went missing no one really seemed to care - that is until in 2001 when their dismembered bodies were found on a ranch in Texas.</description></item><item><title>Episode 159 - The Nepalese Royal Massacre | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400222/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400222/</guid><description>Podcast Description On 1 June 2001 a bloody massacre unfolded within the palace walls of the Nepalese royal family in Kathmandu. It left 10 members of the royal family dead - including the king, the queen and all 3 of their children.
These killings sparked dangerous conspiracy theories across the globe, started a civil war and set in motion a series of events that led directly to the fall of the entire royal dynasty of Nepal.</description></item><item><title>#2 BLM - Breonna Taylor | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400223/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400223/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this month's Black Lives Matter episode we discuss the murder of Breonna Taylor.
#sayhername
Where to help:
Petition: https://www.change.org/p/andy-beshear-justice-for-breonna-taylor #birthdayforbreonna action items (incl email and addresses to contact the Kentucky Attorney General): https://msha.ke/30flirtyfilm/ GoFundMe: https://www.gofundme.com/f/9v4q2-justice-for-breonna-taylor? Louisville Community Bail Fund: https://actionnetwork.org/fundraising/louisville-community-bail-fund/ Recommended reading:
Why I'm No Longer Talking to White People About Race Me and White Supremacy See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Episode 158 - Poisonous Privilege: The Murder of Emily Longley | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400224/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400224/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2011, 17 year old Emily Longley was found dead in her boyfriend - Elliot Turner's parents' house. But it soon became clear that the story the entire Turner family were telling about how Emily died didn't quite add up...
References
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>RedHaunted #4 - Just Get Into The Recovery Position and Close Your Eyes | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400225/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400225/</guid><description>Podcast Description You Spooky Bitches have done it again! We've got another boatload of freaky tales (and quite a few laughs) to get us through the hellscape that is 2020. We need more spooky tales! Send yours in at - redhandedpatreon@gmail.com
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 157 - The Disappearance of Peter Falconio | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400226/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400226/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2001 on a remote stretch of highway in Australia’s Northern Territory, British backpacker Peter Falconio vanished. His girlfriend, Joanne Lees, told police that they had been attacked by a strange man. The subsequent investigation saw local drug runner Bradley Murdoch jailed for life - but questions still linger, especially around the truthfulness of the story that Joanne told...
References
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Episode 156: Stephanie Lazarus: The Detective Who Almost Got Away with Murder | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400227/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400227/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Feb 1986 the body of newlywed Sherri Rasmussen was found in the home she shared with her husband, John. It was quickly ruled a break-in gone wrong, and the case fell into the icy depths of unsolved cold cases. But over 2 decades later the truth finally began to emerge; and for the LAPD it struck closer to home than they could have ever imagined. Poll: https://poll.ly/#/PwXbm7o3 References: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Episode 155 - 'Repent or Die': Panama's Jungle Death Cult | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400228/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400228/</guid><description>Podcast Description Following reports of strange riutals and bizarre religious ceremonies, in January 2020 Panamanian police headed into the country's remote jungle. What they found in a makeshift church, in the isolated indigenous village of Alto Terrón was something straight out of a 70s exploitation horror movie...
Sources:
The Missionary podcast: https://www.iheart.com/podcast/1119-the-missionary-61230211/ https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-46336355
https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2020/04/13/a-missionary-on-trial
https://www.theatlantic.com/international/archive/2018/03/young-missionaries/551585/
https://www.aljazeera.com/indepth/features/2016/04/worlds-panama-indigenous-panama-papers-160408102014340.html
https://www.zegrahm.com/blog/indigenous-cultures-panama-introductory-guide
https://www.abc.net.au/news/2020-01-21/panama-survivor-recounts-chaotic-cult-rite-that-killed-7/11885124
https://www.abc.net.au/news/2020-01-17/panama-exorcism-ritual-leaves-seven-people-killed-15-tortured/11876878
https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/mar/28/panama-sect-massacre-indigenous-official-neglect
https://www.theguardian.com/world/2020/jan/16/panama-burial-pit-children-exorcisms-religious-sect
https://www.scmp.com/news/world/americas/article/3047128/screams-jungle-mystery-panama-cult-sacrifices-children
https://www.thedailybeast.com/inside-the-religious-death-cult-that-massacred-seven-in-panama?ref=scroll
https://www.telemetro.com/nacionales/2020/01/16/congreso-ngaebe-lleva-registro/2445714.html
https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-latin-america-51144629
https://www.eluniversal.com.mx/mundo/secta-religiosa-torturo-y-sacrifico-6-ninos-y-una-mujer-embarazada-en-panama?amp
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description></item><item><title>Episode 154 - Helen Bailey: Close to Home | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400229/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400229/</guid><description>Podcast Description In April 2016 millionaire author, Helen Bailey vanished. After months of searching, she was found much closer to home than anyone could have imagined...
VOTE: https://www.britishpodcastawards.com/vote
Ian Stewart full 999 call: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZsS8X4Zspr4&amp;amp;t=510s
Ian Stewart arrest: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DQnHMHXjx00
https://www.crimeandinvestigation.co.uk/shows/what-the-killer-did-next/articles/the-strange-tragedy-of-helen-bailey https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2018/08/22/killer-childrens-author-helen-bailey-quizzed-police-death-first/ https://www.mirror.co.uk/tv/tv-news/helen-bailey-murder-how-killer-13873266
https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-36814157
https://closeronline.co.uk/real-life/news/janet-street-porter-dead-killed-children-author-helen-bailey-dumb-loose-women-ia/
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 153 - Hillbilly Sex Ring: The Goler Clan | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400230/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400230/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Nova Scotia’s South Mountain, just a few miles away from the apple blossom fairs and prosperous farms of the Annapolis Valley, a despicable evil had gone unnoticed for generations. In 1984 Sandra Goler, a 14 year old girl, finally broke the silence when she revealed the true horror of her family’s predilection for incest, horrific abuse and torture. Sources: redhandedpodcast.com See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>RedHaunted #3: Hop on in Then! Bring the Ghosts Closer to Me | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400231/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400231/</guid><description>Podcast Description A little boy in a trenchcoat, a terrifying doorbell of death and biting tarot cards....this month, in their continued effort to scare us into forgetting about the world’s problems, Hannah and Suruthi tell their scariest tales yet, courtesy of you Spooky Bitches. VOTE: www.britishpodcastawards.com/vote
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 152 - Daniel Bartlam: The Boy with the Hammer | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400232/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400232/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2011 a fire tore through the Bartlam home in Nottingham, England. 14 year old Daniel, his little brother Dominic and the family dog all made it safely outside, but Jacqui, their mum didn't. She had been beaten to death with a hammer and left inside the burning building. Daniel told investigators a masked intruder had killed his mum, but discoveries they made on the boy's computer soon put him at the top of the suspect list.</description></item><item><title>Episode 151 - Jodi Arias: The Sexed-Up Mormon Murder Trial | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400233/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400233/</guid><description>Podcast Description On 4 June 2008, 30 year old Mormon businessman Travis Alexander was found dead in his shower. He’d been shot in the head, stabbed 27 times and his throat had been slit from ear to ear. The only person any of his friends could think that would want to hurt him was his ex-girlfriend Jodi Arias. She maintained her innocence, but the murder trial that followed was filled with scandals, secrets and sordid details.</description></item><item><title>Episode 150 - Cyntoia Brown Long: Road to Redemption | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400234/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400234/</guid><description>Podcast Description One night Cyntoia Brown was picked up by a man named Johnny Allen, he offered her $150 for sex, she agreed and they went back to his house. By the end of the night Cyntoia had shot and killed Johnny Allen. She was just 16 years old. This is the story of Cyntoia's journey through the American justice system.
Merch Here: https://redhandedshop.com/
Vote Here: www.britishpodcastawards.com/vote
Sources:
https://www.express.co.uk/showbiz/tv-radio/1277647/Murder-to-Mercy-who-is-Cyntoia-Brown-where-is-Cyntoia-Brown-Story-Netflix
https://www.womenshealthmag.com/life/a32301407/where-is-cyntoia-brown-now/</description></item><item><title>#1 BLM - George Floyd | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400235/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400235/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode focuses on the murder of George Floyd.
Places to donate and petitions to sign:
https://blacklivesmatters.carrd.co/#petitions
Black Voters Matter: https://movement.vote/funds/black-voter-fund/
The George Floyd Memorial Fund: https://www.gofundme.com/f/georgefloyd Act Blue:https://secure.actblue.com/donate/bail_funds_george_floyd
NAACP Defense Fund: https://www.naacpldf.org/about-us/
Fair Fight: https://secure.actblue.com/donate/fairfight-2020-dtd
Recommendations to watch:
The 13th They See Us Now
4 Little Girls
I Am Not Your Negro
Freedom Riders
Southern Rites
The Force
The Central Park 5
Unseen
Traffic Stop
Full report of complaints against Chauvin:</description></item><item><title>Episode 149 - Nazi Rage: The Murder of MP Jo Cox | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400236/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400236/</guid><description>Podcast Description In June 2016 the chaos of Brexit reached fever pitch in the UK. One week before the referendum vote was set to take place, politician Jo Cox was savagely shot and stabbed to death outside a public library in the middle of the day. According to eyewitnesses, the assailant screamed “Britain first” as he attacked the defenceless MP. The man was soon revealed to be Thomas Mair, a dedicated neo-Nazi whose decades-long rage had seemingly been sparked into violence by Brexit.</description></item><item><title>Episode 148 - Captivity: The Turpin 13 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400237/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400237/</guid><description>Podcast Description On 13 January 2018, a 17 year old girl made a break for freedom from the house of horrors in which she’d been held captive. She called 911 and soon police stormed the disgusting house in Perris, California. They discovered several children chained to filthy beds in a nightmarish room where the floors were lined with faeces. The children were the escapees’ siblings, and those responsible for the torture and imprisonment, were their very own parents.</description></item><item><title>Bonus: RedHaunted #2 - You're Not Here for Culture, You’re Here for Ghosts | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400238/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400238/</guid><description>Podcast Description Let’s leave lockdown behind and find something else to be scared of for a bit...
In this bonus paranormal episode Hannah and Suruthi bring you ghostly tales from some fellow Spooky Bitches!
Merch: www.redhandedshop.com
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 147 - Limos, Lies &amp; Lithuanian Lovers: The Murder of Nisha Patel-Nasri | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400239/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400239/</guid><description>Podcast Description 29 year old Nisha Patel-Nasri had it all; she was happily married, she ran 2 businesses and she even found time to volunteer as a Special Constable for the London Metropolitan Police. So the entire nation was horrified when one night in 2006 Nisha was stabbed to death in her own home... MERCH: www.redhandedshop.com References: Footage of Fadi Nasri making appeal: https://www.dailymail.co.uk/video/femail/video-1544419/Arrogant-killer-Nasri-lets-slip-sly-smile-TV-appeal.html http://www.justjustice.org/prank.html
https://www.theguardian.com/uk/2008/jun/25/ukcrime
https://www.theguardian.com/uk/2008/may/28/ukcrime2
https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/crime/policewoman-killed-by-husband-was-a-secret-vice-madam-842432.html
https://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2019/07/hiring-a-hitman/590620/
https://www.oxygen.com/murder-for-hire/crime-time/how-hitmen-work-contract-killer-research-psychology</description></item><item><title>Episode 146 - The Butcher of Brooklyn: Levi Aron | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400240/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400240/</guid><description>Podcast Description On 11 July 2011, 8 year old Leiby Kletzy was walking home from school when he vanished. After an extensive police hunt for CCTV, Leiby’s tight-knit Hasidic community were shocked to see that the man who had taken the little boy was wearing a yarmulke; he was one of their own...
Merch! www.redhandedshop.com
Sources:
https://nymag.com/news/features/levi-aron-2011-12/
https://murderpedia.org/male.A/a/aron-levi.htm
https://wildabouttrial.com/trial-coverage/levi-aron/
https://www.nytimes.com/2011/07/14/nyregion/borough-park-residents-reeling-with-news-of-boys-death.html
https://www.tabletmag.com/sections/news/articles/sundown-lieby-kletzky-killer-pleads-guilty
https://www.tabletmag.com/sections/news/articles/levi-arons-interview-from-rikers
https://www.tabletmag.com/sections/news/articles/missing-hasidic-boy-found-murdered
https://www.tabletmag.com/sections/news/articles/sundown-signs-of-struggle-before-kletzky-murder
https://crownheights.info/jewish-news/445459/today-3rd-yahrtzeit-of-leiby-kletzky-obm/
https://www.timesofisrael.com/nyc-man-pleads-guilty-in-leiby-kletzkys-murder/
https://www.aish.com/jw/s/In_Memory_of_Leiby_Kletzky.html
https://www.theyeshivaworld.com/news/headlines-breaking-stories/97250/latest-development-leiby-kletzky-spotted-on-cctv-cameras-505pm.html
https://enacademic.com/dic.nsf/enwiki/11778297
https://nypost.com/2017/06/02/brother-of-man-who-dismembered-child-found-dead-in-closet/</description></item><item><title>Episode 145 - Sex, Lies &amp; “Gender Fraud”: Gayle Newland | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400241/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400241/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2015, 27 year old Gayle Newland was convicted of sexual assault after using a dildo on a female friend who believed that she was a half-Filipino, half-Latino man named Kye...
Merch!
Link for store: www.redhandedshop.com Sources:
Real Stories documentary on Gemma Barker:
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1Wng99iH8aE
https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/trans-people-could-face-rape-charges-if-they-don-t-declare-sexual-history-warns-trans-activist-a7076546.html
https://www.nytimes.com/2019/04/23/well/mind/is-sex-by-deception-a-form-of-rape.html
https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-49127545
http://eprints.keele.ac.uk/3293/3/A%20Sharpe%20-%20Queering%20Judgement.pdf
https://webstroke.co.uk/law/cases/r-v-mcnally-2013
https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2017/jul/15/gayle-newland-retrial
https://www.liverpoolecho.co.uk/news/liverpool-news/no-winners-fake-penis-attacker-13260433
https://www.vice.com/en_uk/article/43qvz9/consent-dildos-and-deception-reexamining-the-trial-of-gayle-newland
https://closeronline.co.uk/real-life/news/woman-stunned-discover-long-term-boyfriend-female-friend-wearing-strap-dildo/
https://thesecretbarrister.com/2015/11/13/gayle-newlands-sentence-was-both-entirely-proper-and-wildly-disproportionate/
https://closeronline.co.uk/real-life/news/gemma-barker-girl-pretended-three-guys/
https://www.stoneking.co.uk/literature/e-bulletins/gender-identity-fraud
http://legalvoice.org.uk/oppose-gender-identity-fraud-prosecutions/
https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2017/jul/15/gayle-newland-retrial
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Episode 144 - Candace Newmaker: When "Therapy" Kills | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400242/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400242/</guid><description>Podcast Description New Merch Release: www.redhandedshop.com
10 year old Candace‘s adopt mum, Jeane Newmaker, wanted nothing more than to help her little girl overcome her attachment disorder. But all the medication in the world wasn’t doing much to ease Candace’s difficult behaviour. Then, a desperate June found a “therapist” who promised quick results. But horrifically the 70 minute rebirthing ritual that followed, ended in Candace’s brutal death. References:
https://culteducation.com/group/1115-rebirthing/17893-her-name-was-candace.html
https://culteducation.com/group/1115-rebirthing/17881-no-prison-for-candaces-adoptive-mom-.html</description></item><item><title>Bonus: RedHaunted #1 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400243/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400243/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tales of the paranormal and unexplained sent in by listeners, dramatically retold by Suruthi and Hannah.
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 143 - Charlene Downes: Without a Trace | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400244/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400244/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2003, 14 year old Charlene Downes disappeared. Rumours quickly spread that she had been murdered, dismembered and her remains had been sold as kebab meat in local takeaway shops. Her story brought to light a dark secret that had lay hidden for years under the illuminations and arcade noises of the English seaside town of Blackpool.
Support the show and get access to weekly bonus content at patreon.</description></item><item><title>Bonus: Let’s Get Quizzical! | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400245/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400245/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re all on lockdown, so just for a bit of fun (and because you all really deserve it right now for staying home/being an amazing key worker) we thought we’d bring you a little bit of extra content, and hopefully a smile!
In this very special bonus episode see how much Hannah and Suruthi know about true crime, their own podcast and each other...
Plus, meet the latest Spooky Bitch to join the RedHanded ranks.</description></item><item><title>Episode 142 - Johann “Jack” Unterweger: The Poet of Death | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400246/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400246/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Austria in 1974, Johann Unterweger was sentenced to life for the murder of a young woman. From behind bars he was soon writing beautiful poetry and painting a heartbreaking image of a man who had endured a hard childhood, made some mistakes - but who was now the poster boy for rehabilitation. Johann went in to prison an illiterate murderer, and with the help of his many elite supporters, he came out early - as a bestselling author.</description></item><item><title>Episode 141 - Zach &amp; Addie: Katrina "Cannibal" | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400247/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 07:00:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400247/</guid><description>Podcast Description In October 2005 police walked into a flat, above a voodoo temple, in New Orleans. What they discovered was straight out of the grisliest of horror films. In this episode Hannah and Suruthi delve into the case of the so-called “Katrina Cannibal” for a story of murder, suicide, Iraqi torture prisons, voodoo temples, marinaded human remains and potential necrophilia…
Support the show and access bonus content on Patreon: www.</description></item><item><title>Episode 140 - "Rough Sex" - The Murder of Grace Millane | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400248/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400248/</guid><description>Podcast Description In December 2018, 21 year old Grace Millane was backpacking around New Zealand. One evening she agreed to a date with a man, tragically by the following morning Grace would be dead. The man claimed it was all just an accident, a result of consensual “rough sex” - but the evidence suggested otherwise... We Can't Consent To This: https://wecantconsenttothis.uk/ Sources:
https://www.businessinsider.com/grace-millane-murder-killer-wont-look-mom-court-statement-2020-2?r=US&amp;amp;IR=T
https://www.theguardian.com/world/2019/nov/21/grace-millane-trial-closing-arguments-new-zealand
https://www.vox.com/2019/11/21/20976064/grace-millane-death-new-zealand
https://www.irishtimes.com/news/world/asia-pacific/uk-backpacker-strangled-to-death-during-tinder-date-nz-court-told-1.4074106
https://www.irishtimes.com/news/world/asia-pacific/new-zealand-police-search-for-shovel-in-uk-backpacker-murder-inquiry-1.3727259
https://www.irishtimes.com/news/world/asia-pacific/man-jailed-for-life-for-murdering-uk-backpacker-in-new-zealand-1.4180184
https://edition.cnn.com/2020/02/21/world/grace-millane-sex-game-gone-wrong-intl-gbr/index.html
https://www.itv.com/news/2020-02-21/grace-millanes-killer-jailed-why-cant-we-name-him/</description></item><item><title>Episode 139 - Ecclesiastes 12: The Strange Death of Charles “Chuck“ Morgan | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400249/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400249/</guid><description>Podcast Description When Chuck Morgan was found dead in the desert - shot in the head, wearing a bulletproof vest and with a $2 note hidden on his body covered in mysterious bible code - it was unbelievably ruled a suicide.
And it was just the beginning of a series of bizarre and unexplained deaths that seem to go all the way to the top...
Tin foil hats on everyone.</description></item><item><title>Episode 138 - Witch-Hunt: The San Antonio Satanic Panic | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400250/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400250/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Texas from 1997 to 1998 four lesbian Latina women were accused and convicted of sexually abusing two young girls in unbelievable devil worship rituals. Homophobia, and the rampant "satanic panic" at the time, sealed the fates of these young women and with no evidence - except the testimony of their young accusers - they were each imprisoned and labelled child rapists.
This is the story of their fight for freedom.</description></item><item><title>Episode 137 - "Nirbhaya": Jyoti Singh &amp; The Delhi Rape Case | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400251/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400251/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nirbhaya means "the fearless one", and it was the name given by the Indian media to a 23 year old woman - Jyoti Singh - after she was brutally gang raped on a bus by 6 men. Jyoti’s rape and murder was a watershed moment in India, it made grisly headlines across the world, and brought tens of thousands of protesters onto the streets of Delhi to demand a change in how the nation deals with violence against women and girls.</description></item><item><title>In Conversation with Former DCI Colin Sutton | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400252/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400252/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this exciting bonus episode Hannah and Suruthi sit down with former DCI Colin Sutton - the Senior Investigating Officer who caught serial killer Levi Bellfield.
They dig into the behind the scenes work that went into such and important investigation - but also find out a bit more.
The Kray Twins even make a surprise appearance.
You can buy Colin's book here: https://www.amazon.co.uk/dp/B07LGHWYFF/ref=dp-kindle-redirect?_encoding=UTF8&amp;amp;btkr=1
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description></item><item><title>Episode 136 - Levi Bellfield: The Hammer Man | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400253/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 07:59:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400253/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2002 13 year old Milly Dowler vanished from a bus stop on her way home from school; this sparked one of the nation’s biggest investigations, but sadly her remains were found 6 months later.
Over the next few years, one by one more women started being attacked across South London. The MO was often different, the vehicle was always different, but the police were convinced that they had a serial killer on their hands.</description></item><item><title>Introducing 'Under the Duvet': A RedHanded Patreon Production | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400254/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400254/</guid><description>Podcast Description Under the Duvet is RedHanded's brand new weekly post-show, mini-show! It's developed exclusively for $5+ patrons - but this week we are giving everyone a little sneak peek of what usually goes down after we stop recording! So enjoy last week’s Valentine’s Day + despot themed episode.
If you like it and fancy getting your hands, and ears, on more RedHanded, head on over to patreon.com/redhanded now! Sign up as a $5+ patron and you can listen in on Under the Duvet after every single episode of RedHanded to hear the ladies talk about whatever random stuff comes to mind.</description></item><item><title>Episode 135 - The Vampire King: Marcus Wesson | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400255/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400255/</guid><description>Podcast Description On 12 March 2004, police walked into an office building in Fresno, California and found the bodies of 9 women and children; they had each been shot once in the eye. It was discovered that all of the victims shared the same biological father, a man named Marcus Wesson - but this man was also all of their “husbands”.
This shocking find unravelled a twisted tale of incest, abuse, rape and vampires.</description></item><item><title>Episode 134 - Lindsay Souvannarath &amp; The Valentine's Massacre Plot | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400256/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400256/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2015, self-proclaimed Nazi - Lindsay Souvannarath and her murderous bae, James Gamble plotted to commit a Valentine's Day mass shooting at a mall in Nova Scotia. Thankfully their plan failed.
But to understand what led these two "lovebirds" on a sadistic path of rage and murder, we need to explore the dark world of online radicalisation, white supremacy, esoteric Hilterism and teen Tumblr romance...
Expect a lot of cock swastikas, meme chat and race hate.</description></item><item><title>Episode 133 - The UK's Most Prolific Rapist: Reynhard Sinaga | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400257/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400257/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 18 year old, Peter, woke up in a mystery flat after a night out he was scared. It was then with horror that he realised he couldn't move his arms, and a strange man was sexually assaulting him...
That man was Reynhard Sinaga; and thanks to Peter, in January 2020, Sinaga was finally convicted of 159 sexual offences, including 136 counts of rape. For years he'd been preying on the men of Manchester, England - attacking with impunity and going totally undetected thanks in large part to his innocent looks, and the copious amounts of GHB that he plied his victims with.</description></item><item><title>Episode 132 - Michelle Carter &amp; Conrad Roy: “Love You Forever” | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400258/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400258/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 18 year old Conrad Roy was found dead in his truck it looked like an obvious suicide. But as detectives started their investigation it soon became clear that this was anything but obvious. Conrad and his 17 year old online girlfriend, Michelle Carter, had exchanged a series of troubling messages in the lead up to his death. Ones in which Michelle seemingly encouraged Conrad to kill himself.</description></item><item><title>Episode 131 - Louise Woodward &amp; Shaken Baby Syndrome | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400259/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400259/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 8 month old Matthew Eappen was admitted to hospital with signs of a severe head trauma, and died just days later of his injuries, doctors and police suspected abuse. Louise Woodward, Matthew’s 18 year old British au pair, was quickly arrested and tried for his murder; and although she denied ever hurting the baby, many experts seriously doubted her story. With the medical evidence pointing in every direction, in this week’s episode Suruthi and Hannah put shaken baby syndrome and the case of Louise Woodward under the microscope.</description></item><item><title>Episode 130 - Ana Kriégel &amp; The Case of Ireland’s Youngest Convicted Killers | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400260/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400260/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 14 year old Ana Kriégel was found in an old, abandoned Manor House in Lucan, Dublin the sheer brutality of her murder horrified a nation. But the revelation that the perpetrators of this incredibly violent, sexually-motivated crime were themselves kids - even younger than Ana - raised dark questions about guilt, innocence and the idea of dangerous children. References:
https://www.irishtimes.com/news/crime-and-law/courts/criminal-court/ana-kriegel-murder-boy-a-sentenced-to-life-boy-b-sentenced-to-15-years-1.4072944
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f7D4jygfJTY
https://www.belfasttelegraph.co.uk/news/northern-ireland/boy-convicted-of-ana-kriegel-murder-incredibly-sorry-38642533.html
https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/breaking-ana-kriegel-murder-boy-20815532
https://www.irishexaminer.com/breakingnews/ireland/ana-kriegel-verdict-the-evidence-the-jury-did-not-hear-931435.html
https://www.thesun.ie/news/4876479/ana-kriegel-hellhole-house-renovations-demands-demolish/
https://edition.cnn.com/2019/11/05/europe/ana-kriegel-ireland-youngest-killers-scli-intl/index.html
https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-7629567/Mother-murdered-Ana-Kriegel-haunted-torture-sadistic-violation-daughter.html</description></item><item><title>Episode 129 - Fighting for Freedom: Julie Rea &amp; Rodney Lincoln | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400261/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400261/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode the girls delve into the cases of Julie Rea Harper and Rodney Lee Lincoln, two people falsely imprisoned for horrific murders most likely committed by serial killer Tommy Lynn Sells.
Brace yourself for how they fought for their freedom even when everything was stacked against them.
References: Crime Watch Daily documentary:
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-t3tccEM2tw
Donate to Investigating Innocence:
https://investigatinginnocence.org/donate
“Through the Window” by Dianne Fanning:
https://www.amazon.co.uk/Through-Window-Martins-Crime-Library/dp/0312985258
https://www.ucmjinvestigations.com/pdf/5837-PI-magazine-article.pdf</description></item><item><title>Episode 128 - White House Farm Revisited: The Contested Evidence | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400262/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 07:51:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400262/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeremy Bamber is currently 35 years into of a whole of life sentence for murdering 5 members of his own family.
To this day he claims to be innocent, and on 6 December 2019 Bamber launched a high court challenge to the Crown Prosecution accusing them of failing to disclose material evidence that undermines the safety of his 1986 conviction.
He wants to build a challenge by contesting key pieces of evidence, so in this episode we are revisiting White House Farm to look into his claims.</description></item><item><title>Episode 127 - Tommy Lynn Sells: The Coast to Coast Killer | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400263/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400263/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the 31 of December 1999 10 year old Krystal Surles woke up to find a man standing in her room. She watched in horror as he killed her friend Katy, slit her own throat and then walked out. Somehow Krystal survived and went on to testify against her attacker; he turned out to be one of America’s most prolific serial killers.
Sources:
https://murderpedia.org/male.S/s/sells-tommy-lynn.htm
ABC News created a 10-minute mini-documentary 'Tommy Lynn Sells - The Mind of a Psychopath'.</description></item><item><title>Episode 126 - Who Killed JonBenét Ramsey? | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400264/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400264/</guid><description>Podcast Description When 6 year old beauty queen JonBenét Ramsey was found dead in the basement of her family’s mansion on Boxing Day 1996 - it sparked a relentless mystery that still endures 25 years later.
Leave what you think you know behind and join Hannah and Suruthi to try and sort fact from fiction...Happy Christmas.
References: https://www.rollingstone.com/culture/culture-news/jonbenet-ramsey-murder-gary-oliva-confession-letters-778025/
https://www.biography.com/crime-figure/jonbenet-ramsey
https://twentytwowords.com/unsettling-facts-about-the-mysterious-death-of-jonbenet-ramsey/
https://www.newidea.com.au/jonbenet-ramsey-case-everything-you-need-to-know
https://www.crimemuseum.org/crime-library/cold-cases/jonbenet-ramsey/
https://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/jonbenet-ramsey-doc-will-encourage-people-to-come-forward-with-leads-on-notorious-cold-case-says-investigator
https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2016/dec/11/jonbenet-ramsey-the-brutal-child-that-still-haunts-america
https://eu.usatoday.com/story/entertainment/music/2019/07/29/ariana-grande-follows-apology-jonbenet-ramsey-joke-new-song-teaser/1858584001/
https://www.vanityfair.com/hollywood/2019/01/jonbenet-ramsey-brother-burke-cbs-lawsuit-settlement
https://skepticalinquirer.org/2017/07/jonbenet_murder_mystery_solved_not_by_psychics/
https://www.crimeandinvestigation.co.uk/article/jonbenét-ramsey-case-the-quiz
https://archive.nytimes.com/www.nytimes.com/interactive/2013/10/26/us/ramsey-indictments.html
https://www.nytimes.com/2008/08/10/books/review/Churchwell-t.html</description></item><item><title>Episode 125 - “The Family” &amp; Anne Hamilton-Byrne | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400265/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400265/</guid><description>Podcast Description For “The Family” or “The Great White Brotherhood”; Anne Hamilton-Byrne was the female reincarnation of Jesus Christ, and her word was final. Unfortunately her word mainly consisted of stealing babies, beating, abusing and injecting terrified children with LSD and poisoning unsuspecting people in order to carry out her “miracles”...
Documentaries:
The Cult That Stole Children:
https://youtu.be/6pmapR9oULc
60 Mins Australia - Interview with Anne Hamilton-Byrne:
https://youtu.be/NFFAJkTRmWc
Other sources:
https://steemit.com/wikileaks/@steemtruth/deconstructing-julian-assange-and-wikileaks-his-childhood-in-a-cult</description></item><item><title>Episode 124 - École Polytechnique: The Montreal Massacre | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400266/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400266/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 6th of December 2019 marks the 30 year anniversary of the Montreal massacre, a dark day in Canadian history. It was the day that gunman Marc Lépine walked into an engineering school and shot dead 14 female students. As he shot the women, he exclaimed that he hated feminists, and that feminists had ruined his life. This sentiment was backed up in his manifesto. A manifesto that shares a great number of themes with that of Isla Vista killer Elliot Roger, or the motivations the 2018 Toronto van killer, Alek Minnassian.</description></item><item><title>Episode 123 - Christopher Foster: Behind Closed Doors | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400267/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400267/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the early hours of the 26th of August 2008, a fire ripped through Osbaston House a 5 bedroom mansion set in 16 acres of beautiful land in Shropshire, England. It was home to the Foster family.
The investigation quickly revealed that the fire was indeed arson, and once the police stepped into the remains of the destroyed mansion, one by one the family's dark secrets started to surface.</description></item><item><title>Episode 122 - Paul Ingram: Satanic Ritual Abuse &amp; Repressed Memory | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400268/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400268/</guid><description>Podcast Description MERCH STORE: RedHandedShop.com
In 1988 sisters Ericka and Julie Ingram were at Bible Camp when they were hit with a sudden memory. It was a memory of being sexually abused by their father, Paul Ingram - the Deputy Sheriff of Thurston County in Washington.
As time passed their stories became more and more terrifying; they were remembering robed men attacking them, sacrificing babies and drinking blood. Were these memories real?</description></item><item><title>Episode 121 - Jeni Haynes: The Woman With Over 2000 Personalities | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400269/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400269/</guid><description>Podcast Description In February 2019 in The District Court of New South Wales a woman named Jeni Haynes entered the witness box - but she wasn't alone. 6 different personalities spoke that day through Jeni's body; in a landmark case that saw a person with DID (Dissociative Identity Disorder, formerly referred to as Multiple Personality Disorder) testify in her many alters, and secure a conviction.
This week the ladies cover this truly inspirational story.</description></item><item><title>Episode 120 - Kermit Gosnell: Doctor Death | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400270/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400270/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a filthy clinic in West Philadelphia that had been left uninspected for years, despite a sizeable drugs bust, Dr Kermit Gosnell was exploiting poor, desperate women seeking to terminate their pregnancies after the legal limit of 24 weeks. His absolute callous recklessness makes this one of the more grisly crimes that RedHanded has delved into - given the subject matter, listener discretion is advised.
Get your spooky bitch merch (international shipping available): redhandedshop.</description></item><item><title>Episode 119 - LIVE from Shoreditch House: Halloween Special Part 2 - Ghost Pirates &amp; Tree Surgeons | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400271/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 11:03:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400271/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this second instalment of Halloween at RedHanded the girls come to you live from London’s Shoreditch House with tales of a mysterious ghost ship and a killer with a penchant for all things tree. Join Hannah and Suruthi as they ask the important questions like: could it have been aliens? What’s the perfect squirrel ice lolly recipe? And what even was WW1? Get your spooky bitch merch (international shipping available): redhandedshop.</description></item><item><title>Episode 118 - Halloween Special Part 1: Demons of Murder &amp; Tantric Child Sacrifice | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400272/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400272/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s Halloween so that means that it’s time for a troubling story swap. Join Hannah and Suruthi in part one of this Halloween special as they turn their stomachs with the case of a cult-ish Anglican exorcism, and harrowing stories of modern-day Indian child sacrifice...
Spooky Bitch merch available now (with international shipping) at: www.redhandedshop.com
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Episode 117 - The Hello Kitty Murder: Fan Man-Yee | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400273/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400273/</guid><description>Podcast Description In May 1999 a scared 14 year old girl walked into a Hong Kong police station and told the confused officers that she was being terrorised by a ghost. At first the police didn’t take her seriously, but then she elaborated that the reason this ghost was haunting her, was because she had helped to torture a young woman named Fan Man-yee to death. The girl then led police to a flat in the city, and what they found there shocked even a nation going through an already unbelievably violent decade.</description></item><item><title>Episode 116 - Hannah Foster: Followed | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400274/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400274/</guid><description>Podcast Description For weeks 17 year old Hannah Foster had been experiencing an uneasy feeling; she was sure that a strange man was following her. Terrifyingly, she wasn’t just imagining things... And one night, when Hannah was just yards from her front door, she was abducted. 6 days later her body was found. The stellar police investigation that followed quickly identified a suspect, but unbelievably he had already fled the UK and disappeared to India, a nation of over a billion people.</description></item><item><title>Episode 115 - The Yuba 5 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400275/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400275/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1978, five men piled into a car after a local basketball game, they stopped at a shop to pick up some snacks and then they vanished. The next day their car was found on a mountain road, without a scratch, half a tank of petrol and in perfect running order. Why would the men have left the car and entered the freezing wilderness?
It wasn’t until the summer that four of the men were found, well at least their bodies were.</description></item><item><title>Episode 114 - “Bishop” Gary Heidnik: The Real-Life Buffalo Bill | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400276/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400276/</guid><description>Podcast Description Between 1986 and 1987 in Pennsylvania, self-appointed “Bishop” Gary Heidnik abducted six women and held them prisoner in a pit that he’d dug into the floor of his basement. The brutal torture that these women suffered at Heidnik’s hands is incomprehensible - especially when you consider that the entire time Heidnik was running his own church just meters above where these women were trapped.
This month’s $10+ bonus Patreon episode is out Monday 7 October - on The Colt Incest Clan.</description></item><item><title>Episode 113 - Gable Tostee: Part 2 - The Aftermath | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400277/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400277/</guid><description>Podcast Description 2 years after Gable Tostee was arrested for the murder of Warriena Wright he stood trial. In this week’s episode the girls delve into the aftermath, the court case, Tostee’s bizarre past behaviour towards women - and vitally all of the information that the jury weren’t told at his trial...
Sources:
What The Gable Tostee Jury Wasn't Told
https://www.news.com.au/lifestyle/real-life/what-the-gable-tostee-jury-wasnt-told/news-story/3d7799ae491cfb454f05254e067df8c7
Gable Tostee could face fresh charges for death of Tinder date Warriena Wright on Gold Coast</description></item><item><title>Episode 112 - Gable Tostee: The Fall - Part 1 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400278/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 07:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400278/</guid><description>Podcast Description On August 8, 2014 28 year old Gable Tostee and 26 year old Warriena Wright met for a first date in Surfer’s Paradise on The Gold Coast. The pair had matched on Tinder - and the date was only ever meant to be a casual hook up, so they went straight to Tostee’s 14th floor flat. In the early hours of the following morning Warriena plunged to her death from Tostee’s balcony.</description></item><item><title>Episode 111 - Tortured to Death: Kelly Anne Bates | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400279/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 06:51:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400279/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the 16th of April 1996 James Patterson Smith walked into Gorton police station and told officers that his 17 year old girlfriend had drowned in the bath. This was of course a lie; Kelly Anne had sustained weeks of torture at the hands of Smith - and her story left even seasoned detectives and pathologists lost for words. So brutal was the crime that it was the first time in Manchester Crown Court that jurors were offered counselling, every single one accepted.</description></item><item><title>Episode 110 - Murder Mansion: Glensheen &amp; Marjorie Congdon | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400280/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 07:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400280/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1977 an intruder entered the beautiful Glensheen mansion on the shores of Lake Superior. In the night of terror that followed, in a macabre game of Cluedo come to life, the wealthy heiress and her nurse were savagely murdered. There were suspects aplenty but the police knew from the start that the answers lay close to home...
Sources:
'Glensheen's Daughter: The Marjorie Congdon Story' by Sharon Darby Hendry</description></item><item><title>Episode 109 - Andrea Yates &amp; The Devil | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400281/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400281/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2001 Andrea Yates did the unthinkable when one-by-one she killed all 5 of her children; what had possessed this seemingly ordinary, loving mother? Well, according to Andrea it was Satan himself. Join the girls this week as they ask did the devil really make Andrea do it? Recommended viewing:
Andrea Yates: A Mother’s Madness: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qsYS-guaNHg
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s2pNZPJPdoc
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Episode 108 - Jeremy Forrest: Runaway Teacher | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400282/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400282/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s “Lolita” on the English Rivera this week as the girls follow the story of a 30 year old Maths teacher, Jeremy Forrest, and his obsession with a 15 year old student - Gemma Grant*.
Their relationship escalated from casual conversations to constant messaging, to kissing to a full blow sexual affair; and soon the whole world knew. In 2012, taking a final stab at being together, the pair ran off to France sparking an international manhunt which left both of their lives in tatters.</description></item><item><title>Episode 107 - Pakistan’s Kim Kardashian &amp; The Selfie That Killed | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400283/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400283/</guid><description>Podcast Description Qandeel Baloch was a social media sensation, women’s rights activist - and a queen of controversy. In 2016 Qandeel released a series of photos and videos that she had captured with one of Pakistan’s most influential and powerful clerics. She also accused him of sexually harassing her - 25 days later Qandeel was murdered; rocking Pakistan as much in death as she had done in life.
If you want to skip Suruthi's travel tales, please skip to 7:40</description></item><item><title>Episode 106 - Train Tracks: The Murder of Vera Jo Reigle | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400284/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400284/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vera hadn't had it easy; she was a vulnerable woman who had coped with ADHD, serious learning difficulties and sexual abuse all her life. At the age of 22 she began dating a 16 year old boy named Zachary Brooks. And while this may sound predatory, it wasn't Vera who was the dangerous one. It was the matriarch of the Brooks family - Cheri Brooks aka "Sugar Babe". When Vera got pregnant, Cheri's determination to meet her grandchild created a horrifyingly dangerous situation for the young mother.</description></item><item><title>Episode 105 - Julie Ward: Murder on the Massai Mara | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400285/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400285/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1988 Julie Ward headed off on the trip of a lifetime to Kenya, but just a week before she was set to return home she took one last trip into the Massai Mara game reserve - and vanished. Julies Father John flew to Kenya immediately to help with the search, but in a cruel twist just a week later it was he who found his daughters dismembered remains in a remote spot on the park.</description></item><item><title>Episode 104 - Stephen Griffiths: The Crossbow Cannibal of Bradford | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400286/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400286/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the 26th of May 2010 Peter Gee, caretaker of a block of flats in Bradford was checking the CCTV when something going on outside flat 33 caught his eye. The man who lived there often had sex workers over so when Peter saw a woman going into the flat he wasn't surprised, but he was not prepared for what happened next. A few minutes later he saw the woman running out of the flat, the man was chasing her.</description></item><item><title>Episode 103 - Daniel LaPlante: Fact vs Fiction | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400287/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 06:32:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400287/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week the girls do some much needed myth-busting surrounding the notorious Daniel LaPlante. With a story that features seances, multiple murders, creepy suitors and an alleged invader dressed in a wedding dress hiding in a family's cupboard. It's not hard to see why this case has grown to horror movie-esque proportions. Join Hannah and Suruthi as they work to separate fact from fiction, and discover that the truth is just as scary as the lies.</description></item><item><title>Episode 102 - Yahweh ben Yahweh: The Prophet, The Cult &amp; The Temple of Love | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400288/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400288/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ruthless cult - The Nation of Yahweh - hit its peak in the late 80s as the self-proclaimed leader, and son of God, Yahweh ben Yahweh promised the people of Miami salvation through messages of black power, total devotion and obedience. His message spread, but so did the fear and control as reports of beatings, extortion, arson, and grisly murders - at the hands of his notorious "Death Angels"</description></item><item><title>Episode 101 - Joanna Dennehy: Spree Killer | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400289/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400289/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week's episode the girls are off to the ditches of Peterborough to cover the case of spree killer Joanna Dennehy, only the third woman in Britain to ever receive a whole of life sentence. Joanna was just 30 years old when she went on a 14 day killing spree that left 3 men dead, dumped in the ditches in rural Cambridgeshire. They were found covered in stab wounds consistent with a frenzied attack, and placed in humiliating poses - what led such a young woman to kill with such rage?</description></item><item><title>Episode 100 - Gilberto Valle: Cannibal Cop | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400290/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400290/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2012 Kathleen Valle started to become suspicious of her New York City police officer husband Gilberto. He was spending all of his time on the computer, and Kathleen, who had just had their baby was afraid he was being unfaithful. When she finally broke and checked his online activity - what she found was far more horrifying than anything she had imagined.
Gilberto Valle had been on cannibal fetish forums talking to strangers about how he wanted to abduct, rape, torture, kill and eat women - including Kathleen.</description></item><item><title>Episode 99 - Black Magic, Murder &amp; Malaysian Pop: Mona Fandey | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400291/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400291/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week the girls are off to Malaysia to cover a case of money, murder, black magic and Malaysian pop music. Mona Fandey was a one hit wonder in the 80s - but when she realised that her singing career was going nowhere, she and her husband turned to black magic...which of course, ended in murder. See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Bonus - The Deal with the Devil: Karla Homolka &amp; Paul Bernardo | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400292/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 07:15:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400292/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this very special 'thank you' episode the girls cover the brutal case of the Ken and Barbie killers, a Canadian couple who abducted, viciously raped and murdered multiple women, including Karla's own teenage sister Tammy. After the pair were caught Karla was quick to put the blame solely on Paul but the evidence casts considerable doubt on her claims of helplessness
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description></item><item><title>Episode 98 - Sally Challen: A Case of Coercive Control | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400293/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400293/</guid><description>Podcast Description One Saturday morning in November 2010 Sally Challen walked into the kitchen and hit her husband Richard in the head with a hammer. She hit him over 20 times. In the trial that followed Sally was painted as a possessive, jealous woman who murdered her husband in cold-blood. This year, in 2019, Sally won a land mark appeal to have her conviction overturned as a fresh defence was shaped around her mental state owing to the years of emotional and psychological abuse she had suffered at the hands of her husband.</description></item><item><title>Episode 97 - Bruce McArthur: The Gay Village Murders | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400294/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400294/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the late 2000s a spate of South Asian and Middle Eastern Men in Toronto's Gay Village vanished. The local community noticed almost immediately by the police seemed unable or unwilling to investigate the disappearances. By the time they realised that they had a serial killer on their hands the situation had escalated into horror movie proportions. See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Episode 96 - The Tuam 796 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400295/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400295/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1975, two little boys, Frannie and Barry were playing on the site of an old Mother and Baby home in Tuam, County Galway, when they discovered a pit full of bones.
Later that same year, Mary Moriarty fell into a tunnel in the same spot, where she saw piles little bundles laid on top of each other like steps.
It would take the tireless research of Catherine Coreless to uncover the grim reality of what they actually saw.</description></item><item><title>Episode 95 - Abraham Shakespeare: Lucky Numbers | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400296/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400296/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2006 all of Abraham Shakespeares' dreams came true. He won 30 million dollars on the lottery, it looked like all his troubles were over. But within 3 years all of his money disappeared and soon after, Abraham disappeared too. See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Break-ins, Booby Traps, and the Eccentric Gynaecologist | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400297/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400297/</guid><description>Podcast Description Courtesy of our friends at ADT.
Please hop over to www.adt.com/podcast
In 1947 the NYPD had to break down the door of the infamous Collyer Mansion in Harlem after the smell of death was reported by a neighbour. A rabbit warren of tunnels made from junk, lined with booby traps waited for them on the other side. See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Episode 94 - The Murder of Alesha McPhail | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400298/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400298/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2018 on the tiny Scottish island of the Isle of Bute, 6 year old Alesha MacPhail vanished from her bed in the middle of the night. The community was left reeling when just a few hours later her body was found. The question that tore though the small town now was who could have done this? And when the truth was revealed it was more shocking than anyone could have imagined.</description></item><item><title>Episode 93 - David Parker Ray: Part 2 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400299/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400299/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, in the concluding part of the David Parker Ray series, the girls head into the infamous torture trailer - “The Toy Box”.
This episode is not for the faint-hearted as Suruthi and Hannah discuss the terrifying torture tactics Parker Ray used on his victims...
Vote for us in the Podcast Awards here: https://www.britishpodcastawards.com/vote PLEASE
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Episode 92 - David Parker Ray: Scrap Metal Sex Toys | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400300/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400300/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, the girls head to Truth or Consequences, New Mexico, to cover arguably the most terrifying offender they have encountered: David Parker Ray aka The Toy-Box Killer. In 1999 a 911 call alerted police to a naked woman, covered in blood, running down the dusty desert streets - she had a dog collar around her neck and a 6 foot metal chain trailing behind her. Upon investigation, this small-town police team uncovered the truly unbelievable horrors that had been unfolding right under their noses in an innocuous looking trailer behind 513 Bass Road&amp;hellip; Sources: redhandedpodcast.</description></item><item><title>Director Joe Berlinger on Ted Bundy: Live | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400301/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 07:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400301/</guid><description>Podcast Description Extremely Wicked, Shockingly Evil and Vile is the new Ted Bundy film; in this very special episode of RedHanded Joe Berlinger, the director, joins the girls for an exclusive Q&amp;amp;A to delve into the psychology of Ted Bundy. On the panel is also Mary Fenwick, agony aunt for Psychologies magazine, who has her own take on what drives men like Bundy and the people who love them.
Extremely Wicked, Shockingly Evil and Vile is a Sky Cinema Original and is in cinemas and on Sky Cinema May 3.</description></item><item><title>Episode 91 - Raymond Buys: "Not Man Enough" | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400302/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400302/</guid><description>Podcast Description On April 20th 2011, 15 year old Raymond Buys was pronounced dead. Some of the doctors who treated him were so traumatised by the injuries sustained by the emaciated young boy that they needed counselling to cope. But what really happened to Raymond at the Echo Wild Game Rangers Camp that promised to "make men out of boys"
South Africa Expert &amp;amp; Accent Coach - Gita Du Toit</description></item><item><title>Episode 90 - Strangers at the Door: The Murder of Kanika Powell | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400303/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400303/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2008 28 year old Kanika Powell, an army veteran, experienced a series of odd encounters on her doorstep. Mysterious men in different guises were turning up at her home asking for her by name. Kanika, knowing that something about their behaviour was very wrong, never opened the door. Scared by the strangers she started to take precautions to stay safe, but one day when Kanika returned home she found a man waiting for her.</description></item><item><title>Episode 89 - Shafilea Ahmed: The Price of "Honour" | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400304/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400304/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2003 16 year old Shafilea Ahmed disappeared from her family home in Warrington, she was presumed missing but the truth was much more horrific. She’d been killed by her own parents because the “dishonour” she was bringing to her family was just too high a price to pay for her to live. Join the girls this week as the delve into the infuriating and heartbreaking world of “honour” based violence and murder.</description></item><item><title>Episode 88 - The Mysterious Death of Elisa Lam | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400305/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400305/</guid><description>Podcast Description In March 2013 college student Elisa Lam checked into The Cecil Hotel on LA’s infamous skid row. Soon she started displaying some odd behaviour; some of which was caught on CCTV - this footage then went viral on the internet after Elisa’s body was found 3 weeks later in a water tank on the roof of the hotel. Forums still buzz with theories about what really happened to Elisa.</description></item><item><title>Episode 87 - Ruth Ellis: The Last Woman to be Hanged in Britain | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400306/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400306/</guid><description>Podcast Description "Six revolver shots shattered the Easter Sunday calm of Hampstead, and a beautiful platinum blonde stood with her back to the wall. In her hand was a revolver." These were the headlines that the hit the nation after Ruth Ellis, a young, welsh-born hostess shot and killed her lover - David Blakely - in broad daylight. The pair had had a violent and tumultuous affair, and there was no doubt that it had been Ruth who had pulled the trigger, but had another one of her lovers primed her to kill?</description></item><item><title>Episode 86 - The Community of Christ: Kirtland Cult | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400307/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400307/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Kirtland Cult were an offshoot of an offshoot that broke away from the Reorganised Church of Latter Day Saints in 1987. Like most cults they were led by a single-minded, self-appointed, narcissistic leader - Jeff Lundgren - who demanded absolute control of his followers; exploiting them psychologically, sexually and financially. Soon after the group moved onto a remote compound in Kirtland, Ohio the stockpiling and the paranoia began - and it would end in the brutal murder of a family of 5.</description></item><item><title>Episode 85 - The Central Park 5 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400308/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400308/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1989 5 young black and Latino boys from Harlem were accused and convicted of the rape and assault of Trisha Meili, a young white woman. They spent between 5 and 13 years in prison until finally in 2003 their sentences were vacated. As we approach the 30th anniversary of this notorious case join the girls, and their special guest - Tracy Clayton - for an in depth look into a brutal crime, and racially charged social, political and media response that still resonates today.</description></item><item><title>Episode 84 - Otto Warmbier: What Really Happened in North Korea? | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400309/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400309/</guid><description>Podcast Description This case starts with a pretty mundane crime; an accusation of poster theft. But it ends in the mysterious and tragic death of a 22 year old man - Otto Warmbier. Otto died after he was arrested while on holiday in the secretive and mysterious nation of North Korea. But what really happened to Otto? The evidence is anything but clear cut...
https://www.nytimes.com/2017/06/19/us/otto-warmbier-north-korea-dies.html
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1mTZjWePlxI&amp;amp;t=30s
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description></item><item><title>Episode 83 - Omaima Nelson: "Cannibal" Kitchen | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400310/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400310/</guid><description>Podcast Description At just 23 Omaima Nelson killed her 56 year old husband, Bill. 3 days after the murder police entered the Nelson home and found a nightmare scene; not only had Omaima killed and dismembered Bill, she'd also been cooking his remains...
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 82 - Jenelle Potter: Catfish | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400311/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400311/</guid><description>Podcast Description Someone was cyberbullying Jenelle Potter; they hurling online abuse and threatening her life with claims that she was "too pretty to live". As things escalated, inexplicably, the CIA seemed to become involved and Jenelle's parents felt the only way to save their vulnerable daughter was to take matters into their own hands. But once her "bullies" were dead questions quickly surfaced about Jenelle's behaviour... See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description></item><item><title>Episode 81 - Ian Watkins: Rock Star, Paedophile, Nepiophile | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400312/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400312/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week the girls delve into the all too common world of the celebrity paedophile and institutions who turn a blind eye.
Ian Watkins was the lead singer of Welsh rock band Lostprophets. He toured all over the world, playing to sold out stadiums of adoring fans - so in 2012 when he was arrested and charged with 13 counts of child sex offences, including against a child as young as 11 months old, the world was shocked.</description></item><item><title>Episode 80 - Ball Gags, BDSM &amp; A Body in the Woods: The Murder of Elaine O'Hara | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400313/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400313/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week the girls head to Ireland to cover the "nearly perfect murder" of Elaine O'Hara. So called, because it was only a year after Elaine mysteriously vanished that police made a series of chance discoveries so unbelievable that they would make a CSI script writer squirm... But these discoveries did go on to unmask a devious killer and rip him from his idyllic suburban life to pay for a brutal murder.</description></item><item><title>Episode 79 - Incest, Murder, Suicide: Steven &amp; Katie Pladl | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400314/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400314/</guid><description>Podcast Description To the outside world they looked like a normal couple, but they were anything but “normal”. Steven Pladl was not only his wife’s lover, but also her biological father - and needless to say this story doesn't end with a happily ever after. In April 2018, less than a year after they were married Pladl shot and killed his daughter/wife Katie, their 7 month old son and Katie's adoptive father - Tony Fusco.</description></item><item><title>Episode 78 - Ariel Castro &amp; The Horror at 2207 Seymour Avenue | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400315/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400315/</guid><description>Podcast Description Between 2002 and 2004 Ariel Castro abducted three young women and chained them up in his basement at 2207 Seymour Avenue. Over the course of the next decade he systematically broke them down, tortured them, raped them, brutalised them - until finally, and miraculously they escaped.
This week we cover the case of Ariel Castro and the three remarkable women who survived an unbelievable ordeal; Michelle Knight, Amanda Berry and Gina DeJesus.</description></item><item><title>Episode 77 - Chris Watts: Family Annihilator | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400316/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400316/</guid><description>Podcast Description In August 2018 Shannan Watts’ body was found buried on a remote oil field in rural Weld County.
In a oil tank nearby were the bodies of her two young daughters; Bella and Celeste.
With only one real suspect who fit the crime, this case left the world asking - what makes a seemingly ordinary man, who appeared to have it all, kill his pregnant wife and children?</description></item><item><title>Episode 76 - Sandy Charles: The Boy Who Wanted to Serve Satan | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400317/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400317/</guid><description>Podcast Description At just 14 Sandy Charles started hearing voices. He thought the voices were ghosts, and they were telling him to kill. On July 8 1995 Sandy obliged by luring 7 year old Johnathan Thimpsen out into the woods.
What Sandy did to Johnathan, in the hopes of "pleasing Satan", shocked the world.
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Episode 75 - William Melchert-Dinkel: "Webcam Suicide Nurse" | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400318/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400318/</guid><description>Podcast Description Celia Blay knew that William Melchert-Dinkel was a dangerous predator.
He had been lurking in internet forums for years, manipulating vulnerable people into disingenuous suicide pacts . This week Hannah and Suruthi follow the bizarre case of the so called "webcam suicide nurse" and the woman who wouldn't stop until justice was served, even after authorities told her to look the other way.
Canada Expert: Cheryl Nash
See acast.</description></item><item><title>Episode 74 - Tracie Andrews: The Road Rage Killer | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400319/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Dec 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400319/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Dec 1 1996, Tracie Andrews and her fiancé Lee Harvey were driving home from an evening at the pub when they got caught up in a cat and mouse game with a couple of maniacs in another car. The road rage turned into a brutal attack and Lee Harvey died after being stabbed over 40 times; and despite also being attacked Tracie survived. At least this was the story that Tracie told police, the press and anyone who would listen.</description></item><item><title>Episode 73 - Mary Vincent: Survivor | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400320/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400320/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mary was just 15 and desperately looking for a way to get home to her family when she accepted a ride from a kindly old looking man. What transpired that night however is the stuff of nightmares. The man, Lawrence Singleton, abducted, raped and maimed Mary with an axe, leaving her for dead at the bottom of a 30ft ravine. But Mary survived. See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description></item><item><title>Episode 72 - Darlie Routier: Beyond Reasonable Doubt? | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400321/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400321/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1997 Darlie Routier was convicted of murdering her 5 year old son, Damon, and sentenced to death. But for 21 years she has sat on death row protesting her innocence, claiming that the real killer was a stranger who broke into the house and attacked her and her sons.
Is she a lying cold-blooded killer, or a tragic victim of brutal injustice? The evidence seems to point in every direction.</description></item><item><title>Episode 71 - Satanic Panic: The Fall River Cult Murders | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400322/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400322/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the 1970s the US was in the throes of a unique cultural phenomenon - the ‘satanic panic’. The devil and devil worshipping cults were everywhere and they were coming to get you. This week Hannah and Suruthi follow the case of the Fall River cult murders, a brutal killing spree carried out by a group of self-proclaimed devil worshippers that saw 2 young women bound, raped and tortured to death, and a third missing with only skull fragments and a harrowing story left behind.</description></item><item><title>Episode 70 - Dylann Roof &amp; The Charleston Church Shootings | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400323/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400323/</guid><description>Podcast Description On June 17 2015, 13 people sat down for bible study at the historically black Mother Emanuel Church in Charleston. But one of them was a stranger - and by the end of the night, in a brutal attack, 9 of the congregants would be viciously murdered. When the killer, Dylann Roof, was captured it became clear that he was driven by a racist ideology of white supremacy and the dream of sparking a violent race war.</description></item><item><title>Episode 69 - The Vampire of Bucharest | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400324/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400324/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1970 a serial killer stalked the streets of Romania's capital, assaulting over twenty young women and brutally murdering at least four. He was quickly dubbed "the vampire of Bucharest" after his victims were found with chunks of their flesh missing and holes poked in their necks, as if someone had been feeding on them.
When the killer was eventually captured further twists surfaced as authorities began to wonder if vampirism and serial killing ran in this man's family.</description></item><item><title>Episode 68 - Halloween Special Part 2: There's Someone in the Attic with Incest | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400325/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400325/</guid><description>Podcast Description Halloween continues at RedHanded this week as Hannah and Suruthi bring you two more disturbing cases to keep you up all night. So, if you're not up for hearing about a murderous man secretly living in a family's attic, or about a stomach churning incestuous relationship between a mother and her adult son; I'd give this one a miss...
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Episode 67 - Halloween Special Part 1: Scary Tupperware &amp; Drywall Knives | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400326/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400326/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's Halloween, so in RedHanded tradition, the girls switch up the format and pull together the most disturbing and little known cases they can find to freak everyone the F out. This week's episode features a rather grim serial killer with some serious Ed Gein vibes, and a woman who will go to any grisly lengths to get what she wants. So curl up, hit play and prepare for scares.</description></item><item><title>Episode 66 - Little Boy Pot Pie: The Depraved Mind of Nathaniel Bar-Jonah | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400327/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400327/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nathaniel Bar-Jonah was a terrifyingly single-minded man; his only focus in life was to hunt, rape, torture and kill children. His depravity became clear in early childhood, and due in part to a lack of consequences for his dangerous behaviour, things only escalated. Eventually Bar-Jonah was arrested and what police officers found in his house led to one of the most stomach churning investigations in US history. It appeared that Bar-Jonah had not only been eating his victims but also feeding them to his unsuspecting neighbours.</description></item><item><title>Episode 65 - Witchcraft, “Muti” &amp; Murder: The Case of Victoria Climbié | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400328/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400328/</guid><description>Podcast Description The murder of Victoria Climbié was the first case to drag the horrors of witchcraft ritual abuse in Britain into the public consciousness. In this week's episode the girls follow the story of 8 year old Victoria's journey to London from the Ivory Coast and how she met her end at the hands of an abusive man who claimed that she was possessed by the devil. In this disturbing episode Suruthi and Hannah also explore other notorious cases of ‘Muti murder’ right here in the UK - like that of the little boy “Adam” and the torso in the Thames.</description></item><item><title>Episode 64 - A Modern Maori Exorcism: The Death of Janet Moses | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400329/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400329/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the 12th of October 2007, 22 year old mother of two, Janet Moses drowned...in the middle of her family's living room.
Janet's family had become troubled by her increasingly odd behaviour in the days preceding her death. After consulting with a Maori priest they believed that she had been possessed by a demon; water, chanting and eye gouging became their only weapons in their desperate fight against the "</description></item><item><title>Episode 63 - An Imperfect Witness: The Story of Kevin Green | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400330/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400330/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kevin Green called 911 claiming that he had come home to find his pregnant wife, Dianna, had been brutally attacked. The beating was so vicious that Dianna lost her unborn baby, she lost her ability to speak and she completely lost her memory surrounding the attack. That was until a few weeks later when she pointed the finger at her seemingly grieving husband. But with a serial killer also on the loose at the time, who was the real attacker?</description></item><item><title>Episode 62 - The Sims Family Murders | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400331/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400331/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1966 Robert, Helen and Joy Sims were murdered in a grim “Strangers” style slaying in their home in Tallahassee, Florida. Nothing was taken from the house, nothing was left behind, there was no sign of forced entry and no one reported seeing anyone suspicious in the area - police were stumped.
But massive overkill on 12 year old Joy Sims suggests that not only was she the intended target, but that this was personal.</description></item><item><title>Episode 61 - Marc Dutroux: The Beast of Belgium | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400332/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400332/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over the course of two summers across Belgium six young girls went missing - their captor, Marc Dutroux, seemed untouchable as he brazenly abducted, imprisoned, raped and murdered his young victims.
But this is much more than a sad story about a sick, sadistic pedophile; how Dutroux evaded arrest time and time again raises serious questions as to whether he was just a small part of a powerful pedophile network stretching to the highest levels of Belgian society.</description></item><item><title>Episode 60 - Ken McElroy: The Town That Got Away With Murder | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400333/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400333/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1981 Ken McElroy was shot dead in front of at least 30 people in his hometown. Not one person called for help, not one person came forward to give evidence and to this day his murder remains unsolved. But people weren't afraid of Ken's killers, this was vigilante street justice exacted against a violent bully and pedophile, who had raped, abused, assaulted - and generally terrorised the people of Skidmore, Missouri.</description></item><item><title>Episode 59 - Danny Casolaro: The Man Who Knew Too Much | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400334/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400334/</guid><description>Podcast Description Governments kill people who try to uncover their dirty dealings, that's a fact. But is that what happened to Danny Casolaro? Danny claimed to be on the verge of connecting the dots between multiple governmental scandals and uncovering an international network of unbelievable crimes. 2 days after meeting his final source, Danny was found dead, could he have been onto something? See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description></item><item><title>Episode 58 - Sharon Lopatka: The Woman Who Dreamt of Being Tortured to Death | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400335/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400335/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Hannah and Suruthi delve into the dawn of the web, following the case of Sharon Lopatka, a woman who fantasised about being tortured to death. One day Sharon had enough and decided to make her fantasy a reality; she met her dream man online - a man who dreamt of torturing women. Eventually Sharon was found buried in a shallow grave, but the state of her remains left many unanswered questions about what really happened to her.</description></item><item><title>Episode 57 - House of Horrors: The Murder of Tia Sharp | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400336/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400336/</guid><description>Podcast Description 12 year old Tia Sharp adored her Grandmother’s partner, Stuart Hazell. He'd been in Tia’s life since she was a baby, and he'd always been her loving “Grandad”. But unbeknownst to anyone in the family Hazell, a man with a dark past, was starting to have sick sexual fantasies about Tia...
One day, out of the blue she vanished and her panic stricken family had no idea that they would eventually find her closer to home than they could ever have imagined.</description></item><item><title>Episode 56 - Snowtown: The Bank Vault Body Barrels - Part 2 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400337/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400337/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week in the concluding episode of the harrowing Snowtown saga; John Bunting and Robert Wagner start to spiral. As they killed with increasing impunity, the net began to close - and their eventual capture led to a trial so gruesome members of jury walked out in disgust.
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 55 - Snowtown: The Bank Vault Body Barrels - Part 1 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400338/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400338/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the 21st of May 1999 police in South Australia went to investigate the contents of a derelict bank in the small town of Snowtown. Inside, they found 6 large barrels full to brim with decomposing human remains. Little did they know, this was just the beginning of what would become one of Australia’s most unrelenting and harrowing cases.
Australia Expert - Kelly Ryan
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description></item><item><title>Episode 54 - Charlie Brandt &amp; His Demons | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400339/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400339/</guid><description>Podcast Description Charlie Brandt was a happily married family man, until September 2004 when he was found hanging in his niece's garage. The scene he left behind was brutal beyond belief, and no one could make sense of what had happened - until his sister Angela turned up to reveal Charlie's dark childhood secret.
All families have secrets, but none quite so dark as the one the Brandts had kept hidden for almost 30 years.</description></item><item><title>Episode 53 - Crocodile Tears, Sex Caravans &amp; Arson: The Mick Philpott Story | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400340/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400340/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the early hours of May 11, 2010 a fire tore through 81 Victory Road; inside 6 children were trapped, outside stood their parents.Tragically all 6 of the Philpott children died and the nation mourned for a grieving Mick and Mairead Philpott. But as the days passed, their behaviour, and their stories about what had happened that night started to raise serious suspicion...
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=frmdzbTAdQc
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_5IrbrO7SQ0
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description></item><item><title>Episode 52 - Cruise Crime: The Disappearance of Amy Bradley | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400341/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 23:08:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400341/</guid><description>Podcast Description One morning 23 year old Amy Bradley got up, got dressed, grabbed her cigarettes - seemingly went for a walk - and vanished. And what makes this case even stranger is that Amy was on a ship, out at sea on a Caribbean cruise with her family. How does one just disappear from a ship, never to be seen again?
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Episode 51 - The Moors Murders: Beyond Redemption - Part 2 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400342/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400342/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week's episode Myra Hindley and Ian Brady escalate; abducting, torturing, raping and murdering four more children. In their arrogance and hedonistic pursuit of violent pleasure, they make the grave mistake of trying to involve a new accomplice - one who would ultimately reveal their evil to the world. See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.</description></item><item><title>Episode 50 - The Moors Murders: Beyond Redemption - Part 1 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400343/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400343/</guid><description>Podcast Description Between 1963 and 1965, Ian Brady and Myra Hindley - a seemingly ordinary pair of twenty-somethings abducted, tortured and killed 5 children in North West England. The Moors Murders, so named because the victims' bodies were found on the barren and remote Saddleworth Moor, still remain Britain's most infamous case half a century later.
But what drove these two to commit crimes so heinous that they scarred the psyche of a generation?</description></item><item><title>Episode 49 - Dinner with a Cannibal: Armin Meiwes | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400344/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400344/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you want to be killed, is it still a murder? This is the question that sits at the heart of this week's case of cannibalism and consent.
Even at the dawn of the internet there were dark corners where you could find anything you wanted - as Armin Meiwes and Bernd Branders knew only all too well. They were a perfect online match, Armin wanted to dine and Bernd wanted to be dinner.</description></item><item><title>Episode 48 - Can Dreams Kill? - The Ryan Ferguson Story | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400345/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400345/</guid><description>Podcast Description On Halloween night 2001 Chuck Erickson got blackout drunk with his friends. 2 years later a 19 year old Chuck, who had been plagued with dreams that he and his friend Ryan Ferguson had killed a man that night, went to the police and confessed to the murder of local man Kent Heitholt. Ryan was adamant this never happened, and there was no physical evidence linking either of them to the crime - so what really happened that night?</description></item><item><title>Episode 47 - Snuff Films &amp; Submarines: The Murder of Kim Wall | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400346/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400346/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2017 intrepid super-journalist Kim Wall scored an underwater submarine interview with eccentric Danish 'inventrepreneur' Peter Madsen.
17 hours later Madsen was rescued from the sinking vessel, but Kim was no where to be seen. Exactly what happened during those 17 hours is hard to tell, but as Kim's dismembered body began to surface, alongside the library of torture porn Madsen had on his computer, it was clear this twisted man had lived out his sordid sexual fantasy 20,000 leagues under the sea.</description></item><item><title>Episode 46 - Stephen Lawrence | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400347/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400347/</guid><description>Podcast Description The brutal, racially motivated murder of 18 year old Stephen Lawrence on the streets of South East London was a watershed moment in British history. It revealed the shocking institutional racism that lay at the heart of the London Metropolitan Police. In this week’s episode Hannah and Suruthi trace this difficult, but desperately important, story from the climate of race relations before Stephen’s murder, how this fed into a corrupt police investigation - and ask why 25 years later, justice has still not been done.</description></item><item><title>Episode 45 - The Virgin Killer &amp; The Angry World of the 'Incel' | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400348/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400348/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rage fuelled by violent misogyny; the defining trait of the ‘incel’, or so-called ‘involuntary celibate’. It's rage like this, coupled with psychopathy, that led to the recent Toronto attack and the Isla Vista Massacre in 2014. Join Hannah and Suruthi as they reveal what they discovered when they went creeping into the grimy depths of the ‘manosphere’ to understand this rage, the radicalisation and the ramifications of the hate group known as ‘incels’.</description></item><item><title>Episode 44 - Sex, Drugs &amp; Satanism: Miranda Barbour | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400349/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400349/</guid><description>Podcast Description A man is found stabbed to death in a small Pennsylvanian town and unbelievably a young, local couple were arrested and charged with his murder. Despite there being no clear motive it seemed an open and shut case, until the 19 year old woman confessed to being a demonically possessed, satanic serial killer - who had already killed 22 people...
Vote for us in the British Podcast Awards here:</description></item><item><title>Episode 43 - The 'Swedish Case' | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400350/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400350/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1989, Swedish backpackers Heidi Paakkonen and her fiancé Urban Hoglin disappeared into the bush on the Coromandel Peninsula in NZ.
A local man, David Tamihere, was convicted of their murders - and it seemed like it was case closed, until they found Urban's body that is...
Because the story his remains told was very different to the one which sent Tamihere away.
What really happened to Heidi and Urban?</description></item><item><title>Episode 42 - Murder or Suicide: The Mysterious Death of Rebecca Zahau | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400351/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400351/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rebecca Zahau’s naked body was found hanging in the mansion she shared with her millionaire boyfriend Jonah Shacknai and his son, Max. Just days before Rebecca's apparent suicide she had been babysitting Max when he was fatally injured - had Rebecca taken her own life out of guilt? The evidence suggests otherwise...
Audio mastered by Conrad Hughes
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Episode 41 - How Not to Fake Your Death: John Darwin - Canoe Man | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400352/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400352/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dying is easy, coming back is hard.
In 2002 John Darwin took his red, handmade canoe out to sea and disappeared. He was eventually declared dead, but 5 years later in 2007 he walked into a police station claiming to have no memory of the past half decade. How had John Darwin vanished? And why had he come back?
Audio mastered by Conrad Hughes
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description></item><item><title>Episode 40 - How Larry David Saved a Man From Death Row | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400353/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400353/</guid><description>Podcast Description What would you do if you were arrested for a crime you didn't commit? What would you say if the police told you they had definitive proof it was you?
When 16 year old Martha Puebla was shot dead, Juan Catalan faced this exact nightmare situation - and his life seemed doomed - until he was saved in the most unexpected way...
Audio mastered by Conrad Hughes. See acast.</description></item><item><title>Episode 39 - A Killer in the Family: The Murder of Becky Watts | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400354/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400354/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2015, when shy 16 year old Becky Watts suddenly went missing no one could believe it. But tragically within days her dismembered body was found just a mile from her home. As the true motivations behind the murder were revealed it quickly became clear that someone in the family knew more than they were letting on...
Audio Mastered by Conrad Hughes See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description></item><item><title>Episode 38 - Phil Spector &amp; Lana Clarkson: Murder &amp; Music Production | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400355/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400355/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Los Angeles celebrity justice system comes under scrutiny this week. Convicted murderer and one time music producer Phil Spector sits in a Californian prison medical centre, actor Lana Clarkson is dead and River Deep Mountain High is regrettably still a banger. Audio mastered and Hannah's editing tantrum patiently endured by Conrad Hughes. See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Episode 37 - Where is Sabrina Aisenberg? | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400356/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400356/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a frantic 911 call on the 24th of November 1997 Marlene Aisenberg reported her 5 month old baby, Sabrina, missing. The FBI launched a nationwide search and the media relentlessly covered the story.
But soon the parents’ odd behaviour left onlookers wondering what they really knew about their daughter’s disappearance...
Audio mastered by Conrad Hughes
48 Hours Mystery - Where's Our Baby? - Dateline NBC
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description></item><item><title>Episode 36 - Richard Chase: The Vampire of Sacramento Part 2 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400357/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2018 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400357/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s episode Hannah and Suruthi follow a spiraling, unmedicated and (literally) bloodthirsty Richard Chase as he dives into a brutal killing spree. With suburban home invasions, bloody eviscerations, necrophilia and vampiric lore made real, this is truly a disturbing and haunting finale. See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 35 - Richard Chase: The Vampire of Sacramento Part 1 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400358/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 08:39:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400358/</guid><description>Podcast Description Clinical vampirism, terrifying delusions and paranoid schizophrenia. This week the girls enter the bloody world of their very first truly psychotic spree killer, Richard Trenton Chase. Join them as they follow his evolution from cat-murdering child, to drug-addicted teen, to blood-smeared twenty-something; unpicking the unbelievably shocking story of one of America’s bloodiest killers.
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Episode 34 - The Most Dangerous Prisoner in Britain | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400359/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 08:03:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400359/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a Perspex box, in Wakefield maximum security prison sits alleged cannibal, confirmed killer and rumoured inspiration behind "Hannibal" - Robert Maudsely. Named the most dangerous prisoner in Britain, after 39 years in solitary, Maudsely now also holds the record for the longest time served in soltiary confinement in the world. Join the girls this week as they get knee-deep in prison politics and the reality of managing a man like Robert Maudsley.</description></item><item><title>Episode 33 - Oscar Pistorius &amp; Reeva Steenkamp: The Valentine's Day Murder | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400360/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 08:24:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400360/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the early hours of Valentine's Day 2014, 29 year old model Reeva Steenkamp was shot to death by her partner; South African Olympic sprint runner and double amputee, Oscar Pistorius. He still claims that it was a tragic case of mistaken identity, but the forensics and the messages Reeva left before her death tell a very different story.
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Episode 32 - The Brit on Death Row: Linda Carty | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400361/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 08:24:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400361/</guid><description>Podcast Description Starting on Trafalgar Square’s fourth plinth and ending up in Texas via the Caribbean, Suruthi &amp;amp; Hannah unpick how a British grandmother and DEA informant ended up on death row. Many campaign for Linda Carty’s release, but is she as innocent as they would have you believe?
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 31 - The Lady Killer and the Human Pelt | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400362/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 13:30:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400362/</guid><description>Podcast Description Toxic masculinity, Borderline Personality Disorder and a whole lot of abattoirs. We're off to Australia this week to unravel why Australian big hitter Katherine Knight skinned John Price and hung him up like a pair of curtains. See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 30 - The Chucky Doll Killer | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400363/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 08:24:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400363/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week the girls explore the phenomenon of ‘amphetamine induced psychosis’ in one of most violent cases they’ve ever covered. Join them as they follow the brutal torture and murder of 16 year old Suzanne Capper by the manipulative ‘Chucky Doll Killer’ - Bernadette McNeilly - a woman later described as ‘the most evil inmate’ on a prison wing she shared with notorious child killers Rose West and Myra Hindley.</description></item><item><title>Episode 29 - The Cult with No Name | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400364/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 08:27:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400364/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week it's cults and the girls follow the Pied Piper of Death to Matamoros Mexico to explore the ‘the cult with no name’(sometimes dubbed by the press as ‘The Narcosatanistas’ or ‘The Believers’).
This cult was led by Palo Mayombe priest, ‘El Padrino’ and consisted of a dedicated group of disciples who believed that rites of human sacrifice made them untouchable - but this very belief is what finally led police to uncover the truth about what lay out at Ranch Santa Elena.</description></item><item><title>Episode 28 - The Wests &amp; The Cellar at Number 25 Cromwell Street - Part 2 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400365/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2018 08:35:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400365/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week the girls head into the infamous torture cellar at 25 Cromwell St. to uncover the horrifying truth about the Wests’ years of depravity. As body after body was found, a haunted Fred confessed to it all - but Rose stayed silent. Today hear the incredible survivor testimony that broke a nation’s heart and finally labelled Rosemary West as one of the most evil female serial killers in history.</description></item><item><title>Episode 27 - The Wests &amp; the Cellar at Number 25 Cromwell Street - Part 1 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400366/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2018 08:24:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400366/</guid><description>Podcast Description Incest, rape, murder and torture dungeons; in a harrowing part 1 the girls take on one of Britain's most notorious serial killer couples - Fred and Rose West.
Over a span of 25 years this pair of sexual sadists carried out unspeakable evil in their cellar at the now infamous 25 Cromwell St, and when the truth was finally revealed it shocked the world.
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description></item><item><title>Episode 26 - Madness, Murder &amp; Munchausen by Proxy: The Case of Gypsy Rose Blancharde | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400367/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 09:27:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400367/</guid><description>Podcast Description Things aren't always what they seem...
To the world Dee Dee Blancharde was the perfect mum. She dedicated her life as a single mother to taking care of her incredibly ill and disabled child. But one night Dee Dee was brutally murdered, and what was revealed shocked the world. It turned out that her daughter Gypsy had never been sick at all.
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description></item><item><title>Episode 25 - The Grindr Killer | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400368/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 08:33:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400368/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join the girls today as they delve into the murky world of London’s most recent serial killer, the Grindr Killer - Stephen Port. They’ll pull apart this bizarre case of GHB poisoning, catfishing galore, the world’s most fake suicide note and utterly sh*t body disposal, to ask the very serious question of how Port’s crimes were missed
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Episode 24 - Murder in the Alps | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400369/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 08:22:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400369/</guid><description>Podcast Description On a remote mountain road, high in the Alps, a French cyclist and a British Iraqi family face an ambush blitz attack. Within a minute four people are dead.
But who was the real target of this execution? What was the true motive in this senseless slaughter?
What secrets lay beneath the seemingly ordinary facades of those killed? Join the girls today as they delve into this bizarre mystery - crisscrossing between international espionage and dark family secrets.</description></item><item><title>Episode 23 - The Girl in the Box: Colleen Stan | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400370/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 08:26:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400370/</guid><description>Podcast Description 20 year old Colleen Stan was abducted in 1977, she wouldn't be free for 7 years and what happened to her in between is unimaginable. If you needed another reason to stop hitchhiking, this is it. See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 22 - How Ancestry.com Solved a 32 Year Old Cold Case | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400371/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 08:18:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400371/</guid><description>Podcast Description Abandoned at age five, Lisa never knew where she came from. It was her quest to uncover her birth parents via sites like ancestry.com that unraveled a chilling quadruple homicide that had been left unsolved for 32 years. Be careful who you send your DNA to.
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 21 - What Killed Zigmund Adamski? | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400372/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 08:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400372/</guid><description>Podcast Description One day Zigmund Adamski mysteriously disappeared, and if his family thought that this was strange - nothing would prepare them for what was to come.
Because five days later Zigmund was found dead at the top of 12ft coal pile in a locked up coal-yard, and still that was just the beginning of the bizarre events that played out in the summer of 1980 in Yorkshire, England…
Who, or what killed, Zigmund Adamski?</description></item><item><title>Episode 20 - Halloween Special Part 2 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400373/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2017 08:17:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400373/</guid><description>Podcast Description Halloween continues at RedHanded this week as the girls plan to traumatise themselves, each other and you with tales of a blackout home invasion and a satanic cannibal cult. So, keep the spirit of Halloween alive and listen now, if you're ready for round 2 that is...
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 19 - Halloween Special Part 1 | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400374/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 07:51:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400374/</guid><description>Podcast Description For Halloween, the girls bring you the most disturbing cases they could find for their very own treehouse of horror, filled with kiddnapping, a Buffallo Bill copy cat and shivers for days. Get cosy and grab the dog as Hannah &amp;amp; Suruthi take you through 2 harrowing cases, told to each other for the first time. See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Episode 18 - The Love Triangle Killing | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400375/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 07:05:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400375/</guid><description>Podcast Description What happens when a stranger turns up at your front door and hands you a bouquet of petrol station flowers?
Broken hearts, English countryside and an electric blue Renault Clio set the scene for today's episode as Suruthi and Hannah unpick the tragic death of super sucessful business woman Sadie Hartley. See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Episode 17 - Who Killed Billie-Jo Jenkins? | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400376/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 19:07:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400376/</guid><description>Podcast Description One afternoon 13 year old Billie-Jo Jenkins was bludgeoned to death with an 18 inch tent spike whilst doing chores “home alone”. Suspicion immediately grew around her foster father Sion Jenkins - but 3 trials and 20 years later he is a free man. Did Sion Jenkins really murder Billie? And if so, then why? Join the girls this episode as they explore the truth behind the disturbing murder of Billie-Jo Jenkins.</description></item><item><title>Episode 16 - The Drag Queen &amp; Her Costume Cupboard Corpse | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400377/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2017 12:14:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400377/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dorian Corey, drag queen superstar, was the queen of queens in life - but when she died, a bizarre and horrifying mystery was revealed.
What her friends found hidden in the back of her costume cupboard, zipped up in a dress bag, shocked the world.
We still don't know exactly what happened, but join the girls this episode as they try unravel this confusing case.
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description></item><item><title>Episode 15 - The Spy in the Bag | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400378/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2017 09:33:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400378/</guid><description>Podcast Description In August 2010, 31 year old MI6 cryptologist Gareth Williams was found dead, in his flat, in his bath, padlocked inside a bag.
Pretty much zero forensics would be found, and the case still remains unsolved to this day.Was Gareth murdered? If so, then who by? And why?
And is it likely that a spook could be murdered in his home, just yards from MI6 HQ, and they can't find who did it?</description></item><item><title>Episode 14 - The Three Trials of Timothy Hennis | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400379/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2017 16:11:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400379/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's 1985 in North Carolina and a crying baby is found alone in her home surrounded by the dead bodies of her family. With only one clear suspect in this brutal massacre, the police bring in Staff Sergeant Timothy Hennis. But do they have enough? This is the story of an unprecedented side stepping of double jeopardy...
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Episode 13 - Serial Killer Survivor to YouTube Star | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400380/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 00:26:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400380/</guid><description>Podcast Description Stranded on the side of a Californian desert with no way home, would you refuse a lift from a stranger?
This is how our case this week begins as we explore the story of Jennifer Asbenson, a woman who escaped violent rapist and serial killer - Andrew Urdiales
Join us as we detail her escape, his atrocities and the bizarre fame Asbenson has cultivated since her ordeal.
See acast.</description></item><item><title>Episode 12 - The Dexter Copycat Killer | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400381/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 18:24:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400381/</guid><description>Podcast Description Exasperation station this episode as Suruthi &amp;amp; Hannah take you through the crimes of aspiring horror filmmaker, The Edmonton Killer and the cracking police work that stopped him in his tracks. Incapable of a single original idea in addition to a desperate need for fame, Mark Twitchell impersonated TV show character Dexter Morgan online and took on his dark passenger.
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Episode 11 - The Butcher Baker of Alaska | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400382/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2017 21:21:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400382/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we explore one of the most nightmarish cases we’ve covered. Robert Hansen aka The Butcher Baker of Alaska, was a small town family man, quiet and unassuming - but beneath the surface a monster was lurking. He would abduct women off the streets, take them to his secluded cabin, rape them, strip them naked and set them free in the surrounding woods - so that he could fulfil his second passion - and hunt them like game…</description></item><item><title>Episode 10 - The Oklahoma Girl Scout Murders | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400383/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 07:08:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400383/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the summer of 1977 on the very first night at Camp Scott, the tents shook against a raging thunderstorm as a dark and sinister presence stalked the woods. By morning 3 young girls would be dead; molested and murdered in the middle of the night.
40 years later this brutal crime still remains unsolved - what really happened to the murdered Oklahoma Girl Scouts?
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description></item><item><title>Episode 9 - The Beast with a Human Face | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400384/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 05:37:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400384/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2002, missing hostess, Lucie Blackman was found dead. Her body had been dismembered and her head encased in concrete. She was found buried in a shallow grave under a bathtub in a cave on a secluded beach in Miura, Kanagawa - just South of Tokyo.
Where this discovery would lead Japanese police shocked the world.
Join us this week as we follow this disturbing case to understand the evil that stole Lucie, and ask how many victims truly fell prey to ‘The Beast with a Human Face’.</description></item><item><title>Episode 8 - The Honeymoon Murder | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400385/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 04:39:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400385/</guid><description>Podcast Description What happened on their honeymoon that left Anni Dewani dead (in one of Cape Town's most notorious townships) and her husband of just 2 weeks, Shrien Dewani under suspicion of her murder?
Join us as we tread the twisted timeline of a bizarre honeymoon murder this week - and ask if it really was the husband...
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Episode 7 - The Lake Bodom Murders | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400386/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 07:17:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400386/</guid><description>Podcast Description Four teenagers go camping on the shores of Lake Bodom in Finland. Three are brutally murdered and one survives. Then three confessions, two suicides and a high-profile trial 44 years later - the case still remains unsolved. So today we explore who murdered the Bodom Three? And why? If you think you know this one, think again.
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.</description></item><item><title>Episode 6 - The White House Farm Massacre | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400387/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 07:14:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400387/</guid><description>Podcast Description A secluded farmhouse, religious mania, psychosis and a total bloodbath. Today we attempt to untangle one of the most notorious cases in British history. When five members of the Bamber family were slaughtered in one bloody night - what really happened?
What does the evidence say and why does so much of it seem totally contradictory? We examine the old evidence, the new evidence and even poke around the ‘missing’ evidence to ask if justice has really been served.</description></item><item><title>Episode 5 - Bible John | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400388/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 21:58:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400388/</guid><description>Podcast Description A real mystery for you, as we head to Scotland for the case of Bible John, an unknown serial killer who raped and murdered 3 women between 1968-1969. Apart from their physical similarities and the MO there was one alarming point to note, all the women were menstruating on the nights they were attacked. How did he know? What did it have to do with anything? And crucially, who was he?</description></item><item><title>Episode 4 - The Enfield Poltergeist - What Really Happened? | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400389/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 06:53:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400389/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we dip our eager feet into the paranormal with this puzzling case that left the police, occult experts and an entire nation transfixed and terrified. With so much evidence of ghostly goings on, from demonic voices caught on tape, possessed children screaming and barking to flying furniture scaring police and reporters, what was really happening to 11 year old Janet Hodgson?
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.</description></item><item><title>Minisode 1 - Grisly Deaths from the Violin Cupboard | RedHanded</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8058400390/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 18:53:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8058400390/</guid><description>Podcast Description What happened one Sunday afternoon when the girls try out a makeshift "studio" and end up locked in a 1x0.5m cupboard. How do they escape? What were they thinking? And most importantly, did the sound quality improve?
See acast.com/privacy for privacy and opt-out information.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>