<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/the-subtle-art-of-not-giving-a-fck-podcast/</link><description>Recent content in The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 17:26:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/the-subtle-art-of-not-giving-a-fck-podcast/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>7 Paradoxes That Will Change How You See Everything | The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3366430012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 17:26:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3366430012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Some of the most important truths in life are found in paradoxes. Paradoxes seem like opposites on the surface, but once you look deeper beneath what are seeming contradictions, there are real grains of wisdom that emerge.
In this episode, I cover some of the most life-changing paradoxes I’ve ever come across, and discuss how they can improve how you approach your life.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to Give Up Everything to Save Yourself (ft. Matt from Yes Theory) | The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3366430011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 05:47:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3366430011/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2021, Matt from Yes Theory, one of YouTube's biggest channels, revealed he was quitting the platform.
Despite being an internet celebrity, Matt&amp;rsquo;s story is a common one—about someone who gave away too much of themselves to be liked by others, and now desperately trying to get themselves back. In this episode, Matt and I unpack this familiar dilemma, as well as covering topics like codependence, managing success, dealing with parasocial relationships, determining when vulnerability goes too far, and much more.</description></item><item><title>How to Give Up Everything and Save Yourself (ft. Matt from Yes Theory) | The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3366430010/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3366430010/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2021, Matt from Yes Theory, one of YouTube's biggest channels, revealed he was quitting the platform.
Despite being an internet celebrity, Matt&amp;rsquo;s story is a common one—about someone who gave away too much of themselves to be liked by others, and now desperately trying to get themselves back. In this episode, Matt and I unpack this familiar dilemma, as well as covering topics like codependence, managing success, dealing with parasocial relationships, determining when vulnerability goes too far, and much more.</description></item><item><title>7 Life Lessons I Wish I Knew Sooner | The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3366430009/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 23:01:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3366430009/</guid><description>Podcast Description A comprehensive list of lessons you shouldn’t wait too long to learn.
In this episode, I’m sharing 7 important lessons I learned far too late in life. I’m doing this so that you don’t have to live through as many clusterfucks as I did to find a bit of peace in life.
Some of these lessons you may already know, some may surprise you. But they’re all guaranteed to help you live a better life.</description></item><item><title>7 Life Lessons I Wish I Knew Sooner | The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3366430008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3366430008/</guid><description>Podcast Description A comprehensive list of lessons you shouldn’t wait too long to learn.
In this episode, I’m sharing 7 important lessons I learned far too late in life. I’m doing this so that you don’t have to live through as many clusterfucks as I did to find a bit of peace in life.
Some of these lessons you may already know, some may surprise you. But they’re all guaranteed to help you live a better life.</description></item><item><title>Is Technology Ruining Our Minds? (ft. Scott Barry Kaufman, PhD) | The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3366430007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 23:50:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3366430007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do I exist if I’m not on social media? Can I fake it till I make it? What’s the secret to a good life?
In this week’s episode, I enlist my old friend and host of the wildly popular The Psychology Podcast, Scott Barry Kaufman, PhD. to dissect our psyche in the social media age.
Reflecting on his personal experience and drawing on a wealth of psychological research, Scott asks—and answers—questions that might reveal aspects of yourself you never knew were there, and set you on the path to a better life.</description></item><item><title>How to Know When to End a Relationship | The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3366430005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3366430005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Make up or break up? Knowing when to call it quits.
If you’ve ever been through a rough patch, you know this is a painful question to answer. Do you stick it out? Do you cut the cord and run? Do you sacrifice more to make it work? Do you demand your partner give up everything and run away to Fiji and live happily ever after?
These are the hard questions we answer in this episode.</description></item><item><title>What Nobody Tells You About Getting Rich (ft. Morgan Housel) | The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3366430004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3366430004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Everybody wants to get rich. But is the pursuit of wealth really about the money, or are we actually chasing something much deeper?
These are just a couple of the fun ideas I toss around in this episode with Morgan Housel, New York Times Bestselling author of the smash hit, The Psychology of Money, which has sold more than four million copies worldwide.
We’ll dig deep to uncover our relationship with money, answer the timeless question “Will getting rich make me happy?</description></item><item><title>5 Harsh Truths That Will Change Your Life | The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3366430001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3366430001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why is it that the most important truths in life are also the most painful to hear?
In this episode, I discuss five of the most uncomfortable truths that have changed my life and will likely change yours—from human suckage to the cheeriest truth of all… death.
So put your safety harness on, the ride’s about to get bumpy…
Transcript</description></item><item><title>How to Reprogram Your Brain for Success (ft. Derek Sivers) | The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3366430002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3366430002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you your own worst enemy? Ever think that your life would be so much easier if you could just change your mind about a couple things? Yeah, me too.
In this inaugural episode, I am joined by my old friend Derek Sivers, the one person I know who is better at questioning beliefs and changing his mind than just about anyone… and a bona fide grandmaster at not giving a fuck.</description></item><item><title>Trailer: The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck Podcast | The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3366430003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 14:07:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3366430003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mark talks about the new pod.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>