<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Leading on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/leading/</link><description>Recent content in Leading on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:10:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/leading/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>51. Tim Peake: Will humans colonise Mars? | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280053/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280053/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is the future of human space exploration? Will people live on Mars in our life time? Are there plans to grow human organs on the moon?
British astronaut Tim Peake joins Rory and Alastair to discuss everything from his time in the army, to the geopolitics of space exploration, to the future of colonising other planets.
TRIP Plus: Become a member of The Rest Is Politics Plus to support the podcast, receive our exclusive newsletter, enjoy ad-free listening to both TRIP and Leading, benefit from discount book prices on titles mentioned on the pod, join our Discord chatroom, and receive early access to live show tickets and Question Time episodes.</description></item><item><title>50. Angela Rayner: From zero GCSEs to Britain’s most powerful woman? | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 00:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Could Labour still lose the next election? What really went wrong under Jeremy Corbyn? What do the left actually think of the right? Rory and Alastair are joined by Labour&amp;rsquo;s Deputy Leader, Angela Rayner, to discuss all this and more on today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Leading.
TRIP Plus: Become a member of The Rest Is Politics Plus to support the podcast, receive our exclusive newsletter, enjoy ad-free listening to both TRIP and Leading, benefit from discount book prices on titles mentioned on the pod, join our Discord chatroom, and receive early access to live show tickets and Question Time episodes.</description></item><item><title>49. Christiana Figueres: COP28, Costa Rica, and surviving the climate crisis | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 00:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280002/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do countries cooperate to tackle the climate emergency? Is it unusual for the United Nations Climate Change Conference to be held in the oil rich UAE? What does the future hold for renewable energies and reducing carbon emissions?
Rory and Alastair are joined by Costa Rican diplomat Christiana Figueres to discuss COP28, The Paris Agreement, what it was like growing up in a political family in Costa Rica, and how to balance working in public service and with positive mental health.</description></item><item><title>48. Simon Sebag Montefiore: The impact of conflicting histories in the Israel-Hamas and Russia-Ukraine wars | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is understanding history a means to peace between Israel and Palestine? Has Putin’s obsession with Russia’s imperial history motivated his invasion of Ukraine? Is it possible to dismantle Hamas under Netanyahu’s leadership? Rory and Alastair are joined by British historian Simon Sebag Montefiore to answer these questions and more in today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Leading.
TRIP Plus: Become a member of The Rest Is Politics Plus to support the podcast, receive our exclusive newsletter, enjoy ad-free listening to both TRIP and Leading, benefit from discount book prices on titles mentioned on the pod, join our Discord chatroom, and receive early access to live show tickets and Question Time episodes.</description></item><item><title>47. Tony Klug: Could the Israel-Hamas conflict restart the peace process? | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280004/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 00:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is peace possible in the Middle East? What is the difference between a one-state solution and a two-state solution? What is the role of the international community in resolving the conflict between Israel-Hamas?
Rory and Alastair are joined by Tony Klug, leading expert on the two-state solution and conflicts in the Middle East in today&amp;rsquo;s bonus episode.
TRIP Plus: Become a member of The Rest Is Politics Plus to support the podcast, receive our exclusive newsletter, enjoy ad-free listening to both TRIP and Leading, benefit from discount book prices on titles mentioned on the pod, join our Discord chatroom, and receive early access to live show tickets and Question Time episodes.</description></item><item><title>46. Arancha González Laya: The World’s Most Powerful Organisations | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are increased military budgets needed following on from Russia&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Ukraine? Will Europe take the same approach to regulating AI as China and the US? What is it like being a woman in front-bench politics?
Rory and Alastair are joined by former Minister of Foreign Affairs in Spain and the Dean of the School of International Affairs at Sciences Po in Paris to discuss all this and more in today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Leading.</description></item><item><title>Introducing... Legacy | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Everyone leaves a legacy. In their new podcast series, produced by Goalhanger &amp;amp; Wondery, Afua Hirsch and Peter Frankopan tell the wild stories of some of the most extraordinary men and women ever to have lived – and ask whether they have the reputation they deserve.
Search Legacy now, wherever you get your podcasts, or binge the entire season ad-free on Amazon Music. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>45. Dr Comfort Ero: Resolving deadly conflicts &amp; reforming the UN | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280007/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 00:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280007/</guid><description>Podcast Description How important is the role of the international community in resolving conflict? Is peace possible in the Middle East? How relevant is the United Nations today? Rory and Alastair are joined by CEO of the Crisis Group, Dr Comfort Ero, to discuss all this and more in today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Leading.
TRIP Plus: Become a member of The Rest Is Politics Plus to support the podcast, receive our exclusive newsletter, enjoy ad-free listening to both TRIP and Leading, benefit from discount book prices on titles mentioned on the pod, join our Discord chatroom, and receive early access to live show tickets and Question Time episodes.</description></item><item><title>44. Mark Carney: Bank of England, Trussonomics, and Brexit | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 00:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can financial markets help fight climate change? What&amp;rsquo;s the true economic theory behind austerity? What does the Bank of England actually do?
Tune in to today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Leading, where Mark Carney joins Rory and Alastair to answer all these questions and more.
TRIP Plus: Become a member of The Rest Is Politics Plus to support the podcast, receive our exclusive newsletter, enjoy ad-free listening to both TRIP and Leading, benefit from discount book prices on titles mentioned on the pod, join our Discord chatroom, and receive early access to live show tickets and Question Time episodes.</description></item><item><title>43. Arnold Schwarzenegger: Trump, Biden, and the American Dream | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280009/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 00:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280009/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do we fix the polarisation in the US? What made him move from Hollywood movies to the world of politics? Does he still identify as a Republican?
Rory and Alastair are joined by Arnold Schwarzenegger to discuss his childhood in Austria, coming to the US, marrying into the Kennedy family, and how he feels about politics today.
TRIP Plus: Become a member of The Rest Is Politics Plus to support the podcast, receive our exclusive newsletter, enjoy ad-free listening to both TRIP and Leading, benefit from discount book prices on titles mentioned on the pod, join our Discord chatroom, and receive early access to live show tickets and Question Time episodes.</description></item><item><title>42. Sayeeda Warsi: Britain and the Muslim World | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280010/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 23:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280010/</guid><description>Podcast Description How prevalent is islamophobia in the UK? How can we help Jewish and Muslim communities at this time? Why have the Oslo Accords failed?
Rory and Alastair are joined by the first Muslim woman Chair of the Conservative Party, Baroness Sayeeda Warsi, to discuss her politics, life growing up in an immigrant family in Northern England, the ongoing conflict in the Middle East, and much more.
TRIP Plus: Become a member of The Rest Is Politics Plus to support the podcast, receive our exclusive newsletter, enjoy ad-free listening to both TRIP and Leading, benefit from discount book prices on titles mentioned on the pod, join our Discord chatroom, and receive early access to live show tickets and Question Time episodes.</description></item><item><title>41. Reid Hoffman: Bankrolling Biden to beat Trump, the "PayPal Mafia", and Musk's messiah complex | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280011/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 23:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280011/</guid><description>Podcast Description How does life in Silicon Valley compare to the United Kingdom? What was it like working with Elon Musk and Peter Thiel starting PayPal? Is the future of AI as bleak as it seems? Rory and Alastair are joined by tech entrepreneur, author, and fellow podcaster Reid Hoffman to discuss everything from the dangers of AI during an election to the benefits of friendships.
TRIP Plus: Become a member of The Rest Is Politics Plus to support the podcast, receive our exclusive newsletter, enjoy ad-free listening to both TRIP and Leading, benefit from discount book prices on titles mentioned on the pod, join our Discord chatroom, and receive early access to live show tickets and Question Time episodes.</description></item><item><title>40. Minette Batters: The Most Powerful Farmer in Britain | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280012/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 23:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280012/</guid><description>Podcast Description 70% of British land is agricultural - yet we don&amp;rsquo;t speak about farming much. What is the politics of the UK&amp;rsquo;s farming industry? How has Brexit affected British produce and trade? And what is it like to represent British farmers interests to a revolving door of politicians in government? To answer these questions and more is the first woman leader of the National Farmers Union, Minette Batters.
TRIP Plus: Become a member of The Rest Is Politics Plus to support the podcast, receive our exclusive newsletter, enjoy ad-free listening to both TRIP and Leading, benefit from discount book prices on titles mentioned on the pod, join our Discord chatroom, and receive early access to live show tickets and Question Time episodes.</description></item><item><title>39. Theresa May: Donald Trump, David Cameron, and ‘Brexit means Brexit’ (Part 2) | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280013/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 23:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why did Theresa May prefer Gordon Brown to Tony Blair as a Prime Minister? Does the former PM have any regrets over Brexit? How did things unfold behind the scenes after the Salisbury poisoning of a former Russian spy?
In the second of two episodes, Rory and Alastair are joined once again by former Conservative Prime Minister, Theresa May.
Instagram: @restispolitics Twitter: @RestIsPolitics Email: restispolitics@gmail.com
Producers: Dom Johnson + Nicole Maslen Exec Producers: Tony Pastor + Jack Davenport Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>38. Theresa May: Windrush, police, and the cult of personality (Part 1) | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280014/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 23:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280014/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is Theresa May’s biggest regret from her time as Home Secretary? Why was the Hillsborough disaster such an abuse of power? What’s it like to stay on as an MP after occupying the highest office in the land?
On today’s episode of Leading, Rory and Alastair are joined by former Conservative Prime Minister, Theresa May.
Want to hear next Monday’s episode - “Theresa May: Donald Trump, David Cameron, and ‘Brexit means Brexit’ (Part 2)&amp;rsquo; - right now?</description></item><item><title>37. Chris Hipkins, New Zealand PM: Working with Xi Jinping, fighting to stay in power, and zero covid's double-edged sword | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280015/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 23:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280015/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is it like going from cabinet minister to Prime Minister? Are politicians in New Zealand more courteous than politicians in the UK? Why was New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s Covid-19 response so effective?
From the middle of his campaign trail for re-election, New Zealand&amp;rsquo;s Prime Minister Chris Hipkins is here to discuss all these questions and more with Rory and Alastair in this week&amp;rsquo;s Leading.
TRIP Plus: Become a member of The Rest Is Politics Plus to support the podcast, enjoy ad-free listening to both TRIP and Leading, benefit from discount book prices on titles mentioned on the pod, join our Discord chatroom, and receive early access to live show tickets and Question Time episodes.</description></item><item><title>36. Andy Burnham and Andy Street: A Tale of Two Cities | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280016/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 23:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280016/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is it like to run a metropolitan area? How does devolution impact the citizens of regional areas? Does party affiliation affect the decisions a mayor makes? Andy Burnham, Labour Mayor of Greater Manchester, and Andy Street, Conservative Mayor of the West Midlands, meet with Rory and Alastair to discuss their two cities, their contrasting politics, and working towards their shared goal of further devolved powers for city regions.</description></item><item><title>35. Cathy Ashton: Dealing with Putin and Lavrov, Kosovo–Serbia, and 'radical humility' | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280017/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 23:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280017/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do we retain empathy when negotiating with a stranger who has a radically different worldview to our own?
As the former High Representative of the Union for Foreign Affairs, Cathy Ashton worked with many world leaders: Vladimir Putin in Russia, Serbia&amp;rsquo;s Ivica Dacic, Kosovo&amp;rsquo;s Hashim Thaci, and Iran&amp;rsquo;s Foreign Minister Mohammad Javad Zarif.
Former Leader of the House of Lords, Cathy Ashton has also been nominated for the Nobel Peace Prize for her diplomacy.</description></item><item><title>34. Ed Davey: Leading the Lib Dems, fighting the Tories, and a coalition with Starmer’s Labour? | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280018/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 23:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280018/</guid><description>Podcast Description What was it like for the Liberal Democrats in coalition? Would Ed Davey be prepared to work alongside Keir Starmer in another coalition government? Is tactical voting a good idea? Join Rory and Alastair as they speak with leader of the Liberal Democrats, Ed Davey, to discuss all these questions and more.
TRIP Plus: Become a member of The Rest Is Politics Plus to support the podcast, enjoy ad-free listening to both TRIP and Leading, benefit from discount book prices on titles mentioned on the pod, join our Discord chatroom, and receive early access to live show tickets and Question Time episodes.</description></item><item><title>33. Mustafa Suleyman: Will AI save or destroy humanity? | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280019/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 23:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280019/</guid><description>Podcast Description How much do you really know about the dangers of AI? Is it the best hope we have of surviving as a species, or will it lead to the destruction of humanity?
On today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Leading Alastair and Rory are joined by Mustafa Suleyman as he recounts his rise from North London council estate to the vanguard of the tech revolution.
TRIP Plus: Become a member of The Rest Is Politics Plus to support the podcast, receive our exclusive newsletter, enjoy ad-free listening to both TRIP and Leading, benefit from discount book prices on titles mentioned on the pod, join our Discord chatroom, and receive early access to live show tickets and Question Time episodes.</description></item><item><title>32. Miriam González Durántez: Navigating Silicon Valley, the Cameron-Clegg years, and the fight for gender equality | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280020/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 23:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280020/</guid><description>Podcast Description How can we empower young women to seek positions of power? What was it like having a ringside seat during the Cameron-Clegg government? Is there more inequality between the sexes in the UK, Spain, or California?
Leading international trade lawyer and vice chair of UBS Europe, Miriam González Durántez, speaks to Alastair and Rory about growing up in post-Franco Spain, the state of Spanish politics, how Brexit has changed the UK&amp;rsquo;s international &amp;lsquo;clout&amp;rsquo;, and her experiences with David Cameron and George Osborne as Deputy Prime Minister Nick Clegg&amp;rsquo;s wife.</description></item><item><title>31: Yuval Noah Harari: The dangers of AI and the future of humanity (Part 2) | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280021/</guid><description>Podcast Description What makes homo sapiens unique from other living creatures? What will happen to society if artificial intelligence dictates culture? Why have conservative parties the world over “committed suicide”? Join Rory and Alastair for the second part of their discussion with historian and intellectual Yuval Noah Harari. TRIP Plus: Become a member of The Rest Is Politics Plus to support the podcast, enjoy ad-free listening to both TRIP and Leading, benefit from discount book prices on titles mentioned on the pod, join our Discord chatroom, and receive early access to live show tickets and Question Time episodes.</description></item><item><title>30: Anthony Joshua: Responding to failure, Saudi Arabia, and Tyson Fury | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280022/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 23:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280022/</guid><description>Podcast Description From raving and &amp;ldquo;wheeler-dealing&amp;rdquo; to heavyweight champion of the world, Anthony Joshua&amp;rsquo;s story is unmissable. Listen to Rory, Alastair and AJ talk about the culture of boxing, socialism, how imperative a positive mindset is to winning, and whether a highly anticipated fight with Tyson Fury will ever happen&amp;hellip;
Our second episode with Yuval Noah Harari will be released next Monday 14th August. If you can&amp;rsquo;t wait until then, it&amp;rsquo;s already available to members of TRIP Plus.</description></item><item><title>29: Yuval Noah Harari: Crisis and tragedy in Israel (Part 1) | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280023/</guid><description>Podcast Description ‘We are facing spiritual and moral destruction.’ Is Israeli democracy facing the most dangerous moment in its history? Yuval Noah Harari joins Rory and Alastair to discuss his first-hand experience of the protests against the government of Benjamin Netanyahu during this politically existential moment for the country.
Our second episode with Yuval will be released next Monday, where he talks about history, AI, and the future of humankind. If you can&amp;rsquo;t wait a week and want to listen right now, it&amp;rsquo;s already available to members of The Rest Is Politics Plus.</description></item><item><title>28: Paul Nurse: The power of genetics, battling politicians, and the fight against cancer | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280024/</guid><description>Podcast Description How close are we to finding a cure for cancer? What did the government do wrong - in scientific terms - during the pandemic? Do Labour or the Tories have a proper plan to harness the power of British science?
On today’s episode of Leading, Alastair and Rory are joined by Nobel Prize-winner Sir Paul Nurse to answer all these questions and more.
TRIP Plus: Become a member of The Rest Is Politics Plus to support the podcast, enjoy ad-free listening to both TRIP and Leading, benefit from discount book prices on titles mentioned on the pod, join our Discord chatroom, and receive early access to live show tickets and Question Time episodes.</description></item><item><title>27: Feargal Sharkey: Teenage Kicks, Bobby Sands, and saving our rivers | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 18:42:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can we reverse the damage done to our polluted rivers and seas? What was it like to write Teenage Kicks? How has Brexit hamstrung the music industry? From punk singer to political activist, Feargal Sharkey is now the leading figure in the fight against sewage and water pollution in the UK. On today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Leading he sits down with Alastair to discuss environmentalism, growing up in Derry, the success of The Undertones, and much, much more.</description></item><item><title>26: Francis Fukuyama: Trump, Modi, and ‘The End of History’ | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280026/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280026/</guid><description>Podcast Description What was the worst political mistake in modern history? How do religious Republicans bring themselves to support Trump? Was it wrong to describe the fall of the Soviet Union as ‘The End of History’?
On today’s episode of Leading, Alastair and Rory sit down with political scientist and writer Francis Fukuyama to answer all these questions, discuss why he coined the phrase ‘The End of History’, and argue whether authoritarian regimes are ‘destined’ to fail.</description></item><item><title>25: Michael Ignatieff: Fighting Orban's Global Conservative Cabal | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280027/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280027/</guid><description>Podcast Description What&amp;rsquo;s it like to know how your obituary will read? What makes the democratic system the best for fighting against climate change? How does politics change a person, whether they like it or not? Alastair and Rory sit down with politician, academic, and writer Michael Ignatieff on today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Leading to discuss all this and more.
TRIP Plus: Become a member of The Rest Is Politics Plus to support the podcast, enjoy ad-free listening to both TRIP and Leading, benefit from discount book prices on titles mentioned on the pod, join our Discord chatroom, and receive early access to live show tickets and Question Time episodes.</description></item><item><title>24: John Major: The Gulf War, Black Wednesday, and Populism (Part 2) | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280028/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280028/</guid><description>Podcast Description What was it like fighting New Labour? Why did Black Wednesday happen? How did Ian McKellen help bring the campaign for gay rights into Downing Street?
Join Alastair and Rory as they answer all these questions with Sir John Major in the second of two episodes with the former Tory prime minister.
TRIP Plus: Become a member of The Rest Is Politics Plus to support the podcast, enjoy ad-free listening to both TRIP and Leading, benefit from discount book prices on titles mentioned on the pod, join our Discord chatroom, and receive early access to live show tickets and Question Time episodes.</description></item><item><title>23: John Major: From Brixton to Downing Street (Part 1) | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280029/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why is Sir John Major a Tory? How did he make it from Brixton to 10 Downing Street? What was it like to witness the fall of Margaret Thatcher first hand?
In the first of two episodes, Rory and Alastair are joined by the former prime minister to answer all these questions and more.
John Major - Episode 2: If you&amp;rsquo;d like to hear episode two right now, sign up to The Rest is Politics Plus at therestispolitics.</description></item><item><title>22: Kate Raworth: Doughnut economics and thriving in balance | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280030/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280030/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the 21st century, the impact of financial and environmental crises can be felt by all. But how do we marry the nature of the economy with the ever depleting means of the planet? Rory and Alastair discuss the radical doughnut economic model with economist Kate Raworth to unpick how it could work politically, and how it is already helping cities to thrive in balance.
TRIP Plus: Become a member of The Rest Is Politics Plus to support the podcast, enjoy ad-free listening to both TRIP and Leading, benefit from discount book prices on titles mentioned on the pod, join our Discord chatroom, and receive early access to live show tickets and Question Time episodes.</description></item><item><title>21: Mary McAleese: Building bridges as the President of Ireland | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280031/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280031/</guid><description>Podcast Description For former President of Ireland Mary McAleese, the personal is the political. Growing up in Belfast with a deeply personal link to sectarian violence, her aim as President was to promote unity and build bridges between political, religious and cultural divides. Alastair speaks to her about misogyny in the Catholic Church, her role as a human rights lawyer, the violence of the Troubles, and much, much more.
TRIP Plus: Become a member of The Rest Is Politics Plus to support the podcast, enjoy ad-free listening to both TRIP and Leading, benefit from discount book prices on titles mentioned on the pod, join our Discord chatroom, and receive early access to live show tickets and Question Time episodes.</description></item><item><title>20: Jonathan Powell: How to negotiate with terrorists | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280032/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280032/</guid><description>Podcast Description The role of Downing Street Chief of Staff was created for him, and he was the only senior advisor to last the whole period of Tony Blair&amp;rsquo;s premiership - but who is the real Jonathan Powell, and how did he do it? Rory and Alastair are joined by Jonathan Powell to discuss the New Labour years, the Northern Ireland peace process, how he negotiates with terrorists, and more.</description></item><item><title>19: Leo Varadkar: Ireland's Taoiseach on NATO, China, and Joe Biden | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280033/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280033/</guid><description>Podcast Description How does the Irish Taoiseach feel about Brexit? Would Leo Varadkar consider himself a Tory in the English parliamentary system? Does Ireland have a problem with alcohol?
Leo Varadkar speaks to Rory and Alastair about all this, plus his childhood in Dublin, juggling social liberalism with economic conservatism, and the future of AI in healthcare.
Instagram: @restispolitics
Twitter: @RestIsPolitics
Email: restispolitics@gmail.com
Producers: Dom Johnson + Nicole Maslen Exec Producers: Tony Pastor + Jack Davenport</description></item><item><title>18: George Osborne: Austerity, Boris Johnson, and the UK's next Prime Minister | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280034/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Does George Osborne regret leaving politics? Does he think Sunak can win the next general election? What did he admire about New Labour, Tony Blair, and Gordon Brown?
Tune in to today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Leading to hear Alastair and Rory&amp;rsquo;s conversation with the former Chancellor of the Exchequer.
TRIP Plus: Become a member of The Rest Is Politics Plus to support the podcast, enjoy ad-free listening to both TRIP and Leading, benefit from discount book prices on titles mentioned on the pod, join our Discord chatroom, and receive early access to live show tickets and Question Time episodes.</description></item><item><title>17: Gerry Adams: The Troubles, Margaret Thatcher, and the IRA | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280035/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280035/</guid><description>Podcast Description How much do you know about Thatcher&amp;rsquo;s back channels with Irish republicans during the Troubles? What are Gerry Adams&amp;rsquo; emotions towards the 1984 Brighton hotel bombing, looking back now in 2023? Who were the most important people in the negotiations that brought peace to the island of Ireland?
Alastair and Rory sat down with the former Sinn Féin president to discuss all these questions and more in today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Leading.</description></item><item><title>16: Tony Blair: Taking insults, swallowing pride, and negotiating with both sides | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280036/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280036/</guid><description>Podcast Description How was peace achieved in Northern Ireland? What was it like speaking to the IRA, loyalist paramilitary groups and victims simultaneously? Who were the most important individuals involved in the peace process?
To mark the 25th anniversary of the Good Friday Agreement, Alastair and Rory are joined by former UK Prime Minister Tony Blair to answer all these questions and more.
Instagram: @restispolitics
Twitter: @RestIsPolitics
TRIP Plus: Become a member of The Rest Is Politics Plus to support the podcast, receive a weekly newsletter, enjoy ad-free listening to both TRIP and Leading, join our Discord chatroom, and receive early access to live show tickets and Question Time episodes.</description></item><item><title>15: Hillary Clinton: Fighting Putin, the Return of Trump, and the Killing of Osama Bin Laden | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280037/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Will Donald Trump return to the White House? What happened behind the scenes during the killing of Osama Bin Laden? How should we combat the insidious effect of technology and social media on the younger generation?
Alastair and Rory are joined by Hillary Rodham Clinton to discuss all this and more on today&amp;rsquo;s episode of Leading.
Instagram: @restispolitics
Twitter: @RestIsPolitics
TRIP Plus: Become a member of The Rest Is Politics Plus to support the podcast, receive a weekly newsletter, enjoy ad-free listening to both TRIP and Leading, join our Discord chatroom, and receive early access to live show tickets and Question Time episodes.</description></item><item><title>14: David Miliband: The Age of Impunity | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280038/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why did David Miliband leave British politics? How did he get involved in the New Labour project? And what does he spend his time doing now?
Join David as he talks to Rory and Alastair about Labour, international development, US politics, life in New York City, and the International Rescue Committee.
Instagram: @restispolitics
Twitter: @RestIsPolitics
TRIP Plus: Become a member of The Rest Is Politics Plus to support the podcast, receive a weekly newsletter, enjoy ad-free listening to both TRIP and Leading, join our Discord chatroom, and receive early access to live show tickets and Question Time episodes.</description></item><item><title>13: Brian Cox: Succession, socialism, and Scotland | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280039/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280039/</guid><description>Podcast Description What do the Murdochs think of Succession? Should the SNP change its name? Why do some actors swear by method acting while others find it such an alien approach?
Actor Brian Cox sits down with Alastair to answer these questions and talk Succession, Scotland and socialism&amp;hellip;
Instagram: @restispolitics
Twitter: @RestIsPolitics
TRIP Plus: Become a member of The Rest Is Politics Plus to support the podcast, receive a weekly newsletter, enjoy ad-free listening to both TRIP and Leading, join our Discord chatroom, and receive early access to live show tickets and Question Time episodes.</description></item><item><title>12: David Baddiel: God, Anti-Semitism and the Y-Word | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280040/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280040/</guid><description>Podcast Description How aware are you of anti-Semitism in Britain? Comedian and author David Baddiel tells Alastair and Rory about his family, his upbringing and his views on anti-Semitism in modern Britain.
Instagram: @restispolitics
Twitter: @RestIsPolitics
TRIP Plus: Become a member of The Rest Is Politics Plus to support the podcast, receive a weekly newsletter, enjoy ad-free listening to both TRIP and Leading, join our Discord chatroom, and receive early access to live show tickets and Question Time episodes.</description></item><item><title>11: Gary Lineker: Politics, football and the BBC | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280041/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gary Lineker is regularly told to &amp;lsquo;stick to football&amp;rsquo;. Now, after recently tweeting his views on the Government’s refugee policy, the Match Of The Day presenter sits down with Alastair and Rory to discuss his upbringing, life in the public eye, and what really happened after he was suspended (and later reinstated) in his role at the BBC.
Instagram: @restispolitics
Twitter: @RestIsPolitics
TRIP Plus: Become a member of The Rest Is Politics Plus to support the podcast, receive a weekly newsletter, enjoy ad-free listening to both TRIP and Leading, join our Discord chatroom, and receive early access to live show tickets and Question Time episodes.</description></item><item><title>10: Rahima Mahmut: The Uyghur Genocide | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280042/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280042/</guid><description>Podcast Description How much do you know about what&amp;rsquo;s happening to the Uyghurs in Xinjiang, China?
Alastair is joined by Rahima Mahmut, an Uyghur artist, activist, and the chair of &amp;lsquo;Stop Uyghur Genocide&amp;rsquo; to explore the harrowing topic in detail.
Instagram: @restispolitics
Twitter: @RestIsPolitics
TRIP Plus: Become a member of The Rest Is Politics Plus to support the podcast, receive a weekly newsletter, enjoy ad-free listening to both TRIP and Leading, join our Discord chatroom, and receive early access to live show tickets and Question Time episodes.</description></item><item><title>9: Bernie Sanders: A fight for equality | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280043/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Longest serving independent Senator of the United States Bernie Sanders has spent his life fighting for the rights of working people. Today, he joins Rory and Alastair to discuss income inequality, the two-party system and its limitations, healthcare reform and whether or not his success in debates against Hillary Clinton inadvertently played a part in Trump&amp;rsquo;s presidential victory&amp;hellip;
Buy Bernie Sanders&amp;rsquo; new book It&amp;rsquo;s OK To Be Angry About Capitalism here: coles-books.</description></item><item><title>8: Bertie Ahern: The Troubles, peace, and the future of Ireland | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280044/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280044/</guid><description>Podcast Description How did the violence of The Troubles come to an end on the island of Ireland?
Bertie Ahern, former Irish Taoiseach who served from 1997 to 2008, speaks to Alastair about his father&amp;rsquo;s time in the IRA, how Ireland has changed over the last three decades, and what it was liking working alongside Tony Blair, Bill Clinton, Martin McGuinness and Ian Paisley on the road the Belfast Good Friday Agreements.</description></item><item><title>7: Fiona Hill: Working with Trump and fighting against Putin | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280045/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280045/</guid><description>Podcast Description From a coal-miner&amp;rsquo;s daughter to the White House. Fiona Hill became a leading foreign policy advisor to three presidents, a United States National Security Council official, and a key witness in Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s 2019 impeachment hearings. In this fascinating interview for Leading, Hill talks about her upbringing in Bishop Auckland, the future of the Ukraine conflict, and what it was really like working under Trump…
Read There Is Nothing For You Here by Fiona Hill now: https://coles-books.</description></item><item><title>6: David Lammy: The Future of Foreign Policy | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280046/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is David Lammy the next politician to represent Britain on the global stage? Alastair and Rory speak to the Shadow Secretary of State for Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Affairs about his upbringing, the Department for International Development, the Labour Party, tribalism in politics, and the role of foreign policy for Britain today.
Instagram: @restispolitics
Twitter: @RestIsPolitics
TRIP Plus: Become a member of The Rest Is Politics Plus to support the podcast, receive a weekly newsletter, enjoy ad-free listening to both TRIP and Leading, join our Discord chatroom, and receive early access to live show tickets and Question Time episodes.</description></item><item><title>5: Michael Johnson: Politics, protest, and sport | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280047/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do athletes now have a responsibility to use their platform to promote political change?
Four-time Olympic gold medalist Michael Johnson sits down with Alastair to discuss the future of athletics, drugs in sport, political polarisation, and recovering from a stroke that doctors feared could stop him from ever walking again.
Instagram: @restispolitics
Twitter: @RestIsPolitics
TRIP Plus: Become a member of The Rest Is Politics Plus to support the podcast, receive a weekly newsletter, enjoy ad-free listening to both TRIP and Leading, join our Discord chatroom, and receive early access to live show tickets and Question Time episodes.</description></item><item><title>4: Michel Barnier: The Truth Behind Brexit | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280048/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who is the EU&amp;rsquo;s man behind Brexit? How did he combat Britain&amp;rsquo;s negotiating tactics? What is life like at the top of European politics?
Alastair and Rory are joined by Michel Barnier, the EU&amp;rsquo;s chief Brexit negotiator, three years on from Britain&amp;rsquo;s exit from the European Union.
Instagram: @restispolitics
Twitter: @RestIsPolitics
TRIP Plus: Become a member of The Rest Is Politics Plus to support the podcast, receive a weekly newsletter, enjoy ad-free listening to both TRIP and Leading, join our Discord chatroom, and receive early access to live show tickets and Question Time episodes.</description></item><item><title>3: Alan Milburn: Can the NHS be saved? | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280049/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is the NHS beyond saving? Could a Labour government fix it? How should Rishi Sunak deal with strikes?
This week on Leading, Alastair and Rory are joined by former Secretary of State for Health, Alan Milburn. Alan is credited for delivering modernisation to the NHS in the New Labour years, introducing foundation trusts, and is Rory’s hero for his work on reform.
Tune in to hear his thoughts on the struggles of being an MP, the biggest challenges facing the NHS, and Labour’s lack of clarity in opposition.</description></item><item><title>2: Marina Litvinenko: Fighting Putin's poison | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280050/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alexander Litvinenko: the man who solved his own murder after being poisoned by the Russian State in London.
Marina, his widow, battled for justice successfully in both a UK public enquiry and a case at the European Court of Human Rights.
As a leading critic of Vladimir Putin&amp;rsquo;s regime, &amp;lsquo;mafia state&amp;rsquo; and invasion of Ukraine - Marina sat down with Alastair to discuss Alexander&amp;rsquo;s murder, her fight for justice, being in Ukraine when Russia invaded last February, and how the Kremlin tried to conscript her son for the war in Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>1: Michael Heseltine: From Thatcher to Sunak | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280051/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280051/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the first ever episode of ‘Leading’, Alastair and Rory are joined by former Deputy Prime Minister, Michael Heseltine. One of the biggest names in the last half-century of British politics, Lord Heseltine discusses everything from his crucial role in the rise and fall of Margaret Thatcher to his current position in the House of Lords. Tune in to hear Michael talk about how politics has changed, why he lost the Conservative whip, Europe, Brexit, and the Miners’ Strike.</description></item><item><title>Trailer | Leading</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9179280052/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 17:50:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9179280052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rory Stewart and Alastair Campbell, hosts of Britain&amp;rsquo;s biggest podcast (The Rest Is Politics), have joined forces once again for their new interview podcast, ‘Leading’. Every Monday, Rory and Alastair interrogate, converse with, and interview some of the world&amp;rsquo;s biggest names - from both inside and outside of politics - about life, leadership, or leading the way in their chosen field. Whether they&amp;rsquo;re sports stars, thought-leaders, presidents or internationally-recognised religious figures, Alastair and Rory lift the lid on the motivation, philosophy and secrets behind their career.</description></item></channel></rss>