<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fess Up on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/fess-up/</link><description>Recent content in Fess Up on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/fess-up/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ep #10: The Good, the bad and the ugly of 2023. | Fess Up</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8546060001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8546060001/</guid><description>Podcast Description As it's the season of pampering and reflection, this week Nikki and Liz take the opportunity to discuss their 'Good,Bad And Ugly Of 2023'. They get into what fads and tweakments are wirth it and the others they believe are a waste of money and be warned, there's a horrifying tale about why you absolutely should NEVER try waxing at home. If you want to get in touch with Liz and Nikki, send us a message on Instagram</description></item><item><title>Ep #9: Catherine Noone, the politics of appearance.. | Fess Up</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8546060002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8546060002/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week's episode Nikki and Liz are joined by former Fine Gael politician and senator, Catherine Noone who provides an incredibly unique and honest insight into the appearance pressures faced by women in politics as well as her own lifelong journey with weightloss and childhood experiences of disordered eating.
If you want to get in touch with Liz and Nikki, send us a message on Instagram
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep #8: Laura Dowling, Viva La Vulva! | Fess Up</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8546060003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8546060003/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week Liz and Nikki are joined by the Fabulous Pharmacist herself, CEO &amp;amp; Founder of Fabuwellness, and the wonderwoman that is Laura Dowling to discuss her transformative and holistic approach to women's health, her advocacy of mucshrooms and her incredible Viva La Lulva tour. If you want to get in touch with Liz and Nikki, send us a message on Instagram
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep #7: Terry Prone, a Fess Up trailblazer | Fess Up</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8546060004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8546060004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Terry Prone has been nothing short of a legend of the communications game for decades but apart from all her professional achievements she could rightly be called an early Fess Up heroine. Following a near fatal car accident which "broke evry bone in her body apart from one arm" Terry began her journey with plastic surgery and made the very brave decision for the time to be very public about her procedures.</description></item><item><title>Ep #6: Monica Ivani, Ireland's Brow Queen | Fess Up</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8546060005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8546060005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Having moved from her native Hungary 24 years ago, Monica Ivani has established herself as Ireland' Brow Queen and this week she joins Nikki and Liz to discuss her approach to her craft, her experience of blepharoplasty and why, when it comes to treatments, nothing is off the suregeons table. If you want to get in touch with Liz and Nikki, send us a message on Instagram.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep #5: Hilda &amp; Courtney Smith, from birth to bum lifts. | Fess Up</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8546060006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8546060006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Courtney Smith is a style icon and has built up a remarkable career in fashion media and once you meet her equally iconic mother Hilda her early influences are obvious. In this week's episode they discuss the generational differences in their approach to beauty, bum lifts and to face lift or not to face lift. If you want to get in touch with Liz and Nikki, send us a message on Instagram.</description></item><item><title>Ep #4: Rob Kenny, deer placenta and teeth whitening | Fess Up</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8546060007/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 11:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8546060007/</guid><description>Podcast Description PR guru, presenter and influencer Rob Kenny has a lot of spinning plates – but that doesn't mean he's slacking on his self-care! This week on Fess Up, we find out what he thinks of cosmetic dentistry, what he's using deer placenta for and how he's finding life as an engaged man!
If you want to get in touch with Liz and Nikki, send us a message on Instagram.</description></item><item><title>Ep #3: Michelle Regazzoli Stone, boob jobs and HArmonyCA | Fess Up</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8546060008/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8546060008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Make-up artist Michelle Regazzoli Stone has been building her business for twenty years now, and even has her own BPerfect cosmetics range. But sometimes you want more than make-up to transform your look and this week, she's fessing up to which treatments she's loved –&amp;nbsp;and why as an influencer, it's tricky to accept treatments as gifts.
If you want to get in touch, send us a message on Instagram.</description></item><item><title>Ep #2: Marian Keyes, Ozempic and fillers versus botox | Fess Up</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8546060009/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8546060009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Best-selling author Marian Keyes is fessing up to everything –&amp;nbsp;how she felt about trying botox, her fears around threading and how she's found her HALO treatment.
Plus, Nikki lets us know how she's getting on with the 'skinny jab,' Ozempic.
If you want to get in touch, send us a message on Instagram.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep #1: Sophie Anderton, vampire facials and the business of botox | Fess Up</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8546060010/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8546060010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to Fess Up, the brand new podcast were we invite well-known faces to 'fess up' to what work they've had done to keep themselves looking and feeling good. We've got the international lingerie model Sophie Anderton joining us for the first episode, telling us how she lost her hair and what she thinks of vampire facials.
Plus, Liz and Nikki share some tips on what we need to know about botox!</description></item><item><title>Welcome to Your New Beauty Podcast, Fess Up! | Fess Up</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8546060011/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8546060011/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is your new weekly beauty podcast, Fess Up. Brought to you by Liz and Nikki Dwyer, a pair of sisters who run the Future Beauty Show and know their emsculpt from their coolsculpt!&amp;nbsp;
They’ve tried just about every beauty treatment and tweakment out there –&amp;nbsp;and they’re not afraid to tell you about it. Every week, they’ll have a well-known face on to fess up to what exactly they're getting done to their bodies.</description></item></channel></rss>