<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Scamanda on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/scamanda/</link><description>Recent content in Scamanda on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 19:09:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/scamanda/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Surviving El Chapo Returns for Season 2 | Scamanda</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5230390001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 19:09:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5230390001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hey Scamanda listeners! We wanted to let you know about the return of Lionsgate Sound&amp;rsquo;s Surviving El Chapo: The Twins Who Brought Down A Drug Lord. It follows the story of the Flores twins, who after becoming El Chapo&amp;rsquo;s right hand men, turned themselves over to the US authorities and cooperated against El Chapo to bring him down. Season 2 begins as they are taken into US custody and have to adjust to prison life before testifying in court against the world&amp;rsquo;s most notorious drug lord.</description></item><item><title>BONUS: Nobody believed me: pushed out co-worker on Amanda the painful Principal | Scamanda</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5230390002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5230390002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Before she was indicted, Amanda became the Principal of Pacific Point Elementary School. How did she become a Principal, and what was she like to work with? Find out from an anonymous guest who in the end had to leave her teaching career. Scamanda is a Lionsgate Sound podcast: http://lionsgatesound.com Hosted by Charlie Webster. Listen to another Lionsgate Sound podcast hosted by Charlie Webster, Died &amp;amp; Survived: https://link.chtbl.com/diedandsurvived?sid=sc Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>BONUS: Amanda’s Early Exploits: Was she ‘sick’ even back in college? | Scamanda</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5230390003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5230390003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hear from two people who knew Amanda years ago - before the blog, before Lisa and Steve - back when she was a college student and Resident Advisor. What was she like during her time at San Jose State? And what exactly was she doing? Be prepared! Scamanda is a Lionsgate Sound podcast: http://lionsgatesound.com Hosted by Charlie Webster. Listen to another Lionsgate Sound podcast hosted by Charlie Webster, Died &amp;amp; Survived: https://link.</description></item><item><title>BONUS: Uncovering Amanda’s blogs | Scamanda</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5230390004/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5230390004/</guid><description>Podcast Description If there’s one thing people have been talking about non-stop, it’s the blogs and exactly how Amanda was able to pull this off. And where exactly are these blogs? Charlie and Nancy work through the extreme detail and the lengths Amanda went to, not just in the blog but also on the stand in court to stop Nancy. Scamanda is a Lionsgate Sound podcast: http://lionsgatesound.com Hosted by Charlie Webster.</description></item><item><title>BONUS: We go behind the scenes with Charlie and Nancy. | Scamanda</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5230390005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5230390005/</guid><description>Podcast Description The world now knows about Amanda Riley and what she did. Charlie sits down with Nancy, the person whose dogged pursuit of Amanda is the reason she’s in prison, to take a peek behind the curtain and delve even further. Scamanda is a Lionsgate Sound podcast: http://lionsgatesound.com Hosted by Charlie Webster. Listen to another Lionsgate Sound podcast hosted by Charlie Webster, Died &amp;amp; Survived: https://link.chtbl.com/diedandsurvived?sid=sc Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 8 — Finale: Indicted | Scamanda</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5230390006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5230390006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Nancy’s eight year long obsession culminates in the indictment of Amanda C. Riley for wire fraud. It sends a shockwave through the local community. Amanda reads a statement to the court, and the judge gives her verdict. The Amanda C. Riley case is the only one of its kind in IRS history. Amanda is currently serving the longest federal prison sentence in history for soliciting donations for faking cancer.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 7 — This Lady Royally Sucks | Scamanda</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5230390007/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5230390007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amanda moves to Gilroy for a huge promotion - to Principal of a local Christian School. Nancy is still making trouble for her. In an attempt to get Nancy off her back, Amanda takes Nancy to court to get a restraining order against her. An explosive piece of evidence is submitted to the court. Scamanda is a Lionsgate Sound podcast: http://lionsgatesound.com Hosted by Charlie Webster. Listen to another Lionsgate Sound podcast hosted by Charlie Webster, Died &amp;amp; Survived: https://link.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 6 — High As Hell | Scamanda</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5230390008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5230390008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amanda lands a new job as a middle school teacher. But while #TeamAmanda continues to grow in popularity, there’s an ever-growing Team Nancy. Detective Martinez and Nancy team up and bring the IRS into the fold, launching a federal investigation into Amanda. Scamanda is a Lionsgate Sound podcast: http://lionsgatesound.com Hosted by Charlie Webster. Listen to another Lionsgate Sound podcast hosted by Charlie Webster, Died &amp;amp; Survived: https://link.chtbl.com/diedandsurvived?sid=sc Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 5 — Faith in the Truth | Scamanda</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5230390009/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5230390009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Convinced Amanda is lying about her cancer, Nancy enlists the support of San Jose Detective Jose Martinez. Amanda’s birthday brings a massive rally of support, including a #TeamAmanda video that gets the attention of thousands, set to the tune of Rachel Platten’s Fight Song. Scamanda is a Lionsgate Sound podcast: http://lionsgatesound.com Hosted by Charlie Webster. Listen to another Lionsgate Sound podcast hosted by Charlie Webster, Died &amp;amp; Survived: https://link.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 4 — Terminal. Miracle. | Scamanda</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5230390010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5230390010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amanda’s journey with cancer is like a rollercoaster that never ends. Her friend Lindsey explains that it was a constant back and forth of terminal, miracle, terminal, miracle. Nancy continues looking into whether Amanda is really faking it all. Amanda drops a bombshell on her friends Lisa and Steve. Scamanda is a Lionsgate Sound podcast: http://lionsgatesound.com Hosted by Charlie Webster. Listen to another Lionsgate Sound podcast hosted by Charlie Webster, Died &amp;amp; Survived: https://link.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 3 — No Coincidences | Scamanda</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5230390011/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5230390011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Despite everything, Amanda falls pregnant with her second child - the miracle baby. Amanda’s rockstar status is cemented at church, but not before getting the most devastating news yet - her cancer has progressed to Stage Four. Scamanda is a Lionsgate Sound podcast: http://lionsgatesound.com Hosted by Charlie Webster. Listen to another Lionsgate Sound podcast hosted by Charlie Webster, Died &amp;amp; Survived: https://link.chtbl.com/diedandsurvived?sid=sc Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 2 — Roaring Goddess | Scamanda</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5230390012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5230390012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amanda’s good news doesn’t last long. Her mother, Peggy, the ‘Roaring Goddess,&amp;rsquo; posts a guest blog to keep Amanda’s followers updated. Her family launches a donation website for #TeamAmanda to donate directly to the cause. The custody battle rages on. Scamanda is a Lionsgate Sound podcast: http://lionsgatesound.com Hosted by Charlie Webster. Listen to another Lionsgate Sound podcast hosted by Charlie Webster, Died &amp;amp; Survived: https://link.chtbl.com/diedandsurvived?sid=sc Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Chapter 1 — Amanda is Dying | Scamanda</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5230390013/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5230390013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Meet Amanda. Her world is about to be shattered by some life-changing news during the birth of her first child. She’s dying. Or at least, that’s what she tells the world in her brand new blog. Scamanda is a Lionsgate Sound podcast: http://lionsgatesound.com Hosted by Charlie Webster. Listen to another Lionsgate Sound podcast hosted by Charlie Webster, Died &amp;amp; Survived: https://link.chtbl.com/diedandsurvived?sid=sc Learn more about your ad choices. Visit megaphone.</description></item><item><title>Meet Scamanda | Scamanda</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/5230390014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 22:04:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/5230390014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amanda is a wife. A mother. A blogger. A Christian. A charming, beautiful, bubbly, young woman who lives life to the fullest. But Amanda is dying, with a secret she doesn’t want anyone to know. She starts a blog detailing her cancer journey, and becomes an inspiration, touching and captivating her local community as well as followers all over the world. Until one day investigative producer Nancy gets an anonymous tip telling her to look at Amanda’s blog, setting Nancy on an unimaginable road to uncover Amanda’s secret.</description></item></channel></rss>