<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Uncanny on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/uncanny/</link><description>Recent content in Uncanny on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 12:59:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/uncanny/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>S3 Christmas Special: The Haunting of Daisy May Cooper | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040001/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 12:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Daisy May Cooper believes her house is haunted. Three years ago, the award-winning actress and writer moved to a new-build house in the Cotswolds, but within weeks odd events start to trouble Daisy and her family: phantom footsteps, objects moving by themselves and ghostly apparitions. Now she’s called on the help of Danny to investigate. Will he survive the night in Daisy’s haunted house?
Written and presented by Danny Robins
Editing and sound design: Charlie Brandon-King
Music: Evelyn Sykes
Theme music by Lanterns on the Lake
Produced by Danny Robins and Simon Barnard</description></item><item><title>You might like The Lovecraft Investigations | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Enter the world of The Lovecraft Investigations, a thrilling investigation into witchcraft, the occult and secret government operations. All four series are available now on BBC Sounds.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>S3. Case 6: Good Evening | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040003/</guid><description>Podcast Description 1989, and Anne moves to a new house in a new town with her husband and baby. Life seems unremarkable, until one day she’s prodded in the back and hears a refined voice in her ear… but there’s no-one there. It happens again, and then again. Is Anne's imagination getting the better of her? Or does something want her attention?
Written and presented by Danny Robins
Editing and sound design: Charlie Brandon-King
Music: Evelyn Sykes
Script editor: Dale Shaw
Theme music by Lanterns on the Lake
Produced by Danny Robins and Simon Barnard</description></item><item><title>S3. Case 5: Double Trouble | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040004/</guid><description>Podcast Description An Uncanny double bill, featuring two cases that will chill and perplex. The first features a bizarre, impossible experience on a family day out in Newcastle, the second, a life-changing moment for an unwell woman in Coventry.
Written and presented by Danny Robins
Editing and sound design: Charlie Brandon-King
Music: Evelyn Sykes
Theme music by Lanterns on the Lake
Produced by Danny Robins and Simon Barnard
A Bafflegab and Uncanny Media production for BBC Radio 4</description></item><item><title>S3. Case 4: Elton’s Phone | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Christmas 1982, and 6-year-old Elton loves playing with his younger sister's present, a toy telephone. But joy turns to fear when it starts ringing by itself. Can an object really be haunted? Or is something unseen playing with the telephone?
Written and presented by Danny Robins
Editing and sound design: Charlie Brandon-King
Music: Evelyn Sykes
Script edtor: Dale Shaw
Theme music by Lanterns on the Lake
Produced by Danny Robins and Simon Barnard</description></item><item><title>S3. Case 3: The Ghost Who Hated Parties | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040006/</guid><description>Podcast Description 1986, and three art students move into digs in Waterford, Ireland. But they discover the house seemingly disapproves of visitors, reacting to talk of student parties with lights flickering and cupboard doors banging. It’s funny at first, but not for long…
Written and presented by Danny Robins
Editing and sound design: Charlie Brandon-King
Music: Evelyn Sykes
Theme music by Lanterns on the Lake
Produced by Danny Robins and Simon Barnard</description></item><item><title>Miss Howard, The Bearpark Poltergeist and The Oxford Exorcism - Case Update | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040007/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Danny explores your theories and questions about the Uncanny TV specials - Miss Howard, The Bearpark Poltergeist and The Oxford Exorcism - and we hear brand-new new evidence.
Written and presented by Danny Robins
Editor and Sound Designer: Charlie Brandon-King
Music: Evelyn Sykes
Theme Music by Lanterns on the Lake
Produced by Danny Robins and Simon Barnard
A Bafflegab and Uncanny Media production for BBC Radio 4
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Classic Case: The Todmorden UFO | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor and writer Laurence Rickard, who plays caveman Robin in the BBC sitcom Ghosts, picks his favourite classic Uncanny episode.
Retired policeman Alan Godfrey tells us the story of the case that has obsessed him for his whole life. When Alan tries to solve a weird and seemingly impossible murder in the small northern town of Todmorden, it leads to a bizarre UFO sighting and then a strange and sinister government cover up that ends up affecting Alan’s life.</description></item><item><title>Classic Case: Don't Sleep in this House | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Writer and actress Daisy May Cooper picks her favourite classic Uncanny episode.
Christmas 1974, and two young climbers stumble across an abandoned house in the Scottish mountains. It’s a bothy - a safe shelter for hunters and climbers out in the wilds of the highlands. But Phil and Jimmy are about to experience the most terrifying night of their lives, alone in the middle of nowhere.
Is a violent spirit determined to drive them out into the freezing night?</description></item><item><title>Classic Case: Harry Called | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040010/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor and writer Reece Shearsmith chooses his favourite classic episode of Uncanny.
When a spirit called Harry makes contact via a Ouija board, student Will thinks his friends are playing a joke. But then Harry starts calling him…
Written and presented by Danny Robins
Editor and Sound Designer: Charlie Brandon-King
Music: Evelyn Sykes
Theme Music by Lanterns on the Lake
Produced by Danny Robins and Simon Barnard
A Bafflegab and Uncanny Media production for BBC Radio 4</description></item><item><title>S3. Case 2: Uncle Jack | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040011/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tim moves from London to a 16th century coaching house in Cornwall, to find it already occupied by a long-dead previous owner - Uncle Jack. Tim and his partner quickly adjust to the constant noise of Jack's spectral footsteps jumping from the upstairs window. But then one night, things change…
Written and presented by Danny Robins
Editing and sound design: Charlie Brandon-King
Music: Evelyn Sykes
Theme music by Lanterns on the Lake
Script editor: Dale Shaw
Produced by Danny Robins and Simon Barnard</description></item><item><title>S3. Case 1: The Blue Man | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040012/</guid><description>Podcast Description 16-year-old Sarah moves to a new house in North Wales, and every night wakes to see a man standing at the end of her bed, accompanied by a terrible feeling of intense sadness. She thinks it’s a dream, but then realises she’s not the only one to see him… Written and presented by Danny Robins
Editing and sound design: Charlie Brandon-King
Music: Evelyn Sykes
Theme music by Lanterns on the Lake
Script editor: Dale Shaw
Produced by Danny Robins and Simon Barnard</description></item><item><title>S3. Uncanny is back: Season 2 Case Update | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040013/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Danny answers your questions and theories about Season 2, and reveals some startling new evidence. And we have some big news about Season 3...
Written and presented by Danny Robins
Editing and sound design: Charlie Brandon-King
Music: Evelyn Sykes
Theme Music by Lanterns on the Lake
Produced by Danny Robins and Simon Barnard
A Bafflegab and Uncanny Media production for BBC Radio 4
Transcript</description></item><item><title>S2. Case 12: The Ghost That Followed Us Home | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Strange and terrifying events occur at a family wedding in rural France… and back in England, things escalate even further. Has a paranormal entity followed the family home?
Written and presented by Danny Robins
Editor and Sound Designer: Charlie Brandon-King
Music: Evelyn Sykes
Theme Music by Lanterns on the Lake
Script editor: Simon Jacobs
Produced by Danny Robins and Simon Barnard
A Bafflegab and Uncanny Media production for BBC Radio 4</description></item><item><title>S2. Case 11: Uncanny Live at Hay | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Danny Robins is joined by writer and broadcaster David Baddiel and paranormal expert Evelyn Hollow for this special episode, recorded live at the Hay Festival 2023. Written and presented by Danny Robins
Editor and Sound Designer: Charlie Brandon-King
Music: Evelyn Sykes
Theme Music by Lanterns on the Lake
Produced by Danny Robins and Simon Barnard
A Bafflegab and Uncanny Media production for BBC Radio 4
Transcript</description></item><item><title>S2. Case 10: Harry Called | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040016/</guid><description>Podcast Description When a spirit called Harry makes contact via a Ouija board, student Will thinks his friends are playing a joke. But then Harry starts calling him… Written and presented by Danny Robins
Editor and Sound Designer: Charlie Brandon-King
Music: Evelyn Sykes
Theme Music by Lanterns on the Lake
Produced by Danny Robins and Simon Barnard
A Bafflegab and Uncanny Media production for BBC Radio 4
Transcript</description></item><item><title>S2. Case 9: The Beast of Langeais | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two 17-year-olds from Northern Ireland win the chance to go on a study trip along the River Loire in France. But what happens to them there will haunt them even 40 years later. Did they really have a brush with the devil?
Written and presented by Danny Robins
Editor and Sound Designer: Charlie Brandon-King
Music: Evelyn Sykes
Theme Music by Lanterns on the Lake
Script assistant: Leo Dunlop
Produced by Danny Robins and Simon Barnard</description></item><item><title>S2. Case 8: The Guest Book | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kitty moves into her new partner’s house, a former Victorian cobblers shop in the North West of England... but someone else is already living there with him. Someone who doesn't want her there. Someone who isn't alive.
Written and presented by Danny Robins
Editor and Sound Designer: Charlie Brandon-King
Music: Evelyn Sykes
Theme Music by Lanterns on the Lake
Script editor: Simon Jacobs
Produced by Danny Robins and Simon Barnard</description></item><item><title>S2. Case 7: The Rendlesham UFO | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040019/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Rendlesham Incident is the most famous and controversial case in British UFO history, a story riddled with claims and counterclaims. Danny Robins talks to one of the original witnesses and tries to piece together just what happened back in December 1980 at a US airbase in Suffolk.
Written and presented by Danny Robins
Editor and Sound Designer: Charlie Brandon-King
Music: Evelyn Sykes
Theme Music by Lanterns on the Lake
Script editor: Dale Shaw
Produced by Danny Robins and Simon Barnard</description></item><item><title>S2. Case 6: An Angel Called Bernie | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matthew, a soldier in the Irish Defence Forces, always had a difficult relationship with his grandmother, right up until her death. So can it really be her spirit who saves him from dying in the years that follow?
Written and presented by Danny Robins
Editor and Sound Designer: Charlie Brandon-King
Music: Evelyn Sykes
Theme Music by Lanterns on the Lake
Script assistant: Leo Dunlop
Produced by Danny Robins and Simon Barnard</description></item><item><title>S2. Case 5: Uncanny Live at UncannyCon | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040021/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Danny is joined by actor and presenter Laura Whitmore and Uncanny expert Ciaran O'Keeffe to discuss some brand-new listener cases, recorded live at the first-ever Uncanny Fan Convention, a day-long festival devoted to all things supernatural. Written and presented by Danny Robins
Editor and Sound Designer: Charlie Brandon-King
Music: Evelyn Sykes
Theme Music by Lanterns on the Lake
Produced by Danny Robins and Simon Barnard
A Bafflegab and Uncanny Media production for BBC Radio 4</description></item><item><title>S2. Case 4: Inside Room 611 | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Danny returns once more to Alanbrooke Hall in Belfast, and the supernatural saga of Room 611. He’s joined by former Queens University students Ken and Gary Foster to talk about the case. Recorded live at UncannyCon 2023.
Written and presented by Danny Robins
Editor and Sound Designer: Charlie Brandon-King
Music: Evelyn Sykes
Theme Music by Lanterns on the Lake
Produced by Danny Robins and Simon Barnard
A Bafflegab and Uncanny Media production for BBC Radio 4</description></item><item><title>S2. Case 3: Leave the Lights On | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040023/</guid><description>Podcast Description As the poltergeist activity ramps up dramatically, the family resort to desperate measures. Can they survive living with a vengeful poltergeist? Written and presented by Danny Robins
Editor and Sound Designer: Charlie Brandon-King
Music: Evelyn Sykes
Theme Music by Lanterns on the Lake
Script assistant: Leo Dunlop
Produced by Danny Robins and Simon Barnard
A Bafflegab and Uncanny Media production for BBC Radio 4
Transcript</description></item><item><title>S2. Case 2: My Family's Poltergeist | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040024/</guid><description>Podcast Description James moves with his parents to a new house, but the family are swiftly plunged into a maelstrom of terrifying, violent poltergeist activity which will tear the family apart. Could this be the scariest Uncanny episode yet? Written and presented by Danny Robins
Editor and Sound Designer: Charlie Brandon-King
Music: Evelyn Sykes
Theme Music by Lanterns on the Lake
Script assistant: Leo Dunlop
Produced by Danny Robins and Simon Barnard</description></item><item><title>S2. Case 1: The Boy in Room 3 | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040025/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Danny Robins returns with a brand new season of Uncanny. Homeless, 19-year-old Marie gets a job at a working monastery in the North of England. Night after night, she hears the sound of a young boy crying in an adjacent room, but there's no-one there. What is the dark secret of Room 3? Written and presented by Danny Robins
Editor and Sound Designer: Charlie Brandon-King
Music: Evelyn Sykes
Theme Music by Lanterns on the Lake
Script assistant: Leo Dunlop
Produced by Danny Robins and Simon Barnard</description></item><item><title>Uncanny is back | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040026/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 16:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Uncanny is back... and in Season 2 Danny will continue to explore listeners' chilling tales of the paranormal, encompassing everything from poltergeists to cryptids to UFOs
Transcript</description></item><item><title>S1. Uncanny Live with Mark Gatiss | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040027/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 10:13:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Danny meets actor, writer and Uncanny fan Mark Gatiss, for this very special live episode, recorded at the London Podcast Festival 2022. The pair discuss their mutual passion for ghosts, and investigate some new real-life stories of the paranormal.
Written and presented by Danny Robins
Editor and Sound Designer: Charlie Brandon-King
Music: Evelyn Sykes
Theme Music by Lanterns on the Lake
Produced by Danny Robins and Simon Barnard</description></item><item><title>S1. Christmas Special | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 09:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040028/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s the season for ghost stories, and Danny Robins is back with another real-life tale of the paranormal in this special Uncanny episode that sees a family Christmas turned upside down.
A young child and his mother share a council house in a Scottish village, but as objects start to inexplicably move they get the feeling that they are not alone. Who is the mysterious presence haunting their dreams?</description></item><item><title>Uncanny Meets Ghosts | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040029/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 16:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Danny is joined by an actual Ghost - Laurence Rickard, who plays caveman Robin in the hit BBC sitcom Ghosts - for a special crossover episode. Laurence reveals the supernatural inspirations for the show, and tells Danny about his own real-life paranormal experiences.
You can also listen to Inside Ghosts, the companion podcast to the BBC hit show Ghosts, taking listeners behind-the-scenes on the brilliant new series. Each week Nathan Bryon, who plays Obi in the series, is joined by the Ghosts themselves to chat through the twists and turns of each episode, and to focus in on a particular Ghost each week.</description></item><item><title>S1. Summer Special Part 3: Uncanny Live | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040030/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040030/</guid><description>Podcast Description The third part of this unholy trinity of Summer special episodes. Danny Robins is joined by paranormal experts Ciaran O’Keeffe and Evelyn Hollow, his co-stars on Uncanny and The Battersea Poltergeist, for an exciting live episode, recorded at the Hay Festival 2022. They bring Uncanny’s thrills and chills to a live audience, with a selection of all-new true-life supernatural encounters and a deep-dive on some of the strange phenomena discussed in the series.</description></item><item><title>S1. Summer Special Part 2: The Room Next Door | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040031/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Danny returns once more to Newfoundland, Canada and the family holiday from hell, as we hear from a new witness to the terrifying events of that night in the summer of 1998 – Scott’s Dad, Brian. It turns out Scott and his brother were not the only family members to be menaced by a seemingly malevolent supernatural force. What happened in the rest of that lonely seaside guest house is bizarre, frightening and shocking.</description></item><item><title>S1. Summer Special Part 1: Canadian Horror Story | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040032/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Uncanny is back, with a brand-new case, in this terrifying Summer Special episode. It’s 1998 and teenager Scott goes on his first trip abroad, a summer vacation in the rugged beauty of Newfoundland in Canada. But when Scott’s family stay the night in a remote seaside lodging house, their trip of a lifetime becomes the holiday from hell as they find themselves seemingly face to face with a malevolent supernatural force.</description></item><item><title>S1. Case 15: Bloody Hell Ken | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040033/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040033/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this season finale, Danny returns one more time to Ken's terrifying haunting in Room 611, discovering new evidence and new witnesses to the terrifying events at Alanbrooke Hall, plus there will be major revelations about some of the other cases this series. Can these supernatural mysteries be solved?
Written and presented by Danny Robins
Editor and Sound Designer: Charlie Brandon-King
Music: Evelyn Sykes
Theme Music by Lanterns on the Lake
Produced by Danny Robins and Simon Barnard</description></item><item><title>S1. Case 14: The Haunting of Tanfield House | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040034/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040034/</guid><description>Podcast Description A young woman breaks away from her Catholic background when she attends art school. Memories of a childhood exorcism haunt her, but when it appears there is a poltergeist in her new house, she once again consider the existence of the Devil. But does the poltergeist really mean harm or is it just trying to get a message through?
Written and presented by Danny Robins
Editor and Sound Designer: Charlie Brandon-King
Music: Evelyn Sykes
Theme Music by Lanterns on the Lake
Produced by Danny Robins and Simon Barnard</description></item><item><title>S1. Case 13: The Return of Elizabeth Dacre | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040035/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040035/</guid><description>Podcast Description A young family moves into a historic seaside house converted from a once famous hotel, but when they start to see an apparition who resembles the former owner, they begin to wonder if they are really welcome. Does she want them out of her house?
Written and presented by Danny Robins
Editor and Sound Designer: Charlie Brandon-King
Music: Evelyn Sykes
Theme Music by Lanterns on the Lake
Produced by Danny Robins and Simon Barnard</description></item><item><title>S1. Case 12: Fatal Collision | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040036/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Delivery driver Amanda is driving home in the early hours when she’s involved in a terrible, life-changing accident. Or is she? Danny investigates another eerie tale of the supernatural. He also takes a look back at the series so far, presenting some amazing new evidence and witness accounts for previous cases.
Written and presented by Danny Robins
Editor and Sound Designer: Charlie Brandon-King
Music: Evelyn Sykes
Theme Music by Lanterns on the Lake
Produced by Danny Robins and Simon Barnard</description></item><item><title>S1. Case 11: The Curse of Luibeilt | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040037/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040037/</guid><description>Podcast Description After young climber Phil’s terrifying night in the Scottish highlands, whatever lurks in the abandoned cottage appears to follow him home to Glasgow. He decides to return to Luibeilt to confront his fears and solve the mystery - but what happens next will haunt Phil for the rest of his life.
Danny digs further into this bizarre and scary case. Does it offer proof that ghosts exist?
Written and presented by Danny Robins
Editor and Sound Designer: Charlie Brandon-King
Music: Evelyn Sykes
Theme Music by Lanterns on the Lake
Produced by Danny Robins and Simon Barnard</description></item><item><title>Classic Case: Don't Sleep in This House | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040038/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Christmas 1974, and two young climbers stumble across an abandoned house in the Scottish mountains. It’s a bothy - a safe shelter for hunters and climbers out in the wilds of the highlands. But Phil and Jimmy are about to experience the most terrifying night of their lives, alone in the middle of nowhere.
Is a violent spirit determined to drive them out into the freezing night? Years later, Phil tells Danny Robins his story and about how he researched the house, discovering others had had similar experiences there.</description></item><item><title>S1. Case 9: I Will Kill You All | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040039/</guid><description>Podcast Description Journalist Hannah Betts recounts the terrifying ghost story of her family home – a haunted house filled with paranormal activity seemingly linked to a murder that happened there in Victorian times. Can a house really record the tragic events that took place and replay them, as this house seems to every night? Are the ghosts real or the product of tensions within Hannah’s large family? When a chilling message is revealed to Hannah and her siblings, the haunting gets shockingly close to home.</description></item><item><title>S1. Case 8: The UFO in the Playground | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040040/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Danny Robins returns to his investigation into the Todmorden UFO case to assess new evidence that has come in from listeners - and also hears from two compelling new witnesses, one in Wales and one in Africa, who both experienced UFO encounters as children. Do their experiences shed any light on the ongoing mystery of possible alien contact with humans? Is the truth out there?
Written and presented by Danny Robins
Editor and Sound Designer: Charlie Brandon-King
Music: Evelyn Sykes
Theme Music by Lanterns on the Lake
Produced by Danny Robins and Simon Barnard</description></item><item><title>S1. Case 7: The Angel in the Bathroom | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040041/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Danny Robins talks to Tom, an NHS mental health nurse working with troubled young people. Tom starts to work with Yousuf, a teenage boy from a devoutly Muslim background. His family believe he is possessed by a djinn – an evil spirit, but Tom believes Yousuf is having a crisis of faith which has led him to the brink of suicide. When Yousuf does tries to take his own life, he is rescued in seemingly impossible circumstances.</description></item><item><title>S1. Case 6: The Brooklyn Poltergeist | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040042/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Model and influencer Charli Howard tells her ghost story to Danny Robins. It’s 2017 and Charli is alone in New York, trying to carve out a modelling career. She accepts a room in a shared house with a local couple, but they have not been entirely honest with her. The previous resident of the room fled in fear and Charli is about to experience her very own dose of terror at the hands of a malicious male spirit.</description></item><item><title>S1. Case 5: Return to Room 611 | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040043/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Danny Robins goes deeper on the first Uncanny case, the haunting of Belfast student tower block Alanbrooke Hall in the early 1980s, and talks to new witnesses to the strange events there. Can he come any closer to solving the mystery? Written and presented by Danny Robins
Editor and Sound Designer: Charlie Brandon-King
Music: Evelyn Sykes
Theme Music by Lanterns on the Lake
Produced by Danny Robins and Simon Barnard</description></item><item><title>S1. Case 4: My Best Friend's Ghost | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Laura, a young woman with a wild streak, leaves home and finds a room in a flat-share where she meets Anna, who becomes her best friend. When Anna dies tragically from cancer, Laura is heartbroken, but then… Anna comes back. As Laura tells Danny Robins her story, he explores the world of mediums (is it really possible to contact the dead?) and investigates the greatest of all mysteries – what happens to us when we die?</description></item><item><title>Classic Case: The Todmorden UFO | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040045/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Retired policeman Alan Godfrey tells us the story of the case that has obsessed him for his whole life. When Alan tries to solve a weird and seemingly impossible murder in the small northern town of Todmorden, it leads to a bizarre UFO sighting and then a strange and sinister government cover up that ends up affecting Alan’s life.
Danny Robins explores if there is real evidence of extra-terrestrial visits to Earth.</description></item><item><title>S1. Case 2: The Hanging Room | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040046/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Teenager Millie moves with her family into her grandparents remote historic farmhouse in the English countryside. It is a house with a tragic past that seems to be returning to haunt the family in a way that feels dangerous and disturbing, pushing them to the edge of sanity. Millie tells Danny Robins about her ordeal in this terrifying episode that reveals the true impact of living in a ‘haunted house’.</description></item><item><title>Classic Uncanny: Case 1: The Evil in Room 611 | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040047/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Danny meets Ken, a highly respected geneticist. A man who doesn’t believe in ghosts, but cannot get over the fact that he believes he saw one 40 years ago as a student in Belfast. This is the story of a student bedroom that seems to have a mysterious and frightening impact on those who sleep in it, of poltergeist activity, sinister apparitions and a dark force that Ken describes as ‘pure evil’.</description></item><item><title>Introducing Uncanny | Uncanny</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/7585040048/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 10:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/7585040048/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Battersea Poltergeist’s Danny Robins investigates chilling first-hand stories of paranormal encounters, from ghostly phantoms to sinister folklore and UFOs.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>