<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard on SWIEST - Transcripts 路 Screenplays 路 Lyrics</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/categories/armchair-expert-with-dax-shepard/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard on SWIEST - Transcripts 路 Screenplays 路 Lyrics</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/categories/armchair-expert-with-dax-shepard/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard - Erika Christensen</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1333100020/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1333100020/</guid>
        <description>0:00
Hello, welcome to the armchair expert.
This is Dax Shepard your host.
I&amp;rsquo;m joined with Monica your co-host.
Hello.
And before we get into this episode, which is with my ever beautiful town to TV sister Erika Christensen.
I guess it&amp;rsquo;s a disclaimer.
0:16
I&amp;rsquo;ll say this is something I&amp;rsquo;ve been wanting to bring up for a while and it&amp;rsquo;s just kind of a context.
I&amp;rsquo;m hoping people will think of this podcast in end.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard - Johnny Knoxville</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1333100019/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1333100019/</guid>
        <description>0:00
Hello, welcome to armchair expert.
I&amp;rsquo;m your grateful host Dax Shepard.
Today.
We have an exciting guest on his name is Johnny Knoxville, but that&amp;rsquo;s not really his name.
His name is PJ or in fact, those are his initials.
So that&amp;rsquo;s not even his real name.
But just suffice to say, people call him PJ who are friends with him.
0:16
So you&amp;rsquo;ll hear me referring to him as PJ.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard - Marc Maron</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1333100018/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1333100018/</guid>
        <description>0:00
Hello, welcome to the armchair expert.
I&amp;rsquo;m Dax Shepard.
I&amp;rsquo;m joined by the ever talented and beautiful.
Monika.
Badman.
Hello, an intro.
I&amp;rsquo;ve got more coming your way.
Mmm.
Yeah.
I&amp;rsquo;ve just started drafting them in my head.
Oh boy.
0:15
Yeah.
Wait, I don&amp;rsquo;t think I&amp;rsquo;ll run out of adjectives too soon.
Either.
Okay.
Yeah, before we get into this week&amp;rsquo;s episode.
There was some blowback and I&amp;rsquo;m happy.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard - Bob Mervak</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1333100017/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1333100017/</guid>
        <description>0:00
Hello, welcome to the armchair expert.
I&amp;rsquo;m Dax Shepard.
And today we&amp;rsquo;re going to speak with Bob Moore.
Vac.
Bob.
Novak is my wife Kristen Bell&amp;rsquo;s best childhood friend or one of her best childhood friends, and we came to know each other about 10 years ago through Kristen and I discovered quickly, that Bob is a musical genius, a Phenom, and he and Kristen used to perform together in high school for higher at funerals weddings.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard - Joel McHale</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1333100016/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1333100016/</guid>
        <description>0:00
Welcome to armchair expert.
I&amp;rsquo;m Dax Shepard.
I&amp;rsquo;m joined by my friend Monica.
Badman.
Hello boy.
Oh boy.
Do we have a tall guest today?
I&amp;rsquo;ll drink a water.
Real tall slurp a water and a muscular slurp at that.
Oh, yeah thick water.
Yeah.
I don&amp;rsquo;t think people realize when they see Joel McHale on the television set or on a billboard on the side of the road.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard - Chris Hardwick</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1333100015/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1333100015/</guid>
        <description>0:00
Hello everybody.
I&amp;rsquo;m Dax Shepard in.
This is armchair expert.
I&amp;rsquo;m so delighted to have you join us today because we&amp;rsquo;re talking with someone who was pretty instrumental in me, having a desire to have a podcast.
I think I did his show the first time five or six years ago, and I&amp;rsquo;ve done it two or three times, you know, him as the Nerdist, Chris Hardwick joins us today.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard - Seth Green</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1333100014/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1333100014/</guid>
        <description>0:00
Welcome to the armchair expert.
I&amp;rsquo;m your host Dax Shepard.
Today.
I&amp;rsquo;m going to speak with one of my best friends.
Seth Green, you know, Seth Green.
You love, Seth Green.
It&amp;rsquo;s impossible.
Not to love Seth Green.
He has been endlessly.
Funny.
He is very very witty and if you&amp;rsquo;re an interview with him, which I&amp;rsquo;ve been several different times, you have to really bring your A game because he might be the fastest mind in the west.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard - Katie Couric</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1333100013/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1333100013/</guid>
        <description>0:00
Welcome to the armchair expert.
I&amp;rsquo;m your host Dax Shepard before I tell you about today&amp;rsquo;s guess.
I just want to share something that happened this morning while I was driving my daughter to a gymnastics class.
I didn&amp;rsquo;t even tell you about this yet, Monica.
Okay, unloads Feliz, Boulevard.
0:16
I passed a couple guys in a Range Rover.
And as I pass them, they honk the horn in through the bird, out the window and I could hear them screaming.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard - Lauren Graham</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1333100012/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1333100012/</guid>
        <description>0:00
Hi, welcome to the armchair expert.
Today is a big tree by popular demand and just my own selfish desires.
Lauren G going to join us.
She is, I guess I&amp;rsquo;ll say I&amp;rsquo;m her TV.
Brother not she&amp;rsquo;s my TV sister.
I should give her the status position.
0:16
As it&amp;rsquo;s well deserved.
She probably was most known from Gilmore Girls, you know, her from there.
She&amp;rsquo;s Lorelei my brothers in love with her.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard - Zach Braff</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1333100011/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1333100011/</guid>
        <description>0:00
Hello, everybody.
Welcome to armchair expert.
Today.
We have a guest that a lot of people been asking for for two reasons.
I think a they&amp;rsquo;re just interested in him, which is very natural.
But even I think more pronounced is the desire to hear the two people who look most alike on planet Earth, sit down and talk to one another because for many years now, go over a decade.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard - Anna Faris</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1333100010/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1333100010/</guid>
        <description>0:00
Hi, this is Dax.
Welcome to armchair expert.
Today on a ferris stop by and I just really like on I&amp;rsquo;ve done her podcast.
I&amp;rsquo;ve bumped into her over the years.
I just think she&amp;rsquo;s so supremely talented, as a comedian an actor, but a clip seen all that is her willingness to be vulnerable and honest.
0:19
And if you find that you want even more that after listening to this, you should check out her podcast unqualified.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard - Van Hunt</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1333100009/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1333100009/</guid>
        <description>0:00
Hello, welcome to the armchair expert.
I&amp;rsquo;m your host act Shepherd.
Today.
I&amp;rsquo;m going to speak with a musician named Van hunt.
I was deeply deeply, deeply, obsessed, with fan hunt around two thousand, five and six and onward.
0:16
I&amp;rsquo;ve not ever stop listening to him.
In fact, my four year old daughter&amp;rsquo;s favorite songs is one of his being a girl and I talked about him so frequently and I gifted Monica, some of his music for Christmas and then she and Rob my other producer went behind my back and got a hold of him.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard - Ellen DeGeneres</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1333100008/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1333100008/</guid>
        <description>0:00
Hello, welcome to the armchair expert.
I&amp;rsquo;m your host.
Zach Braff today.
I&amp;rsquo;m speaking with a good friend of mine.
Ellen DeGeneres.
You&amp;rsquo;ve probably never heard of her.
She&amp;rsquo;s mostly unknown.
I mean, she does have a daytime show.
That&amp;rsquo;s pretty popular.
She&amp;rsquo;s had many sitcoms.
In fact, she is such a Powerhouse.
0:16
I think she even has a game show.
That&amp;rsquo;s very popular.
So it&amp;rsquo;s hard to get a few minutes with this woman and she was gracious enough to give us some of her time.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard - Adam Scott</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1333100007/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1333100007/</guid>
        <description>0:00
Hi, welcome to the armchair expert.
Today.
We&amp;rsquo;re going to speak with Adam Scott, who&amp;rsquo;s just an all-around, nice human being on a lot of levels.
He is currently the star of a show.
He produces called ghosted on Fox, which airs Sunday nights, and you&amp;rsquo;ve seen them in a million movies.
0:16
He&amp;rsquo;s unbelievably fun.
He&amp;rsquo;s also an incredibly skilled actor.
If you&amp;rsquo;ve seen the HBO show Monica, what&amp;rsquo;s it called at the women?</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard - Pete Wentz</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1333100006/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1333100006/</guid>
        <description>0:00
Hello, welcome to armchair expert.
I am your host Dax Shepard.
Today.
I&amp;rsquo;m going to speak with Pete Wentz who is the bass player for Fall Out Boy, very popular band, a loved band.
I know P socially through our mutual friend, Ryan Hansen of, probably hung out with him at their house.
0:19
A couple dozen times and he&amp;rsquo;s been to our house.
He&amp;rsquo;s a very, very nice guy.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard - Jimmy Kimmel</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1333100005/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1333100005/</guid>
        <description>0:00
Hello, welcome to the armchair expert.
I&amp;rsquo;m Dax Shepard today.
I&amp;rsquo;m going to talk to a good friend of mine.
Jimmy James Kimmel, you know, him from Jimmy Kimmel Live, or maybe you fell in love with them first, on the man show or Win Ben Stein&amp;rsquo;s Money, or maybe used to listen to him on the radio.
0:16
Maybe you went to college with him and Arizona or Nevada, or wherever he went.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard - Joy Bryant</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1333100004/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1333100004/</guid>
        <description>0:00
Welcome to the armchair expert.
I&amp;rsquo;m Dax Shepard today.
I am joined by my TV wife Joy Bryant, you know, her from Parenthood, Get Rich or Die trying&amp;rsquo; Antwone Fisher.
She&amp;rsquo;s a writer.
She&amp;rsquo;s an actress.
She&amp;rsquo;s a clothing designer.
And one of my all-time favorite people to talk to.
I think we worked together for almost seven years on Parenthood.
0:18
And we never ever tired of shooting the shit.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard - Ashton Kutcher</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1333100003/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1333100003/</guid>
        <description>0:00
Hello and welcome to the armchair expert.
I&amp;rsquo;m Dax Shepard today.
I get a chance to thank the person who started my career Ashton Kutcher, we&amp;rsquo;ve known each other for about 15 years now and I can say, he has been endlessly, generous to me over that time.
0:17
And it was really, really nice to thank him face-to-face.
But in retrospect, if I&amp;rsquo;m being dead honest, after he left, it occurred to me, I stopped short of what I should have really said, as you will hear.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard - Kristen Bell</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1333100002/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1333100002/</guid>
        <description>0:00
Hello and welcome to armchair expert.
I am Dax Shepard.
And today, my guest is the lovely Kristen Bell.
She was Ronica, Mars Sarah Marshall, Princess Anna, and she&amp;rsquo;s currently Eleanor shell strop in the good place.
She can sing.
She can dance.
0:15
She can do drama.
She can do comedy.
She&amp;rsquo;s frustratingly, talented and special, and above all those things.
She&amp;rsquo;s my wife.
And even more importantly, she&amp;rsquo;s an incredible mother to our girls.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard - Introducing: Armchair Expert with Dax Shepard</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1333100001/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1333100001/</guid>
        <description>0:00
Hello and welcome to the armchair expert.
I&amp;rsquo;m Dax Shepard and I&amp;rsquo;m Monica Patman.
Welcome, Monica.
Let&amp;rsquo;s tell everyone what this podcast is all about.
What?
Because there&amp;rsquo;s so many.
How would you select 1 billion?
There&amp;rsquo;s one, there&amp;rsquo;s over a billion known podcast.
Some of them aren&amp;rsquo;t even known yet.
0:15
And so we just want to tell you a little bit.
What about what makes this one unique?</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
