<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/untextbooked-a-history-podcast-for-the-future/</link><description>Recent content in UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 09:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/untextbooked-a-history-podcast-for-the-future/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How Does The Legacy of Settler Expansion &amp; Industrialization Destroy Indigenous Livelihood? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Thousands of protestors joined Indigenous activists at Standing Rock to fight for clean drinking water. At its core, this fight echoes the legacy of broken treaties and settler industrialization. Producer Lily Sones talks with Dina Gilio-Whitaker (Colville Confederated Tribes) about how industrialization halted traditional indigenous food ways and how extractive industries cause health effects across today’s indigenous communities. Dina Gilio-Whitaker is an award-winning journalist and columnist. She is a lecturer of American Indian Studies at California State University San Marcos, and independent consultant and educator on environmental justice and other Indigenous policy-related issues.</description></item><item><title>What Do Our Clothes Reveal About History, Economics, and Gender? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100002/</guid><description>Podcast Description The clothes we wear say a lot about how we express ourselves. But an investigation into how these clothes ended up in our closets reveals a complex history dating back 400 years ago at the dawn of the Industrial Revolution. Producer Ashley Kim sits down with Sofi Thanhauser, the author of “Worn: A People’s History of Clothing” to learn how clothing can teach us about economics, gender and imperialism.</description></item><item><title>Why is Spoken Word Poetry Not Seen as ‘Real’ Literature? With Dr. Joshua Bennett | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Spoken word poetry is an oral tradition dating back centuries. So why is this form of poetry not always taken seriously? Producer Sydne Clarke sits down with Dr. Joshua Bennett, the author of &amp;ldquo;Spoken Word: A Cultural History&amp;rdquo;. His nonfiction debut is a personal investigation into the history of spoken word, specifically the Nuyorican Poets Cafe. This is a cultural hub that started in the Lower East Side living room of Miguel Algarin.</description></item><item><title>PTSD, Poetry and Brotherhood in World War One | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100004/</guid><description>Podcast Description In World War One, millions of soldiers saw industrial warfare unlike anything they’ve seen before: artillery shells, flame throwers, poison gas. Those who saw the war on the frontlines came home with psychological wounds the world had never quite seen before. At one military hospital in Scotland named Craiglockhart, early psychiatrists treat PTSD and soldiers turn to poetry and brotherhood to heal. UnTextbooked producer Faith Stanley sits down to talk with journalist and author Charles Glass.</description></item><item><title>What IS Venture Capital? Does it really run the tech world? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100005/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Entrepreneurs like Elon Musk and products like Chat GPT have been fueled by Venture Capital. In fact, some argue that Venture Capital has shaped our modern technology more than any other entity. But what is Venture Capital and what makes it unique? This week, UnTextbooked producer and college student Oliver Wang talks to author Sebastian Mallaby to learn about the shadow history of venture capital. What once started as a way to liberate eight scientists from a difficult boss now is a medium to inspire innovation across the world.</description></item><item><title>The Many Contradictions of Longtime FBI Director J. Edgar Hoover | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100006/</guid><description>Podcast Description J. Edgar Hoover was a man of contradictions. As the Director of the FBI from 1924 to 1972, he spearheaded homophobic, racist, and anti-communist policies – which arguably shaped half a century of the United States. But he also had an intimate personal relationship with a man and he believed in the role of government to support social conservatism. Beverly Gage is the author of “G-Man: J. Edgar Hoover and the Making of the American Century”, which won a Pulitzer Prize in Biography.</description></item><item><title>The ‘Stunt Work’ That Launched Women Into Investigative Journalism | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Women including Ida B. Wells and Nellie Bly were on the front edge of investigative journalism in the 1800s. But even with these historical trailblazers, why were women excluded from reporting hard news until recent history? Producer Jordan Pettiford sits down with author, journalist and professor Brooke Kroeger to find out. Brooke has authored six books and her most recent book is “Undaunted: How Women Changed American Journalism”. Listen to new episodes every Thursday.</description></item><item><title>Is Freedom of Speech Around the World Backsliding? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100008/</guid><description>Podcast Description From banned books to freedom of speech in academic settings, censorship is a topic that affects the everyday lives of young people. This week, UnTextbooked producer and college student Karly Shepherd talks to Eric Berkowitz, human rights lawyer, journalist and author. His latest book “Dangerous Ideas: A Brief History of Censorship from the Ancients to Fake News” covers about 2,000 years of censorship history. Censorship has existed since the dawn of language, consistently targeting themes like sex, religion and politics.</description></item><item><title>UnTextbooked is back with Season Four! | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100009/</guid><description>Podcast Description This season, we talk to an original member of the Black Panther Party. We explore the extremely contradictory life of longtime FBI director J. Edgar Hoover. We talk to Smithsonian curators about the historical connection of Disneyland to American identity. Plus, we cover topics including censorship, fast fashion, women in journalism, PTSD, Internet hackers, and more. History is full of gems to discover and pitfalls to avoid. But you wouldn’t know it when sitting in a high school history class.</description></item><item><title>UnTextbooked Out of the Studio: Reimagining a New Vision for Education at the ASU+GSV Summit | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100010/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100010/</guid><description>Podcast Description UnTextbooked heads to sunny San Diego, California, for the ASU+GSV Summit and we brought our microphones with us! Host Gabe Hostin and founding producer Victor Ye talked to innovative EdTech leaders, teachers and social entrepreneurs to discuss how we can collaboratively write a new chapter in the history of education. Plus, they ask the question, what else do we need to unlearn? This week’s guests: Steven Hernandez, ESQ, Executive Director for the Connecticut Commission on Women, Children and Seniors.</description></item><item><title>Introducing: History Detective | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode in Partnership with History Detective: On this episode of History Detective, host Kelly Chase introduces us to Tarenorerer, the Tasmanian First Nations female warrior who led her tribe against the British colonists.
About History Detective: History Detective is a podcast for teachers, students and lovers of history. It delves into stories from the past that don’t always get told in the textbooks. Every episode will include an original song that compliments the topic.</description></item><item><title>Introducing: Getting Smart | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode in Partnership with Getting Smart: On this episode of the Getting Smart Podcast Nate McClennen is joined by three incredible students who recently competed in the Regeneron Science Talent Search, an event co-hosted with Society for Science. Check out our podcast episode with Maya Ajmera to hear more about Society for Science. The students are Christine Ye, a student at Eastlake High School Aseel Rawashdeh, a student at Anderson High School, and Elijah Burks, a student at Caddo Parish Magnet High School.</description></item><item><title>Introducing: Changing Course | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus Episode in Partnership with Changing Course: Host Jonathan Santos Silva speaks with leaders and educators from The Center for Black Educator Development in Philadelphia, PA, about how to create safe spaces that value and invest in young Black leaders. The Center is the first teaching academy in Philadelphia dedicated to investing in the next generation of Black teachers, starting as early as high school. Guided by the lens that excellent education is a political act, Sharif El-Mekki and his team at the Center demonstrate how restoring education to disenfranchised students is the purest form of activism.</description></item><item><title>Best of Season 3 | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100014/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100014/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re wrapping up this incredible third season of UnTextbooked by looking back at the great work of our team of young producers. They covered topics and questions that really matter, including the rise of authoritarianism, mass incarceration, unprecedented changes in the Supreme Court, and much more! Each topic highlights how history isn’t just in the past, but also present in all of our lives.
In this episode, our host Gabe Hostin and our Youth Program Coordinator CeCe Payne discuss excerpts from episodes we couldn’t stop thinking about this season:</description></item><item><title>Is the current Supreme Court a threat to justice? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100015/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 2020, the Supreme Court was on the verge of transformation. Seismic events like the death of former Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg, the appointment of conservative justice Amy Coney Barrett, and a polarizing presidential election laid the groundwork for major changes in decision-making seen today. On this episode of UnTextbooked, producer Karly Shepherd interviews Pulitzer Prize-winning New York Times journalist Linda Greenhouse to discuss the Supreme Court’s increasing politicization and domination by the religious right.</description></item><item><title>How do democracies die? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is our democracy in danger? In the years after Trump’s presidency, it’s tempting to say “not anymore,” but nowadays threats to democracy are no longer as obvious as a military coup or revolution. Instead, a democracy in danger manifests in much more subtle ways including: the steady decline of longstanding political norms and weakening of essential institutions such as the United States press and its courts system, both of which are already in jeopardy.</description></item><item><title>Did the American Civil War ever truly end? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Although the American Civil War ended many years ago, the fight for “a more perfect union” never quite did. A few months after the union army’s victory, confederate-style, white supremacist resistance emerged even stronger than before. On this episode of UnTextbooked, producer Arya Barkesseh interviews Dr. Jeremi Suri, who argues that opposition to the union army’s victory started almost immediately after the war ended, preventing Lincoln’s vision of a genuinely united country from actually taking root.</description></item><item><title>How did citizen protests help end the Cold War? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100018/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100018/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Cold War was marked by a bitter rivalry between the United States and the Soviet Union. Although former WWII NATO allies, what emerged was an atmosphere of constant fear for national security and a dangerous nuclear arms race. On this episode of UnTextbooked, producer Lap Nguyen and Professor Susan Colbourn unpack the power of citizen protest and the crucial factors that eventually brought the contentious war to a peaceful end.</description></item><item><title>How does naval domination control who runs the world? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100019/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the 1930s, six naval powers roamed the world’s oceans: Great Britain, the United States, France, Italy, Germany, and Japan. Each nation was subject to the Washington Naval Treaty, which granted 60% of the world’s battleships to the Royal and US Navy, 20% to Japan, and 20% to France and Italy. However by 1945, the United States Navy had expanded to a fleet larger than that of all the great powers.</description></item><item><title>Was the fall of the USSR inevitable? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100020/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100020/</guid><description>Podcast Description By 1945, the Soviet Union was a founding member of the United Nations and a global superpower controlling half of Europe. By 1991, with five thousand nuclear missiles at its disposal and an army four million strong, the USSR was a formidable rival for the United States. But by the end of the year, the union would meet its untimely demise. Most historians have argued that the fall of the USSR was inevitable, but Vlad Zubok author of Collapse: The Fall of the Soviet Union sees things differently.</description></item><item><title>Is the U.S. government spying on its own citizens? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100021/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100021/</guid><description>Podcast Description As human beings, our privacy is one of our most basic needs and most sacred rights. However, in the modern information age, these rights are constantly under attack. How does the American federal government collect our data and what happens when the institutions meant to protect our privacy opts to instead use that information for their gain? On this episode of UnTextbooked, producer Victor Ye interviews Robert Scheer to discuss how we can best protect ourselves in an era where the U.</description></item><item><title>What does history teach us about the future of technology? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Technology plays a vital role in our society day-to-day, but what exactly is our role when it comes to managing our tech? How do our internal biases impact the products we create? Can technological advances actually be “neutral” as a product of human imagination? These are all questions to consider as we take a look at how human and computational infrastructures overlap. On this episode of UnTextbooked, producer Caroline Somers interviews Professor Thomas S.</description></item><item><title>What was the gay bar and how did it shape gay identity? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100023/</guid><description>Podcast Description The gay bar has long since been a locale of sexual expression, community, and most importantly, identity. If the gay bar was what Atherton Lin describes as, “a place where we hoped we could find ourselves,” what does it mean for queer identity when the spaces that once shaped and defined it are steadily vanishing in urban centers world-wide? In his wistful personal and cultural memoir, Gay Bar: Why We Went Out (named one of the best books of 2021 by the New York Times, NPR, and Vogue), essayist Jeremy Atherton Lin speaks to the impact of the gay bar on his own identity development and how the gathering space created a generation of chance encounters that shaped his life.</description></item><item><title>Is mass incarceration doing more harm than good? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100024/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100024/</guid><description>Podcast Description More American residents are behind bars than any other nation. While the U.S. Criminal Justice System was established to regulate peace and order, it has since become the catalyst for criminalizing of people of color. Fueled by initiatives like Nixon’s “War on Drugs” campaign, which unfairly targeted communities of color, mass incarceration has steadily been on the rise. Despite the staggering amount of people behind bars, the crime rates haven’t exactly been on the decline, raising the question: do prisons actually keep us safe?</description></item><item><title>How did guns divide the United States? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100025/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100025/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Second Amendment to the U.S. Constitution has roots in strong firearm regulation and gun safety policy, but over the years, it’s become a mantra for gun rights advocates. On this episode of UnTextbooked, producer Ellie Carver-Horner interviews Professor Adam Winkler about how over time, the Second Amendment to the U.S. Constitution (the right to bear arms) historically caused a major divide in the United States and the impact of that extreme split today.</description></item><item><title>What is religious racism and how has it progressed from past to present? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100026/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100026/</guid><description>Podcast Description The first amendment to the United States Constitution guarantees that everyone has the right to practice his or her own religion or no religion at all. A similar guarantee exists in Canada under its Charter of Rights and Freedoms. However, this right to religious freedom hasn’t necessarily been assured for practitioners of traditional African religions throughout history in North America and beyond. On this episode of UnTextbooked, producer Jordan Pettiford interviews Dr.</description></item><item><title>Are we telling U.S. Indigenous history wrong? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100027/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100027/</guid><description>Podcast Description There are more than five hundred federally recognized Indigenous nations in the United States today, nearly three million people, but their stories have largely been omitted from the nation’s history. On this episode of UnTextbooked, producer Gavin Scott interviews acclaimed historian and activist, Professor Roxanne Dunbar-Ortiz and takes a look at U.S. History through the lens of Indigenous Peoples and unpacks what we’ve been missing as a nation without their perspective.</description></item><item><title>Season Three: New Questions, New Answers | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100029/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Untextbooked is a movement of curious students from around the world &amp;ndash; and we are BACK with new episodes and new questions. What perspectives do we miss in history class? What historical forces shape our lives today? We study up on topics that interest us &amp;ndash; indigenous history, the status of democracy, future of technology &amp;ndash; and then reach out to scholars to have a conversation for the podcast.</description></item><item><title>What is causing the global fall of democracy? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100028/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Throughout the world, democratic progress has not only halted, but receded over the past few years and the United States has been one of the main perpetrators.
On this episode of UnTextbooked, producer Oliver Wang interviews Former Deputy National Security Advisor of the United States (Obama Administration), Ben Rhodes to discover who is to blame for the global fall of democracy and how we might return to a truly democratic identity.</description></item><item><title>Best of Season 2 | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100030/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 02:51:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100030/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’ve completed our second season of UnTextbooked! Our team of young producers have done phenomenal work exploring topics and questions that really matter, including episodes about the War on Terror, Native American boarding schools, population control, and much more. In this episode our editor Bethany Denton shares excerpts from four of her favorite Season 2 episodes: Is every presidency doomed to fail? Can the War on Terror ever truly end?</description></item><item><title>Did anyone win the Cold War? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100031/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100031/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Cold War was a decades-long military conflict that dominated geopolitics in the latter half of the 20th century. And as Americans, we often see it framed as a binary conflict between the United States and the Soviet Union; one that ended around the time the Berlin Wall came down in 1989. But historian Odd Arne Westad, author of The Global Cold War, thinks that version of the story is incomplete.</description></item><item><title>Did segregation in America ever really end? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100032/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100032/</guid><description>Podcast Description The United States is still reckoning with its history of racism. For a century after slavery ended, US businesses, banks, schools, and neighborhoods were segregated by race. It took a series of Supreme Court cases and acts of Congress to legally ban discrimination based on race, but discrimination isn’t just a switch that can be turned from “on” to “off.” The legacy of these unfair laws still affect Black Americans today.</description></item><item><title>When will Asian Americans stop being seen as "perpetual foreigners"? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100033/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100033/</guid><description>Podcast Description There is a fundamental duality in how Asian Americans are perceived in our country. They’ve at times been held up as the “model minority”, affirming this idea that the American Dream is alive and well if only immigrants could work harder. At other times they’ve been regarded as threatening and perpetually foreign. A recent example of this is the dramatic rise in anti-Asian violence in the wake of the covid-19 pandemic.</description></item><item><title>What does American cuisine tell us about the United States? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100034/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100034/</guid><description>Podcast Description American food is unlike anything else in the world. And it goes a lot deeper than hamburgers and pizza. The thing that makes American food special is the stunning variety of options and how accessible it is to the average consumer. Also some regional American dishes that are impossible to find anywhere else on the planet Dr. Paul Freedman is a historian who thinks that all of these factors&amp;ndash;standardization, variety, and regionality&amp;ndash;can tell us a lot about American culture and identity.</description></item><item><title>Why do Brazilian cars run on sugar? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100035/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100035/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s no secret that society will eventually have to transition away from fossil fuels. Some governments and businesses think the answer is biofuels,like ethanol. Ethanol is a type of alcohol—the same type of alcohol that humans have been producing for millenia. And so, in much of the world, the techniques to produce ethanol are already known and exploited. All it takes is the fermentation of sugary crop, like potatoes, corn, or sugarcane.</description></item><item><title>What does resilience look like for Iranian women? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100036/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100036/</guid><description>Podcast Description For centuries, Iran had a strict social hierarchy that prevented women—particularly upper class women—from participating in public life. This started to change in the early 20th century when Iranians became disillusioned with the ruling class and had a constitutional revolution. This new constitution established a parliament, public schools, and also opened the door for women to start asserting their own rights to education and employment. Following the constitutional revolution was a period of rapid modernization in Iran.</description></item><item><title>How did tolerance become an American value? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100037/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100037/</guid><description>Podcast Description There’s a lot of evidence that America is more divided than ever. Our politics, media, and ideologies are so polarized that it puts a stress on our unity as a country. But Dr. Denis Lacorne says that, in spite of that tension, America’s strength comes from our nation’s commitment to tolerance. The trick is figuring out the balance of tolerating the intolerant. On this episode of UnTextbooked, producer Karly Shepherd interviews Dr.</description></item><item><title>Is every presidency doomed to fail? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100038/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100038/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Founders of the United States envisioned the presidency as an office that would be minimal in reach. They didn’t want the USA to be a monarchy. But incrementally, the executive branch has expanded. And now, scholars like Dr. Jeremi Suri argue that the modern presidency is crushed by its own power and unable to be fully wielded by the President, leading to decades of broken promises and deep disillusionment amongst citizens.</description></item><item><title>How did Black Americans forge a cultural identity? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100039/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100039/</guid><description>Podcast Description UnTextbooked producer Sydne Clarke thinks that African American history is often oversimplified or overlooked. Often that history is taught as things that happened to African Americans. We don’t often hear about the ways in which African Americans fought for and took care of themselves. Dr. Leslie Alexander studies Black resistance movements, particularly in America. In her research Dr. Alexander has discovered communities and people who were vital to Black activism, but are often forgotten in re-telling African American history.</description></item><item><title>Were history’s greatest leaders generalists or specialists? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100040/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100040/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Greek poet Archilochus said “a fox knows many things, a hedgehog knows one big thing.” This phrase inspired a famous essay by a 20th century philosopher named Isaiah Berlin, who said that pretty much all people can be categorized as either “foxes” or “hedgehogs”. Foxes tend to be agile and perceptive, whereas hedgehogs tend to be resolute and hyper-focused on their end goal. Historian John Lewis Gaddis took Berlin’s framework one step further.</description></item><item><title>Is there an American Empire? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100041/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100041/</guid><description>Podcast Description With a name like “The United States of America”, it can be easy to forget that this country’s borders extend well beyond the fifty states of the union. In fact, millions of American citizens live on US territory well outside those borders. It’s not just Guam, Puerto Rico, American Samoa, the US Virgin Islands, and the North Mariana Islands, but the many military bases we occupy across the globe too.</description></item><item><title>Does population control work? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100042/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100042/</guid><description>Podcast Description A hundred years ago, there were roughly 2 billion people in the world. Today, there are almost 8 billion. This rapid quadrupling of the world’s population has people asking, is the planet overpopulated? Some say, yes. Others say that it’s not so simple. This isn’t a new question. Researchers in the 19th and 20th centuries warned that unfettered population growth would lead to famine, poverty, and climate destruction. Some governments and aid agencies took those warnings to heart, and implemented programs to try and lower fertility rates.</description></item><item><title>Why were Native American kids required to attend boarding schools? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100043/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100043/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the spring of 2021, UnTextbooked producer Gavin Scott read a headline that made his heart sink. The remains of 215 indigenous children were discovered buried in a mass grave near the Kamloops Indian Residential School in Kamloops, British Columbia. Over the next few months, more mass graves were found outside of other Canadian residential schools. Before they died, these children had been part of a program of forced assimilation.</description></item><item><title>Can protests save lives? How ACT UP helped tame the AIDS crisis. | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100044/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100044/</guid><description>Podcast Description One morning in 1991, Senator Jesse Helms’ house was covered with a giant fake condom in an act of protest. Helms had been a vocal opponent of funding AIDS research and he had introduced an infamous and popular bill amendment that prevented federal money from being spent on AIDS research. There were few treatments available at the time, and with no help from the government, HIV was actively spreading across the country.</description></item><item><title>Can the War on Terror ever truly end? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100045/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100045/</guid><description>Podcast Description The War On Terror is the longest foreign war the United States has ever fought. So long that many of the soldiers fighting weren’t even alive when it started. But the WoT seems unusual for another reason—it’s not a war on a nation, or even an organization—it’s a war against a concept. September 11, 2001 was the alleged start date of this conflict, after the Twin Towers fell. President George W.</description></item><item><title>Season 2 is coming soon! | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100046/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Season 2 of UnTextbooked is near! New episodes starting Monday, Octoberr 18th, 2021.
Join us for 15 more interviews where young people ask historians the questions that matter most. Watch the video trailer: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nB46hxDFQ58 And come to our launch party: https://us02web.zoom.us/meeting/register/tZEkcO6vqTkiGdRvraFhbERExj8gxGWbW2DR
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of Season 1 | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100047/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100047/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’ve wrapped our first season of UnTextbooked! Our producers have explored race, food, piracy, gender, medicine and so much more. In this episode, UnTextbooked editor Bethany Denton shares five of her favorite moments from the season: How a Black teenager and his young lawyer changed America&amp;rsquo;s criminal justice system. Most Americans eat like kings without realizing it. Damnation to the governor and confusion to the colony. Germany addressed its racist past.</description></item><item><title>Why did American Jews march for Black equality? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100048/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Throughout this series, we’ve heard historians say that the way Americans think about race is changing, as evidenced by the unprecedented numbers of Americans marching after George Floyd’s death. And along with this surge in action are critical conversations about what it means to be an ally, and what it means to “perform” allyship. UnTextbooked producer Daniel Ardity noticed what he thought to be a lot of empty support for the Black Lives Matter movement in the summer of 2020&amp;ndash;particularly when his Instagram feed was full of black squares one day in June.</description></item><item><title>Why do so many Westerners fear the veil? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100049/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 19:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100049/</guid><description>Podcast Description People in the West have many harmful perceptions about Muslim women being submissive or oppressed. In fact, a study conducted by the Pew Research Center found that only 19% of Americans believed that Islam is respectful of women. These beliefs have been reinforced for centuries through media portrayals and stereotypes. One of those persistent stereotypes is that Muslim women are forced against their will to wear hijab, and as a result the veil has come to symbolize women’s oppression.</description></item><item><title>Most Americans eat like kings without realizing it. | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100050/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 19:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100050/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s undeniable that the way people eat has changed drastically in the last century. It took thousands of years for human societies to transition from hunter-gatherers to farmers. By contrast, it’s only been in the last hundred years or so that people have moved away from growing their own crops and raising their own livestock to getting most of their food from a restaurant or store. Food historian Rachel Laudan thinks that this recent and rapid transition is ultimately a good thing.</description></item><item><title>Why do we forget the cruelty of the British Empire? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100051/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100051/</guid><description>Podcast Description On April 13, 1919, thousands of Indians gathered in Amritsar, Punjab to celebrate Baisakhi - a religious holiday. Such gatherings had been banned by the British colonial government, but the people gathered anyway to celebrate and to protest British imperialism. What followed was the Jallianwala Bagh Massacre; British General Reginald Dyer ordered his troops to open fire without warning on the crowd of unarmed protesters. They fired until they ran out of ammunition, killing 379 and wounding more than a thousand people (though the final death toll has been disputed over the years.</description></item><item><title>How America’s fear of communism paved the way for a Chilean dictator. | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100052/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100052/</guid><description>Podcast Description During the Cold War, the United States feared the rise of Communism across the world. But in Latin America, the United States took action. In 1970, Salvador Allende won the Chilean presidency with just a third of the vote. He was a socialist who started shaking things up across the country. Within just a couple years, a military coup removed him from power, and Augusto Pinochet, the American-backed strongman, replaced him.</description></item><item><title>Damnation to the governor and confusion to the colony. | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100053/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 19:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pop culture misremembers the Golden Age of piracy, and usually portrays pirates as apolitical agents of chaos. But historians now believe that many pirates followed a democratic and egalitarian structure that put them directly at odds with the world’s biggest governments. In the 1700’s, life as a European sailor left a lot to be desired. Wages were low, conditions were dangerous, and captains could be cruel. A lot of sailors wanted out.</description></item><item><title>How much influence does America still have? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100054/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100054/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1987, the historian Paul Kennedy published a massive, nearly 700 page book called The Rise and Fall of the Great Powers. In normal circumstances, the book might have been lumped in with the rest of academic writing that’s seen only by scholars…if it weren’t for the book’s conclusion, which flew in the face of American exceptionalism and certainly upset some people. In that final section of the book, Kennedy suggests that the United States had begun a period of relative decline that began in the 1960’s.</description></item><item><title>The forgotten mothers of American gynecology. | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100055/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100055/</guid><description>Podcast Description James Marion Sims has a complicated legacy. He was a surgeon in the 19th century who, for decades, was heralded as the ‘Father of American Gynecology’ for his contributions to the field, including inventing the speculum. But those innovations came at the expense of the poor and enslaved women that he performed experimental surgeries on. Not much is known about the Black enslaved women and poor Irish immigrants he experimented on, but without their contributions, gynecology would not be what it is today.</description></item><item><title>When did Americans become so dependent on processed foods? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100056/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100056/</guid><description>Podcast Description For decades, experts have warned that the average American diet is potentially harmful. Americans tend to eat food that is laden with too much sodium, fat, and added sugars, and it&amp;rsquo;s making people sick. What’s insidious about this is that a lot of Americans don’t even know that the food they’re eating is unhealthy. A lot of foods are deceptively sweeter, saliter, and fattier than one would assume. And those added ingredients make processed foods addictive.</description></item><item><title>A historical argument against the gender binary. | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100057/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 19:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100057/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a kid, UnTextbooked producer Gavin Scott loved listening to his grandfather tell stories about their people. He used to like to imagine what his home was like back before white settlers came. As much as Gavin enjoyed learning about his culture, he sometimes felt out of place as the only gay person he knew of in his small hometown. So when he had the opportunity to work on this podcast, he decided to research LGBT Native Americans to learn more about people who were like him.</description></item><item><title>How a Black teenager and his young lawyer changed America’s criminal justice system. | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100058/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2020 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Picture this: You’re nineteen years old, it’s a summer afternoon, and you’re driving around your hometown. You notice a group of other teenagers on the side of the road. As you get closer you realize that two of them are your cousin and nephew. You can tell by body language that things are getting heated, tempers are flaring. So you pull over. You get out of your car. You step in between your family and the other teenagers that are trying to fight them, and in the process you put your hand on the other kid’s arm.</description></item><item><title>The false mythology of good leadership. | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100059/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100059/</guid><description>Podcast Description There’s a certain mythos around the founders of the United States. George Washington gets this treatment to the extreme. He’s painted riding brilliant white horses, standing up in boats, and puffing out his chest as he presides over the signing of the Constitution. He’s essentially an American folk hero. What’s odd is that this mythical understanding of a real person conceals the truth of what real leadership looks like.</description></item><item><title>Does America live up to its own ideals? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100060/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 20:30:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Democracy: a small word and a big concept foundational to the United States. Ideally, we’re a country of pluralism and self determination, but the reality is often different. Many dark chapters exist in our history: Slavery and the extermination of Native Americans, Disenfranchisement and voter suppression. Japanese internment and white supremacy. And yet, many of the ideals that surround the founding of our country do slowly bend us towards justice.</description></item><item><title>History fails when it ignores the BIPOC women who made it. | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100061/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 18:11:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Women of color have been at the forefront of many movements, yet are often neglected, demonized, or ignored. Your history class probably didn’t teach you about Josephine Baker, who was not only a famous Black dancer and entertainer, but also a spy aiding in the French Resistance. You likely didn’t learn about Claudette Colvin either. She was the Black, pregnant fifteen year old whose civil disobedience kicked off the Montgomery Bus Boycott.</description></item><item><title>Germany addressed its racist past. Can America do the same? | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100062/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 17:31:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100062/</guid><description>Podcast Description As the ashes of the Third Reich settled, a divided Germany struggled to come to terms with what just occurred. Generations of German philosophers, politicians, academics, and common citizens slowly and collectively decided to confront the horrific actions of the Nazis. They called this process “Vergangenheitsaufarbeitung”, or “working off the past”, though it has several names. Step by step, through a feeling of collective guilt and moral responsibility, they were able to make amends with the world and build legal and societal safeguards against hatred and extremism.</description></item><item><title>Introducing UnTextbooked: a history podcast for the future. | UnTextbooked | A history podcast for the future</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6336100063/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 21:31:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6336100063/</guid><description>Podcast Description UnTextbooked is a history podcast for the future. Brought to you by teen changemakers who are looking for answers to big questions. We interview famous historians who have some of the answers. These intergenerational conversations bring the full power of history to you with the depth and vividness that most textbooks lack. Real history, to help you find answers to your big questions. UnTextbooked makes history unboring forever. Full episodes coming Fall 2020.</description></item></channel></rss>