<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Amazing Sport Stories on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/amazing-sport-stories/</link><description>Recent content in Amazing Sport Stories on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 01:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/amazing-sport-stories/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Curse of County Mayo: Ep 3 | Amazing Sport Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9013060010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9013060010/</guid><description>Podcast Description As Mayo prepare for the All-Ireland Championship, a formidable obstacle stands in their way. Will the men from Mayo finally win the coveted tournament and vanquish talk of the curse once and for all? Meanwhile, the truth about what really happened that day in Foxford more than 70 years ago is finally within reach. Episode 3 of 3. Let us know what you think of #AmazingSportStories
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Curse of County Mayo: Ep 2 | Amazing Sport Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9013060001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9013060001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Was County Mayo’s Irish football team really cursed in 1951? Sports reporter Dave McKenna hears from the last remaining member of the 1951 Mayo All-Ireland squad. Does he remember a priest cursing the team? And does he believe the curse is real? Dave’s investigation leads him to the town of Foxford, the site where legend dictates it all began. And sad news changes the course of the investigation. Episode 2 of 3.</description></item><item><title>The Curse of County Mayo: Ep 1 | Amazing Sport Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9013060002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9013060002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is County Mayo’s Gaelic football team cursed? You might have heard of the “Curse of Bambino” for the Boston Red Sox in US baseball. This is the story of Ireland’s equivalent. Irish-American sports reporter Dave McKenna investigates this curious case to find out if a decades old hex is behind their recent failures. Did the team really disrespect a funeral in 1951? And did that cause the mysterious bad luck that’s plagued the team ever since?</description></item><item><title>Trailer: Cursed? | Amazing Sport Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9013060003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9013060003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ireland’s “cursed” Gaelic football team – our next amazing sport story. Can County Mayo’s failure to win the All-Ireland Championship really be the result of a curse put on the team more than 70 years ago?
The three-part season with Dave McKenna is coming soon.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The never-ending tunnel | Amazing Sport Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9013060004/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9013060004/</guid><description>Podcast Description At 200 miles, it might not be the world's longest race, but Tunnel Ultra is certainly the darkest. It's a gruelling two-day endurance event where competitors run underground laps in single-file, to a backdrop of classical music. Headphones are banned but hallucinations are all but guaranteed, with sightings of abominable snowmen, giant slugs and orange blobby monsters all reported. So why do people do it? This is the story of those who do, including one who suffered temporary blindness.</description></item><item><title>Frozen Out: Ep 3 | Amazing Sport Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9013060005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9013060005/</guid><description>Podcast Description The backlash becomes serious, but Justine Blainey refuses to give up. Will her long journey for equality on the ice rink be finally over? She’s stayed strong through the backlash from haters and a succession of court cases. She is now breathtakingly close to her dream of playing for a boys’ ice hockey team. Hosted by double Olympic gold medallist Cassie Campbell-Pascall. Episode three of three. Let us know what you think #AmazingSportStories</description></item><item><title>Frozen Out: Ep 2 | Amazing Sport Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9013060006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9013060006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Justine takes her fight to court. If she’s the best, why does her gender matter? The legal team argue it is her constitutional right. Despite supportive family and teammates, Justine is only 12 and the pressure is getting to her. The judge is about to make the ruling. Can Justine win her case? Hosted by double Olympic gold medallist Cassie Campbell-Pascall. Episode two of three. Let us know what you think #AmazingSportStories</description></item><item><title>Frozen Out: Ep 1 | Amazing Sport Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9013060007/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 01:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9013060007/</guid><description>Podcast Description “You're good enough but you’re a girl”. Twelve year old Justine just wants to play ice hockey – with the boys. When she’s told she can’t, she writes a letter which will change everything. Double Olympic gold medallist and former Canadian team captain Cassie Campbell-Pascall tells the story of Justine Blainey. Episode 1 of 3.
Let us know what you think of #AmazingSportStories
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trailer: Frozen Out | Amazing Sport Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9013060008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9013060008/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Yes you’re good enough, we wish we could take you. But you’re a girl.” Schoolgirl Justine’s fight for the right to play in a boys’ ice hockey team. She is a talented player who wants to get to the top of her game. And her fight to change the rules takes her all the way to Canada’s highest court of justice. Presented by double Olympic ice hockey gold medallist Cassie Campbell-Pascall.</description></item><item><title>Introducing Amazing Sport Stories | Amazing Sport Stories</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/9013060009/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/9013060009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sport but not as you know it. Imagine being stranded in the “death zone” on one of the world’s highest mountains. How about running 200 miles in a dark tunnel? We’ve been searching the world for the most amazing sport stories. Other podcasts bring you the scores and team news. This one tells the stories you’ll wish you’d known about and now probably won’t forget. You don’t need to be obsessed with sport to find yourself immersed in our mini-seasons and short stories.</description></item></channel></rss>