<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Western Australia Police Force: Cold Case on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/western-australia-police-force-cold-case/</link><description>Recent content in Western Australia Police Force: Cold Case on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/western-australia-police-force-cold-case/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Jimmy Taylor | Western Australia Police Force: Cold Case</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3638260001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3638260001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jimmy Taylor was a 12-year-old boy when he disappeared from the Kimberley town of Derby on 29 August, 1974. His disappearance has been connected to a notorious child killer who is currently incarcerated in Tasmania.
Want to help us solve cases just like these? Let’s Join Forces. Find out more about a career with WA Police: https://letsjoinforces.wa.gov.au/ If you have any information relating to the cases featured in the Cold Case WA podcast, contact Crime Stoppers on 1800 333 000 or https://www.</description></item><item><title>Felicia Wilson | Western Australia Police Force: Cold Case</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3638260002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3638260002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Felicia Wilson was a 19-year-old beauty pageant contestant who was engaged to be married when her life was brutally cut short in Kwinana on 10 January, 1979. Listen here for interviews with detectives close to the case, and her family – who continue to search for answers regarding Felicia’s death. Want to help us solve cases just like these? Let’s Join Forces. Find out more about a career with WA Police: https://letsjoinforces.</description></item><item><title>Welcome to Cold Case WA | Western Australia Police Force: Cold Case</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3638260003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3638260003/</guid><description>Podcast Description They&amp;apos;re the crimes that continue to haunt grieving family members and the wider community - cold case murders.
Cold Case Western Australia is the official podcast of WA Police Force which examines unsolved murders.
The series includes in-depth interviews with detectives investigating the cases, and with family members of the victims.
Cold Case Western Australia is hosted by Neil Poh - a veteran crime reporter and a former media advisor for WA Police Force.</description></item></channel></rss>