<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Wolf and Owl on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/wolf-and-owl/</link><description>Recent content in Wolf and Owl on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 03:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/wolf-and-owl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>S2 Ep 84: Santas &amp; Celebrities | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390001/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… 100 day coughs, Christmas fairgrounds, I’m A Celebrity contestants, very boring stories, Heathrow hassles, family songs, legendary roast dinners, a Chesney Hawkes revelation, exchanging phone numbers and two Mary Poppins auditions. Plus, email questions about Cyberpunk 2077 and a potentially friendship-ending secret Santa gift. For questions or comments, please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Instagram - @wolfowlpod TikTok - @wolfowlpodcast YouTube - www.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 83: Wonka Premiere &amp; Radio Rom | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390002/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… a week of Wonka, hotel apologies, concentrating on content and social media memes, premiere parties, red carpet regrets, Rom’s new Radio 2 show, using local greengrocers and Tom’s takeaway crisis. Then it’s email time, with questions on taking a punt on reaching out to a celebrity and attitudes to calling in sick at work. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 82: Hotel Snobs &amp; Rom’s HYROX | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390003/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… Christmas shopping, hotel rejections and snobbish staff, Rom’s HYROX challenge (shout out to Chrissy!), Jill Scott smashing it on ALOTO, excessive swearing, great gigs and shaky warm-up shows, miss-pronouncing place names, missing out on a roast, a rescued phone and some lacklustre anecdotes. Plus, the Wolf &amp;amp; Owl at the Wonka premiere! For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 81: Cocaine Hippos &amp; On-Screen Kissing | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390004/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… listener complaints, Christmas lunch confirmations, travel shows and Asian Provocateur, Pablo Escobar’s hippos, how to brag, failed auditions, on-screen kisses, snogging vs French kissing, a curious case of the cooties and dickhead mints. Plus, a couple of tricky email questions about a relative’s offensive language and a sex chat-bot dilemma. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Instagram - @wolfowlpod TikTok - @wolfowlpodcast YouTube - www.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 80: Double Illness &amp; A Christmas Lunch | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 14:02:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390005/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… tattoos and hair-do’s, meeting 50 Cent, an ill Tom and a very run-down Rom, sad hotels, a round of golf with Jim, a Ranganathan and Davis family Christmas lunch, burgers followed by curry and the wonders of echinacea. Then we answer some email questions about recording live stand-up shows and advice on muffling farts - plus a very surreal debate about moody hippos and smiling giraffes. Trigger warning - this episode contains an excessive amount of bleeping.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 79: Friday Bonus with a Laughing Emoji | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390006/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390006/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s bonus time! And we’re talking… love for the North, hotel upgrades, supporting actors, losing your temper, Ross Kemp rabbit holes and an Emoji Movie remake. Then it’s onto some email questions about putting your foot in it at a wedding and a best mate’s annoying habits (read at Rom’s x2 speed). Thanks for all your messages - keep them coming at wolfowlpod@gmail.com Instagram - @wolfowlpod TikTok - @wolfowlpodcast YouTube - www.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 78: Wardrobes, Coffee &amp; TikTok Tom | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390007/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… messy wardrobes, high-level hygiene, a very strange dinner table, the errors of hanging up T-shirts, loud irons, cap collections, Tom’s new TikTok videos, social media food reviewers, Pret problems, bogus baristas, a very dubious story about cronuts and some calorie confusion. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Instagram - @wolfowlpod TikTok - @wolfowlpodcast YouTube - www.youtube.com/WolfandOwlPodcast Merch &amp;amp; Mailing List - https://wolfandowlpod.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 77: Space Food &amp; Scandalous Seeds | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390008/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… party Tom, old-school hotel rooms, lost light switches, catering in space and astronaut caretakers, moon tourism, asking a stranger the time, party icebreakers, round two of the great fruit &amp;amp; veg seed debate, DIY successes, eureka moments, first day filming and looking good (or bad) in lycra. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Instagram - @wolfowlpod TikTok - @wolfowlpodcast YouTube - www.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 76: Stand-Up Celebrations &amp; Saturday Chefs | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390009/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… Tom at the Hackney Empire, Rom’s warm-up gigs, end of show celebrations, the acceptability of jumping into the crowd, some mischievous misreporting, the mystery of a very intimidating audience member and dealing with successes and criticisms. Then it’s a glowing report from Rom’s recent appearance on Saturday Kitchen, the challenges of not swearing on live TV, a minor sticky toffee pudding scandal, some serious beef with burgers and the difference between fruit and veg.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 75: Friday Bonus &amp; A Seinfeld Quiz | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390010/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Before we hit the emails, Rom challenges Tom to a Seinfeld quiz and we discuss our current TV obsessions, life after reality shows and the problems with YouTube boxers. Then we answer some more of your questions - this week about how to switch off and relax whilst juggling a hectic life, making the first move with a work colleague and some inspiration for a romantic gesture. Thanks for all your messages - keep them coming at wolfowlpod@gmail.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 74: Self-Tan &amp; Airport Pranks | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390011/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390011/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… Tom’s broken boiler, holidaying in Spain, a calamitous self-tan lotion miss-communication, hotel prank calls, bumpy landings, duty-free scares, the best flabbergaster in the game, Rom’s West Country gigs, the brilliant Fatiha El-Ghorri and a query about backstage banter. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Instagram - @wolfowlpod TikTok - @wolfowlpodcast YouTube - www.youtube.com/WolfandOwlPodcast Merch &amp;amp; Mailing List - https://wolfandowlpod.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 73: Friday Bonus &amp; Sporting Fails | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390012/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bonus emails time! First we discuss some of our sporting disappointments and general lack of competitiveness, along with some recent feedback about recycling. Then it’s time for the main event - a real mix bag of questions on manscaping, calling out a friend for being racist, impressions of each other and a ‘would you rather’ challenge. Thanks for all your messages - keep them coming at wolfowlpod@gmail.com Instagram - @wolfowlpod TikTok - @wolfowlpodcast YouTube - www.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 72: No Ideas &amp; Insta Strategies | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390013/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390013/</guid><description>Podcast Description After worrying they’ve absolutely nothing to talk about on this week’s pod, Rom and Tom pull 50 minutes of chat out the bag! We’re talking… bedroom presenting, Apollo shows, the greatness of Denise van Outen, illnesses and tour show tickets, making friends with actors, Instagram strategies, TikTok obsessions, a Wolf &amp;amp; Owl FPL update, film stars and billionaires, the Beckham documentary, buying a football club and Tom learning to drive (again).</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 71: Friday Bonus &amp; An A.I. Email | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390014/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390014/</guid><description>Podcast Description First up - a bit of pod admin, some chat about nicknames, Rom’s rap with Verb T and Doc Brown, a potential school for Grace (featuring the Pythagorasaurus) and some back-pedalling from Tom on Mervyn Stutters. Then we answer emails about a parenting clash over a bowl haircut, our first question from A.I. and the acceptability of having a chamber pot in your bedroom. Thanks for all your messages - keep them coming at wolfowlpod@gmail.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 70: Crawley Gigs &amp; Neglected Elbows | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390015/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… revealing T-shirts, self-deprecating texts, panic attacks, Rom’s mum at Tom’s Crawley gig, neglecting your elbows, thanking inanimate objects, Mathew McConaughey (again!), deodorants and aftershave, three recycling questions, the phenomena of Harry Styles and our old friend Married At First Sight. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Instagram - @wolfowlpod TikTok - @wolfowlpodcast YouTube - www.youtube.com/WolfandOwlPodcast Merch &amp;amp; Mailing List - https://wolfandowlpod.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 69: Friday Bonus &amp; A Sleep Story | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390016/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s bonus time again! And this week we tackle email questions about which wrist to wear a watch on (WARNING: this topic is not as innocent as it may sound), going to stand-up gigs on your own, a fraudulent boss, experimenting with ASMR and a Wolf and Owl Sleep Story. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Instagram - @wolfowlpod TikTok - @wolfowlpodcast YouTube - www.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 68: Fringe Issues &amp; Renewed Vows | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390017/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… celebrity best friends, not swearing on TV shows, regrettable tour posters, Tom’s problems with a Pick Of The Fringe show, Newcastle buskers, QR codes, Rom’s new tattoo, thirsty Hobbits, renewed marriage vows and getting very lost. Don’t miss the bonus episode on Friday for this week’s emails. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Instagram - @wolfowlpod TikTok - @wolfowlpodcast YouTube - www.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 67: Our Best Bonus Show Ever | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390018/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390018/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s all about hugely positive vibes on this week’s super-special bonus episode! And once we catch our breath after all the excitement, we answer emails on Wolf &amp;amp; Owl adverts, advice for finding a partner, Tom’s recent Cambridge gig and Rom presenting A League Of Their Own. Have yourselves a wonderful Friday! Thanks for all your messages - keep them coming at wolfowlpod@gmail.com Instagram - @wolfowlpod TikTok - @wolfowlpodcast YouTube - www.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 66: Mushroom Powder &amp; An E-Scooter | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390019/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… croaky voices, very chatty audiences, punting problems, unexpected house visitors, a missing Swan, post-show etiquette and showing enthusiasm, farmer’s markets, a very charming mushroom powder salesman and Rom’s very short-lived electric scooter plans. Look out for the bonus episode on Friday! It&amp;rsquo;s already recorded so definitely happening. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Instagram - @wolfowlpod TikTok - @wolfowlpodcast YouTube - www.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 65: Confetti Cannons &amp; Lost Keys | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390020/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… confetti cannons, new W&amp;amp;O Live dates, a carvery gold card, the similarities between carrots and lemmings, new boxer shorts, lost house key conundrums, night pisses, deep-fried boiled eggs and early stand-up travel missions. Apologies for Rom’s poor sound quality - we had some serious technical gremlins on this one. New Wolf &amp;amp; Owl Live date! Thursday 2nd November at the Hammersmith Apollo, London. Sign up to our mailing list at wolfandowlpod.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 64: Carvery Love &amp; Insect Apologies | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is it a bonus episode - or a part two to last week’s show? We&amp;rsquo;re not really sure but either way, we’re talking… second halves, eating on camera, Toby Carveries and very early roasts, open-mic spots, Rom’s blazer years, some hard back-peddling on Tom’s attitude to insects and deciding when to retire (or not). For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 63: Spiders, Wasps &amp; Baby Flies | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390022/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… late starts, sore throats, swearing at football matches, Tom’s new tour, speedy spiders and baby flies, wasp stings and bee allergies, Takeshi’s Castle (mango!) and friends in the front row. It’s a shorter show than usual this week but fingers crossed we’ll have a bonus episode for you on Friday. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Instagram - @wolfowlpod TikTok - @wolfowlpodcast YouTube - www.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 62: Film Pitches &amp; Teeth Cheats | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390023/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… guest rap verses, an 8 Mile remake, Tom&amp;rsquo;s film pitches for Rom and The Rise of ‘Easy’ Eliot Buchanan, very patient dentists, not following instructions, a holiday debrief, airport fast-food, travel trouble, massage pants and keeping flexible. Then some email questions on how best to deal with a wacky sales assistant and a scandalous secret about a meat-eating vegan. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 61: Family Holidays &amp; Root Canals | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390024/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… curtain calamities, two wrong hotels, holiday swimming challenges and a near death experience, Lionesses pride, an FPL ‘Sexy Ballers’ update, root canal after-care, talking too loudly in public, troubling TikTok videos and responding to trolls. Plus, some new TV chat and an email question about a very problematic boss. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Instagram - @wolfowlpod TikTok - @wolfowlpodcast YouTube - www.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 60: ’Hope is a prick in disguise’ | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390025/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390025/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… a hungover Wolf, bad golf and getting stroppy, the benefits of a losing mentality, hosting stresses, tidy houses, music playlist bullies, an FPL Sexy Ballers team, booking the wrong holiday, Segway crashes and a mysterious couple at Centre Parks. Then some email questions on the consequences of being too open with friends and meeting up with listeners of the pod (or not). For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 59: Fashion Fails &amp; Fantasy Football | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390026/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390026/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… not wearing shorts, skinny jeans and snug tracksuits, outfit planning, online clothes shopping gripes, bad camera angles and being filmed for the pod, a personalised West Ham shirt, glory clubs, football celebrations and the long-awaited details of our Fantasy Premier League. Then we answer some email questions on making the most of your hair and a problem with a neighbour&amp;rsquo;s parcel. That all important code for our FPL - 3bgl86 For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 58: Twitter Trouble &amp; A Visible Penis | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390027/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390027/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… safety signage, hand washing, not being recognised, Maaate gate and a busy week on Twitter, festival comedy, Rom’s 50 Years Of Hip Hop set at Latitude, Tom’s excessive bogies and an unfortunate incident with a visible penis on a train. Then, after another update on the long-awaited Mukbang Special, we answers email questions on a sour cream controversy and a sensitive parental problem. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 57: Body Talk &amp; Hot Sauce | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390028/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… manhandling cameras, disappointing photos, moobs and fluctuating body-confidence, a pact to talk more positively about ourselves, staying hydrated, miniature bottles of hot sauce, food regrets and very early bedtimes. Plus, we tackle a tricky email question about a moral conflict at work. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Instagram - @wolfowlpod TikTok - @wolfowlpodcast YouTube - www.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 56: Two Streets, One Name | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390029/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390029/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s a slightly shaky start to the show but the Wolf and Owl are back in the studio together! We’re talking… street name confusion and late arrivals, heavy tipping, alpha vibes, dour demeanours and being wanton, an Educating Rita remake, Sunday Brunch, one-line texting, Weetabix wars and some parental discipline roll-play. Plus, we offer advice to a listener on whether to buy a motorbike or not. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 55: Summer Fetes &amp; Death | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390030/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390030/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… vegan fish &amp;amp; chips, finger-licking eating, Mukbang poll results, bare-feet podding, getting caught short on trains, noisy fruit, enjoying summer fetes, contemplating death and working out what heaven’s like. Then we answer some email questions on how to deal with a bullying manager at work, disappointment with dating apps and the possibility of a W&amp;amp;O fantasy football league. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 54: New Wi-Fi &amp; A Bonus Show | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390031/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390031/</guid><description>Podcast Description After last week’s internet dramas and shortened show, we’re kicking off this week with an extra episode! We’re talking… dressing room pressures, mistaken identities, pod reviews and Insta polls, ‘Richie’ Sunak, the greatness of Glasgow, being back in the Wi-Fi game, hobbit furniture and pizza pioneers. Plus, a W&amp;amp;O trip to New York and an email question about not liking birthdays. We&amp;rsquo;ll be back again as usual on Wednesday… For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 53: The Skid Mark Episode | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390032/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Whilst Tom&amp;rsquo;s still struggling with no internet at home, the boys valiantly attempt recording an episode over the phone. It might be a short show but they still manage to pack in loads of chat&amp;hellip; making marks in the gym, pioneering the Mukbang craze, takeaway pick-ups, cool names, entertaining maths lessons, very bad time keeping and W&amp;amp;O remakes of Good Will Hunting and Goodfellas. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 52: New Homes &amp; Big Bugs | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390033/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390033/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… welcome returns, stalkers and Stans, Tom’s new home and its broken broadband, becoming Prime Minister, combating memory loss, grazed knees, insect superpowers, house names, a huge hornet and horrible hotel rooms. Then, after a film-star coffee revelation, we answer email questions about a childish boyfriend and some baby name suggestions. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Instagram - @wolfowlpod TikTok - @wolfowlpodcast YouTube - www.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 51: Best Bits Vol. 2 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390034/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yes, that’s right - it’s the second of our Best Bits compilations! More classic stories, lively banter and favourite email questions from the first 150 episodes of the pod. Rom and Tom will be back next week with a brand new show. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Instagram - @wolfowlpod YouTube - www.youtube.com/WolfandOwlPodcast Merch &amp;amp; Mailing List - https://wolfandowlpod.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 50: Best Bits Vol. 1 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390035/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390035/</guid><description>Podcast Description While Rom and Tom take a well earned break, here’s the first of two Best Bits compilations - featuring some of our favourite stories and funniest moments from the past two and half years of the pod. Enjoy! For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Instagram - @wolfowlpod YouTube - www.youtube.com/WolfandOwlPodcast Merch &amp;amp; Mailing List - https://wolfandowlpod.com/ A Shiny Ranga Production For sales and sponsorship enquiries: HELLO@KEEPITLIGHTMEDIA.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 49: Porn Debates &amp; Breakfast Shtick | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390036/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390036/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… pontificating on pornography, Monaco dinners, Grand Prix miss-pronunciations, beard and hair dye, breakfast TV time pressures, doing your shtick, mid-meal vaping and droopy microphones. Then, some email questions on medium size clothing, unadventurous mates, dating after a diagnosis and tips on wedding planning timeframes. Apologies for Tom’s ongoing sound issues - improvements coming soon. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 48: Theme Parks &amp; Being Dumped | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390037/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390037/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… chat show Rom, upsetting emails, stubbed toes and smacked bottoms, theme park problems, our worst dumping experiences, Tom’s microphone troubles, low confidence phone calls, morale-boosting mates, strange heckles and a very blocked ear. Plus a few email questions on a missing teeth quandary and an anger provoking miss-pronunciation. Apologies for Tom’s ongoing sound issues - improvements coming soon. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 47: Palace Appointments &amp; Due Diligence | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390038/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390038/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… being earnest, a W&amp;amp;O fantasy football league, breakfast energy drinks, meeting King Charles, due diligence (or a lack of), royal performances, palace toilets, too much choice in shops, size 12 trainers, pre-gig eating and 3D printed burgers. Then some email questions on relatives copying the things that you like and the acceptability of spitting. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 46: BAFTA The Future | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390039/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… big openers, a BAFTA de-brief, chat-show anecdotes, afterparty invites, Crawley droughts, the brilliance of Back To The Future, being a shoulder double and pilot flops. Then, after a quick sing-song and some nursery grime anxiety, we answer emails on looking like a pig, rat or horse, six inch alterations and using other people’s catchphrases. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 45: Sharp Suits &amp; Backwards Caps | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390040/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390040/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s a very special show this week as Rom and Tom are together in the same room! We’re talking… Eeyore energy, dodging rounds at the pub, wonderful weddings, wearing suits on stage, very bad cap decisions, awkward photo shoots, visible bum cracks, portmanteaus and BAFTA outfits. Plus, email questions about a partner’s snooze alarm tactics and sharing uneven incomes. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 44: Dandelions &amp; Paranoia | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390041/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390041/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… blowing on dandelions, childhood myths, theme park panics and abseiling tears, workplace injuries, gym rats, making the most of travel, controlling our paranoia and absolutely loving taxi bikes. Plus, emails questions on the pitfalls of family phone tracking and horror films on a first date. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Instagram - @wolfowlpod YouTube - www.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 43: Busted Chairs &amp; A Brand New Air Fryer | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390042/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390042/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… real vs fantasy football, cool American drinks, the fallacy of builders tea, disappearing into obscurity, broken chairs and bruised egos, Tom’s shocking return to air frying and techniques for unlocking your creativity. Then we answer some email questions on encouraging words for your partner, getting over disappointments and a tricky visible nipple issue. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 42: Lightsabers &amp; Noisy Sandwiches | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390043/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390043/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… multiple apologies, building your own lightsaber, sandwich-gate and some very angry listeners, sexing up the King’s coronation, the pain of picnics, agro wasps, the dangerous combination of tight trunks and a full bladder, embarrassing nearly-naked experiences and audition let-downs. Plus, a jam-packed email about fatherhood, envy and playing FIFA online. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Instagram - @wolfowlpod YouTube - www.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 41: Dental Care &amp; Disney World | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390044/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… early morning starts, minty fresh breath, burping actors, a trip to Disney World, Marvel Rom vs Star Wars Rom, being born as a 43-year-old, Pontins talent contests, quitting Twitter and coming up with character voices. Plus, a couple of email questions answered about being on celebrity shows and our best (or worst) spontaneous decisions. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 40: Birthdays and Brass Necks | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390045/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390045/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s Rom’s Birthday! And to celebrate the special day, we’re talking… early morning gym sessions, naming names, extreme beard trims, rubber necking, brass necks, Tom’s beef with Married At First Sight, the mystery of Ryan Reynolds and anecdote angst. Then, after Tom’s very lengthy explanations about why time exists and snakes hiss, we just about manage to squeeze in some email questions. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 39: Dull Detectives &amp; Fake Injuries | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390046/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390046/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… dull detectives, ounces of Idris, constructive criticisms, working on walks, sleeping sounds, fire-hydrant attacks, attentions-seeking injuries and losing your rag in public. Plus, an email question about appropriating your partners recommendations and another suggestion for a ‘would you rather’ quandary. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Instagram - @wolfowlpod YouTube - www.youtube.com/WolfandOwlPodcast Merch &amp;amp; Mailing List- https://wolfandowlpod.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 38: Visible Nipples &amp; Museum Snacks | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390047/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390047/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… velour loungewear, visible nipple issues, zips and buttons, museum snacks, a Wolf &amp;amp; Owl male sports bra, hair plugs vs wigs and the many quandaries of cosmetic surgery. Then, after a bit of Apprentice chat, we answer email questions on sharing mortgage costs, doing things in the wrong order, Far East travels and photo mishaps. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 37: Bad Breath Paranoia &amp; Donut Doubts | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390048/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390048/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… Sunday mornings, moody audience members, ghosting rock stars, the fall-out from Tom’s cheesecake controversy, non-hibernating squirrels, lazy bears, smelly trailers, messy burritos and some extremely unwanted toothpaste. Then, after Rom tells us all about his awkward donut gifts, we answer questions on strange co-incidences and the viability of genetically traced dog-poo fines. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 36: Return Of The Bonus | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390049/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390049/</guid><description>Podcast Description The bonus episodes are back baby! First up, a quick chat about post-exercise aches and the long-awaited return of Party Rom. Then we tackle some email questions about doing standup whilst being a teacher, getting over heart-break, not missing someone, more nicknames and a potential new jingle for the pod. Thanks for all your messages - keep them coming at wolfowlpod@gmail.com For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 35: Embarrassing Impressions &amp; Cheesecake Controversy | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390050/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390050/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… Instagram initiatives, oversharing on the pod, showing off with impressions, crimes against hair, crushingly embarrassing videos, texting anxieties, Oliver Twist’s gruel buffet and Tom’s controversial take on cheesecake. Plus, email questions about peeing dogs, worst and best nicknames, a new ‘would you rather’ section and getting scammed on holiday. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Instagram - @wolfowlpod YouTube - www.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 34: Music vs Comedy | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390051/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390051/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… stand-up comedy in music venues, aggressive gigs, performing at festivals, singing feedback and a Wolf &amp;amp; Owl Christmas single, bootlace belts, bad parenting and the possibility of giving up swearing. Plus, some email questions on sporting injuries, favourite nicknames and getting to grips with grief. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Instagram - @wolfowlpod YouTube - www.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 33: Horrible Hangovers &amp; Valentines Panics | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390052/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390052/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… hungover chores, Zoom fights, rugby days and donkey dicks, emergency valentines plans, homemade margaritas, brewing beer, the world&amp;rsquo;s happiest countries and the pros and cons of never having to sleep again. Followed by email questions on vaping in bed, audio book obsessions and restaurant ordering etiquette - and an all important update on Tom’s ghost! For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 32: Tough Cops &amp; Soft Water | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390053/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390053/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… a BO shirt update, spa-day podcasts, walking in London, happy dentists, New York hussles, oversharing at the gym, the amazingness of water softeners and a gritty Wolf &amp;amp; Owl police drama. Then some of your email questions on dealing with bullying, doorbell cameras, squeamish incidents and planning a wedding party playlist. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 31: Car De-Icing &amp; Seriously Singing | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390054/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390054/</guid><description>Podcast Description S2 Ep 31: Car De-Icing &amp;amp; Seriously Singing We’re talking… punctual podding, car windscreen de-icing, opticians and eye hankies, the Wolf &amp;amp; Owl singing their hearts out, smelly football shirts, bad B.O. and growing ears. Then some of your email questions answered on toilet tackle logistics, a problematic father-in-law, making peace with past sins and undignified operations. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 30: Sandwiches, Ghosts &amp; Toothache | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390055/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390055/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… Rom’s stealth sausage sandwich, stressful mornings, work-in-progress shows, toothaches and insomnia, the principal of ghosts, exotic exorcisms and Tom’s non-existent hotel booking. Then we answer some more of your emails - this week about a disgusting discovery, suitable presents for a new boyfriend and how best to announce leaving your job. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 29: Tidying Up &amp; Bothering Barmen | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390056/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390056/</guid><description>Podcast Description S2 Ep 29: Tidying Up &amp;amp; Bothering Barmen We’re talking… being back in the garage, enjoying tidying up, spending too long in pubs, drinking at family meals, bothering barmen, morning panics and hypnotherapy help. Then some of your email questions on having more inspiring weekends, managing exasperation with your family and a flatmate fridge-management problem. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 28: Live in Manchester | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390057/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Recorded last week at the Manchester Opera House - it’s the Wolf and Owl Live! For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Instagram - @wolfowlpod YouTube - www.youtube.com/WolfandOwlPodcast Merch &amp;amp; Mailing List- https://wolfandowlpod.com/ A Shiny Ranga Production For sales and sponsorship enquiries: HELLO@KEEPITLIGHTMEDIA.COM Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 27: New Years &amp; Not Jogging | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390058/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390058/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… a brand new 2023, tour show worries, corporate gigs and Chesney Hawkes, new year joggers, The Traitors, ginger biscuits in space and Tom’s tricky time on The Last Leg Special. Then, after a minor spat about truffles in everything, we answer email questions on a friendship group problem, making enough time for parents and a difference of attitudes on drugs. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 26: Punctual Partners &amp; Bogey Pride | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390059/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390059/</guid><description>Podcast Description For our final show of the year, we’re talking… Instagram spam, punctual partners (or not?), physical hang-ups and bogey pride, plummeting fart rates, night-time driving, youthful success and overly bored kids. Plus, some advice on managing friendships after having a baby and learning to love your yourself just as you are. Have a very happy New Year and we’ll see you in 2023! For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 25: The Drunk Christmas Special | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390060/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390060/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s finally here! No, not Christmas. Our Christmas special - and it’s the merriest Christmas special of them all! The Wolf and Owl together in a podcast studio with a bar full of booze. What could possibly go wrong? Ho ho ho! For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Instagram - @wolfowlpod YouTube - www.youtube.com/WolfandOwlPodcast Merch &amp;amp; Mailing List- https://wolfandowlpod.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 24: New Tattoos &amp; Travel Meltdowns | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390061/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390061/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… Wolf &amp;amp; Owl tattoos, Tom’s real-life Planes, Trains and Automobiles ordeal, customer service meltdowns, bizarre complaining styles, coming home to curry and the correct number of papadums to order. Then, after some World Cup commiserations and celebrations, we answer email questions on shaving all your hair off and being comfortable accepting help from your parents. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 23: Sickly Tom &amp; A West End Trip | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390062/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390062/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… Tom’s very sick week, passionate languages, beige diets and Imodium, rucksack dads, theatre trips, a serious beef with M&amp;amp;M&amp;rsquo;s and the heaven and hell of visiting Hamleys. Followed by some email questions on our favourite moments from the pod, a maid of honour problem, snoring solutions and perfecting efficient packing. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Instagram - @wolfowlpod YouTube - www.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 22: Superheroes &amp; Small Talk | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390063/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390063/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… off-duty superheroes, international takeaways, teutonic troubles, cultural differences, small talk styles, World Cup concerns and Netflix Specials. Then, some email questions answered on long distance running, a very difficult career decision and a colleague with some pretty unpleasant habits. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Instagram - @wolfowlpod YouTube - www.youtube.com/WolfandOwlPodcast Merch &amp;amp; Mailing List- https://wolfandowlpod.com/ A Shiny Ranga Production For sales and sponsorship enquiries: HELLO@KEEPITLIGHTMEDIA.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 21: Fire Alarms &amp; Straddle-Gate Updates | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390064/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390064/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… Tom’s very persistent hotel fire alarm, Rom’s gig-heavy week, getting locked out of your bank account, an all important update on straddle-gate, playing make-believe as kids and finding enjoyable ways to exercise. Then, after Rom sets a little test for the Swan, we answer email questions on maintaining healthy friendships, the different phases of a relationship and a missing package left with a neighbour. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 20: Egg Addictions &amp; Suspect Straddling | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390065/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390065/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… helping out at hotels, heavy egg consumption, being drunk on podcasts, Tom’s mighty press-up challenge, a bit of sports massage advice and a highly controversial straddling incident. Plus, we answer emails about weird dreams, a neighbour’s builders and adjusting to returning home after a year away travelling. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Instagram - @wolfowlpod YouTube - www.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 19: Tech Troubles &amp; Heavy Petting | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390066/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390066/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… technical difficulties, anxious batteries, some very heavy petting at the pool, being beardless, a supermarket challenge, restaurant banter, even more internet problems and a very special announcement. Plus, a few email questions answered on wedding invitations and advice for regaining lost confidence. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Instagram - @wolfowlpod YouTube - www.youtube.com/WolfandOwlPodcast Merch &amp;amp; Mailing List- https://wolfandowlpod.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 18: Halloween Rom &amp; Pancake Problems | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390067/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390067/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… broken phones, missing merch, halloween party costumes, spoilt roasts and hotel pancake problems, boxing for babies, TV series quitters and arthouse cinema bores. Plus, email questions on not being homesick, coping with a long-distance relationship and toddlers peeing in public. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Instagram - @wolfowlpod YouTube - www.youtube.com/WolfandOwlPodcast Merch &amp;amp; Mailing List- https://wolfandowlpod.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 17: Robot Chefs &amp; Crap Cap Service | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390068/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390068/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… podding on an empty stomach, awards for cowardice, footie training pick-ups, fast-food ordering screens, robot chefs, bad customer service and homemade burgers. Then after quite a bit of toilet talk, we answer emails about some relationship advice, a work place predicament and presents for parents. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Instagram - @wolfowlpod YouTube - www.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 16: Chinese Soup &amp; A Creepy Conman | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390069/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390069/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… phlegm-filled openers, charity gigs, Tom’s creepy Chinese restaurant swindler, an eye-gate update, Twitter trolls, Rom’s train waffle champion, Bristol’s GPS dog and our favourite comfort films. Plus, emails on maintaining a relationship with an ex, bad smells in public places, and the great ‘sit or stand’ debate. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Instagram - @wolfowlpod YouTube - www.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 15: Gym Jocks &amp; Over-indulging | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390070/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390070/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… becoming ‘Locker Room Joes’, fitness app Top Trumps, deteriorating take-aways, homemade curries, over-indulging on free food, the false economy of a free bar limit and Tom’s charity push-up challenge. Then after a rather controversial follow-up email, we answer questions on excessive eating and drinking on holiday, the right time and place to approach a celebrity and how best to help a lonely family member. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 14: Slow Service &amp; Cringey Complaints | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390071/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390071/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… awesome animations, restaurant letdowns, embarrassing complaint letters, awkward interactions and a stressful encounter with a charity meerkat. Then we tackle email questions about a parent’s past catching up with them, relationship age gaps, more sock swaps and a debate on a very specific benefit of weight loss. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Instagram - @wolfowlpod YouTube - www.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 13: Radio Jobs &amp; Roller Coasters | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390072/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390072/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re back baby! And kicking things off with… early career radio jobs, kids TV show presenting, holidaying at home, celebrity SAS, the pleasure of fast-track tickets, a bizarre sock-thieving incident and traumatic roller coaster experiences. Then we answer some more of your emails, this week on keep in contact with friends, playing rude lyrics around kids and having to downsize your home. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 12: After Parties &amp; Airport Scares | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390073/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390073/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… a Dave Chappelle party, dodgy bar tactics, embellishing stories, action heroes and Mr Maths, airport scares, Fantasy Football woes, big-beer Tom and anxious toilet trips. Plus, email questions on banter with new mates, wearing dirty clothes at home, gaming all-inclusive holidays and some feedback on cooking risotto and pissing in pools. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 11: Holiday Beers &amp; Needy Risotto | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390074/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390074/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… mini-Sagres beers, vegan bacon dust, needy risottos, signing pebbles, Tom’s new TV obsessions, the ever-changing Kanye West and getting creative in stand-up. Then we take a look at some of your emails, with questions on losing weight to please a partner, putting off seeing the doctor and the rights and wrongs of pissing in swimming pools. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 10: Making Beds &amp; Windy Auditions | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390075/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390075/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… tidy teenagers, long vs short holidays, a surprise second dog, celebrity crushes, Tom’s windy Eastenders audition, Sprite challenges, foreign exchange trips and two aching backs. Then we answer some email questions on invasive in-laws, dirty toilets, camp cavemen and an unattractive obsession with hair removal cream. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Instagram - @wolfowlpod YouTube - www.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 9: Portugal Rom &amp; Dry Clean Tom | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390076/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390076/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… dodgy Zoom backgrounds, borrowed pants and saggy pouches, dry cleaning doubts, skinny jeans regrets, giving up golf, holiday gyms and snake oil posture fixes. Then, after some more arse pebble clarifications, we answer emails on an obsession with running, a favourite restaurant closing down and thoughts on a certain type of energy. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 8: Big Brags &amp; Embarrassing Photos | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390077/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390077/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… big bragging, gigging at Hooters, keeping tour shows fresh, dealing with embarrassing photos, beer-drinking sweet spots and Tom Hanks vs Matthew McConaughey. Plus, we answer some great emails on tips to keep the neighbours happy, how to get a partner to help out with housework and a very strange twist on Tom’s arse-pebble idea. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 7: Red Bull Rom &amp; Glasgow Golf Trips | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390078/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390078/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… party clowns, prop comics and comedy competitions, the return of Red Bull Rom, Spanish lesson updates, mobile samosa feasts, Love Island gripes, triumphant Lionesses and Tom’s very ambitious golf trip to Glasgow. Then some emails on beach confidence, a name mix-up with a new friend and correcting a partner’s unpleasant habit. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 6: Puppy Piss &amp; Ruined Rugs | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390079/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390079/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… hair gel techniques, puppy piss and a ruined rug, Sunday lunch spills, Henry the Eighth, mortal combat with the kids, phones in the toilet, a pact to learn Spanish and the end of Neighbours. Then some email questions answered on dating a friend&amp;rsquo;s ex, an expensive wedding invite, and a mystery tidy-upper. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 5: 40 Degrees &amp; Santa Issues | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390080/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390080/</guid><description>Podcast Description On the hottest day of the year, we’re talking… staying hydrated, a world without carpets, a universal secret Santa, picture-perfect Christmases, culturally sensitive penguins and Charles Dickens by the pool. Then, after a quick tally of seaweed responses from our listeners, we answer emails on confident beach swims, tube-train deposits, returning clothing and an unfortunate incident with a nightie. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 4: Sleeping Styles &amp; Seaweed Scandals | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390081/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390081/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… hot sleeps, night-time toilet trips, beach bodies, prams on the sand and screaming into the sea, security tags, spring-loaded napkins and a scandalous revelation about crispy seaweed. Then we take a look at some emails about ‘hotness as a state of mind’, birthday trip ideas, favourite films and a tricky relationship quandary. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 3: Sunny Days &amp; Funny Nights | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390082/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390082/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… summer weather, making time for romance, crazy fussiness, the daunting thought of sex, the highs and lows of last week’s gigs, Tom’s most gluttonous meal ever and the burden of handsome mates. Then, after a bit of a disagreement about sweet potato fries and broccoli, we answer emails on techniques to help with relaxing, dealing with difficult in-laws, and an uplifting message from a newlywed. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 2: Paper Maps &amp; Gig Mishaps | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390083/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390083/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking…. loud openings, paper maps vs sat nav, car racing hobbits, star quality and false modesty, Crawley gig mishaps, awkward photo moments, working the room and divisive fashion. Then, after an update on last week’s ‘arse pebble’, we answer emails about not having many friends, maintaining a relationship through university, and meat-based wedding cakes. For questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>S2 Ep 1: Or should that be Episode 100? | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390084/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390084/</guid><description>Podcast Description As the Wolf &amp;amp; Owl Podcast reaches its 100th episode, we’re talking…. the start of a brand new series, muddled numbering, new podcast strategies, the results of Jamie Redknapp’s listener poll, mace-strength chilli challenges, Tom’s secret curry pebble tip and never-ending film franchises. Then onto some of your email questions about dealing with nerves when public speaking and managing expectations when moving house. Instagram - @wolfowlpod YouTube - www.</description></item><item><title>Ep 74: Middle Age Partying &amp; County Fairs | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390085/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 05:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390085/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking…. acceptable venues for middle age nights out, elderflower lager, county fair attire, sleeveless shirts, extreme shaving, festival infatuations, little white lies and the intimidating thought of dating again. Plus, we receive a shocking revelation on the ‘My Guy!’ debate and answer a few of your emails too. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Ep 73: Crap Raps &amp; A Solid Night’s Sleep | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390086/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 05:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390086/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking…. cringeworthy rapping, overenthusiastic hecklers, hen and stag parties, sleep help from the night ninja, spring-clean-itus, the parable of the new neighbour, panel show pilots and celebrity freebies. Plus, email questions on pursuing an ex-boyfriend and finding a compromise with your partner on food treats. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>Ep 72: Local Radio &amp; Celebrating Celebrations | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390087/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 05:00:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390087/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking…. local radio presenters, annoying adverts, talking to professional footballers, making the most of celebrations, airport drinking, attitudes to awards, hanging out on set together, catering letdowns and an all-important update on Tom’s sugar ban. Then it’s onto some more hot topics - baths in the middle of hotel rooms, echoey garages, listener gripes and a few of your email questions. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Ep 71: Quitting Sugar &amp; Addictive TV | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390088/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 05:00:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390088/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking…. Tom’s ambitious plan to give up sugar, opposite mums, fizzy drinks, bespoke pasties, biscuit gluttony, addictively tepid TV, great bedtime storytelling and the awesomeness of satsumas - or maybe that should be clementines? Then some email questions answered on dealing with uneven incomes, the seven deadly sins, and coming up with sayings and catchphrases. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>Ep 70: Burritos &amp; Wedding Cakes | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390089/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 05:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390089/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking…. a Wolf and Owl burrito shack, foam wedding cakes, family favouritism, having your flaws pointed out to you, disappointing male attitudes, chatty swans, advice on learning lines and bad front row decorum at gigs. Then we get serious answering your emails - this week on standing up against homophobia, a dilemma on mending a family rift and a very varied three-part question. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Ep 69: Stopping Swearing &amp; Family Gatherings | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390090/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 05:00:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390090/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking…. too much swearing, the art of expletives, a Wolf &amp;amp; Owl family meet-up, re-telling embarrassing stories, being in the doghouse, dropping a baby, happy health food shops, snobby estate agents and the pitfalls of using public toilets. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Ep 68: Sandwich Joy &amp; Stolen Sauces | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390091/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 05:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390091/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking…. celebrating sandwiches, misplaced S’s, best-before dates, stolen hot sauce, hide and seek, learning to sing, pretending to sing, watching the boxing and an unfortunate vegan slip-up. Then we answer a couple of email questions on advice about running a pub and holidaying alone after a recent break-up. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Ep 67: Nervous Laughs &amp; T-Shirt Weather | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390092/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 05:00:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390092/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking…. nervous laughter, not paying attention, cocky pups and dog whistles, single-layer temperatures, embarrassing gym moments, sweaty trains, nose plasters, wrinkled T-shirts and bonding through badminton. Followed by a couple of email questions on secret take-aways and a very messy lodger who&amp;rsquo;s outstayed their welcome. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>Ep 66: Garage Life &amp; Sugar Fasting | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390093/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 05:00:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390093/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking…. working in the garage, double curry days, giving up sugar and other fasting plans, bed wars, puppy gates, online customer services and Instagram influencers. Then after a bit of F45 training and some messages from our imaginary sponsors, we answer emails on a troublesome ex, the loss of a pet, ideas for a bike riding honeymoon and an organ donation. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Ep 65: Show Openers &amp; Oscars Shockers | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390094/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 05:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390094/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking…. how to open the show, patience with risotto, the much-neglected pearl barley, complaining in restaurants, eating interventions, the Owl’s birthday, working a room, being anxious in crowds and that Oscars shocker. And a massive thank you to all those who came out to the live shows last week - we had a blast! For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>Ep 64: Heath Checks &amp; Arrogant Animals | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390095/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 06:00:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390095/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking…. hotel lifestyles and heath checkups, medical scares, failures at fasting, red or white meat, the arrogance of pigs, visiting farms and the pitfalls of homemade kefir. Plus some email questions on helping a friend who’s obsessed with exercise, the acceptability of wearing caps in your 40’s, and our most awkward heckler anecdotes. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>Ep 63: Home Haircuts &amp; Restaurant Beef | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390096/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 06:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390096/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking…. befriending barbers, having a gardener, restaurant letdowns, noisily enjoying food, making enemies with hypnotists, baby stresses and overdosing on Big Tasty’s. Then, after a quick tot-up of podcast guest appearances, we take a look at some emails on balancing family life with work, a topical debate about wheels and doors, and a heartwarming relationship update. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>Ep 62: Hotel Rooms &amp; Vegan Eggs | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390097/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 06:00:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390097/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking…. favourite seasons, hotel room invasions, buffet portion control, egg ordering protocols, bald auctions, wholesome living and awkward public interactions. Then onto some listener’s email questions - this week on the end of a relationship, giving advice to your friends, and the right time and place to ask someone out. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>Ep 61: Driving Lessons &amp; Live Shows | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390098/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 06:00:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390098/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking…. Rom teaching Tom to drive, drink drivers, the Wolf &amp;amp; Owl on stage, more hair challenges, baby crap, undercover investigations, messy rooms and some real-life imposters. Followed by a few of your emails, this week on meeting up with an internet acquaintance and supporting your daughter’s captainship of the local football team. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>Ep 60: Valentine's &amp; The Super Bowl | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390099/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 06:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390099/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking…. romantic gestures, upside-down NFL extravaganzas, rum sponsorship, Twitter spats, football dads, movie star magic, Sunday food excesses and a hair loss re-growth challenge. Then some more of your sweet sweet emails - this week on a partner’s past, snow opinions and women going on stag-do&amp;rsquo;s. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>Episode 59 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390100/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 06:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390100/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking…. a &amp;lsquo;party Rom&amp;rsquo; spin-off film, exercise endorsements, goldfish bowls, getting excited about storage, folding or rolling, the launch of The Curse, and two rather invasive health check-ups. Plus, some thoughts on a couple of emails about clothing and an all-important update on the Wolf &amp;amp; Owl merch. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Episode 58 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390101/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 06:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Whilst Rom struggles with an epic hangover (and a lot of gloating from Tom), we’re talking…. late nights and afterparties, food delivery mix-ups, not dressing your age, a potential fashion consultation, baby stresses and more wi-fi woes. Followed by some thoughtful responses to a couple of listener’s emails - and a banging final thoughts collaboration to close the show. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Episode 57 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390102/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 06:00:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390102/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking…. Rom’s awesome weekend, Manchester’s curry mile, overdosing on ghee, inadvertently becoming a West Ham fan, clubbing in your 40s, bonding with Leonardo DiCaprio and badly fitting suits. Then onto more listener emails - this week about poetry, film screenplays, an update on dating again, and advice on giving advice. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>Episode 56 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390103/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 06:00:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390103/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking…. Tom’s covid troubles, being naked at home, hecklers, broken headphones, style over substance, and a crazy idea for audio tattoos. Then we answer your email questions on dealing with potentially aggressive situations, the early days of Rom and Tom, getting into stand-up, and a relationship quandary. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Bonus New Year Episode | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390104/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 06:00:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Despite Tom’s awful internet connection, we’re talking… a new year&amp;rsquo;s greeting, spectacular moustaches, meeting famous footballers, smelling great, AWOL food deliveries, a bit of baby parenting advice and the ups and downs of autograph-hunting. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description></item><item><title>Episode 55 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390105/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 06:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390105/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… all about Tom’s brand new baby daughter, of course! Plus, getting emotional, night feeds, pricey popcorn, cinema gripes and the rights and wrongs of bespoke burgers. We also answer a few email questions, this time on bad experiences getting dumped and making the decision to change careers. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Episode 54 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390106/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 06:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390106/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… the greatest musical ever made, popcorn cinema, bonding over nostalgic films, an incisive bit of dream analysis, not dancing anymore and learning not to be so hard on ourselves. Followed, of course, by some more of your email questions - this week on damaged clothing, puppy training tips and a very odd way to cut toenails. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Email Episode #24 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390107/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 06:00:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390107/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a speedy apology about our new merch selling out so quick, we dig into some chat about Christmas cards, role models, political parties and yet another pretty disgusting story. Then some more of your emails - this week about a drunken night’s stay in a hotel, settling with remaining single and the meaning of a ‘G’. Thanks for all your messages - keep them coming at wolfowlpod@gmail.com Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Episode 53 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390108/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 06:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390108/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… the big Wolf &amp;amp; Owl merch drop, poster shops, teenage clothing mistakes, new shows and new puppies, washing before sleep and making the most of hotel showers. Then some email questions on getting engaged, coping with a partner’s phone addiction and memorable night bus journeys. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>Episode 52 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390109/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 06:00:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390109/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… breakfast radio presenters, a change of heart on plastic Christmas trees, dirty fingernails, sweetcorn love, phone pranks, Idris Elba and an important meeting at Butlin&amp;rsquo;s. Then, after clearing up the difference between colds and flu, we answer a few email questions on shameful drunken antics, voiceovers and early TV appearances. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Email Episode #23 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390110/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 06:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390110/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Wolf &amp;amp; Owl podcast is one year old! So it’s time to celebrate with an impromptu bonus episode - and a special birthday theme-tune remix too. Then, after some reminiscing about embarrassing teenage infatuations, we tackle email questions on what to do about a partner&amp;rsquo;s annoying habits, beer fear and messing up when trying to make a good first impression. Thanks for all your messages - keep them coming at wolfowlpod@gmail.</description></item><item><title>Episode 51 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390111/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 06:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390111/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… camouflage fashion, dealing with unruly pupils, sixth form proms, Tom’s calamitous time in the Scouts, an embarrassing fall for Rom and Mustaffa the lion. Then a few of your emails, this week about a revelatory hack to reduce phone use, advice on helping out a nephew and comparing morning routines. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>Episode 50 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390112/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 06:00:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390112/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… nose hair, clever dinosaurs, celebs and politics, Rom as a Crawley Councillor, chatting to supermarket staff and working on the trollies. Then after a quick James Bond review from Tom, we answer email questions on getting your teeth straightened, helping out at your kid’s school and Christmas present inspiration. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>Episode 49 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390113/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 07:00:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390113/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… podcast reviews, the return of some scat chat, stag-do’s and the prankmeister general, a new puppy and a phone screen-time challenge. We also answer some of your emails, of course - this time on back pain, opinions on ‘private time’, and the best way to cook a potato. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Episode 48 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390114/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 07:00:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390114/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… shiny trench coats, wardrobe classics, body shame issues, different type of laughs and hanging out with TV people. Then a couple of email questions on the rights and wrongs of preferring a quiet night in and sleeping with separate duvets. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Episode 47 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390115/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 06:00:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390115/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… new homes, family holidays, fashion statements (explained via The Transformers), removal companies, excessive hypochondria and the possibilities of a Romesh statue in Crawley. Plus, we answer some of your email questions on getting over embarrassing moments, the right way to deal with workplace abuse, and a Tom Davis positivity generator. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>Episode 46 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390116/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 06:00:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390116/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… fashion Russian-roulette, not going on runs, bonding over mountains, playing poker with zoo animals, computer game tuition and some unfortunate news about Tom’s dog. Plus, some email questions answered on TV shows our families bonded over, using rap to teach maths, and a problem with loud eating. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Episode 45 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390117/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 06:00:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390117/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… morning hair, dangerous dentists, making movies and meeting film stars, takeaway splurges, charity marathons and the many parts of Tom’s heart. Then it’s email time with a few questions answered on veggie recipe inspiration and a flatmate quandary. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Episode 44 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390118/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 06:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390118/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… sore throats and posture straps, osteopathy cults, social media meltdowns and some very exciting trainspotting news. Then some of your email questions on someone getting your name wrong, celebrating a retirement and how to tell if a guy’s into you. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Episode 43 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390119/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 06:00:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390119/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… toenails, unfortunate lookalikes, lipcare, ear specialists, the invention of plates, and the scourge of parsley and rocket. Then some email question advice on noisey neighbour sex, how to break a pet’s death to your child, the rights or wrongs of paying compliments and toxic ball syndrome. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Email Episode #22 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390120/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 06:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390120/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Wolf &amp;amp; Owl Bonus Episode is back! In this week&amp;rsquo;s show, we tackle&amp;hellip; a query on real friendships, updates on the meat drought and DOMS awareness, collecting dead dogs&amp;rsquo; teeth, getting on well with kids, a new pair of kittens and a disappointing experience losing your virginity. Thanks for all your messages - keep them coming at wolfowlpod@gmail.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Episode 42 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390121/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 06:00:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390121/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… exercise routine recoveries, DOMS and ray guns, airfryer-gate, meat droughts, abattoirs and fast food serial killers. Then after a quick apology, we answer some email questions on a 40th birthday outfit, Wikipedia pages, BO solutions, feet on train seats and Married at First Sight UK. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>Episode 41 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390122/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 06:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390122/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… late night food orders, the evolution of ovens, the cult of air-fryers, body odour issues and deodorant mash-ups. Then some of your email questions answered on the appeal of lab-grown meat products, wearing a football shirt on a first date and moving things on in a relationship. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Episode 40 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390123/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 06:00:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390123/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… clerical parenting, embarrassing dads, the early days of sat-nav, cold baths, beautiful beaches and restaurant banter. Then, after some laughing tests and sparing a thought for neglected bread rolls, we tackle emails on energy drinks, body hair and a hot neighbour. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Episode 39 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390124/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 06:00:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390124/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… a bad sleep, noises in the night, chicken shop troubles, consolation kebabs, burglar swag bags and teenage subjects of admiration. Then, after a bit of a debate about animal-based sayings, we answer email questions on balancing work with a relationship, asking a father for his daughter’s hand in marriage and the consequences of discovering aliens. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>Episode 38 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390125/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 06:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390125/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… writing a book, hedgehog-itis, beardlessness, eye tests, being a butterfly, awkward public interactions and podcast reviews. Plus, we answer more of your emails and come up with some ideas for a Wolf &amp;amp; Owl Lethal Weapon remake. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Episode 37 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390126/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390126/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… dad jokes, losing a beard, hiding some fish, waterpark worries and swimming pool pranks. Followed by some more of your emails, with questions on favourite TV night snacks and how the Wolf and Owl would cope with military training. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Episode 36 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390127/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390127/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… summer holidays! The greatest pair of sliders ever made, beachwear and holiday meals, clean lines in clothing, gaming the Pizza Hut buffet deal and a medley of swimming successes and failures. Plus, we answer some email qustions about revealing your past whilst dating, problems with a career in sport and acting alongside a close friend. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>Episode 35 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390128/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390128/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… writing lyrics, the return King Gary, becoming a monk, mickey-drip solutions, Tom’s adventures in Greece and holiday parenting. Plus some advice on email questions about announcing a job change to parents, moving to the UK from Australia and dying on your ass on stage. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>Episode 34 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390129/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390129/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… Tom’s holiday preparations, travel test troubles, fortune-tellers, gods, ghost stories and dodgy hotels, Then some more of your email questions - this time on summer wedding clashes, eating food with your hands or cutlery, and sitting or squatting in public toilets. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Email Episode #21 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390130/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390130/</guid><description>Podcast Description We tackle… Tom’s biggest exercise day ever, a Wolf &amp;amp; Owl bike ride and the shameful decline of Feast ice-creams. Then some advice on not overreacting, how to navigate a supermarket, under-rated comedians and failing your driving test. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 33 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390131/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390131/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… morning walks, wasps and bees, hungover bug exterminators, TV recommendations, TikTok pasta recipes, a big debate about beans and being too old for bars and clubs. Plus, more of your email questions of course. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Email Episode #20 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390132/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390132/</guid><description>Podcast Description First up - dealing with spots, banter with strangers on public transport, dying on stage and the pitfalls of corporate gigs. Then we tackle some of your emails about favourite sitcoms, a housemate’s update, buying clothes for your weight-conscious partner and a tricky situation with a misplaced rabbit. Thanks for all your messages - keep them coming at wolfowlpod@gmail.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Episode 32 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390133/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390133/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… podcast logistics, post-match positives and negatives, limo bikes, diminishing drinking stamina, keeping healthy minds and eating a huge amount of poppadoms. Plus we answer email questions on dealing with piss-taking mates, good glasses, Shakespeare dreams, writing stand-up and working with an ex-girlfriend. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Episode 31 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390134/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390134/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… birthday parties, childhood heartbreak, extremely spicy noodles and kids bedtimes - followed by some advice on crooked teeth, dealing with laddish attitudes and friends becoming neighbours. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonus Email Episode #19 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390135/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390135/</guid><description>Podcast Description First up - England victories, epic celebrations and taking the rough with the smooth. Then we tackle some more of your email questions, which this week include tips for looking after your mobile phone, exchanging podcast roles, Tom’s ideal spaceship crew and a broken camembert dish. Thanks for all your messages - keep them coming at wolfowlpod@gmail.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Episode 30 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390136/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390136/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… Tom’s technical meltdown, Euro predictions, vegan shoes, rugby challenges and a startling lack of holiday romance success. And if all that wasn’t enough, we then answer some email questions about Ed Sheeran, life changes since lockdown and tips for looking after a bald head. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Email Episode #18 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390137/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 06:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390137/</guid><description>Podcast Description We tackle… sheets, mattresses and how to behave in a bed shop, dating app profiles, making the right impression with new work colleagues and un-relocating for your job. Thanks for all your messages - keep them coming at wolfowlpod@gmail.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 29 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390138/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390138/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… He-Man and pizzas, the England vs Scotland match, mistaken identities, phone problems, Uber ratings, insomnia and too many fizzy drinks. Plus, some answers to more of your sweet sweet emails of course. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description></item><item><title>Bonus Email Episode #17 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390139/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390139/</guid><description>Podcast Description First we check Rom’s mercury levels and get to the bottom of becoming a weather presenter. Then we tackle email questions on… fantasy 5-a-side football teams, decriminalising cannabis, advice on dropping your old mates, rugby club sleepovers and secret tattoos. Thanks for all your messages - keep them coming at wolfowlpod@gmail.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 28 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390140/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390140/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… kissing marathons, banishing pesky birds, a fitness and health update, logo T-shirts, the likelihood of pigs taking over the world and Rom and Tom’s preparations for watching their very first live football match together. Plus some reminiscing on old cartoon favourites and more of your email questions answered. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Email Episode #16 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390141/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390141/</guid><description>Podcast Description We tackle… boxers vs Y-fronts, the long bollock - fact or fiction, the perils of changing room showers and a happy turnaround in Tom’s rocky relationship with Leon. Plus we answer email questions on what to chat about when meeting a celebrity, dealing with sarcastic comments and having pressures to conform. Thanks for all your messages - keep them coming at wolfowlpod@gmail.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Episode 27 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390142/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 06:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390142/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… technical problems, getting back into stand-up, Josh Widdicombe’s brother, disastrous dates and gigs that we’d really rather forget about. We also answer a question on a tricky unrequited love scenario and get some good news from a previous emailer. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Episode 26 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390143/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390143/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… big openers, football nerds, getting into gardening, pony tails, hair plugs, summer clothing and flattering mirrors. Plus, we answer some email questions on wedding date clashes and family football teams - and Romesh gets a well-needed pep talk. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Email Episode #15 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390144/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390144/</guid><description>Podcast Description We tackle… gentle dentists and Enya, unwanted guests, personal bests and favourite jackets. Then we answer some listener questions on sharing showers, pub quiz names and dog-sitter predicaments. Thanks for all your messages - keep them coming at wolfowlpod@gmail.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 25 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390145/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390145/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… more hangovers, another broken tooth, badminton and golf, a Centre Parks holiday and being brilliant at escape rooms. Plus, we get a heartwarming update from a previous emailer and answer questions on old flames, dealing with a loved-one’s past and displays of affection. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Email Episode #14 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390146/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390146/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, a rather hungover Owl and Wolf tackle questions on… moving schools, judging people on first impressions, drinking limits, embarrassing condiments and more troublesome neighbours. Tom also offers some sage advice on befriending mammals and fish. Thanks for all your messages - keep them coming at wolfowlpod@gmail.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 24 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390147/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390147/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… gourmet donuts, sharing treats, theatre snacks, DIY and being really really bad at complaining. We also take a listen to a flurry of new delivery driver recordings, and answer some of your email queries on dogs and a gift-buying debate. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Email Episode #13 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390148/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390148/</guid><description>Podcast Description We tackle… doggers and deniers, horror movies, double screening, Paddington Bear and imaginary friends. Plus our favourite ice creams and some advice on age-appropriate clothing and getting over a heartbreak. Thanks for all your messages - keep them coming at wolfowlpod@gmail.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 23 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390149/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390149/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… clothes, freebies and football dads, recent TV appearances, mis-reading the room and work pranks. We also listen to our very first ‘thanking your delivery driver’ recording and answer questions on a beef jerky quandary and socialising without alcohol. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Email Episode #12 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390150/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390150/</guid><description>Podcast Description We tackle… competing with kids, trying not to swear, hanging out with the Friends cast, first dates, face masks and getting to know your neighbours. Plus, there may or may not be some serious backpedaling from the Wolf on his celebrity endorsements beef. Thanks for all your messages - keep them coming at wolfowlpod@gmail.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>Episode 22 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390151/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390151/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… stolen bicycles, problems with having funny mates, being back at pubs, energy drinks vs water, dodgy clothing clubs and Kevin Hart’s hot pants. Plus, we answer this week&amp;rsquo;s listener emails with some friendship and relationship advice. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Email Episode #11 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390152/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390152/</guid><description>Podcast Description We tackle… changing names, potential guests, coping with being the centre of attention, problematic neighbours, future plans for the podcast and best man duties. Thanks for all your messages - keep them coming at wolfowlpod@gmail.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 21 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390153/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390153/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… heartfelt apologies, new names for a Wolf &amp;amp; Owl team member, golfing gags, exercise regimes, an update on Tom’s watergate scandal and more of your sweet sweet emails. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonus Email Episode #10 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390154/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390154/</guid><description>Podcast Description First up on this week’s bonus show, the Wolf &amp;amp; Owl’s very own watergate scandal, a new health regime and news of some successful advice. Then we tackle… dealing with pressures to drink, the ups and downs of the Edinburgh Festival, food hacks and fast food favourites. Thanks for all your messages - keep them coming at wolfowlpod@gmail.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Episode 20 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390155/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390155/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… apologies, water polo, over-ordering on takeaways, variable success buying birthday presents, young love and finding yourself in the friend-zone. Plus, we answer emails asking for advice on playing golf again and dealing with unhygienic work colleagues. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Episode 19 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390156/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390156/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… Newcastle hotel rooms (Rom’s to be precise), Ross Kemp meditation videos, meeting your heroes, eating fish, food ethics and hair control. Plus some email questions about getting on well with your agent and ideas for announcing a surprise birthday present. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Email Episode #9 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390157/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390157/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is one big occasion! For the first time ever, the Wolf and Owl are together in the same room to record an episode of the podcast. On this week’s bonus show, we tackle… balancing relationships, roast dinner side dishes, a new car valeting business, making friends in pubs and yet more pronunciation issues. Thanks for all your messages - keep them coming at wolfowlpod@gmail.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.</description></item><item><title>Episode 18 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390158/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390158/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… character traits, Westerns and Hobbits, the problems with on-screen eating, hypochondria, ice-cream vans and baked beans. Plus, we answer some of your emails and Romesh gets put to the test live on air. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Email Episode #8 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390159/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390159/</guid><description>Podcast Description We tackle… toenails and trench foot, hip hop names and F-bombs, tajin recipes, van voiceovers, growing up tall, coping with a naturally sulky face and a British remake of The A Team. Plus, a 100 meters charity running race challenge is on! Thanks for all your messages - keep them coming at wolfowlpod@gmail.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>Episode 17 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390160/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390160/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… battle raps, scaffolding and stand-up, boring anecdotes, awful auditions, a potential John the Baptist role and some great film trilogies. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonus Email Episode #7 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390161/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390161/</guid><description>Podcast Description We tackle… working from home, techniques for switching off and relaxing, some tricky relationship advice, the pitfalls of stealing anecdotes and the sentimental value of objects. Plus a great tip for some Mexican chilli fruit treats. Thanks for all your messages - keep them coming at wolfowlpod@gmail.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 16 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390162/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390162/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… swearing, childhood clothing, coping with growing up, filming cock-ups and getting into heaven, hell or purgatory. Plus, the long-awaited resolution to our cafe owner / jogger insult debate. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonus Email Episode #6 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390163/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390163/</guid><description>Podcast Description We tackle… inappropriate adverts, social media (mis)management, incommunicative flatmates, lads chat, more of those pesky inner voices and dealing with the family dog. Thanks for all your messages - keep them coming at wolfowlpod@gmail.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 15 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390164/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390164/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… Pelé and the pitfalls of panel shows, stand-up shockers, lookalikes (or not at all-alikes) and celebrity snaps. Plus some advice on careers, a change of heart and a heated debate about losing a customer. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Email Episode #5 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390165/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390165/</guid><description>Podcast Description It&amp;rsquo;s email bonus time! We tackle… conflicts with your favourite music, lockdown marriage proposals, The Wolf and Owl wedding crashers and an update on Tom’s teeth troubles. Thanks for all your messages - keep them coming at wolfowlpod@gmail.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 14 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390166/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390166/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… new presenting styles for the podcast, retail aggravations, vindictive DIY tools, getting control of your inner voice and more tiny toilets. Plus some helpful advice on hair. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 13 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390167/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390167/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… keeping up with the cool kids, when to help out a stranger (or not), sweet souls, man-bags and Mulberry handbags, and traumatic encounters with tradesmen. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonus Email Episode #4 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390168/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390168/</guid><description>Podcast Description Undeterred by Tom’s dodgy wi-fi signal throughout the recording, it’s time to answer more of your emails! We tackle… vegan bacon, after-work drinks, frustratingly small clothes sizes, some advice on patience in relationships and getting caught short at the seaside. Thanks for all your messages - keep them coming at wolfowlpod@gmail.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 12 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390169/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390169/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… getting used to wearing jeans again, the mind-blowing genius of zips, personalised cards, buying gifts and unconventional uses for a cheese and onion pasty. Plus our old friends persnickety and Kreme both make a return appearance. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Email Episode #3 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390170/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390170/</guid><description>Podcast Description First on this week&amp;rsquo;s bonus show, there’s a serious doughnut disagreement to settle. But once that’s all sorted, we tackle… more mispronunciations, sitting or standing, changing careers, lack of self-awareness and a very awkward train journey. Thanks for all your messages - keep them coming at wolfowlpod@gmail.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 11 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390171/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390171/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… owning your own style, having a good bedside manner (or lack of), making up new words and hand shakes vs fist-bumps. Plus a dramatic revelation about someone’s age. Oh and just so you know, Tom’s still not oiled his chair. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Bonus Email Episode #2 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390172/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390172/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s another Friday bonus show - if you keep sending us questions, we’ll keep answering them! We tackle… round three of Tom’s celebrity endorsement beef, some advice on getting into acting, dealing with compliments and vegan insult comebacks. Thanks for all your emails - keep them coming at wolfowlpod@gmail.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 10 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390173/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390173/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… massage etiquette, cookery brags, the pitfalls of staying overnight at friend’s houses and an utterly life-changing toilet disaster. Plus news on Tom’s percentage-gate shocker from last week&amp;rsquo;s show. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Bonus Email Episode #1 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390174/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390174/</guid><description>Podcast Description Following an epic response to our email callout, this week we’ve recorded a special bonus episode to answer more of your questions. We tackle… having a coffee with George Clooney, hooking up with old friends, dealing with fame and some advice on child-friendly hip hop. Thanks for all your messages - keep them coming at wolfowlpod@gmail.com Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Episode 9 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390175/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390175/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… hair gel, spicy mackerel snacks, grief with teeth and a wrestling tag-team challenge. Plus more of your emails answered and an update on Married At First Sight. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 8 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390176/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390176/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… making coffee, interpreting dreams, favourite cinema snacks and the pros and cons of meeting a complete stranger for a pint. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 7 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390177/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390177/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… listener reviews, stalking reality TV stars, morale-boosting music and dodgy WhatsApp groups. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 6 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390178/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390178/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… chicken tikka masala, soccer celebrations, town rivalries and broken teeth. Plus the hotly anticipated results of our Tom vs Rom Cyberpunk poll. For any feedback, questions or comments please email us at wolfowlpod@gmail.com - we’d love to hear from you. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 5: Pilot #1 - Aliens | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390179/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390179/</guid><description>Podcast Description Before the Wolf and Owl podcast was revealed to the world, Tom and Romesh recorded a number of pilots with each show themed on a single topic. Some were great, a few were average and one potentially career-ending. Undeterred, we’ve decided to release a selection of these recordings and here’s the first - it’s all about aliens. Enjoy! Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Episode 4 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390180/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 08:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390180/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking…. gaming, names, Keanu Reeves adverts, and some advice on clothing and cleaning. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 3 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390181/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390181/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… lookalikes, pub lunches, flatmate quandaries and scriptwriting advice. Oh, and some more on Christmas trees too. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 2 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390182/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390182/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re talking… Christmas trees, premature mid-life crises, life before mobile phones, and chat-up disasters. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Episode 1 | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390183/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390183/</guid><description>Podcast Description Here it is - our first show! We’re talking… hats, early starts, annoying colleagues and cramming for exams. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Wolf &amp; Owl Podcast Trailer! | Wolf and Owl</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2729390184/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 18:30:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2729390184/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Wolf &amp;amp; Owl Podcast is coming soon - subscribe now to make sure you don&amp;rsquo;t miss out. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>