<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>How's Work? with Esther Pere on SWIEST - Transcripts 路 Screenplays 路 Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/hows-work-with-esther-pere/</link><description>Recent content in How's Work? with Esther Pere on SWIEST - Transcripts 路 Screenplays 路 Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/hows-work-with-esther-pere/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How's Work? with Esther Pere - We Sell Happiness But We're Miserable</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1309700022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309700022/</guid><description>0:02
How&amp;rsquo;s work is an unscripted one time counseling session focused on work?
For the purposes of maintaining confidentiality names, employers and other identifiable characteristics have been removed, but their voices, and their stories are real.
0:38
He is the pastry, chef is the creative guy.
He is busy with the products.
He is anything to do with customer contact, customer care, the logistics, basically, everything to do with what happens to the macaroons from the door out, and it&amp;rsquo;s a lot.</description></item><item><title>How's Work? with Esther Pere - My Promotion Ended Our Friendship</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1309700021/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309700021/</guid><description>0:01
How&amp;rsquo;s work is an unscripted one time counseling session focused on work?
For the purposes of maintaining confidentiality names, employers and other identifiable characteristics have been removed, but their voices, and their stories are real.
0:29
Some friendships carry an unspoken it dose of loyalty.
That if we are really in this together, you are not to go ahead without me in this relationship.
There is a she and there is a day, we were friends.</description></item><item><title>How's Work? with Esther Pere - I'm Your Special One</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1309700020/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309700020/</guid><description>0:01
How&amp;rsquo;s work is an unscripted one time counseling session focused on work?
For the purposes of maintaining confidentiality names, employers and other identifiable characteristics have been removed, but their voices, and their stories are real.
0:26
Creative relationships are complex multi-layered and often intense, whether it is an actor and the agent, a writer and their editor.
0:42
Or in this case, an artist and her art dealer, these relationships often straddle that Dimension, that is highly personal and intimate with Business and Professional.</description></item><item><title>How's Work? with Esther Pere - Since I Can't Be Myself, I Try To Be You</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1309700019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309700019/</guid><description>0:01
How&amp;rsquo;s work is an unscripted one time counseling session focused on work?
For the purposes of maintaining confidentiality names, employers and other identifiable characteristics have been removed, but their voices, and their stories are real.
0:26
So I&amp;rsquo;m gonna listen to each of.
You see if I can discern your voices, the voices of identical twins.
We all see if she can figure it out.
Okay, let&amp;rsquo;s go.
So I&amp;rsquo;m older 30 seconds older.</description></item><item><title>How's Work? with Esther Pere - Breaking News Has Broken Us</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1309700018/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309700018/</guid><description>0:03
How&amp;rsquo;s work is an unscripted one.
Time counseling session focused on work for the purposes of maintaining confidentiality names, employers and other identifiable characteristics have been removed, but their voices and their stories are real.
0:32
It&amp;rsquo;s an understatement to say that this is the hardest gear that are new things have happened.
I&amp;rsquo;m not meeting co-founders or colleagues for this session for this session.
I chose to meet an entire team.</description></item><item><title>How's Work? with Esther Pere - Couples Therapy with My Boss</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1309700017/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309700017/</guid><description>0:02
How&amp;rsquo;s work is an unscripted one.
Time counseling session focused on work for the purposes of maintaining confidentiality names, employers and other identifiable characteristics have been removed, but their voices and their stories are real.
0:33
We generally remember the first day.
We met our manager, the impression they left on us, or the first impression.
We left on them.
I was really nervous about having a new manager, feeling really good about my position.</description></item><item><title>How's Work? with Esther Pere - He Gets the Respect, She Gets the Toilet Paper</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1309700016/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309700016/</guid><description>0:03
How&amp;rsquo;s work is an unscripted one.
Time counseling session focused on work for the purposes of maintaining confidentiality names, employers and other identifiable characteristics have been removed, but their voices and their stories are real.
0:33
We are celebrating our 10-year wedding anniversary in January and we&amp;rsquo;re celebrating 7 years of business.
They are co-founders who opened the gym together.
She&amp;rsquo;s 10 years older than him.
He came from Ireland and they live together in Canada.</description></item><item><title>How's Work? with Esther Pere - You'd Be Perfect for Ralph Lauren</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1309700015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309700015/</guid><description>0:01
How&amp;rsquo;s work is an unscripted one time counseling session focused on work?
For the purposes of maintaining confidentiality names, employers and other identifiable characteristics have been removed, but their voices, and their stories are real.
0:28
Do you want to call each other by your names?
Or do you want to keep that Anonymous and say you and she, and let&amp;rsquo;s try with you and she something.
Yeah, did you have aliases?</description></item><item><title>How's Work? with Esther Pere - Race, Gender and Money</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1309700014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309700014/</guid><description>0:03
How&amp;rsquo;s work is an unscripted one.
Time counseling session focused on work for the purposes of maintaining confidentiality names, employers and other identifiable characteristics have been removed, but their voices and their stories are real.
0:33
He&amp;rsquo;s been with this rock for me in the last five, six years of life, all the things that I almost didn&amp;rsquo;t know that men could be.
I just really don&amp;rsquo;t want to lose it.</description></item><item><title>How's Work? with Esther Pere - If I Quit, What Will People Say?</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1309700013/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309700013/</guid><description>0:01
How&amp;rsquo;s work is an unscripted one time counseling session focused on work?
For the purposes of maintaining confidentiality names, employers and other identifiable characteristics have been removed, but their voices, and their stories are real.
0:30
I had an eight-year affair with my career.
You took a crisis for him to find out.
You said before that sometimes the solution to our problems should be just to lie better, if I&amp;rsquo;m not saying that any book.</description></item><item><title>How's Work? with Esther Pere - Introducing: Couples Under Lockdown</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1309700012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309700012/</guid><description>0:00
In my ongoing, exploration of couple Dynamics, I had to do a series probing, the intricacies of couples under lockdown, but in this instance, it isn&amp;rsquo;t the loss of job.
0:24
That is so heightened, but the Deep commitment to preserving.
One sense of leadership and position and that may put the family at risk.
So while this episode in, Nigeria belongs to my podcast, where should we begin?</description></item><item><title>How's Work? with Esther Pere - Special Episode: Esther and Adam Grant of WorkLife</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1309700007/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309700007/</guid><description>0:01
Hello, it&amp;rsquo;s a stir and I&amp;rsquo;m very pleased to tell you that.
This is a special episode for how is work.
I&amp;rsquo;ve invited my colleague, Adam Grant, who&amp;rsquo;s an organizational psychologist and the host of his own podcast work.
0:18
Life to join me on housework.
Both of us have been exploring the Dynamics in the workplace, his ass trying to make work, not suck.
And mine has been looking at the invisible forces that shape workplace Dynamics and relationships, but work has changed, meaning dramatically in just about a few days work.</description></item><item><title>How's Work? with Esther Pere - Separated at Home But Still Together at Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1309700011/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309700011/</guid><description>0:00
What you&amp;rsquo;re about to hear is an unscripted one time counseling session focused on work for the purposes of maintaining confidentiality names, employers and other identifiable characteristics have been removed, but their voices and their stories are real.
0:17
We get along really great.
We just, we&amp;rsquo;ve had issues.
I&amp;rsquo;ve had a couple of Affairs.
We&amp;rsquo;ve filed for divorce.
We aren&amp;rsquo;t really doing that.
Now, it&amp;rsquo;s kind of just at a standstill and when you work together, how would you describe your working relationship?</description></item><item><title>How's Work? with Esther Pere - The Boss, The Client, and the Hairdresser</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1309700010/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309700010/</guid><description>0:00
What you&amp;rsquo;re about to hear is an unscripted one time counseling session focused on work for the purposes of maintaining confidentiality names, employers and other identifiable characteristics have been removed, but their voices and their stories are real.
0:15
I got to be honest.
I choose this job because there was really nothing for me to do.
And I just thought, if I can go to the school, it&amp;rsquo;s nine months long.</description></item><item><title>How's Work? with Esther Pere - Stuck in a Job, for Years</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1309700009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309700009/</guid><description>0:00
What you&amp;rsquo;re about to hear is an unscripted one time counseling session focused on work for the purposes of maintaining confidentiality names, employers and other identifiable characteristics have been removed, but their voices and their stories are real.
0:18
Very nice to meet you.
I&amp;rsquo;m glad I&amp;rsquo;m sad.
I didn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily think it would be us on the couch.
But but that works, she&amp;rsquo;s roped you into.
Yeah, I was like, oh, what did you think?</description></item><item><title>How's Work? with Esther Pere - From Bartender to Business Partner</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1309700008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309700008/</guid><description>0:00
What you&amp;rsquo;re about to hear is an unscripted one time counseling session focused on work for the purposes of maintaining confidentiality names, employers and other identifiable characteristics have been removed, but their voices and their stories are real.
0:17
He&amp;rsquo;s been the bartender.
She&amp;rsquo;s been the boss.
He&amp;rsquo;s been more than the bartender.
He&amp;rsquo;s been the loyal manager of the bar.
And for the 1st time, they are going to partner together and open attic area, which they hope will become the beginning of a chain of successful Tech areas for the last few years.</description></item><item><title>How's Work? with Esther Pere - You're Inching Me Out</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1309700006/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309700006/</guid><description>0:00
What you&amp;rsquo;re about to hear is an unscripted one time counseling session focused on work for the purposes of maintaining confidentiality names, employers and other identifiable characteristics have been removed, but their voices and their stories are real.
0:20
I think dicks are hilarious.
RNA.
Really is the two people who run a Communications company.
We have both like drastically terrible book communicating.
They had been together for 13 years as business partners as close friends that had met in college that stumbled upon this new idea that turned into a very successful business studies on the number of continents and bicoastal and the business is actually doing really well.</description></item><item><title>How's Work? with Esther Pere - Laid Off and Starting Over</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1309700005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309700005/</guid><description>0:02
I just I feel continually undermined.
The child has always been that place where I&amp;rsquo;ve been needed in.
I feel important.
A lot of the people that work for me are like an extension of my family.
There&amp;rsquo;s no doubt that you&amp;rsquo;re emotional and relational diary comes with you to work.
0:22
Imagine going to work every day, and I&amp;rsquo;m really busy place and no one will make eye contact with you.</description></item><item><title>How's Work? with Esther Pere - Not Many Men Work For Their Moms</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1309700004/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309700004/</guid><description>0:00
What you&amp;rsquo;re about to hear is an unscripted one time counseling session focused on work for the purposes of maintaining confidentiality names, employers, and other identifiable characteristics have been removed, but their voices and their stories are real.
0:17
Wella sit sit, sit sit anywhere you want.
We&amp;rsquo;re going to speak in English.
And if you have any difficulty, yes, you just say the word.
Yes, and we will translate for you so much.</description></item><item><title>How's Work? with Esther Pere - Sex Work: The Unofficial Resume</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1309700003/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309700003/</guid><description>0:00
What you&amp;rsquo;re about to hear is an unscripted one time counseling session focused on work for the purposes of maintaining confidentiality names, employers and other identifiable characteristics have been removed, but their voices and their stories are real.
0:21
Which names do we want to use?
Just so I understand.
But the lines are kind of modeling, you know, like now when I&amp;rsquo;m introducing myself with someone I&amp;rsquo;m like, oh wait, that&amp;rsquo;s not my real name, but it&amp;rsquo;s kind of becoming that and when you become close to each other do you start to call each other?</description></item><item><title>How's Work? with Esther Pere - The Break-Up</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1309700002/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309700002/</guid><description>0:02
I just I feel continually undermined.
The job has always been that place where I&amp;rsquo;ve been needed and I feel important a lot of the people that work for me are like an extension of my family.
There&amp;rsquo;s no doubt that you&amp;rsquo;re emotional and relational.
0:20
Derek comes with you to work.
Imagine going to work every day, and I&amp;rsquo;m really busy place and no one will make eye contact with you.</description></item><item><title>How's Work? with Esther Pere - Prologue: What Couples Therapy Teaches Us About Work</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1309700001/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1309700001/</guid><description>0:05
I just feel continually marginalized a company that I&amp;rsquo;ve loved and given my all and countless late nights and weekends, and wheat, lost sleep.
I just feel like my joy and desire to do.
0:26
It is just crushed.
You may be listening to this on your way to work right now, or maybe you&amp;rsquo;re actually coming home from work.
You may be trying to stop thinking about work, but you can&amp;rsquo;t the fact is we take home to work and we take work home love and work at a two pillars of our life.</description></item></channel></rss>