<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>We Can Do Hard Things on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/we-can-do-hard-things/</link><description>Recent content in We Can Do Hard Things on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 05:01:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/we-can-do-hard-things/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>266. How to Love Family When You’re Divided On Beliefs with adrienne maree brown &amp; Autumn Brown | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220277/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220277/</guid><description>Podcast Description Just in time for the holidays: adrienne maree brown and Autumn Brown join us for a heart-opening, mind-bending conversation about sisterhood, justice, family, and how to love ourselves and people with different values simultaneously. Why their family holidays used to end in explosions – and the strategy they used to transform family time into peaceful respites.
Their intentional practice for creating a more beautiful way of spending time together - including their weekly “Sister Check-ins.</description></item><item><title>265. Megan Falley Knows What Love Is | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220001/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220001/</guid><description>Podcast Description When was the first time you were made aware of your body or made to feel ashamed of your body? As promised, poet and author, Megan Falley, returns and blows Glennon’s mind with her explorations into the complexities of body, gender, and love. Megan reflects on her earliest memories of body shame and the lessons she learned about love from her family (and how she’s able to hold both the good and the bad at once).</description></item><item><title>264. Disentangling from Emotionally Immature People with Lindsay C. Gibson | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Author and clinical psychologist, Lindsay C. Gibson, is back to share practical steps to disentangle ourselves from emotionally immature people (EIPs), emphasizing the importance of repetition, persistence, and consistency in communication as well as boundary setting.
Lindsay addresses questions about being in relationship with EIPs including: Are people raised by EIPs prone to entering relationships with similar dynamics?
What happens when we try to have conversations or engage in conflict with EIPs?</description></item><item><title>263. Healing from Emotionally Immature Parents with Lindsay C. Gibson | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220003/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Author and clinical psychologist, Lindsay C. Gibson, helps us identify the characteristics of emotionally immature people (EIPs) like ego-centrism, lack of empathy, and fear of emotional intimacy.
Lindsay shares the effects of being raised by emotionally immature parents, mapping out two routes children often take – becoming internalizers or externalizers – and how that plays out in adult relationships and professional lives. Emphasizing the importance of self-compassion, Lindsay explains how often the most important step toward healing is identifying the EIPs in our lives.</description></item><item><title>262. Aubrey Gordon: On Freedom from Anti-Fatness | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Aubrey Gordon – activist, author, and teacher – talks to us about anti-fat bias and the way it manifests in employment disparities, our healthcare system, our dinner table conversations, and our parenting. She teaches us about “concern trolling” and other ways anti-fatness hides inside of our “do-gooding.” Sharing her personal experiences, Aubrey illuminates the subtle and not-so-subtle ways that our culture perpetuates anti-fatness – and examines the roots of thinness as a system of supremacy.</description></item><item><title>261. How to Stretch Time with Jenny Odell | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220005/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Author and artist, Jenny Odell, discusses how to break from the attention economy long enough to feel fully alive in a culture obsessed with productivity. She shares stories of her encounters with nature, how to be creative instead of productive, how to be less useful in order to survive, and the real reason for art and rest. This is a deep dive about how to stay human in a world that wants us to become machines.</description></item><item><title>Your Hilarious (&amp; Heartwarming) Holiday Stories! (Encore) | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220006/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Glennon, Abby, Amanda and the Pod Squad share their most brutiful and hilarious holiday stories.
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>260. Roxane Gay: Should We Quit Social Media? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220007/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Author and cultural observer, Roxane Gay, examines the landscape of the internet and our relationship with it. We discuss the line between constructive criticism and online toxicity; how to decide when to speak up and when to stay quiet; and how to stay human and allow redemption in an online world that demands perfection.
Plus, a breakdown of our shared unguilty pleasure: Naked Attraction.
About Roxane: Roxane Gay is the author of several books, including Ayiti, An Untamed State, New York Times bestsellers Bad Feminist and Hunger; and the national bestseller Difficult Women.</description></item><item><title>259. The Cure for Emotional Isolation | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220008/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220008/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do we bring our full selves into our relationships without fear of rejection? Today, Abby shares more about what’s been happening in her life since she’s stopped “bright siding” including powerful truth-telling she’s unleashed in business and her family of origin.
Glennon shares how Abby embracing her full emotions has led to deeper intimacy and connection, and a feeling of “un-loneliness” in their partnership – the opposite of what Abby feared might happen.</description></item><item><title>258. Abby Asks, “Why Can’t I Love Myself?” | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220009/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Abby opens up about starting therapy and the work she’s been doing to unearth and express uncomfortable emotions like anger and sadness. She shares her long-held fear that if she feels and expresses her full self, people will leave her.
In a profound moment, Abby shares a deep longing to truly love herself. She explains that this love has been clouded by messages she’s received since childhood which have led to difficulty trusting others, equating anger with not being okay, and a feeling like something is “wrong” with her.</description></item><item><title>257. How to Finally Forgive with Nadia Bolz-Weber | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220010/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Where does all our suffering come from and how can we free ourselves?
Pastor, author, and speaker, Nadia Bolz-Weber, discusses how she finally became healed and whole enough to choose romantic love from freedom instead of desperation. With her characteristic raw honesty, Nadia shares that the secret to her healing has been “honestly, a lot of pain.”
Plus, Nadia leads Abby to a heartbreaking, cathartic moment of clarity – and shares a blessing that she wrote for Abby and all queer people.</description></item><item><title>256. How to Host a Magical Gathering with Priya Parker | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220011/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Priya Parker is here to discuss what Glennon called “the most important thing in the world” – connection – and how to make our time with other people have more of it. She teaches us: How – whether it’s a wedding or a retirement party – you can create new gathering rituals that forge truer, deeper relationships;
Why the outcome of every gathering is decided before anyone steps in the room; and Why so many of us hate parties – and what to do about it.</description></item><item><title>255. Glennon on One Year of Recovery! | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Glennon tells three stories that reveal how recovery from anorexia has changed who she is and how she experiences the world.
Together in G’s home, recording for the first time, Abby and Amanda respond with their reflections and the impacts that G’s recovery work has had on the entire family.
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>254. Dolly Parton: How to Make Decisions (Even If They Break Your Heart) | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220013/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220013/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this special episode, Glennon, Abby, and Amanda sit down with icon Dolly Parton for a heartfelt conversation about how to start something new at 77, how she mothers the world, and how she broke her own heart when Elvis asked to record her hit song. Plus, the advice Dolly would give to Glennon and Abby’s daughter, Tish, as she enters the music business. About Dolly: Dolly Parton is the most honored and revered female country singer-songwriter of all time and was recently inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.</description></item><item><title>253. Is it Real Love or Spider Love? With Martha Beck | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220014/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brilliant life coach, Martha Beck, works her magic for our Pod Squad.
In this treasure trove of profound insight and practical guidance, Martha teaches us how to find purpose in midlife, how to use our longing as a map, and how to know for sure if what we have is real love. If you’d like to go back and listen to the episodes mentioned in today’s conversation, check out episodes: Martha Beck Helps Amanda Let Go How to De-Stress: Relaxation Intervention for Amanda (and You)!</description></item><item><title>252. Martha Beck Helps Amanda Let Go | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220015/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this incredibly raw episode, Martha Beck coaches Amanda through a transformative, therapeutic session to help heal her overfunctioning, resentment, and burnout. Martha uncovers the different parts of Amanda that have existed inside her since childhood – and invites them to speak and then finally rest into peace, joy, and enoughness. If you’d like to go back and listen to episodes referenced in today’s conversation, check out: 238. How to De-Stress: Relaxation Intervention for Amanda (and You)!</description></item><item><title>251. How to Break Cycles with Allison Russell | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Singer, songwriter, and instrumentalist, Allison Russell, shares her incredible life story and teaches us how she healed from abuse through music, sisterhood, and returning to her body. This hour is a soul-stirring reminder of the life-saving, cycle-breaking power of truth telling, art, and love. About Allison: Allison Russell has spent her career in multiple bands, including Po’ Girl, Our Native Daughters and Birds of Chicago. After a career spent as a gifted multi-instrumentalist, backing numerous other artists, she finally dared to release her solo project in 2021.</description></item><item><title>250. Why Do We Have Sex? Asexuality with Angela Chen | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, Angela Chen teaches us how understanding asexuality helps us understand ourselves and the true meaning of sex. Angela describes: The misconception that blocks us from fully understanding our own sexuality;
Why your sexuality is a relationship between YOU and YOU; How there are MANY reasons people have sex. (Glennon says sexual attraction only accounts for 5% of her sexual experiences.); and
The shame underlying compulsory sexuality – and how to stop apologizing for not wanting sex.</description></item><item><title>249. The Best Advice We’ve Got on Loneliness &amp; Jealousy | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220018/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who do we go to for advice? And do we really even WANT advice — or just a good listener?
Glennon, Abby, and Amanda tell us who they each go to when they don’t know what to do next — and offer their best advice to Pod Squaders dealing with loneliness and the unexpected jealousy of their partner&amp;rsquo;s affection for a pet.
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>248. The One Way to Get the Truth from Someone | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220019/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amanda shares the one proven way to get the truth from someone – plus:
Why Glennon calls her lying style “The Puppeteer” – and why you’ll never know what Amanda’s really feeling. Amanda defends our right to lie, and debunks myths about how we can tell if someone is lying. What’s the difference between lying and controlling, manipulating, and filtering the truth?
Glennon’s fear of judgment from the next generation, and How to foster real connection in a world where lying is normal.</description></item><item><title>247. Kerry Washington on the Family Secret that Shaped Her | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220020/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kerry Washington shares the deeply personal story of what happened when her parents finally told her the truth about a long-held and shocking family secret:
How uncovering the truth – as painful as it was – led Kerry to reclaim her self trust; How the revelation made her the lead character of her own life for the first time;
Walking the line between protection and deception;
Breaking the cycle of gaslighting within families; and How defying her father freed both of them.</description></item><item><title>246. The Answer to Caregiving Burnout with Ai-jen Poo | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220021/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Calling all Caregivers! Today is a tribute to the everyday efforts of all caregivers who are holding up the sky for everyone else. Ai-jen Poo is here shining a light on why caregivers are exhausted, unsupported, and overwhelmed – all while doing the work that makes everything else possible. We talk about how to give the people we love the care they deserve without neglecting our own needs, and what can be done to right the systemic failures that leave caregivers fending for themselves.</description></item><item><title>245. An Unforgettable Double Date with Andrea Gibson &amp; Megan Falley | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Andrea Gibson returns with their partner, Megan Falley, for a gorgeous, hilarious double date with Glennon and Abby:
An Andrea health update and what each has learned since Andrea’s cancer diagnosis;
How their chemistry ignited with Andrea’s questionable move on a sweaty dance floor – and the text moment Andrea knew Megan was the one;
How each of their relationships with their bodies has been transformed by Andrea’s illness;</description></item><item><title>244. Stop Carrying Other People’s Pain with Chloé Cooper Jones | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Where do you go to escape the pain of reality? Today, author Chloé Cooper Jones shares: The survival strategy many of us use to retreat from our lives and how to become more present; How she grapples with the world dehumanizing her disabled body; Why desire and disgust are so connected – and what they teach us; and The thing Chloé wants most – to be seen as inherently whole – and how to get it.</description></item><item><title>Introducing Say More with Dr? Sheila | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220024/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2023 06:13:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220024/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the world of feelings, there are winners and losers, and somebody has to be the judge. World-renowned, self-proclaimed couples therapist Dr? Sheila invites you to sit in on her private sessions with clients. (For legal reasons, Dr? must be said in the form of a question.) Each week, a new couple…and a new puzzle to crack. You’ll get to hear, and benefit from, many of her famous techniques as she counsels patients on overcoming disagreements, dealing with an overstepping mother-in-law, navigating open relationships, and much more.</description></item><item><title>243. Oprah Shares “The Letter from Glennon that Freed Me” | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220025/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220025/</guid><description>Podcast Description The moment Oprah finally knew who she really was;
The hidden gift of criticism, and the image to remember when you’re envious; Why “Slugging It Out” is a losing game;
How to let go of outcomes – and make peace with what you have to offer; and Oprah reads the letter Glennon wrote to her after her mother died – which she says changed her life. Read Oprah’s newest book BUILD THE LIFE YOU WANT.</description></item><item><title>242. We’re All Liars: What’s Your Lying Style? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220026/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Liar, liar – all of our pants are on fire. In this juicy conversation about lying:
Why the question isn’t “DO you lie?” – but “HOW and WHY do you lie?”
What constitutes a lie to you: defining what makes something a lie;
Figuring out our own particular lie languages – and why Abby’s a Bullshitter; and
Deciding if there is anyone you can be completely honest with – and how to create the algorithm of honesty.</description></item><item><title>241. Being Left Out: Navigating that Lifelong Ache | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220027/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220027/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amanda, Glennon and Abby explore how to survive the lifelong, universal pain of being left out:
What Abby felt when she heard “We don’t want you here” – and its long-lasting impact; Why it is so painful, and how to process feelings of rejection and isolation;
How dissociation helped Glennon cope with rejection in the cafeteria; What parents should and should not do when helping kids navigate exclusion; and The real difference between “fitting in” and “belonging.</description></item><item><title>How People are Using Psychedelics to Help Their Relationships with Dr. Hillary McBride | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Hillary McBride is back to continue our thrilling conversation about PSYCHEDELICS — and how folks are using them to enhance their relationships and lives. She helps us understand: The importance of seeing our partners – and letting ourselves be seen – without any defenses; How combining therapy with psychedelics is helping people stay close to their feelings; Why the first step toward healing is feeling safe in your body; and An important question for us all: Why is being here so hard?</description></item><item><title>240. Are Psychedelics an Answer? with Dr. Hillary McBride | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220029/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why is everyone talking about psychedelics?!?! Today, Dr. Hillary McBride joins us to answer all of our questions about therapeutic psychedelics, and: Her personal, step-by-step journey with therapeutic psychedelics; The science behind how psychedelics help break old patterns and create new ones; How she uncovered the root of her eating disorder; and How psychedelics can reveal your innate goodness. For our Embodiment conversation with Dr. McBride, check out: Ep 206: How to Follow the Wisdom of Your Body with Dr.</description></item><item><title>239. Why Are We Never Satisfied? with adrienne maree brown | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220030/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Are you capable of being satisfied? Today, adrienne maree brown helps us uncover: How to find beauty and connection in the everyday;
How to stop wasting your time on things that don’t feel good;
Why the greatest risk of life is also where its preciousness comes from; How, through the discipline of pleasure, we can ALL be satisfied. About adrienne: adrienne maree brown is a pleasure activist, writer, and radical imaginist who grows healing ideas in public through writing, music, and podcasts.</description></item><item><title>238. How to De-Stress: Relaxation Intervention for Amanda (and You)! | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220031/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Abby and Glennon attempt a Relaxation Intervention, which Amanda sabotages – resulting in a riveting discussion of why we can’t (don’t) de-stress, and how relaxation can help us ALL feel a little more human:
Why so many of us have lost our playful, silly, absurd selves – and how we might recover them; The “Relaxation Homework” Abby assigned to Amanda; How over-functioners can channel their superpower into being fully alive; Why it’s not our job to ensure things won’t fall apart, but to accept that they absolutely will; And the one “tracking” tool Amanda will use to find more moments of connection.</description></item><item><title>237. Why We Love the Way We Love: Attachment Styles with Dr. Becky Kennedy | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220032/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Glennon and Amanda share why they love this wildly popular conversation with Dr. Becky Kennedy and how it radically changed their approaches to parenting their kids (and reparenting themselves). Dr. Becky Kennedy guides us through Attachment Styles, how our past comes alive in our present – and how to free ourselves and raise freer kids.
Why attachment styles are at the heart of our most intense conflicts (in ourselves and with others).</description></item><item><title>236. Abby Wambach: Will I Ever Be Truly Loved? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220033/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, we celebrate the one-and-only Abby – and her rare gift of vulnerability and storytelling.
Our favorite person on the planet – Abby Wambach – is going deep, answering the questions that we all have, but that only Glennon and Amanda can ask.
Abby shares, in an intensely new and courageous way, about her lifelong pursuit of love – including her complicated relationships with her mom, soccer, her first marriage, queerness, and her “shadow self” – and why she has questioned her own lovability for so much of her life.</description></item><item><title>235. Tracee Ellis Ross: How to Make Peace in Your Own Head | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220034/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220034/</guid><description>Podcast Description Abby shares one of her all-time most impactful conversations – delving inside the “wonderful, dangerous” mind of Tracee Ellis Ross covers:
Tracee’s go-to strategies to stop questioning herself, to pick herself up when she feels unlovable, and to tether herself to her truest self.
How she made peace with the fact that she’s “not everyone’s cup of tea” – and stopped trying to change the things about her that others don’t like (but she does).</description></item><item><title>234. Glennon’s Diagnosis &amp; What’s Next | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220035/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Glennon reflects on the episode that has been the biggest marker of change in her life in the last five years. Glennon shares from the messy middle about her new diagnosis and what’s next for her recovery.
If talk about eating disorders and mental illness helps: Listen today. If it triggers: Skip today.
CW // eating disorders
If you have an eating disorder, you may find the National Alliance for Eating Disorders a helpful resource: https://www.</description></item><item><title>233. What’s Next for We Can Do Hard Things | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220036/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join Glennon, Abby, and Amanda in celebrating, and closing out, the first season of the pod – and help them write the next chapter:
What it felt like for Glennon to listen – for the first time – to her anorexia diagnosis episode; How their parents’ 50th Wedding Anniversary party showed Glennon how to stop performing and just BE; The crucial distinction Amanda is exploring between tension and conflict; Abby’s recent decision to explore her relationship with anger; and How to join in shaping the future of the pod.</description></item><item><title>232. What’s Your FAMILY DRAMA Style? with Nedra Glover Tawwab | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220037/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220037/</guid><description>Podcast Description We all want tools to navigate (and minimize!) family drama. Today, Nedra Glover Tawwab teaches us how we can create drama free families: How to speak up for yourself when it feels like going against the group; Why confrontation is often the kindest thing; When, exactly, we should bring up conflict &amp;amp; when to let it go;
The most loving way a parent can respond to a child in pain.</description></item><item><title>231. Life-Changing Wisdom You Need to Hear | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220038/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, Glennon, Abby, and Amanda dive into the Pod Squad’s words of wisdom:
How to identify bad advice; How to stop “walking on eggshells”; When to not tell your kids you’re proud of them (and what to say instead); The advice about masturbating that Glennon can live by.
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description></item><item><title>230. The Best Advice We’ve Ever Received | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220039/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220039/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Best Advice We’ve Ever Received
Today, Glennon, Abby, and Amanda remember – and share! – the best advice they’ve ever received:
How to honor your needs and become the ultimate expert of you; Why we all need a friend who believes in our greatness; How to encourage your kids to live open-hearted; And why Glennon’s truest thing is that she doesn’t know anything. Plus, we hear from two pod treasures – Sara Bareilles and Glennon’s 7th grade government teacher, Mrs.</description></item><item><title>229. THE WORLD CUP WITH ABBY: Inside Her Most Stunning Moments &amp; 2023 Predictions | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220040/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Time to HUDDLE UP, Pod Squad! Our most beloved The Soccer expert – Abby Wambach – prepares us for the World Cup, bringing us inside her personal rollercoaster journey through four World Cups:
The real scoop behind her impossible, iconic goal against Brazil in 2011; The moments she will never forget from the brutal loss against Germany;
How she really reacted when learning she would not be starting for the 2015 US Team; How we can ALL learn to lead from the bench; and</description></item><item><title>228. Do You Have Any of These Beige Flags? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220041/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, Glennon, Abby, and Amanda delight in “Beige Flags” – the hilarious internet sensation that invites us all to share our people’s weirdest and most baffling traits. You’ll learn why Glennon changes her clothes 5 times a day, Abby sounds like she’s from yonder yore, and Amanda has a drawer full of washed out Ziploc bags.
Plus, we read YOUR Beige Flags and debate: Is that actually a red flag or a green flag?</description></item><item><title>Introducing Classy with Jonathan Menjivar | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220042/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Introducing Classy with Jonathan Menjivar, a new podcast from Pineapple Street Studios. Classy is a collection of surprising stories, juicy and uncomfortable interviews, and engaging segments that explore the ways that class infiltrates our day-to-day lives. In the host seat is Jonathan Menjivar – a working-class Latino kid who joined the media elite and became someone who likes oysters, wears cashmere socks, and is very conflicted about all of it.</description></item><item><title>227. MEGAN RAPINOE: A Legend Says Goodbye to the Game | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220043/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Laser-focused on her final World Cup, MEGAN RAPINOE chooses our podcast to go deep on her bittersweet decision to retire from her iconic soccer career:
Why she is excited – and ready – to say goodbye to soccer; Why representing America is so important to her in this moment; Why she doesn’t believe in sacrificing herself for the team; How dissociation helped her on the field – and hurt her in life – and how she’s working to give it up.</description></item><item><title>Fix Your Most Important Relationships with the Enneagram: Suzanne Stabile | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220044/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220044/</guid><description>Podcast Description We all have that one relationship that needs fixing… Today, Suzanne Stabile is back to tell us how we can use the Enneagram to improve our relationships and love our people better. She guides us through: How to stop misjudging and misunderstanding people; How to start respecting your own innate gifts; How to get rid of codependency; and How to get what you are missing – more thinking, feeling, or doing – in your life.</description></item><item><title>226. Enneagram: Why You Are the Way You Are with Suzanne Stabile | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220045/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Enneagram Godmother Suzanne Stabile guides us through: What the hell is the Enneagram and why does it matter? The gifts and struggles each Enneagram type faces;
Why the worst part of you is also the BEST part of you;
The core desire / fear that explains your behavior; and Why, if Suzanne ever needs brain surgery, she’s finding a doctor who’s an Enneagram 1.
And we FINALLY answer the question: Is Amanda a 3 or a 1?</description></item><item><title>225. How to Find 5 Seconds of Peace with Morgan Harper Nichols | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220046/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220046/</guid><description>Podcast Description Morgan Harper Nichols is here today to help us – finally! – breathe deep and pay attention: What the hell is this elusive “peace” anyway?
How to create your own peace practice
How she has found a truer way to communicate than words How her adult autism diagnosis helped her finally set boundaries Concrete strategies to find peace even in chaos Plus, she helps us understand why we don’t need to add “Presence” to our to-do list: It’s already right here.</description></item><item><title>224. Get REAL Pleasure &amp; Stop Faking It with Vanessa Marin | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220047/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220047/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sex Therapist Vanessa Marin is back on the pod to discuss how we can all make sex more ENJOYABLE. She shares with us: How we can stop faking our orgasms and experiment with real pleasure; How to communicate honestly with our partners about what we want in bed; and
Why masturbation can be an opportunity for self-exploration and reclamation.
She also offers empowering advice for individuals recovering from sexual trauma.</description></item><item><title>223. Get What You Want at Work &amp; Home: How to Negotiate with Mori Taheripour | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220048/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220048/</guid><description>Podcast Description If the word “negotiation” makes you feel tense and sweaty and like the last thing you want to do is listen to this conversation . . . then what you absolutely need to do is listen to this conversation. Because it turns out we&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about negotiation all wrong, and today we empower ourselves to think about it differently. Mori Taheripour guides us through the top things we all get wrong in negotiation; the most effective tool in asking for a raise; the ways the vast majority of women undercut our own value; how we can best advocate for ourselves; and how to hold non-negotiable boundaries.</description></item><item><title>222. Jia Tolentino: The 1% of Life that Makes It All Worth It | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220049/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jia Tolentino joins us to discuss how to finally accept all sides of you: Why your un-productivity matters most; When your shame is good; How to make your real life bigger than your internet life;
How to let motherhood energize you instead of drain you; and How to stop scrolling in the middle of the night. Plus, we talk acid trips, the sorority rush that Jia and Amanda shared, why Glennon’s friends track Jia’s words – and whether Glennon’s mug shot will inspire Jia’s next show.</description></item><item><title>221. How to Lose Half of Your Guilt | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220050/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Glennon, Abby, and Amanda help us shed guilt through a freeing reframe inspired by a conversation with Dr. Becky Kennedy.
Listen to learn: How to know what is true guilt and what is just the uncomfortable ickiness of defying expectations; how to hold boundaries in order to live shamelessly within our own values; and how to maintain empathy by staying with our own emotions instead of internalizing the emotions of others.</description></item><item><title>220. Why So Many Women Don’t Know They are Autistic with Katherine May | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220051/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Author Katherine May recounts the moment she – at age 37 – discovered she is autistic and recognized herself for the first time. Living as an autistic person in a world that often misunderstands her, Katherine shares:
How the prevailing understandings of autism erase the lived experiences of autistic women and girls; The way autism looks and feels for adult women; and
How she navigates social interactions and sensory overload.</description></item><item><title>Craig Melton on DATING!!! – with Logan Ury | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220052/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Logan Ury helps Glennon’s former husband and co-parent, Craig Melton, navigate the wild world of dating as a grown up: How to identify your patterns that aren’t working for you; how to know if something’s really a deal breaker; why dating in your twenties is like “start-up” while dating later in life is a “merger”; an honest audit of Craig’s online dating profile; how to ensure you’re meeting who you want to meet; and how Craig factors whether or not Glennon and Abby will like who he’s dating.</description></item><item><title>219. How to Make a Friend &amp; Find a Date with Logan Ury | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220053/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220053/</guid><description>Podcast Description How the hell do grown ups date and make friends? Behavioral scientist turned dating coach, Logan Ury is here to help us make dating and meeting new friends easier: how to identify what you really want; why we should stop searching for “the spark”; why we keep going after the same people that are wrong for us; how to talk to our kids about their first love experiences; why we need to have “other significant others”; and the eight questions you should ask yourself after meeting anyone new.</description></item><item><title>218. Kelly Clarkson: Red Flags, Divorce &amp; Starting Over | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220054/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220054/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this deeply personal conversation, Kelly Clarkson – beloved artist, truth teller, and goddamn cheetah – joins us to discuss: How Untamed gave her the clarity and courage to divorce; Why she stayed for as long as she did; The lowest point of her life; What broke her heart the most in her marriage; How to recover yourself after slowly disappearing in a relationship; Her incredible new album chemistry; Embracing singleness; and Why she’s a stronger parent today.</description></item><item><title>Your Joy &amp; Pride Infusion for Today! | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220055/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220055/</guid><description>Podcast Description We need more JOY. In today’s bonus episode, internet sensations corook and Olivia Barton delight us with their performance of “If I Were a Fish.” Plus, Glennon and Abby coach them on how to not let criticism keep you from sharing yourself with the world.
For our other conversations about delight, check out: Episode 216 How to Find DELIGHT Today (and Every Day) with Ross Gay and Episode 217 Start a Daily Delight Practice with Abby, Glennon &amp;amp; Amanda.</description></item><item><title>217. Start a Daily Delight Practice with Abby, Glennon &amp; Amanda! | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220056/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Glennon’s hilarious misunderstanding with a TSA agent she’ll remember &amp;rsquo;til she dies; Amma’s delightful response when Abby rushed onto the soccer field; and the delight Amanda experienced the day she switched it all up by not freaking out. Today’s episode was inspired by our conversation with Ross Gay – if you missed it, check out: Episode 216 How to Find DELIGHT Today (and Every Day) with Ross Gay. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>216. How to Find DELIGHT Today (and Every Day) with Ross Gay | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220057/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ross Gay teaches us how to notice delight and joy in our everyday lives. We discuss: concrete ways to rediscover and capture joy every day; how to rebuild your “delight muscle”; how to dissolve the myth of disconnection between us; and how to “unknow” our people so we can delight in them.
About Ross: Ross Gay is an American poet, essayist, and professor committed to healing the world through observing and articulating joy, delight and gratitude.</description></item><item><title>215. The Bravest Conversation We’ve Had: Andrea Gibson | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220058/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220058/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the conversation that’s meant the most to Glennon, Abby, and Amanda – poet and spoken word artist, Andrea Gibson makes the bravest announcement we’ve ever heard. Andrea shares how to boundlessly, relentlessly love our lives by: paying attention to the only thing we can control; letting go of living in fear; and feeling less alone and terrified through it all.
CW: Discussion of suicidal ideation
About Andrea: Andrea Gibson is one of the most celebrated and influential spoken word artists of our time.</description></item><item><title>214. Insecurity, Anger, ADHD &amp; Abby’s Retirement | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220059/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220059/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s beautiful, vulnerable, and funny conversation, Glennon, Abby, and Amanda reveal what each feels most insecure about. Plus, Amanda connects with a member of the Pod Squad on raising a kid with ADHD and her shift that changed everything; Glennon talks about anger as a guard dog and her discovery while rock climbing on “vacation”; and Abby explains why retirement from soccer was one of the hardest times of her life and how she navigated that massive life transition.</description></item><item><title>213. Sex Fantasies: What Do They Say About Us? with Vanessa Marin | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220060/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220060/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sex therapist Vanessa Marin is back and we’re digging into: why we’re (sadly and ironically) proven to be less likely to try new things in the bedroom the longer we’ve been partnered; how to spice up your sex life when things get bland – including how to find out and explore your sexual fantasies; how not all orgasms (even for men!) are created equal; and the TikTok sex challenges we should probably pass on.</description></item><item><title>212. The Pep Talk You, Your Grad &amp; the Country Needs! | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220061/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220061/</guid><description>Podcast Description For graduates (and all of us), it’s scary and hard to know the way forward. Listen to Abby tell the Class of 2023 (and all of us) the way! Thank you to Loyola Marymount University. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>211. How to Spot a Narcissist with Caroline Strawson | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220062/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Trauma therapist (and survivor of marriage to a narcissist) Caroline Strawson joins us to discuss: how to know if someone’s really a narcissist; how to know if you’re more likely to get into a relationship with a narcissist (and avoid it); strategies for parallel parenting with a narcissist; how the brain and body respond to narcissists; and how to rebuild after ending a relationship with a narcissist. CW: Abusive relationships, self harm</description></item><item><title>210. Calling All Control Freaks: How to Stop Overfunctioning | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220063/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220063/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this unplanned conversation, Amanda speaks up for everyone who’s been labeled a “Control Freak” – anyone who feels like they have to hold up the entire sky for their families or businesses – when what they really want is to feel supported and safe. Amanda shares vulnerably about: how she became an overfunctioner, the blessings and curses of being one, and the practical strategies she’s using to let go – and what her partner is doing to make her feel like she can finally try to relax.</description></item><item><title>209. How to Make Betrayal Beautiful with Maggie Smith | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220064/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220064/</guid><description>Podcast Description For the first time, Glennon requests a one-on-one with our guest – author and poet Maggie Smith – in this deeply honest conversation about: how to tell the brutal truth without betraying our people, how to reclaim ourselves after infidelity and betrayal, how the shaming of women who dare to tell their stories keeps us powerless and isolated, and how they both have embraced acceptance instead of “forgiveness.”</description></item><item><title>208. Can You Find Gender IN You or Just ON You? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220065/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Glennon explains what she meant when she said, “I just can&amp;rsquo;t find gender in me. I can only find it on me,” in this beautiful conversation that began with a question from a college freshman named Nick.
Please revisit our conversations with ALOK here: Episode 74 ALOK: What makes us beautiful? What makes us free? and Episode 75 ALOK: How do we interrupt trauma? How do we heal?</description></item><item><title>207. PSA: How to Not Be an A-hole | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220066/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, Abby, Amanda, and Glennon learn new ways not to be assholes. In this follow up to Episode 191 Why Etiquette is B.S. &amp;amp; New Rules for Living, we share Pod Squad wisdom about ways we can all make the world a less annoying place. Join us as we learn how to deepen our conversations with people by not saying the first thing we think of, spreading “tell me more” energy instead of “let me tell you about me” energy, and not asking “surface” questions that aren’t surface at all.</description></item><item><title>206. How to Follow the Wisdom of Your Body with Dr. Hillary McBride | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220067/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Embodiment teacher, Dr. Hillary McBride, joins us to discuss: what embodiment and disembodiment are; dissociation as survival response, somatophobia, and how to get more comfortable with fear. She offers concrete practices to stop blaming our bodies, and help us become attuned to our body’s messages. If you haven’t listened to Glennon’s latest episodes about her recovery journey and embodiment, check them out here: Episode 199 Why Glennon Says We Should All Be In Recovery and Episode 200 Don’t Tell Glennon to Love Her Body.</description></item><item><title>205. Why Good Photos Make Us Feel Bad | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220068/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amanda’s epiphany on Alice’s school Picture Day about the destructive messages we’re inadvertently sending our kids; our forced pursuit of happiness in photos with our families; why family photo shoots bring out the worst in us; and why we should allow ourselves and our people to just look like we look. Check out past episodes mentioned: Episode 196 How Glennon &amp;amp; Abby Learned to Talk Dirty with Vanessa Marin and Episode 125 WHY ARE THERE NO PICTURES OF US?</description></item><item><title>204. Priyanka Chopra Jonas: How to Care Less About What People Think | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220069/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Priyanka Chopra Jonas dives deep into: the night she fell for Nick at the Met Gala, walking her baby through their harrowing NICU journey, her strategy to make Malti Marie think she’s cool, and why accountability is good – if we know the right people to be accountable to. About Priyanka: Priyanka Chopra Jonas is a multi-faceted talent, New York Times Best Selling Author of UNFINISHED, and one of the most recognized people in the world.</description></item><item><title>203. How to Create Your Own Belonging with Michelle Zauner | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220070/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michelle Zauner on how to begin healing our mother wounds, using her sensitivity to deepen her relationships and be a rockstar, why she’s obsessed with sheetcake and winnebagos, and why she is still “afraid of her mental health.” About Michelle: MICHELLE ZAUNER is best known as a singer and guitarist who creates dreamy, shoegaze-inspired indie pop under the name Japanese Breakfast. She has won acclaim from major music outlets around the world for releases like Psychopomp and Soft Sounds from Another Planet.</description></item><item><title>202. Are You Being Gaslighted? with Dr. Robin Stern | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220071/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220071/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is gaslighting REALLY and what isn’t? Plus, how to know if you’re in a relationship with a gaslighter, the three types of gaslighters, and how to break free from a gaslighter and reclaim yourself. About Dr. Stern: Robin Stern, Ph.D., is the co-founder and associate director for the Yale Center for Emotional Intelligence and an associate research scientist at the Child Study Center at Yale. She is a licensed psychoanalyst with 30 years of experience treating individuals, couples, and families.</description></item><item><title>201. What We’re Watching, Reading &amp; Listening to Right Now | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220072/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is the most relentless question of your day (other than what do you want for dinner?): WHAT SHOULD WE WATCH TONIGHT?
Here to help. Everything we’re watching, listening to, and reading on today’s pod: Yellowjackets, Succession, Calendar Girls, 90 Day Fiancé, and so much more.
Let’s start a Pod Squad list. What are you all watching / reading / listening to?
P.S. Succession Spoiler Alert! Skip through from ~20:38-23:20 if you need to!</description></item><item><title>200. Don’t Tell Glennon to Love Her Body | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220073/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why Glennon respects “body positivity” – but it doesn’t work for her. What if every single thing we’ve learned about who we are is wrong? What if we ARE our Bodies?
What if instead of trying to love our bodies, we could experience being alive on this planet… as bodies? If talk about eating disorders and mental illness helps: Listen today. If it triggers: Skip today.
CW: eating disorders</description></item><item><title>199. Why Glennon Says We Should All Be In Recovery | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220074/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Glennon shares what her recovery – leaving something you can’t live without – feels like: Almost impossible. She explains how she views recovery as an invitation to a great quest that improves life for every person who accepts it. If you haven’t listened to Glennon’s latest episode about her recovery journey and embodiment, check it out here: Episode 194 Glennon Finds Her Healing Partner. If talk about eating disorders and mental illness helps: Listen today.</description></item><item><title>198. Julia Louis-Dreyfus: Why We All Lie &amp; How Honest Can We Be? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220075/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Julia Louis-Dreyfus joins us to dive deep into: going to therapy with her 87-year-old mom, how to love adult kids well, the metaphor that got her through breast cancer, and why we should all be excited about getting older. About Julia: Julia Louis-Dreyfus is one of Hollywood’s most influential, iconic actors and producers. She starred in and executive produced HBO’s hit series Veep, she was Elaine Benes in Seinfeld and Christine Campbell in The New Adventures of Old Christine.</description></item><item><title>197. Cheryl Strayed Tells Us What the Hell to Do Next | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220076/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220076/</guid><description>Podcast Description How to end a relationship lovingly, how to love an addict, and how to keep surprising yourself in midlife (buy the tap dancing shoes). Plus, why Cheryl decided to cut down her drinking. For our past episodes with Cheryl, listen to Episode 118 Cheryl Strayed: Don’t Let Your Dreams Ruin Your Life and Episode 119 It’s Okay to Want What You Want: Cheryl Strayed as Dear Sugar.
For the Amanda episode Cheryl mentioned, listen to Episode 177 How to Face Your Biggest Fears with Amanda Doyle.</description></item><item><title>196. How Glennon &amp; Abby Learned to Talk Dirty with Vanessa Marin | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220077/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220077/</guid><description>Podcast Description How to finally discover what turns us on, how to discuss turn-offs – and how to create “sex menus” with our partners. The real reason so many of us don’t feel like having sex. How to ask for more sex – and how to turn it down without hurting your partner. Orgasm – why it’s not the whole shebang – and what to do if we’ve been faking it.</description></item><item><title>195. Sex Talk &amp; That Night in Miami: Sex Therapy with Vanessa Marin | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220078/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two silent sex queens &amp;amp; Abby invite sex therapist Vanessa Marin onto the pod and into their bedrooms to discuss: Practical, concrete tips for how to get over your discomfort and talk about sex with your partner – and how Vanessa’s advice is currently working for Glennon and Abby. Why women tend to struggle receiving during sex – and how hustle culture shows up in the bedroom. How to activate desire instead of shame when asking for more frequent or different sex.</description></item><item><title>194. Glennon Finds Her Healing Partner | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220079/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Glennon takes us along on her “exile walk” to share how recovery’s going and some new found wisdom that will help us all including: How to shut off the mind and stop over-intellectualizing to allow space for other parts and memories to rise up. Acknowledging that nobody’s “fine” – and we’re all either transforming or transmitting our pain. Glennon&amp;rsquo;s interaction with a young surfer that offended them both (in very different ways).</description></item><item><title>193. MICHELLE OBAMA! | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220080/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220080/</guid><description>Podcast Description MICHELLE OBAMA!
How to develop the one tool that has sustained Mrs. Obama throughout her entire life. How to identify whether you’re deeply satisfied or deeply stuck – and how to reach for the goal of living “comfortably afraid.” What we never knew about Mrs. Obama’s incredible father, Fraser C. Robinson III, and how he shaped her life. How to avoid what Mrs. Obama calls, “Getting lost in the battle of explaining yourself.</description></item><item><title>192. Women at Work &amp; The Episode That Wasn’t with Sarah Spain | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220081/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pioneering sports journalist – the brilliant, hilarious, badass Sarah Spain – joins us to reflect on:
One of our most popular episodes – Episode 147: The Episode That Wasn’t – when we ended an interview after the guest was disrespectful to our team member; The constant indignities and inequities in male-dominated fields; To report or not to report harassment – and what actually happens when you do report?; and How to help ourselves – and come together to help each other – secure safer and more just work spaces.</description></item><item><title>191. Why Etiquette is B.S. &amp; New Rules for Living | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220082/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220082/</guid><description>Podcast Description When is it too late to cancel on someone? How do we split the bill? Text messages: What NOT to do, and is there time-induced amnesty? Phone calls in public: Hell no, or do what you wish? Once and for all: Can we agree on how we all get off the plane? Today, Abby – whose mom sent her to etiquette school to learn to be a “lady” – and Glennon and Amanda – whose mom did not – discuss the New Rules for being human while surrounded by humans; the thin line between manners meant to offer consideration vs.</description></item><item><title>190. Abby’s Christmas Miracle: When All the Heartbreak Made Sense | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220083/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220083/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Part 2 of this Abby conversation, Abby shared the greatest gift she’s ever received. In this Part 3, we dive into: exactly what happened that magical morning from Abby, Glennon, and Amanda’s perspective; Craig’s reaction; and why it was that singular moment that Abby finally felt fully loved and chosen.
If you haven’t listened to Part 1, check it out here: Episode 188 Abby Wambach: Will I Ever Be Truly Loved?</description></item><item><title>189. Abby for the 1st Time On Divorce &amp; Her Unrequited Love | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220084/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220084/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Part 2 of our deeply personal interview with Abby, she reveals for the first time:
Her romance with an unrequited love – someone who strung her along hopelessly for years; Her anguish and rebirth after being arrested; Her sense of loss when being crowned FIFA Player of the Year; Her divorce after fighting for marriage equality – inside her own family and on the public stage; and The night she met Glennon.</description></item><item><title>188. Abby Wambach: Will I Ever Be Truly Loved? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220085/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220085/</guid><description>Podcast Description This is the one! Our favorite person on the planet – Abby Wambach – is going deep, answering the questions that we all have, but that only Glennon and Amanda can ask. Abby shares, in an intensely new and courageous way, about her lifelong pursuit of love – including her complicated relationships with her mom, soccer, her first marriage, queerness, and her “shadow self” – and why she has questioned her own lovability for so much of her life.</description></item><item><title>187. 5 Ways to Be More Present: Indigenous Wisdom from Kaitlin Curtice | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220086/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220086/</guid><description>Podcast Description How to listen to the signals our bodies give us, and other concrete strategies to hold on to being human. The healing power of honoring and reconnecting with our little girl selves and with our Mother Earth. How, if all else fails, we can practice presence and embodiment by talking to a house plant. The traumatizing effect of purity culture, colonization, and assimilation, and how to come home to the wholeness of our core nature, desire, and wisdom.</description></item><item><title>186. Gloria Steinem: Laughing Our Way to Liberation | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220087/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220087/</guid><description>Podcast Description GLORIA STEINEM – who dedicates her life to ensuring we know that we are not broken, but were born into a system intended to break us – lives in the DNA of millions who are giving birth to movements or to themselves.
She reminds us why there’s nothing more radical than telling the truth of our lives, and listening to the truth of others’ lives. She reminds us that leaving our lives unlived is no badge of honor.</description></item><item><title>185. Should We Stay &amp; Fight, Leave, or Do Nothing? with Sarah Polley | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220088/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220088/</guid><description>Podcast Description We saw the film WOMEN TALKING and we couldn’t rest until we had the chance to speak with the genius who wrote, directed, and is nominated for an Oscar for it: Sarah Polley. This conversation is about hope, survival, imagination, and revolution. It’s about burning it all down and building from the ashes. Please listen to this conversation and then please watch the film. You will be powerfully changed.</description></item><item><title>184. When You’re Glad Your Mom Died with Jennette McCurdy | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220089/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why no one talks about the complicated feelings of freedom after the death of a toxic loved one. How Jennette’s mom enforced extreme calorie restriction to control and bond with Jennette, and the moment her body finally said, No. What led Jennette to step away from acting after her iCarly stardom, and why she doesn’t think “resilient” is a compliment. How Jennette found herself still “doing her mother’s work” in therapy – and how she stopped forcing forgiveness.</description></item><item><title>183. How to Love Our People Bigger &amp; Better with Bozoma Saint John | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220090/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hard-won, joyful, practical wisdom from Bozoma’s exuberant life, and her lessons on how to overcome after enduring excruciating loss. How big love and life can be when we are brave enough to be fierce and tender. The rarely talked-about confusion and fear that often come with pregnancy. Why love isn’t enough — and we all deserve a community surrounding our love. Why Boz gave her husband a book report assignment before she’d go out with him, and the heart wrenching truth that you can carry anger toward a loved one even after death.</description></item><item><title>182. Glennon Update: Lessons from Therapy | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220091/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Glennon shares what she’s learning in therapy and what she feels we all could benefit from knowing – especially about wanting, yearning, fixing, and the next right thing. If talk about eating disorders and mental illness helps: Listen today. If it triggers: Skip today.
CW // eating disorders
If you have an eating disorder, you may find the National Alliance for Eating Disorders a helpful resource: https://www.allianceforeatingdisorders.com/
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>181. Hypervigilance &amp; Loss Without Closure | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220092/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220092/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Bonus episode, Amanda answers your follow-up questions:
How do you take care of the person who takes care of everyone else? How do you find peace and closure when you will never know the story of what really happened? The weird way Amanda can only relax when her husband gets fired up. The strategy that now grounds Amanda when she is most activated and afraid. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>180. The Secret to Making &amp; Keeping Friends with Dr. Marisa G. Franco | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220093/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Practical ways to make a friend and become what Dr. Franco calls a “Super-friend.” How to address issues with a friend even if you hate conflict. Why expressing anger is more likely to deepen a relationship than destroy it. How we need to express vulnerability to make friends – but first, what the hell is vulnerability? Destroying the unhelpful myth that friendship happens organically. About Dr. Franco: Dr. Marisa G Franco is psychologist, international speaker, and New York Times bestselling author known for digesting and communicating science in ways tha change their lives.</description></item><item><title>179. How to Fix Our Loneliness with Dr. Marisa G. Franco | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220094/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220094/</guid><description>Podcast Description How your attachment style determines how you make – or don’t make – friends and becomes a self-fulfilling prophecy. How Dr. Franco’s work helped Glennon make healthy adult friendships over the past year. Why we’re lonelier than ever – and how that loneliness can make us sick. Why platonic friendships are beneficial to the health of our romantic partnerships. Learning to “trust the spark” when you meet a potential friend – and concrete steps to foster new friendship.</description></item><item><title>178. Five Criticism Survival Strategies | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220095/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220095/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this bonus episode, Glennon shares her “Sort Your Mail” rules for dealing with the inevitable criticisms you will receive from daring to say anything, do anything, or be anything. Learn to sort your mail so you can keep showing up!
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>177. How to Face Your Biggest Fear with Amanda Doyle | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220096/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220096/</guid><description>Podcast Description Glennon and Abby interview their favorite person and co-host: Amanda Doyle! Examining the relationships, decisions, and travels that led her to today – from hitchhiking across Ireland, to prosecuting child sex offenders in Rwanda, to making the biggest decision of her life in an Ethiopian airport – they dive into Amanda’s lifelong fear of the ordinary.
About Amanda: Amanda Doyle is Glennon Doyle’s Business Manager and co-host of the We Can Do Hard Things podcast with her sister Glennon Doyle and sister-in-law Abby Wambach.</description></item><item><title>176. How to Find Good Love After Bad with Lily Collins | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220097/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today we’re talking about how to build healthy relationships — with ourselves and others — after enduring toxic relationships with both.
Signs of emotional toxicity in romantic relationships – and what finally made Lily get out of her unhealthy relationship. How to begin reprogramming your brain after leaving a toxic relationship in order to trust yourself and other people again. The process that caused Lily to become the smallest, quietest version of herself – and how she recovered into her biggest, brightest self.</description></item><item><title>175. Life Hacks: Strategies to Suffer Less | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220098/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220098/</guid><description>Podcast Description We can do hard things, and yet, sometimes we can try easier. Glennon, Abby, Amanda – and the Pod Squad! — share the strategies they’ve used to suffer less – giving us simple Life Hacks for relationships, home, tech, travel, and saving time.
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>174. How to Finally Let Things Go | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220099/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Big and small ideas for what to let go of — so that we can all live freer this year. The thinking trap that prevents us from creating new habits. The heaven of resigning from the role of everybody’s problem solver. What to say when folks say something offensive – so you don’t have “walk-away regret.” How to know if you are an “overfunctioner” in a relationship – and how to change that destructive dynamic.</description></item><item><title>173. How to be Sexually Confident with Mae Martin | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220100/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mae, Glennon, Abby, and Amanda each explore their sexuality by delving into what sexually attracts each of them. The sex-positive way Mae’s parents taught them about sex – and orgasm(!) – and how they never made assumptions about Mae&amp;rsquo;s sexuality. Gender as creative expression and a way to have fun. Simple ways to switch up the monotony of routine; to transform boredom into exploration; and dopamine-infused alternatives for addictive personality types.</description></item><item><title>172. How Glennon Knew She Needed Help: Recovery Update | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220101/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220101/</guid><description>Podcast Description Glennon shares more from the messy middle about how she knew she needed help and what we can all learn from her early recovery.
If talk about eating disorders and mental illness helps: Listen today. If it triggers: Skip today. CW // eating disorders
If you have an eating discover, you may find the National Eating Disorders Association (NEDA) hotline a helpful resource: https://www.nationaleatingdisorders.org/help-support/contact-helpline To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>171. VP Kamala Harris: Our Post-Roe World &amp; What’s Next | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220102/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Before delivering her speech to mark today’s 50th anniversary of Roe, Vice President Kamala Harris decided to sit down with one community—The We Can Do Hard Things Pod Squad—to get real about:
Her first call, and how she really felt when she heard Roe was repealed;
Why she says the repeal is rooted in shaming women’s sexuality;
What’s at risk for birth control and fertility treatments;
Why she thinks we must “take the flag back” and show up with our “Shoulders Back, Chin Up;&amp;quot;</description></item><item><title>170. The Most Radical Way to Heal: Internal Family Systems with Dr. Becky Kennedy | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220103/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220103/</guid><description>Podcast Description How to make peace inside your own head by getting to know your “parts.” Why our “manager,” “firefighter,” and “exile” parts are running our lives – and how to get them to step back. How Glennon is using Internal Family Systems in her eating disorder recovery process. Understanding that the parts of you that you might struggle with most right now were originally developed by you to protect you.</description></item><item><title>169. Why We Love the Way We Love: Attachment Styles with Dr. Becky Kennedy | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220104/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Becky Kennedy is back to help us understand Attachment Styles, how our past comes alive in our present – and how to free ourselves and raise freer kids.
Why attachment styles are at the heart of our most intense conflicts (in ourselves and with others). How to rewire our original mental coding (75% of which is complete by age 3), so we can have more peace. How our physical and emotional attractions in adulthood are dictated by childhood attachments.</description></item><item><title>168. Sonya Renee Taylor: What If You Loved Your Body? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220105/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Following Glennon’s diagnosis, she, Abby, and Amanda go deep with Sonya Renee Taylor - author of The Body is Not an Apology – exploring the personal and global promise of Radical Self Love:
Examining the way we talk to our bodies – and how to change negative self-dialogue. How to shift from a relationship with our body based on dominance and control to a relationship based on trust. The pitfalls of “body positivity.</description></item><item><title>167. Tracee Ellis Ross: How to Make Peace in Your Own Head | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220106/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220106/</guid><description>Podcast Description This moving conversation delving inside the “wonderful, dangerous” mind of Tracee Ellis Ross covers:
Tracee’s go-to strategies to stop questioning herself, to pick herself up when she feels unlovable, and to tether herself to her truest self. How she made peace with the fact that she’s “not everyone’s cup of tea” – and stopped trying to change the things about her that others don’t like (but she does). Inside Tracee’s 50th birthday party – the honor of being “Fifty and Free,” and what moved her to sing her mother’s song in her mother’s dress.</description></item><item><title>166. We’re On Some New Sh*t: 2023 | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220107/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Glennon, Abby, and Amanda each share a No they are leaving behind – and a new Yes they’re bringing into their lives this year.
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>165. Glennon’s Diagnosis &amp; What’s Next | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220108/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Glennon shares from the messy middle about her new diagnosis and what’s next for her recovery.
If talk about eating disorders and mental illness helps: Listen today. If it triggers: Skip today. CW // eating disorders If you have an eating discover, you may find the National Eating Disorders Association (NEDA) hotline a helpful resource: https://www.nationaleatingdisorders.org/help-support/contact-helpline
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy</description></item><item><title>164. What Anxiety Feels Like | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220109/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220109/</guid><description>Podcast Description At the end of our first full year together, Glennon, Abby, and Amanda reflect on We Can Do Hard Things, this community, some of their favorite episodes, and they reshare the very first show:
The original idea for the podcast and how it’s evolved. Glennon describes how an anxiety attack feels – and the 3 strategies that help her find calm. Amanda shares some special “thank you” messages to Glennon, Abby, and the Pod Squad.</description></item><item><title>163. How to Make Wrongs Right with Rabbi Danya Ruttenberg | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220110/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220110/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why we should stop expecting people to forgive. Rabbi Danya’s five step-by-step process for repairing a relationship. What makes a good – and a terrible – apology. What to do (and to not say) if you want to make amends and change. Why repentance is a process that has nothing to do with the one who was hurt. About Rabbi Ruttenberg: Rabbi Danya Ruttenberg is an award-winning author of 8 books, including On Repentance and Repair: Making Amends in an Unapologetic World.</description></item><item><title>162. Your Hilarious (&amp; Heartwarming) Holiday Stories! | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220111/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220111/</guid><description>Podcast Description Glennon, Abby, Amanda and the Pod Squad share their most brutiful and hilarious holiday stories.
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>161. How to Let Go of Perfection this Holiday | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220112/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Holiday Expectations are the joy robbers. Here’s how to leave room for yourself, and be sturdy this holiday season (and always).
How in our preparation for making things perfect, we leave no room for the peace and joy that is actually in front of us. The opposite revolutions that Glennon and Amanda are having right now – and why they’re at the core the same. The final frontier: How to be who we are wherever we are – and let our people be who they are wherever we are, too.</description></item><item><title>160. Fortune Feimster: A Queer Debutante Walks Into a Hooters . . . | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220113/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220113/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fortune’s life as a debutante without a couch and her first coming out party. Fortune’s 21st birthday, and her family’s complicated relationship with Hooters. The joys and perils of growing up as an 80s kid, and the shock of moving to LA from a small Southern town. What Fortune was watching when she finally realized she was queer, and how she built community when she realized she was the only gay person she knew.</description></item><item><title>FRIENDSHIP GEMS: Best of Friendship Advice | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220114/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Featuring Luvvie, Reese, Ash+Ali, Sam &amp;amp; Cam.
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>159. Family Estrangement: Should You Repair or Run? with Dr. Galit Atlas | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220115/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cutting off contact with family is on a dramatic rise – how to know if there’s hope of repair, or if self-preservation requires distance. How to have present, productive conversations with our parents about the past. Why we grieve the loss of a family member even if we know it’s healthiest to cut them out. Attachment styles, emotional honesty, and the difference between forgiveness and repair. What to do and say – and what NOT to say – when attempting to reconnect with an estranged loved one.</description></item><item><title>158. CULTS Part 2: How Intuition Can Save Us with Sarah Edmondson | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220116/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Glennon, Abby, Amanda, and Sarah Edmondson continue their conversation: “Love bombing” and other red flag strategies used by cults to reel people in. The jarring similarities between cults and abusive relationships – and how in both your best qualities are used against you. What to do if someone you love is pulled into QAnon, 4chan, or another conspiratorial culture. The moment Sarah realized she had been initiated into a sex pyramid, and how she escaped.</description></item><item><title>157. CULTS: How NXIVM Controlled Women &amp; How Sarah Edmondson Helped Take It Down | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220117/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220117/</guid><description>Podcast Description How attending a personal development training at a Holiday Inn led to Sarah being branded in a sex &amp;ldquo;secret sisterhood&amp;rdquo; initiation ceremony. Her path from top recruiter to the whistleblower who helped take down the cult and its leader Keith Ranieri. Why we’re all susceptible to cult culture – the need for belonging, the temptation of simplification, and how we’re trained to deny our gut instincts. CW: Discussion of cult culture and sexual coercion</description></item><item><title>156. JANE F-ING FONDA | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220118/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220118/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why she left her body as a child and how she finally reintegrated 50 years later. How, even as a public warrior for the highest ideals of democracy, she’s never had a democratic marriage – and when she knew she had to leave each one. Her deepest fear, why she became happiest at 62, and a peek behind the scenes of her 85th birthday party. How, despite coordinated FBI and White House campaigns to vilify her, she’s kept showing up.</description></item><item><title>155. When Should We Quit? with Abbi Jacobson | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220119/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220119/</guid><description>Podcast Description How to know when it’s time to get out or stick it out – and the quit that set Abbi on course to meet Ilana and create Broad City. The life lessons of improv comedy: How to get out of your head, trust your choices, and make something together. Abbi and Abby share similar but opposite stories about relationships that changed their lives (and whether to tuck or untuck shirts).</description></item><item><title>154. HAPPYISH HOLIDAYS: Our Top 3 Hacks for Hard Holidays | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220120/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220120/</guid><description>Podcast Description How to eliminate walking on eggshells around family, and avoid feeling badly about ourselves or our people. Amanda shares the first time she broke her family’s biggest holiday tradition—and how it’s now one of her most precious memories. Abby remembers watching her mom stress out by “perfecting” every holiday detail—and the change she made to minimize her own holiday stress. How carrying around a cup of hot tea serves as Glennon’s super shield.</description></item><item><title>153. More Embarrassing Stories! | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220121/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Back by popular demand, it’s more mortifying stories! Glennon, Abby, and Amanda share more of their most embarrassing moments – and cry-laugh in solidarity with Pod Squaders’ new and hilarious voicemail confessions.
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>152. EASY FRIDAYS: How (NOT) to Party | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220122/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220122/</guid><description>Podcast Description No digging deep. No paradigm shifts to be found. It’s Easy Fridays.
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>151. WTF with The Five Love Languages? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220123/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 08:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220123/</guid><description>Podcast Description The good, the bad, and the ugly of Gary Chapman’s The Five Love Languages. How expressing the way we give and receive love can identify misalignments with our partners, friends, and family. How to explore – beyond our “love language” – our deep fears and needs underlying them. Glennon, Abby, Amanda, and Pod Squaders share the specific, hilarious things that make them feel most loved. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>150. Couples Therapy: The Tools You Need with Dr. Orna Guralnik | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220124/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220124/</guid><description>Podcast Description What we are really fighting about when we’re fighting about the dishwasher. We can stop asking whether what’s missing is a “want” or a “need” – and the question to ask instead. How to use what most frustrates you about your partner to bring you closer. How to start thinking of our partnerships as our own mini political systems. What to do if your partner won’t go to therapy, or if you’re feeling invisible in your relationship.</description></item><item><title>149. How to Heal with Alex Elle | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220125/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alex’s four most effective healing techniques that you can start today. How it affects us to grow up never seeing our mothers have joy. Why – if you think you don’t have any self-soothing strategies – you actually just have unhealthy self-soothing strategies. Childhood wounds that surface in adulthood, and the path to intergenerational healing. Where to begin when you never receive the apology and closure you deserve. About Alex: Alex Elle is an author, certified breathwork coach, podcast host, and Restorative Writing teacher.</description></item><item><title>15-MIN MIDTERM REVIEW: WTH Happened!? with Jessica Yellin | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220126/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 23:52:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220126/</guid><description>Podcast Description By popular demand, Jessica Yellin, founder of News Not Noise, returns to update us on the top takeaways from the midterm election yesterday. About Jessica: Jessica Yellin is the founder of News Not Noise, a Webby Award winning independent digital media brand dedicated to giving the audience information, not a panic attack. She is the former chief White House correspondent for CNN and an Emmy, Peabody and Gracie Award winning political correspondent for ABC, MSNBC and CNN.</description></item><item><title>148. WHAT’S AT STAKE TODAY: Election Takeaways with Jessica Yellin | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220127/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Make this podcast part of your VOTING PLAN TODAY! A clear, digestible explanation of what this Election means for you – and why your vote matters: What is most likely to happen today; Who will control Congress, and what they’ll do with that control; What will happen with abortion and reproductive justice; Why the polls could be all wrong; and A reason to be hopeful. Referenced resources: Ballotpedia USAFacts Midterm Map About Jessica: Jessica Yellin is the founder of News Not Noise, a Webby Award winning independent digital media brand dedicated to giving the audience information, not a panic attack.</description></item><item><title>147. The Episode That Wasn’t | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220128/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220128/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this behind-the-scenes episode, Glennon, Abby, and Amanda react immediately after dramatically ending an interview because the guest was disrespectful to a member of their team.
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>146. Esther Perel: Love in War | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220129/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220129/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this deeply intimate collaboration with beloved therapist Esther Perel, she dives deep in a couples therapy session with a Ukrainian couple torn apart by the war.
The wife is compelled to leave the country for the sake of her youngest son; the husband and older son are compelled to stay in the warzone for the sake of their country.
Miraculously, even amid unthinkable loss – and maybe especially amid unthinkable loss – love and connection are unrelenting.</description></item><item><title>145. Geena Davis: How to Thelma &amp; Louise Your Life | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220130/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220130/</guid><description>Podcast Description The politeness curse – and how it almost killed Geena. Geena’s brilliant “Oops…” strategy to get folks to act decent. Abby thanks Geena for the monumental impact of A League of Their Own on her life.
The story behind the iconic ending of Thelma and Louise.
The hilarious story of why Geena’s mom chose her name – setting her on an unlikely feminist path. CW: Brief mention of sexual assault</description></item><item><title>144. EASY FRIDAYS: Trick or Treat | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220131/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220131/</guid><description>Podcast Description No digging deep. No paradigm shifts to be found. Welcome to Easy Fridays.
P.S. Thanks to @ohnochels &amp;amp; @dmc1138 for the haunted house laughs.
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>143. How to Set &amp; Hold Boundaries with Melissa Urban | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220132/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220132/</guid><description>Podcast Description The top (surprising) signs that tell you it’s time to set a boundary. Paying attention to “energy leakage” – when you’re giving out more than you’re getting back. How to set the specific boundaries you need with in-laws, friends, and romantic partners. Scripts for Melissa’s green, yellow, and red system of clear, kind communication in boundary setting. Rethinking boundaries – not as not a response to someone else’s behavior – but as giving voice to your worth and health.</description></item><item><title>142. Codependence: How to Stop Controlling Others with Melody Beattie | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220133/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220133/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Mother of Codependence shares the difference between healthy and unhealthy helping. The daily practice that helps Melody stop controlling others and “Let Life Happen.” Why no one is able to gaslight you more than you. The one area of life where Codependence is necessary. All four of us surrender to the truth that we will never be Codependent No More. About Melody: A pioneering voice in self-help literature, Melody Beattie is the author of many bestselling books, including Codependent No More – a #1 New York Times bestseller, which has sold over 7 million copies – as well as The Language of Letting Go, Playing It by Heart, The Grief Club, and Beyond Codependency.</description></item><item><title>141. Sara Bareilles: How to Remember Yourself | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220134/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Abby shares with Sara the great personal impact Sara’s music has made on her life. Sara and Glennon bond over the joy of solitude, the underrated gifts of being heavy-hearted, and the fact that “there are too many things to be worried about at all times” to be lighthearted. When you are in deep stress, do you try to sabotage your job, relationship, etc.? (Before this conversation, Amanda thought it was just her.</description></item><item><title>140. Alex Morgan: Believe in Your Own Greatness | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220135/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220135/</guid><description>Podcast Description How the Abby+Alex sisterhood began, how hard it was for Alex to watch Abby suffer at the end of her career, and how friends can build each other up. How to get back on the field – in life and in sport – after crushing defeat. The way Alex’s mom helped Alex fulfill her dream, and what Alex is teaching her own daughter, Charlie. How Alex finally stopped comparing herself to others and started resting in her own confidence.</description></item><item><title>139. No More Grind: How to Finally Rest with Tricia Hersey | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220136/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220136/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Nap Ministry’s Nap Bishop shares small, concrete ways to bring rest into our own lives – especially when rest seems impossible. Why so many of us feel like machines instead of humans – and the power of imagination as a spiritual practice to reconnect with our humanity and divinity. Why grind culture – a collaboration of capitalism and white supremacy – wants to keep us exhausted, and how we can resist a culture of overwhelming busy-ness.</description></item><item><title>138. Melissa McCarthy: Sex, Nuns &amp; Ghosts | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220137/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220137/</guid><description>Podcast Description What Melissa’s parents said when she told them about her dream – and how those magic words set the course of Melissa’s life. The green and red flags Melissa tells her kids to look for in a relationship. Why Melissa is a shark, and her brilliant strategy to “Run Around the Block” in almost any difficult situation. Melissa’s and Abby’s experiences with ghosts. How Melissa learned about sex – and the way she talks to her kids about it.</description></item><item><title>137. Celeste Ng: Why You Feel Stuck | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220138/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220138/</guid><description>Podcast Description What to do when you’ve done everything you were supposed to do and ended up in a place you don’t want to be. Why the question “What do you want?” is terrifying – and how to start answering it authentically for yourself. The power of imagining what does not yet exist in order to make space for new possibilities. The gift of a “midlife crisis” What a mother’s job really is.</description></item><item><title>136. CARE-FRONTATIONS: Three Keys for Giving &amp; Receiving Criticism | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220139/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220139/</guid><description>Podcast Description What happens inside us when we receive criticism–and how our brains ensure we’re always in the right (even when we’re not). The three-ingredient recipe for a positive, productive “care-frontation” exchange. The single biggest relationship killer (it’s not conflict) – and how conflict can bring you closer. Amanda navigates a “care-frontation” with her son’s friend’s family – and Abby reevaluates her past relationship with criticism. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Introducing: It Was Said Season 2 | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220140/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220140/</guid><description>Podcast Description It Was Said, the 2021 Webby Award winner for Best Podcast Series, returns with a new season to look back on some of the most powerful, impactful, and timeless speeches in history. Written and narrated by Pulitzer Prize winner and bestselling author-historian Jon Meacham, this documentary podcast series takes you through another season of ten generation-defining speeches. Meacham, along with top historians, authors and journalists, offers expert insight and analysis into the origins, the orator, and the context of the times each speech was given, and they reflect on why it’s important to never forget them.</description></item><item><title>135. Letting Go of How It’s “Supposed to Be” | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220141/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220141/</guid><description>Podcast Description The twinge of loneliness that comes with searching for what it seems like everyone else has. A Varsity-level question from Christie that challenges everything we said about Help on Tuesday’s episode. How to make “your thing” more of an “our thing” in relationships–and how Abby got Glennon into the sports. If there is anything worse than vacationing with your own kids, it’s vacationing with other people’s kids–and the time Glennon staged a sketchy early exit from a group trip.</description></item><item><title>134. HELP: How to Ask for the Help You Need | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220142/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220142/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why sharing your messy middle with someone is a gift and connection builder, not a burden. The reasons why we don’t ask for the help we desperately need. “Vague favs” and why are they a hard No for Amanda. Abby, Glennon, and Amanda each share something they need help with right now. The science behind Help as one of the most effective relationship-enhancing tools, and the best ways to finally ask for it.</description></item><item><title>133. Indigo Girls: Sexuality, Sobriety, Faith &amp; Freedom | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220143/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220143/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why Emily couldn’t stop crying (and it wasn’t because she was emotional). The intervention that got Emily sober – and why Amy wasn’t there. Glennon admits something that she’s never told anyone before. Amy and Abby agree on the shared cost of internalized homophobia and misogyny. About Indigo Girls: One of the most successful folk duos in history – Amy Ray and Emily Sailers aka THE INDIGO GIRLS – has recorded 16 albums and sold over 15 million records.</description></item><item><title>132. Christen Press: How to Get Your Bliss Back | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220144/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220144/</guid><description>Podcast Description The moment Abby – as Christen’s USWNT roommate – walked into their hotel room and knew Christen was very different than any soccer player she’d ever known. The boundary that helps Christen love her people while protecting herself. Christen’s take on death and how to keep the people we’ve lost alive in our lives. How to show our people (including our little athletes) that we love them for who they are, not what they achieve.</description></item><item><title>131. How to Raise Untamed Kids with Dr. Becky Kennedy | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220145/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220145/</guid><description>Podcast Description How to embody your authority while also validating your kid’s experience. The #1 strategy for building resilience. Why consequences and punishments backfire and don’t work. How to sit with your child on the “benches” of their emotions. One thing you can say to your kids to build connection in any circumstance. About Dr. Becky: Dr. Becky Kennedy is a clinical psychologist and mom of three, named “The Millennial Parenting Whisperer” by TIME Magazine.</description></item><item><title>130. Breaking Cycles &amp; Reparenting Yourself with Dr. Becky Kennedy | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220146/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220146/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 3 most important things to say to your kids and partners every day. Why our kids trigger us – and a fail-proof strategy to use when you’re triggered. Why “poorly-behaved kids” can be a sign of good parenting. How to break family cycles by rewiring the way we were raised. How to use Internal Family Systems to heal ourselves. About Dr. Becky: Dr. Becky Kennedy is a clinical psychologist and mom of three, named “The Millennial Parenting Whisperer” by TIME Magazine.</description></item><item><title>129. What Your Sign Says About How You Love: Chani Nicholas | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220147/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220147/</guid><description>Podcast Description How to recognize when you’re dysregulated – so you can slow down and help yourself. The beauty and wisdom in being judgmental, and how that saved Chani’s life. The liberating idea that “The things that happened to me weren’t about me.” How to set and trust boundaries in order to finally rest. About Chani: Chani Nicholas is a Los Angeles-based New York Times bestselling author of You Were Born For This: Astrology for Radical Self-Acceptance.</description></item><item><title>128. HOW GLENNON LOST HER MIND | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220148/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220148/</guid><description>Podcast Description “Weird Glennon” comes back to the pod and shares her #1 sanity strategy. The rule Glennon and Abby set for their wedding week that made everything OK. How Amanda stopped accepting assignments from strangers. How Glennon discovered she couldn’t trust her thoughts – and found the part of herself she could trust. How to know if your thinking is disordered, and how to reorient it to be more effective in your life, relationships, and world.</description></item><item><title>127. Are you a Feeler or a Thinker? Either Way, Genius! | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220149/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220149/</guid><description>Podcast Description An Advocate, Commander, and Entertainer walk into a podcast – and each share how they feel about their labels. Do personality types make you feel boxed in, or give you permission to be you? How to decide when it’s important to work first and play later, or jump on a moment of joy and work later. How Glennon as a strong F (Feeler) and Amanda as a strong T (Thinker) make business decisions together.</description></item><item><title>126. WHAT’S YOUR TYPE? How Personality Shapes Your Life | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220150/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220150/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our desperate desire to figure out: Why are we the way we are? Why Abby once believed she was 100% extroverted, and the fear she uncovered that makes her think she’s not. How what you think about when you see a cactus tells you a lot about your personality. Why some of the best-known personality binaries are just silly – and corporately manufactured. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>125. WHY ARE THERE NO PICTURES OF US?!? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220151/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220151/</guid><description>Podcast Description Deep dive into how it feels to not be in any of your family photos, why it happens, and how to change it. A call-in question from a husband that made Amanda cry. Reimagining “acts of service” and how to know whether actions belong in the “Adulting Bucket” or the “Love Bucket.” Getting the kids to read over the summer went terribly, thanks for asking. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>124. How to Say No: Boundaries with Nedra Glover Tawwab | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220152/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220152/</guid><description>Podcast Description Five signs that you might have a boundary problem. Why each of us should stop pretending we’re not a needy person. How to stop arguing like a lawyer – and start communicating like a kindergartener – to get what you need. How to know when to end an argument, how to exit a friendship, and how to respond to passive aggressiveness. About Nedra: Nedra Glover Tawwab, MSW, LCSW, is a New York Times best-selling author, licensed therapist, and sought-after relationship expert.</description></item><item><title>123. Find Your Towanda with Tig Notaro &amp; Stephanie Allynne | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220153/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220153/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tig and Stephanie’s highly effective and hilarious ways to diffuse their marital feuds. Stephanie’s experience figuring out her sexuality (years after she married Tig)–and how Tig knew Stephanie was the one. Why Tig’s deep in “Towanda-ing” right now–and how that affects their marriage. The power of knowing what you DON’T want in your life. Tig, Stephanie, Abby, and Glennon each share something they’ve discovered they don’t want. About Stephanie: Stephanie Allynne is a writer, actor, producer, and director.</description></item><item><title>122. Why We Should Stop Doing Our Best | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220154/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220154/</guid><description>Podcast Description Abby’s new nightly ritual of 80’s parties and Amanda’s wild adventure at a crawfish boil. Glennon’s transition out of depression, and how she’s moving off “The Landing.” Why our parents are so triggering – and how we can see them differently. Glennon, Abby, and Amanda answer pressing Pod Squad questions. Amanda pays tribute to a particular Pod Squader, Lexi – and to all women of her generation. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>121. Martha Beck &amp; Rowan Mangan: Polyamory &amp; Throuple Life | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220155/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220155/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is Polyamory – and how Martha, Rowan, and Karen make their relationship work. How Martha felt – after years of marriage to Karen – when Karen told her she was in love with Rowan, too. The hilarious moment Martha, Karen, and Rowan told their friends they were now a throuple. A huge lesson for couples based on the revolutionary ways they deal with conflict, jealousy, and daily rituals to stay close.</description></item><item><title>120. Jen Hatmaker’s Back! Forgiveness &amp; the Audacity to Rebuild | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220156/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220156/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why Jen believes none of us is safe from betrayal – but how she knows with certainty it will never happen to her again. The useful part of unforgiveness, the worst thing about forgiveness, and how to know when it’s time to forgive. Brené Brown’s advice to Jen for how to begin rebuilding brick by brick after the life you built implodes. The steps Jen took to learn to trust her body for the first time – and what she calls her body now.</description></item><item><title>119. It’s OK to Want What You Want: Cheryl Strayed as Dear Sugar | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220157/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220157/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pod Squad Qs about co-parenting after infidelity, setting boundaries with friends, and reconciling an estranged parent relationship. How to know when it’s time to leave, and whether your partner deserves to be free of you. Why every problem Cheryl’s ever had has been solved by a list–and how to use her strategy. Ways to be a better advice-giver, and how to keep “floating in the direction of your own life.</description></item><item><title>118. Cheryl Strayed: Don’t Let Your Dreams Ruin Your Life | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220158/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220158/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why Cheryl chose Strayed as her last name – the only one not given to her by a man. How she ruined her life when her mom died, and how we can bear the unbearable. Cheryl’s greatest lesson from her 3-month hike of the PCT, and her mom’s advice she uses everyday. How to make peace with our ITS – “inner terrible someone” – who lives in each of us.</description></item><item><title>117. How to Love Your Body Now with Carson Tueller | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220159/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220159/</guid><description>Podcast Description The question Carson’s sister asked that made him radically reimagine his life. Why Carson is having the best sex of his life. How Carson received sign-off from his Mormon Bishop for his first queer date. The accident that left Carson paralyzed from the chest down at 23. How ableism hurts us all. About Carson: Carson Tueller is a coach, speaker and activist whose work provides people with the tools they need to live authentic, fulfilling, and powerful lives.</description></item><item><title>116. Our Most Embarrassing Stories | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220160/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220160/</guid><description>Podcast Description Glennon, Abby, and Amanda share the most mortifying moments of their lives. Pod Squaders’ hilarious voicemail confessions, which had Glennon, Abby, and Amanda cry-laughing in solidarity. Our new go-to strategy when humiliated (it involves prosthetic penises). We test our hypothesis that sharing our most embarrassing experiences makes us feel less alone. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>115. Chelsea Handler: On Breaking Up &amp; Being Unbreakable | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220161/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220161/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chelsea Handler comes to We Can Do Hard Things to talk for the first time about her breakup with Jo Koy, her definition of real love, and her commitment to never abandon herself. About Chelsea: Chelsea Handler is a comedian, television host, best-selling author and advocate whose humor and candor have established her as one of the most celebrated voices in entertainment and pop culture. She was the host of E!</description></item><item><title>114. Reese Witherspoon on Friendship: What, Like It’s Hard? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220162/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220162/</guid><description>Podcast Description How to make the first friendship move – and how to move on from a friendship with kindness and clarity. The advice Reese passes down to her kids about the three types of people you meet in life. Reese’s Hollywood experience as a young woman – and the solidarity she found in the Time’s Up movement. How Elle Woods – in all her iconic glory – hilariously showed up while Reese was on real-life jury duty.</description></item><item><title>113. The Time Glennon &amp; Abby Called It Off – and Live Pod Squad Q&amp;A! | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220163/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220163/</guid><description>Podcast Description How horrifying advice from a therapist led Glennon to end things with Abby–and how they reconnected. The moments from past episodes that changed us–including Amanda’s new strategy to prevent her anxiety from creating relationship problems. How we decide what to share publicly and what not to–and why we think the dichotomy of “sacred things” versus “private things” is dangerous. Simple guidance to a man who asks how to stand in the fight for women’s rights, a question from 68-year-old Donna that we can’t stop thinking about, and the story of Tish’s We Can Do Hard Things song.</description></item><item><title>112. Abby’s First Love, G Restarts Recovery, and Amanda Tries Meds: Live Event | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220164/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220164/</guid><description>Podcast Description Over 15,000 Pod Squaders joined live to celebrate One Year of the Pod and discuss:
Why Amanda started taking meds, Glennon keeps taking meds–and why Abby might consider taking meds :) The brilliant preemptive post mortem strategy to help you emotionally recover from any gathering. Your frequently asked question of Abby: How she tracked down her first love connection at the Macaroni Grill. The pie chart of showing up–and why it’s rarely ever 100%.</description></item><item><title>111. Natalie Portman: How to Know When to Say YES | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220165/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220165/</guid><description>Podcast Description The moment Natalie called Abby to invite her to be part of Angel City FC–the first majority, women-owned soccer franchise. How to stop people-pleasing and learn to recognize a full body YES from inside of you. Why and how Natalie shows up for big projects before she’s ready or qualified. (Dude Moves). The best advice Natalie’s ever received–and why women should “Gossip Well.” How Natalie counters gender expectations by over practicing empathy with her son and decisiveness with her daughter.</description></item><item><title>110. Why Grief – like Love – is Forever with Marisa Renee Lee | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220166/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220166/</guid><description>Podcast Description Practical tips for guiding friends and family through your grief–and the permission slips to give yourself. 2. Why there is no such thing as grief etiquette–and how it’s less about what you say and more about what you do. What it finally took for Marisa to surrender to the fact that she was not in control of her love or her grief. How to integrate love and grief in order to find joy again after loss–and how, 12 years after her mother’s death, Marisa includes her mom in her son’s life.</description></item><item><title>109. How to Survive This Absurd Life with Samantha Irby | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220167/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220167/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam’s life-changing strategies for (reluctantly) interacting with humans. How we use humor to hide the lava of rage churning beneath our surface. Sam’s friendship theory and why she doesn’t need a deep soul connection with every “lowercase f friend.” Sam’s embrace of JOMO (Joy of Missing Out)–and why she genuinely believes no one else is having a better time (except maybe Abby). The behind-the-scenes story of the “Fat Babe Pool Party” Shrill show–and why that episode was one of the most important things she’s ever written.</description></item><item><title>108. ABORTION: Family Meeting on Four Things to Do Next | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220168/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220168/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pod Squad Family Meeting! To see each other’s rage and grief, talk about how we got here, renew our resolve to fight forward and to take tender care of each other as we do, and to share four concrete steps we can all take to join the fight for reproductive justice. Because what got us here is not going to get us out of here.
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>107. Billie Jean King: Abby’s Hero Shares Her Hardest Battle | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220169/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220169/</guid><description>Podcast Description How Billie Jean could not live as her full authentic self until age 51. The moment Billie Jean knew that Abby was not okay after her USWNT retirement. How to visualize a reality that doesn’t yet exist – so you can be it, even when you don’t see it. How Billie Jean numbed herself through an eating disorder and how she recovered by not being a “good girl.” Why Billie Jean does not regret her pre-Roe abortion, and the degrading process she endured to access it.</description></item><item><title>106. Astrology: Your Sign’s Secrets with Heidi Rose Robbins | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220170/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220170/</guid><description>Podcast Description How Heidi ruined Glennon’s life with a jarring new identity–and why it’s a powerful moment for G to embrace her newfound sign. How we each have a Sun, Moon, and Rising sign–and what each tells us about ourselves. Heidi breaks down the 12 astrological signs–and astrology as a tool for self revelation. Why we keep saying “Mercury’s in retrograde” and what the hell it means. About Heidi: Heidi Rose Robbins has been a professional astrologer for 25 years, helping thousands of clients all over the globe live with more authenticity and clarity.</description></item><item><title>105. Restart Your Sex Life with Dr. Lori Brotto | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220171/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220171/</guid><description>Podcast Description Answers to fascinating sex questions from Pod Squaders–including how to get real in the bedroom after regularly faking orgasm. Concrete mindfulness strategies to get out of your head and into your body, which have been proven to increase arousal and satisfaction. Busting the myth about how long it should take to orgasm. Why talking about sex (including fantasies!) before having sex leads to more satisfying intimacy–and why that feels fun for Abby and impossible to Glennon and Amanda.</description></item><item><title>104. Orgasm: Pleasure is the Final Frontier with Dr. Lori Brotto2 | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220172/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220172/</guid><description>Podcast Description The shocking revelation that many women experience physical arousal but can’t reach orgasm because we are so “stuck” in our heads that we don’t even register it. Glennon and Abby share about their periodic sexual droughts – and Dr. Brotto gives them (us) advice. The biggest predictors of sexual problems for women – including stress/compulsive multitasking – and how to address them. How to know if you are disconnecting from your body during sex, and how to reintegrate to increase your pleasure.</description></item><item><title>103. How to Be More Alive with Cole Arthur Riley | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220173/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220173/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this beautiful conversation–in which Glennon names Cole’s book “This Here Flesh” the Next Right Book–we discuss: What we learned from Cole’s insight that, “If you’re not in your body, someone else is.” A mind-blowing revelation about all of our own faces that we will never stop thinking about. Why the phrase “If you don’t believe you’re beautiful, no one else will” is horseshit. Why dignity is the bedrock to being alive–and how to find it when we haven’t been loved well.</description></item><item><title>102. Ashlyn Harris &amp; Ali Krieger Double Date! | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220174/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220174/</guid><description>Podcast Description Abby’s former USWNT teammates–and dear friends–Ashlyn Harris and Ali Krieger are here for a double date discussing:
Ashlyn and Ali’s wedding, their vision for queer marriage visibility, and Glennon’s top moments of their magical day. Ashlyn and Abby’s friendship–why Ashlyn pulled Abby’s final game captain’s band out of the trash and what she plans to do with it. Who made the first move, which one “knew” first, and how Ashlyn and Ali’s love story started with friendship and mixtapes.</description></item><item><title>101. How to Be the Boss of Yourself with Bozoma Saint John | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220175/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220175/</guid><description>Podcast Description The inspiring pep talk Bozoma gives herself in the mirror – and why we might all want to start using it to rally ourselves. How to navigate the tightrope of corporate expectations for women: to be both self-assured and humble; both hard and soft. The revolutionary realization that you don’t have to be the savior of others – you can save yourself, too. How to know when to dig deep, and stay and fight for change – and when to stop digging and go – and the moment Bozoma knew it was time to leave Netflix.</description></item><item><title>100. Jenny Lawson is Broken (in the Best Possible Way) | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220176/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220176/</guid><description>Podcast Description Content warning: Discussion of suicide. Jenny puts words to her experience of ADD – &amp;ldquo;being a kitten on cocaine&amp;rdquo; – and her anxiety – seeing &amp;ldquo;rainbow fire.” How Jenny felt guilty for years about a way her mental illness impacted her mothering – only to later learn it was her child’s favorite memory. The moment she decided to be honest about her struggles – and how sharing our awkwardness can save the world and cure our loneliness.</description></item><item><title>99. How We’ll Save Our Kids From the Gun Lobby’s Greed with Shannon Watts | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220177/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220177/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why guns are now the leading cause of death for American children and teens, and who is profiting from America’s suffering. What to say today when your child leaves the house to help protect them from gun violence. The lie our leaders are selling us about why they won’t pass the reforms that 90% of Americans want, and how one mom became the NRA’s biggest nightmare. How to safeguard our kids from the negative impact of for-profit active shooter drills in schools.</description></item><item><title>98. How to Live So We Can Die Peacefully with Death Doula Alua Arthur | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220178/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220178/</guid><description>Podcast Description What Alua has learned about living well from the many people she’s helped walk home as a death doula. The “deathbed test” that guides her toward what is important and helps her stay present. Alua eases Abby’s immense fear of death by sharing her glitter-wave vision. The most surprising thing she wants us to know about death. Concrete steps we can take now to help prepare ourselves–and our loved ones–for the inevitable.</description></item><item><title>97. How Family Secrets Shape Us: Emotional Inheritance with Dr. Galit Atlas | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220179/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220179/</guid><description>Podcast Description How we are each haunted by our family’s secrets and trauma–whether we know them or not–and how to break the cycle for future generations. The astounding new research on generational trauma showing that our personal trauma is passed down genetically to our children and grandchildren. Our unconscious need to heal what our parents could not–and how to mourn what we cannot control. Why our bodies carry what our mind won’t remember–and how to release that burden.</description></item><item><title>96. Cameron Esposito: How to Save Your Damn Self | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220180/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220180/</guid><description>Podcast Description Glennon and Abby welcome their dear friend Cameron Esposito to discuss:
Cameron’s brutiful relationship with her body–and how it feels playing a sexy TV role. The way Cameron grew up using humor as self-defense and to become socially “valuable”–and the moment she wondered if comedy was no longer working for her. Why Cameron says she’s able to cry for the first time in 35 years. How as a gender-nonconforming queer kid, Cameron felt “overnoticed”–and how being a comedian allows her to “hide in plain sight.</description></item><item><title>95. Why Elizabeth Gilbert Disappeared &amp; What She Came Back to Say | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220181/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220181/</guid><description>Podcast Description Part Two of our gorgeous conversation with Elizabeth Gilbert:
Liz describes Rayya’s death as “a fist fight”–and how Rayya went out swinging. In the wake of Rayya’s death, how Liz grieved, and what helped. Liz’s spiritual practices: communing with a higher power, her recovery community, and starting over. About Elizabeth: Elizabeth Gilbert is author of the international bestseller, EAT PRAY LOVE, which has been translated into over thirty languages, and sold over 12 million copies worldwide.</description></item><item><title>94. Liz Gilbert Shares the Whole Story for the First Time | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220182/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220182/</guid><description>Podcast Description Part One of our intimate conversation with Elizabeth Gilbert:
When Glennon called Liz about Abby–and Liz then told Glennon about Rayya. The moment Liz imploded her life as she knew it. How, after a decade of friendship, Liz finally told Rayya that she was in love with her. The brutal chaos of Rayya’s addiction at the end of her life–and what Liz had to do and say to protect herself.</description></item><item><title>93. BURNOUT: Do You Feel Half Alive? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220183/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220183/</guid><description>Podcast Description With everything going on in the world, and in our lives, is “Burnout” the reason we all feel like zombies? Why stress is like trash: You have to get rid of it often or your life starts to stink. Emily and Amelia Nagoski – the authors of Burnout: The Secret to Unlocking the Stress Cycle – answer our Pod Squad’s burning questions about how to bounce back from burnout.</description></item><item><title>92. Chanel Miller Promises: We are Never Stuck | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220184/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220184/</guid><description>Podcast Description Thinking of depression as a way of seeing the world … through toilet paper roll binoculars. Why healing might actually just be permission to go. Chanel’s definition of success: refusing to succumb to perfection or exhaustion–and showing up as herself in every moment. The healing moment when Chanel returned to Stanford and was held in sound–which set her free. About Chanel: Chanel Miller is a writer and artist who received her BA in Literature from the University of California, Santa Barbara.</description></item><item><title>91. Better Sex &amp; Lives in Menopause with Dr. Jen Gunter | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220185/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220185/</guid><description>Podcast Description How to get your orgasm back. Dr. Jen Gunter’s advice–and personal mantra–for surviving hot flushes. How to differentiate between mental health challenges and menopause. The one easy thing you can do at the doctor’s office to ensure better care. Is menopause a reboot of the brain and an opportunity to reallocate mental resources? Resource: North American Menopause Society (NAMS) About Jen: Dr. Jen Gunter is an OB/GYN and pain medicine physician and the author of The Menopause Manifesto, The Vagina Bible, and The Preemie Primer.</description></item><item><title>90. Menopause: What We Deserve to Know with Dr. Jen Gunter | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220186/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220186/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hot flushes, night sweats, sleep disturbances, vaginal dryness, and the less common, frequently-missed symptoms of menopause. A strategy and script for how to talk to your doctor without being dismissed. The lies and truth about menopause hormone therapy. Why our culture is fixated on investing to ensure men never lose their erection, but is fine with women losing their quality of life. What we need to know about our bodies and lives during menopause, which will impact up to 20 years of our lives.</description></item><item><title>89. Enneagram: What does your number say about you? with Ashton Whitmoyer-Ober | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220187/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220187/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is your Enneagram number–and how does this ancient wisdom explain WHY you do what you do? Why Glennon really didn’t want to accept her Enneagram number, and how she finally saw herself clearly in it. How the Enneagram helps Amanda have much more compassion for herself–and how she uses it to understand common patterns in her marriage. Glennon and Amanda use the Enneagram to dissect what is actually going on in their conflicts, and how to make each other feel seen and understood.</description></item><item><title>88. Brené Brown &amp; Barrett Guillen Sisters Double Date!! | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220188/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220188/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brené and Barrett share their parenting strategy that Brené calls “the opposite of raising a child that’s full of shame.” The family of origin roles that Brené (the Protector) and Barrett (the Peacekeeper) had to adjust in order to work together–and the two keys to working well with family. The ways in which a child who grows up living on eggshells becomes an adult who is fearful–and how that fear shows up differently for Brené, Barrett, Glennon, and Amanda.</description></item><item><title>87. Jen Hatmaker &amp; Tyler Merritt Double Date! | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220189/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220189/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jen Hatmaker is back with the new man in her life–actor, author, and activist Tyler Merritt–for a double date with Glennon and Abby discussing: How Jen and Tyler met, what first attracted Jen and Tyler to each other–and who made the first move. How not knowing any “dating rules” led Jen to jumpstart the “define the relationship” step. The triggers for Jen that led to an early relationship “wobble” and how Jen is navigating issues of trust and safety after her divorce.</description></item><item><title>86. Jen Hatmaker: What We Win When We Lose It All | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220190/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220190/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jen describes the shock of losing her 26-year marriage overnight. How, looking back, Jen sees that she knew something was wrong in her relationship well before she “knew” something was wrong–and the moment she reached out to Glennon to share it for the first time. 3. Why Jen’s friends told her she was a “human spotlight” and “cleanup crew” in her marriage–and the pain of realizing she was powerful in every role other than wife.</description></item><item><title>85. Susan Cain Says Sadness is a Superpower | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220191/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220191/</guid><description>Podcast Description How to know if you are a “Bittersweet” type. On “stabs of joy”—and why our joy is often accompanied by dread. How to complete the cycle of sadness, in order to live with more joy. Susan and Sister’s best relationship advice: That our longing for the perfect partner is not really about our partner. Why Glennon thinks those who feel the ache are often those who fall into addiction.</description></item><item><title>84. Mothers &amp; Sons with Ocean Vuong (and Chase Melton) | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220192/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220192/</guid><description>Podcast Description Glennon’s son, Chase, joins Glennon for a special conversation with his hero, author Ocean Vuong, to discuss:
Chase shares with Ocean the impact his work has had in his life–and Glennon thanks Ocean for helping mother her son. What Ocean learned from his mother about how to navigate being an Asian boy in America–and Glennon’s recognition that she did not prepare Chase for the same realities. Ocean’s new book, Time is a Mother, and why watching his own mother die gave Ocean a deep empathy and connection to every person.</description></item><item><title>83. Brené Brown: What to Say to Get What You Need | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220193/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220193/</guid><description>Podcast Description How to know when to dig deep–and when to quit digging. The greatest blocker of connection–and how to remove it. How to handle our fear (without obsessively controlling our people and our environment). Why we all deserve a standing ovation for navigating relationships over the past two years. About Brené: Dr. Brené Brown is a research professor at the University of Houston where she holds the Huffington Foundation Endowed Chair at The Graduate College of Social Work.</description></item><item><title>82. Hannah Gadsby: How to Communicate Better | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220194/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220194/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why Hannah describes her later-in-life Autism Spectrum Disorder diagnosis as “an exfoliation of shame.” How neurodiversity affects Hannah’s relationships–and how she connects to the world through what’s “interesting” instead of what’s “important.” Hannah’s revolutionary commitment to stop using self-deprecating humor about her body, sexuality, and gender–and why we might all consider the same commitment. Why it’s easier for Hannah to share her personal stories “in bulk” on stage instead of one-on-one.</description></item><item><title>81. Pro-Aging: Why the Best is Yet to Come with Ashton Applewhite. | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220195/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220195/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why we’ve been sold a lie–and the truth that we actually get happier the older we get! The two most important–and shocking–predictors of aging well. Busting the most prevalent misconceptions and about getting older. How believing the myths about aging literally harms our health and makes us more vulnerable to the fears we hold about aging. Glennon paints a mental picture of her older self–and encourages the Pod Squad to do the same.</description></item><item><title>80. This is 46: Why I’m Pumped About Midlife | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220196/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220196/</guid><description>Podcast Description How Glennon is using her 46th birthday as an intermission–to slow down and decide what to bring with her into Act 2. The counterculture power of knowing what is enough, and letting ourselves go. The way to transition from Role Living to Soul Living–and why Glennon has Joni Mitchell on repeat. The real meaning of “crisis”–and the idea that living well now means reimagining everything we learned in the first half of life.</description></item><item><title>79. The Power of Rethinking Everything with Dr. Yaba Blay | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220197/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220197/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why the construct of beauty is oppressive, but the essence of beauty is freedom. What living with integrity looks like. Why Dr. Blay doesn’t need any more allies—and what she really wants from an accomplice. How “Karens” have been around for centuries—and the direct line from “Miss Anne to Karen.” Dr. Blay’s greatest hope for her granddaughters—even if she doesn’t like it. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>78. REGRET: What if we’d done things differently? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220198/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220198/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amanda shares the biggest regret of her life: the one that still wakes her up in the middle of the night. The five biggest regrets of the dying—and how to make the necessary changes to avoid them. Why we should reframe regret as proof of a life well-lived. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices</description></item><item><title>77. Double Date with Brandi &amp; Catherine Carlile! | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220199/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220199/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this hilarious and heartwarming in-person double date with Abby and Glennon—and their dear friends and brilliant artists Brandi and Catherine Carlile—we learn:
Why Brandi was completely dismayed the first time she met Catherine; Who made the first move—and why it made Catherine sweat; All about the Carlile family compound—where they are raising their girls surrounded by family, band members, and exes; How they communicate and deal with jealousy; and Why Brandi believes this conversation—two queer couples sitting on a couch publicly discussing marriage, family, and domesticity—is revolutionary.</description></item><item><title>76. Brandi Carlile: Live From My Couch! | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220200/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220200/</guid><description>Podcast Description The two disagreements between Brandi and Glennon that started, and cemented, their friendship. Brandi’s lifelong quest to continuously “calibrate” herself so that her outsides are in tune with her insides. The trait Brandi loves most about Catherine—and the sticky note on Glennon’s desk with the same message. About Brandi: Brandi Carlile is a six-time GRAMMY Award-winning singer, songwriter, performer, producer, #1 New York Times Bestselling author and activist, who is known as one of music&amp;rsquo;s most respected voices.</description></item><item><title>75. ALOK: How do we interrupt trauma? How do we heal? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220201/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220201/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do we make a new thing with our life? What is your fingerprint on the world? Who does history try to erase and why? What does pain do to our bodies? 5 .What is our capacity for transformation? About ALOK: ALOK (they/them) is an internationally acclaimed writer, performer, and public speaker. As a mixed-media artist their work explores themes of trauma, belonging, and the human condition. They are the author of Femme in Public (2017), Beyond the Gender Binary (2020), and Your Wound/My Garden (2021).</description></item><item><title>74. ALOK: What makes us beautiful? What makes us free? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220202/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220202/</guid><description>Podcast Description “The days that I feel most beautiful are the days that I am most afraid.” “What feminine part of yourself did you have to destroy in order to survive in this world?” “Why have we been taught to fear the very things that can set us free?”
About ALOK: ALOK (they/them) is an internationally acclaimed writer, performer, and public speaker. As a mixed-media artist their work explores themes of trauma, belonging, and the human condition.</description></item><item><title>73. Pet Love: Are Animals the Closest We Come to Unconditional Love? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220203/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220203/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amanda shares the story of Séamus, the newest addition to her family–and how he has ruined her “religion” of the spreadsheet. Why Glennon says that Honey and Hattie are the only “people” who truly understand her–and what each of them teach her about love. The ways we hilariously project emotions onto our pets–and how Abby has fallen for Tish’s pet hamster, Biscuit. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>72. Double Date with Megan Rapinoe &amp; Sue Bird! | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220204/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220204/</guid><description>Podcast Description For their first (of hopefully many) podcast double dates, Abby and Glennon sit down with the icons, activists, and Olympians Megan Rapinoe and Sue Bird. In this honest and hilarious conversation, we find out:
The delightfully awkward moment Megan and Sue first met; What’s hard for each of them right now; The boundaries they’re working on together; How they communicate and deal with jealousy; and How they help each other show up in the world as champions for change.</description></item><item><title>71. Be Messy, Complicated &amp; Afraid–and Show Up Anyway | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220205/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220205/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, Glennon, Abby, and Amanda continue their conversation about Glennon’s eating disorder relapse and the Next Right Thing for their family. CW // eating disorders
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>70. My Hardest Thing | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220206/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220206/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today, Glennon shares about her recent eating disorder relapse. If talk about eating disorders and mental illness helps: Listen today. If it triggers: Skip today. CW // eating disorders
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>69. Pet Peeves: What Do Our Biggest Annoyances Say About Us? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220207/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220207/</guid><description>Podcast Description Glennon explains her “soundaries”—and why a lack of audiorial yield in public places is her biggest peeve. Abby’s struggle, as a bonus parent, adjusting to a kid-filled life with zero personal space and personal property boundaries. Why Amanda is allergic to the word “fine”—and why she’s stopped saying “I didn’t have time.” To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>68. SARAH PAULSON IS PLAYING GLENNON ON TV!! | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220208/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220208/</guid><description>Podcast Description Glennon reenacts her first emotional and hilarious email exchange with Sarah Paulson about the Untamed TV show. Sarah contemplates how she will prepare for the role of Glennon–and why she’s “never been more excited about anything truly ever. ” Glennon, Sarah and Abby discuss who will play Abby–and how they will recreate the “There She Is” moment. About Sarah: Sarah Paulson’s acting work includes lead roles in FX’s anthology series &amp;ldquo;American Horror Story,” and playing Marcia Clark in &amp;ldquo;The People v.</description></item><item><title>67. How to Get More Joy with Martha Beck | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220209/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220209/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why it’s important to prioritize our own needs, wants, and feelings–and how that creates freedom and peace for those we love. What Glennon says was the hardest thing about telling her kids that Craig and she were getting a divorce–and how truth telling frees us all. Martha’s helpful strategy for how to choose freedom over fear when we’re faced with a tough decision. About Martha:
Dr. Martha Beck is a New York Times bestselling author, life coach, and speaker.</description></item><item><title>66. How to Come Home to Yourself with Martha Beck | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220210/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220210/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do we tap back into living by our inner compass after living by consensus and following outer voices for so long? What Martha said to Glennon and Abby when they told her they were in love but scared to move forward—and how that advice changed their lives. How to make a plan to cultivate joy when it feels like you are army-crawling through life. About Martha: Dr. Martha Beck is a New York Times bestselling author, life coach, and speaker.</description></item><item><title>65. How Do We Make–and Keep–Good Friends? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220211/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220211/</guid><description>Podcast Description How chronic social isolation throughout the pandemic has impacted our friendships–and why that’s affecting our mental health and cravings for connection. Glennon, Amanda, and Abby each make a Next Right Thing plan for prioritizing friendship in their lives. How we grieve a friendship ending when there’s no cultural template or ritual to acknowledge that deep loss. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy</description></item><item><title>64. FRIENDSHIP: What is it and why do we need it now more than ever? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220212/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220212/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why the connection of friendship is emerging as the single best thing for your wellness—and three things that define a healthy friendship. How friendship has changed for Abby since retiring from soccer—and why Glennon fears commitment in friendships more than other relationships. How to recognize ambivalent relationships—and why they can be just as bad for us as toxic ones. CW // eating disorders
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>63. How to Live a Little Happier with Dr. Laurie Santos | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220213/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220213/</guid><description>Podcast Description The simple exercises Laurie conducts with her students at Yale to help them reset their brains and restructure their days in order to access happiness. Why being “time famished” is one of the most common obstacles to happiness, the signals our bodies give us that we are starved of unstructured time, and what we can do to build more of it. How understanding that our brains are wired as “comparison machines” incompatible with happiness can lead to improved wellbeing.</description></item><item><title>62. The Big Lies &amp; the Truth About Happiness with Dr. Laurie Santos | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220214/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220214/</guid><description>Podcast Description One easy thing we can do to increase our happiness by 1% when we’re feeling tired and overwhelmed. Our misconception that happiness is about our circumstances–the next promotion, the new relationship–and the reality that often people with fantastic circumstances are miserable. Why our emotions flow directly from our thoughts–and how we can improve our wellbeing by changing our mind’s interpretation of events. About Laurie: Dr. Laurie Santos is Professor of Psychology and Head of Silliman College at Yale University.</description></item><item><title>61. Are Your Friendships Draining or Charging You? with Luvvie Ajayi Jones | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220215/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220215/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do we build a squad of friends–people we can trust our truth and imperfection with, and who take responsibility for one another’s care? How to know when it’s time to let a friendship go–and how we release one another without the hard feelings. Why when we have a problem trusting others, it sometimes has to do with a lack of trust in ourselves. Why Luvvie says her friends have rewired her brain, and answers the question: Can Black and white women really be friends?</description></item><item><title>60. Telling the Truth of Who We Are with Luvvie Ajayi Jones | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220216/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220216/</guid><description>Podcast Description A hilarious, profound take on judging people, and why Luvvie’s telling the world–and has often told Glennon–to: “Fix your face.” How to prepare for hard conversations with those we love–including the lists Luvvie brings to those talks that help keep her calm and vulnerable. The importance of sitting with the fear behind the questions: “Who am I when I am not giving something to somebody?” and “What is my worth when I have nothing to offer?</description></item><item><title>59. Be Still: How to Listen to That Something Inside That Always Knows | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220217/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220217/</guid><description>Podcast Description What if we stop trying to figure out whether our feelings and intuition are “right” or “wrong”– and instead, just acknowledge them as real–and move toward them? How Glennon is experiencing a little shift in peace, joy, and non-reactivity through her newfound relationship with meditation. Why a lot of our suffering exists in the space between the Knowing and the Doing–and how life is at its best and most exciting when we shorten that gap.</description></item><item><title>58. New Year, Same You: Good News About Bad January Branding | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220218/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220218/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why do we spend our lives trying to become what our culture ascribes as “good” only to burn ourselves out, wake up, and realize: I thought it would all be more beautiful than this? Why Glennon says that stillness has been her greatest teacher–and how she was able to find it in her most rock bottom moments. How listening for and committing to the next right thing then leads us to the next thing–and why we should rush towards whatever looks and feels like freedom.</description></item><item><title>57. Walking Our People Through Hard Things with Kate Bowler | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220219/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220219/</guid><description>Podcast Description What we should STOP saying to people who are struggling—and what to say, or do, instead. How Kate received the support she needed because people were willing to embarrass themselves in their attempts to show up—and why we shouldn’t be scared of doing it wrong. Kate offers some words to a Pod Squader feeling anticipatory grief—and how to accept that we can’t always make it okay for the people we love.</description></item><item><title>56. What to Do with Our Short, Precious Life with Kate Bowler | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220220/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220220/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kate describes the overwhelming feeling of love—not anger—that she felt when she was sure she was near death. Why it’s time we throw out expressions like “Everything is possible” and “What doesn’t kill you, makes you stronger,” and rewrite our cultural cliches. Why Kate delights in celebrating the holidays—and how to survive the holiday season when there’s grief and loss and fear in all of us. Kate and Glennon bond over their love for swear words—and how using them is a reflection of what’s going on inside of them.</description></item><item><title>55. Eff Perfection: Let’s Rest in the Rubble Together | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220221/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220221/</guid><description>Podcast Description What if we deleted the picture in our head of how it’s “supposed to be,” and looked at “what is” right now, as enough? What makes a good apology–and why we shouldn&amp;rsquo;t pretend that it is possible to reorder what we did to people. Glennon describes “the ache”–and how it’s really love, coming and going, and making life more beautiful. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>54. Unexpected Joy: How do we redefine success so we can find joy? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220222/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220222/</guid><description>Podcast Description Glennon, Abby, and Amanda share how opening up and being vulnerable on the podcast has changed their lives. What your preparation style says about your personality—and how some people bring their “magic” while others bring index cards. Abby recalls “the biggest bomb of her life”—and why she was nervous to join Glennon and Amanda on We Can Do Hard Things. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>53. How to Love Yourself &amp; Let Yourself be Loved with Ashley C. Ford | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220223/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220223/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why Ashley says we have to talk about what hurts if we’re ever going to heal. Glennon asks Ashley about the power of apologizing—and why Ashley says we must begin apologizing to the people we love. How many of us are really good at loving other people, but often struggle to let ourselves be loved. Why Ashley says that nothing has ever given her more peace and power than knowing that she doesn’t really need others to believe in her—because she believes so deeply in herself.</description></item><item><title>52. FORGIVING &amp; FINDING PEACE with ASHLEY C. FORD | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220224/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220224/</guid><description>Podcast Description How to find a way to live in peace: to actually love complicated parents without compromising our love for ourselves. How we can’t change our past—and why Ashley says that forgiveness is accepting the fact that the past is never going to be different. The importance of being able to hold two truths at the same time: that, for some of us, our parents did the best they could—and it wasn’t close to good enough.</description></item><item><title>51. First Ever Live Q &amp; A with the Pod Squad! | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220225/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220225/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why embracing that it’s not possible to do everything brings freedom. One change that Amanda made to get back into her body and reclaim her fire. How to navigate our anxieties about the impending “return to normal” and how to hold onto the rhythm many of us have found comforting during the pandemic. How Glennon’s been rethinking her popular Untamed quote “The braver I am, the luckier I get.</description></item><item><title>50. GET UNTAMED (Live!): This is How You Find Yourself | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220226/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220226/</guid><description>Podcast Description What Tish said when asked, “Who has taught you the most about love?”— why it was the best day of Abby’s life, and led her to redefine what it means to be a mother. Glennon declares herself a great adventurer, without movement: an inner travel guide—and how the new journal will help steer us toward our next right thing. How the pandemic brought Amanda’s anxieties, traumas, and relational cracks, previously on a slow burn, to center stage—and what she’s learning from “Be Still and Know.</description></item><item><title>49. Dr. Brené Brown: On Holding Boundaries &amp; Facing Our Fear | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220227/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220227/</guid><description>Podcast Description 1. Brené and Glennon role play through a scenario on how to put boundaries in practice with family members this holiday season. 2. Why Brené insists that starting “a love affair with the thing you’re most afraid of” will change your life. 3. Glennon asks Brené the question she’s been dying to ask about how a woman’s work is defined and received in the world compared to her male counterparts.</description></item><item><title>48. DR. BRENÉ BROWN: How to Know Ourselves &amp; Be Known by Our People | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220228/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220228/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why Brené’s new book ATLAS OF THE HEART is a game changer for communicating hard emotions more easily. Brené breaks down the difference between stressed and overwhelmed—and gives us tools to navigate both. How our survival strategies from our families of origin can become both our superpowers and our stumbling blocks in our relationships and wellness. How we can make sure our kids experience deep, steady belonging—even if they don’t feel like they “belong” out in the world.</description></item><item><title>47. YOUR HOLIDAY PEP TALK: “We ask no questions of this day.” | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220229/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220229/</guid><description>Podcast Description Glennon gives you a beautiful Thanksgiving pep talk that has Amanda and Abby nodding along and rolling with laughter. Why Amanda suggests that we can be free to be our full selves at the Thanksgiving table, if we also each bring our own damn casserole. Why the best predictor of how a family member is going to act is how a family member has always acted. We’re taking holiday-themed questions from our beloved Pod Squad about in-laws, when to break tradition, and how to navigate different family of origin patterns.</description></item><item><title>46. HAPPYISH HOLIDAYS: Our Top Three Hacks | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220230/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220230/</guid><description>Podcast Description How our second holiday hack—“Be unsurprised”—eliminates walking on eggshells around family, and leaving holiday gatherings feeling badly about ourselves or our people. Amanda shares the first time she broke her family’s biggest holiday tradition—and how it’s now one of her most precious memories. Abby remembers watching her mom stress out by preparing and perfecting every holiday detail—and the change she made to minimize her own holiday stress. How carrying around a cup of hot tea serves as Glennon’s super shield.</description></item><item><title>45. RUNNERS &amp; CHEERERS: Marathon Life with Shalane Flanagan | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220231/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220231/</guid><description>Podcast Description How a marathon is an analogy for life: the danger of comparison, the ride of emotions and self-doubt, that love is fuel, and that the world needs both runners and cheerers. The question Abby kept asking herself throughout the race—and why she’s still wearing her marathon medal while doing the dishes and running errands. Why race day was so profound to Glennon— even though she is strongly committed to NOT running—and how she experienced her first sports injury while cheering.</description></item><item><title>44. GABRIELLE UNION: Infertility, Bonus Parents &amp; Free Families | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220232/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220232/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gabrielle shares—as rawly and honestly as we’ve ever heard—about the “emotional chaos” of her years experiencing miscarriage, infertility, and surrogacy. Gabrielle and Abby discuss the label and perception of “stepmom”—Gabrielle shares what she avoids at all costs in that role, and the most vital part of the role for her: consistency. How Gabrielle coached her NBA husband Dwyane before Zaya shared with him that she is gay, and how his reaction encouraged Zaya to tell the people on her “never-ever” list.</description></item><item><title>43. Esther Perel Answers Your Relationship Questions | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220233/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220233/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why Esther often recommends letter writing if you don’t know quite how to start—or have—hard conversations. What to say—and when to say it—to show up for a friend who is in a bad relationship. The importance of rituals in transitioning through breakups—what we should do when it’s time to say goodbye; and what we can do if we’ve never gotten the closure we need. About Esther Perel: Psychotherapist and New York Times bestselling author Esther Perel is recognized as one of today’s most insightful and original voices on modern relationships.</description></item><item><title>42. ARE YOUR RELATIONSHIPS ALIVE? with Esther Perel | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220234/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Nov 2021 05:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220234/</guid><description>Podcast Description How, if you have been struggling in your romantic, parental, family, or work relationships through the lingering uncertainty of the last two years, you are not alone. The revolutionary understanding that, in relationships, “behind every criticism is a longing; behind every anger is a hurt.” What to do when your relationship is a bond of co-parenting / life management instead of a partnership of ongoing discovery. The link between trauma recovery and the process of enlivening “dead” relationships.</description></item><item><title>41. LANDING IN LOVE: Is the settling-in phase the best stage of love? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220235/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220235/</guid><description>Podcast Description How Glennon and Abby transitioned from the “falling in love” phase to “landing in love” at different times—and how Glennon felt “bamboozled” by it. How the self-inflicted guilt of pursuing joy ruins everything. Why a precious gift from Abby made Glennon feel like she’d finally landed in the right galaxy. How the things about our partners that drive us nuts are the same things that attracted us to them.</description></item><item><title>40. FALLING IN LOVE: Is there really “the one” or is “the one” YOU? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220236/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220236/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why “falling in love” feels like you’re losing your mind—and Amanda’s experience when Glennon fell hard for Abby. Why Abby thinks the idea of “the one” is the most romantic way to live, and why Amanda thinks “the one” is unromantic and uninteresting. Glennon’s belief that loves are like plants: some loves are perennials that continue to bloom, others are annuals, full for a season and then back to earth to nourish soil—but that no love is ever, ever wasted.</description></item><item><title>39. Passion, Praise &amp; Getting Personal | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220237/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220237/</guid><description>Podcast Description Glennon makes a “pod-pology”—and why we should stop saying, “I can’t imagine.” Amanda makes the case for no longer praising people as “superheroes”—and why we should stop giving them lip service and bring them a sandwich instead. How we abandon things we love because the environments surrounding them are unbearable—and how to recreate the environment and reclaim what we love. Amanda’s reaction to her new role opening up on the podcast—and how she feels like the very intimate stories she shares are “not personal at all.</description></item><item><title>38. HOW TO SAY NO with Simone Biles and Laurie Hernandez | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220238/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220238/</guid><description>Podcast Description HOW TO SAY NO with Simone Biles and Laurie Hernandez In this very special conversation, three GOATs and Glennon discuss:
What we can learn from Simone’s revolutionary decision at the Tokyo Olympics to choose her physical and mental health over the world’s expectations of her. The tiny decisions that helped Laurie practice trusting herself again after surviving a toxic coach. Why Simone, Laurie, and Abby believe their talent is both a blessing and a curse.</description></item><item><title>37. Creativity, Chemistry &amp; Claiming Your Joy | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220239/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220239/</guid><description>Podcast Description How Amanda’s breaking point—when her life felt like all “shoulds” and no “wants”—led to simple, concrete changes. Why the labels put upon us early—the sporty one, the smart one, the artsy one—can shut us off from exploring other parts of ourselves. How Glennon feels like Ben Affleck in Good Will Hunting—and why she wants Amanda to “go see about a girl.” What the chemistry of fire has to teach us about how we can resurrect our Fun selves.</description></item><item><title>36. WRITING &amp; ART: When does your real self get to breathe and be seen? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220240/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220240/</guid><description>Podcast Description How writing is a lifeline for Glennon because it’s the one place her real self can tell the truth. Why Abby feels that her time on the soccer field was art. The unorthodox way Glennon’s writing evolved from hourly 5AM sessions to survive sobriety with three young kids to three New York Times Best Sellers. Why it’s horseshit that books by women authors are indiscriminately labeled “self-help.” To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>35. UNBOUND with Tarana Burke—Part 2 | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220241/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220241/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re continuing our conversation with activist, founder of the me too movement, and our personal friend and hero,Tarana Burke. We talk about: What Tarana would say to her twelve-year-old self that might have changed the trajectory of her life.
Tarana’s life-shifting realization that her relationship struggles with her mother were not due to her mother’s lack of desire to love her well, but her lack of capacity—and how Tarana built more capacity for her own child.</description></item><item><title>34. UNBOUND with Tarana Burke—Part 1 | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220242/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220242/</guid><description>Podcast Description Please join us in the first part of our joyful, energizing, and hopeful conversation with activist, advocate, and our personal hero,Tarana Burke. We talk about:
How the spoken and unspoken rules for girls led Tarana to constantly perform the role of “good girl” so that “her secret” would never be revealed. The impossible double bind so many survivors live through: that the protection of our community is what saves us, but the need to protect our community is what silences us.</description></item><item><title>33. Living by Your Own Original Music Instead of Crappy Cover Tunes | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220243/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220243/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why Glennon believes the bravest thing she’s ever done was marching into her counselor’s office in high school—and what made her finally say, “I’m not leaving until I get some help.” How we can identify the difference between our Knowing versus our anxiety and conditioning. Why Glennon describes herself as Dory from Nemo, and how she returned to meditation when her mind became unmanageable. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>32. BEING BRAVE: What does it take to REALLY be Brave? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220244/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220244/</guid><description>Podcast Description The story that led to Abby’s iconic haircut—how that decision terrified her, changed how she played the game, and changed how she lives her life. How Abby and Glennon view “brave” differently—and why Amanda believes their perspectives may be more similar than they think. Why for Amanda the bravest decisions feel like “lonely certainty” that can never be explained or defended to others. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>31. Answering Your Sex Questions with Emily Nagoski | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220245/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220245/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re back with author and sex educator, Emily Nagoski, taking our Pod Squad’s questions about sex. How to navigate a relationship when one partner has a lower sex drive and the other has a higher sex drive. The “sleepy hedgehog” practice Emily suggests to help partners find their way back to each other after months (or years) of not having sex. How to raise our kids in a more sex-positive family culture.</description></item><item><title>30. REAL, JOYFUL SEX with Emily Nagoski | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220246/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220246/</guid><description>Podcast Description We welcome our very first guest, author and sex educator Emily Nagoski, who talks with us about how to finally build true, joyful, confident sex lives:
How our sex issues are totally normal—we’re all worrying about the same things. Why more than 75% of women do not orgasm from penetration alone—and why Glennon thinks the world doesn’t want us to know that. The single factor that is most predictive of strong sustained sexual connection over time.</description></item><item><title>29. People Pleasing, Unlocked Doors &amp; First Kisses | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220247/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220247/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why Abby says that people pleasing is both her superpower and her Achilles heel. Why Glennon says playing with kids is just the worst—and insists it’s okay for adults to sit it out. (This is why she’s not a parenting expert.) Why Glennon and Abby decided to say goodbye to Florida and hello to California. Glennon, Abby, and Amanda answer rapid fire questions about: their astrological signs, first kisses, and their morning routines.</description></item><item><title>28. LET HER REST: We respond to the Pod Squad’s mind-blowing questions. | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220248/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220248/</guid><description>Podcast Description The one question to ask ourselves if we want to know if our love is really reaching our people. How Glennon’s dearest friend Liz Gilbert taught her that a relaxed woman is the new revolution. Abby offers tips for bonus parents—and why she says earning her kids’ love has been the most rewarding part in her entire life. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>27. California Love, Sex Fantasies &amp; How to Know What to Do (in Bed) | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220249/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220249/</guid><description>Podcast Description The amazing life hack that has Glennon and Abby replying “Yes” to social invitations. Glennon acknowledges her sexual fantasies … and TRIES (but fails) to share them. Glennon talks about how she “knew what to do” the first time she and Abby were together. The best and worst parts of Glennon and Abby’s big California move. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy</description></item><item><title>26. SEXUAL DESIRE: How do we know who and what we really want? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220250/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220250/</guid><description>Podcast Description How Abby discovered she was gay while out to dinner with her parents at a Macaroni Grill. The moment Glennon knew for sure she was queer (in an Amish Boogie Nights bathroom)—and the song that sealed the deal. How, as a straight, cis woman, Amanda never had to wrestle with her sexuality, why she thinks that stunted her exploration. How Glennon’s failed Van Gogh visit inspired Amanda’s next sex steps.</description></item><item><title>25. You’re NOT A MESS. The world is. | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220251/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220251/</guid><description>Podcast Description The viral note Glennon wrote to herself in her car this week—and how the world’s response confirmed that we’re all struggling right now. How we tend to either Avoid the world’s pain or Be Consumed by it—and how to survive the overwhelm by embracing the Third Way. What Glennon fears most as her oldest child leaves for college. Why we can’t let the fact that we can’t fix everything keep us from doing something—and how Together Rising began.</description></item><item><title>24. ALL THE FEELS: Can we experience our emotions—not as good or bad—but as information to guide us? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220252/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220252/</guid><description>Podcast Description Glennon describes how she’s feeling as her oldest leaves for college—and the survival strategy that’s getting her through. The life secret someone told Glennon in early sobriety that changed her life. Amanda discusses the only two strategies that are proven to help us cope with our emotions and become more resilient. How hard feelings always reveal something to you about you. How the life hack Glennon calls “Save as Drafts” has saved her relationships.</description></item><item><title>23. Lightning Love &amp; Not Calming Down | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220253/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 07:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220253/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amanda presents a case for “summer rain” love—and rejects “lightning love” as the highest form of romantic love. Glennon’s theory for when to speak up and when to shut up. How Abby’s experience in a mostly male meeting showed her that “silent solidarity” is a cowardly lie. The trick Glennon uses to communicate with highly sensitive kiddos. (Abby swears it works every time.) To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>22. REAL TALK: How can we begin to use conversation as a key to unlocking each other? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220254/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220254/</guid><description>Podcast Description Five communication ideas that might help us connect more deeply with people. How Glennon feels that “everyone is talking but nobody is listening to each other ever” and why that’s one of the reasons most of us feel lonely. The conversation strategy that Glennon and Abby use at the dinner table with their kids and friends. Why we love talking about ourselves—and when it helps (and when it hurts) our relationships.</description></item><item><title>21. On Cussing, “Cattiness” &amp; What Feminism Means to G | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220255/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220255/</guid><description>Podcast Description Glennon lets f-ing loose about the misogyny in our cursing lexicon—and how it reveals our hidden conditioning. (Note: Don’t listen with the kiddos.) The connection between how little girls are taught to avoid conflict with each other and how adult women are called “catty.” What Glennon really means when she says she’s a feminist—and why she’s baffled when a group fighting for their own equality turns on another group fighting for theirs.</description></item><item><title>20. PLAYING OUR ROLES: How does culture’s invention of gender typecast every last one of us? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220256/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220256/</guid><description>Podcast Description How, in the business world, Amanda is labeled as aggressive and dominant—and why that’s a gender trap. Abby’s experiences of being publicly misgendered—and how that makes her feel. Why is gender the last place we’re agreed it’s acceptable to make identity assumptions? Why do we tell people who they are before they’re even born—and a thousand different ways every day after? Why Glennon says two women in a marriage, handling their own business, rocks the patriarchal boat.</description></item><item><title>19. SISTER ACT: Who is Amanda—and seriously, how does she know all the things? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220257/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220257/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Pod Squad is peeved that Glennon refers to Amanda as “Sister”—so what should we call her? How Glennon and Amanda both spent their college weekends in jail—but for very different reasons. Getting to know Amanda and her innate obsession with the link between our personal experience and our location within systems of power. What’s making life a little easier for the Doyle sisters this week. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>18. “BEAUTY”: How did we get trapped in this cage, and how do we break free? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220258/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220258/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why are we conditioned to spend so much of our precious time and energy on our appearance? Why is it that when men put work into the world, the world asks if his work is worthy—but when women put work into the world, the world asks if she’s worthy? Why is half the population’s face allowed to exist as is, while the rest of our faces “need” to be covered in concealers, colors, botox, etc.</description></item><item><title>17. EASY THINGS: Why, for some of us, is lightening up the hardest thing to do? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220259/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220259/</guid><description>Podcast Description Glennon’s radical acceptance that she’s always going to be a midnight person in a sunshine world. Our favorite movies and music—and what they reveal about our personalities. Why Abby is objectively hot, but please don’t say that to Glennon at parties. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>16. QUITTING: When is it time to let something or someone go? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220260/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220260/</guid><description>Podcast Description The one question to ask yourself when deciding whether it’s time to quit something. Why Glennon actually believes that quitting each day is necessary for her survival. The big quits that led Abby to Glennon. Amanda’s unexpected great relief—and hope for your relief—in learning about how we’re all just as happy as we’re ever going to be. (And how, as expected, Glennon disagrees.) Rethinking the ending of a marriage as a positive quit and how to talk to friends going through it.</description></item><item><title>15. Sexy Qs, Farewell to Faking It &amp; Vouching for Vibrators | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220261/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 06:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220261/</guid><description>Podcast Description If you’re like 75% of women, Amanda’s hot tips for setting yourself up for success in the bedroom. Detoxing from religious purity / sex shame culture, and raising kids with a healthier relationship to sex. The one sex subject that’s a hard no for Abby and Glennon. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>14. SILENT SEX QUEEN: Why aren’t we talking about sex more? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220262/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220262/</guid><description>Podcast Description Glennon, Amanda, and Abby discuss their sex origin stories and how that shapes their current sex fears. Glennon’s high-pressure situation of sex with Abby for the first time—and how it didn’t go quite as you’d expect. The biggest sex challenges in Glennon, Abby, and Amanda’s marriages now. What Amanda regrets about her past sex life—and how she’s already worried about what she’s going to regret when she’s eighty. How Pod Squaders taught Glennon and Abby about “lesbian deathbed.</description></item><item><title>13. Brave Parenting Qs &amp; the Power of Saying YES! | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220263/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220263/</guid><description>Podcast Description Glennon and Amanda decided to add a second episode each week after Glennon’s big move to California—in the first Thursday episode, they discuss:
Glennon’s experiment of Saying Yes to anything the universe invites her to. How much screen time is too much screen time? Are we all just Pendulum Parenting (over-correcting parents’ mistakes and screwing our kids up in the equal and opposite way our parents screwed us up)?</description></item><item><title>12. PARENTING: How do we make this thrilling, terrifying roller coaster ride a little bit easier? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220264/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220264/</guid><description>Podcast Description The 5 things Glennon wishes she’d known during those early days with young kids. Why it’s important to let our kids see us mess up, cry, and lose it every once in a while. How to let go of Expectation Parenting and embrace Treasure Hunt Parenting. On teaching kids the most important lesson: How to disappoint everyone else (including you) before they disappoint themselves. Why if you’re listening to this podcast worried about how you’re parenting, things are likely already okay.</description></item><item><title>11. REDEFINING FAMILY with Craig: Does letting go of what family “should be” help us embrace the family we have? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220265/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220265/</guid><description>Podcast Description Craig’s first two thoughts the moment Glennon sent him “the text.” How Glennon and Craig told the kids they were divorcing. The big mistake Glennon and Craig agree they made in the early days of blending their family. What Craig says is the most annoying thing about co-parenting with Glennon, and the best thing about co-parenting with Abby. How Craig really feels about Glennon writing their stories. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>10. OUR BODIES: Why are we at war with them and can we ever make peace? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220266/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220266/</guid><description>Podcast Description TW // eating disorders
Glennon’s “final frontier”—her attempt to stop controlling her body. The opportunity costs of a lifetime spent obsessing about our size and shape. How we’ve been taught to fixate over every hair, wrinkle, and pound—but have never been taught how our bodies actually work. How to quit conditioning girls to stay small in body, hunger, ambition, and desire. The tyranny of the weigh-in at the doctor’s office—and why BMI is horseshit.</description></item><item><title>9. QUEER FREEDOM: How can we be both held and free? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220267/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220267/</guid><description>Podcast Description How Abby learned from church as a child to hate herself—and the healing moment she realized that God and religion are not the same. The miraculous letter Glennon received from a reader the day after she came out. Glennon’s response to the statement “I disagree with your lifestyle, but I love you anyway.” When it’s time to either raise hell inside of—or leave—the institutions that require us to deny who we are or what we know.</description></item><item><title>8. SELF CARE: How do we identify our real needs and finally get them met? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220268/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220268/</guid><description>Podcast Description How to create lives that we don’t need to escape from. Why our resentment toward others is our Secret Self-Care Signal. Why refusing to be selfless is the best way to care for others and the world. How to stop passing down the brutal legacy of martyrdom to our children. Glennon’s life-changing spiritual practice: Habitual Quitting. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy</description></item><item><title>7. FIGHTING WELL: Is your conflict style making or breaking your relationships? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220269/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220269/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, in which Abby joins Glennon and Amanda, discover: How Glennon and Abby realized that each of their recurring Five Fights (about money, food, etc.) are all actually about the exact same thing—and how it all goes back to their childhoods. The guardrails Abby and Glennon built to protect each other when they fight. How to handle a relationship in which one partner runs from conflict (Team Abby), and the other rushes toward conflict (Team Glennon).</description></item><item><title>6. OVERWHELM: Is our exhaustion a sign that we’re CareTicking time bombs? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220270/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220270/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the episode discover:
How the constant to-do list ticker looping in Amanda&amp;rsquo;s brain makes her feel like a dormant volcano. The job description we&amp;rsquo;ve somehow accepted for motherhood—and whether self-abandonment is a job requirement. The way gender expectations even creep into Glennon and Abby&amp;rsquo;s marriage. How to know whether your partner is a co-builder or an assistant. How to make the invisible load of caretaking visible—and potentially bearable.</description></item><item><title>5. ADDICTION: How do we love an addict and how does an addict love herself? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220271/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220271/</guid><description>Podcast Description TW // abortion, bulimia, addiction In this episode discover: How Amanda protected their sisterhood from Glennon’s addiction. Which of the 12 steps Glennon refused to take. What it took for Amanda to finally quit the wine. The answer to the Pod Squad’s question about quarantine drinking and how much is too much. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>4. FUN: What the hell is it and why do we need it? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220272/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220272/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode—in which Abby confronts my sister and me about our inability to have fun—discover:
The one “fun” post that caused more people to unfollow me on social media than any other. Why girls may disassociate early from their ability to access fun. Science’s insistence that when we’re gloomy, rest won’t fix us. We gotta play the blues away. A playlist I created for YOU—if you, like me, need daily help awakening your dormant Fun Self:https://open.</description></item><item><title>3. INFIDELITY: How do we trust—and fully love—again? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220273/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220273/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, discover:
The messed up way my sister Amanda learned her marriage was over &amp;ndash; and how that sabotaged her healing process. 2. How we often cling to unforgiveness because it’s the last connection we have left. 3. The one question not to ask someone who is recovering from infidelity and what you can say instead. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.</description></item><item><title>2. BOUNDARIES: Are too few (or too many) why we stay stuck? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220274/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220274/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this Episode, discover:
My quirkiest boundary and how I finally fired Texts as the Boss of Me. Our response to a Pod Squad listener’s question about creating and holding boundaries with her in-laws.
How my aversion to moderation has led me from too few boundaries to way too many.
To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>1. ANXIETY: Is it just love holding its breath? | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220275/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 04:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220275/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode discover:
Glennon’s description of an anxiety attack. The 3 strategies that help her find calm. The original We Can Do Hard Things anthem, written and performed by Glennon&amp;rsquo;s daughter Tish Melton and produced by Brandi Carlile. To learn more about listener data and our privacy practices visit: https://www.audacyinc.com/privacy-policy
Learn more about your ad choices. Visit https://podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>We Can Do Hard Things Podcast Premieres Tuesday, May 11th! | We Can Do Hard Things</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2703220276/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 01:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2703220276/</guid><description>Podcast Description Introducing We Can Do Hard Things with Glennon Doyle! I’m Glennon Doyle, author of Untamed – the book that was released at the very start of the pandemic and became a lifeline for millions. I watched in awe from my home while this simple phrase from Untamed - WE CAN DO HARD THINGS – the mantra that saved my life twenty years ago, became a worldwide rally cry. Here, on WE CAN DO HARD THINGS, my sister, Amanda - my best friend and the person I go to all my hard things &amp;ndash; and I will do the only thing I’ve ever found that has ever made life easier: We will drop the fake and talk honestly about the hard.</description></item></channel></rss>