<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/off-menu-with-ed-gamble-and-james-acaster/</link><description>Recent content in Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 04:00:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/off-menu-with-ed-gamble-and-james-acaster/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ep 216: Dawn French (Christmas Special) | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 04:00:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yuletide greetings to all! We’re back in national tredge territory for our first Christmas special of the year, as we welcome Dawn French to the Dream Restaurant.
Dawn French’s new book ‘The Twat Files’ is out now, published by Penguin. Buy it here. Follow Dawn on Instagram @dawnrfrench and Twitter @Dawn_French Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 215: Paul Rudd | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 04:00:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340002/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s the last episode of series 10, and our true crime podcast finally gets resolved: does Paul Rudd like sauces? Trigger warning: this episode includes talk about dieting. Paul Rudd (and James) star in ‘Ghostbusters: Frozen Empire’, which is in cinemas in 2024. Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 214: Steve-O | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 04:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340003/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is not for the faint-hearted. Professional Jackass Steve-O shows us his new tat, introduces us to his new dog, and threatens to destroy our buttholes in this week’s episode.
Trigger warning: this episode contains talk about addiction, vomiting and, to be frank, so much more.
Steve-O’s new special ‘The Bucket List Special’ is available to stream now from steveo.com.
Steve-O’s Hot Sauce For Your Butthole is available to buy from Amazon.</description></item><item><title>Ep 213: Harriet Kemsley | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 04:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Superb stand-up Harriet Kemsley – as seen on ‘Live at the Apollo’ and ‘Hypothetical’ – has a table booked in the Dream Restaurant / cat cafe this week. Harriet Kemsley’s new special ‘Woman Child’ is available now on 800 Pound Gorilla and YouTube. Follow Harriet on Twitter and Instagram @harrietkemsley.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 212: Garth Marenghi | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 04:00:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dreamweaver, doomsage and Sunday Times best-selling horror writer Garth Marenghi joins us in the Nightmare Restaurant this week. Listen to this episode now, before it’s too late… Garth Marenghi’s new book ‘Incarcerat’ is out now in hardback and audiobook, published by Coronet. Buy it here. Garth’s previous book ‘Terrortome’ in now available in a limited pleather-bound edition. Buy it here. Garth is also on tour. Buy tickets here. Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.</description></item><item><title>Ep 211: Steve Coogan | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340006/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 03:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Steve Coogan joins us in the Dream Restaurant this week. No need for us to write anything else, really. The new Alan Partridge book ‘Big Beacon’ is out now in hardback and audiobook, published by Orion. Buy it here. Steve Coogan stars in ‘Dr. Strangelove’ in London’s West End from October 2024. Buy tickets here. Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 210: Paapa Essiedu | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340007/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 03:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emmy and Bafta-award nominated actor Paapa Essiedu joins us in the Dream Restaurant this week. Hope he doesn’t eat too much, or it may destroy him. Trigger warning: this episode contains talk about vomiting from eating. Series 2 of ‘The Lazarus Project’ is coming soon to Sky Max.
Follow Paapa on Instagram @pessiedu and Twitter @paapaessiedu
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 209: Dr Maggie Aderin-Pocock | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 03:00:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340008/</guid><description>Podcast Description All the important scientific questions get asked this week, as space scientist and ‘The Sky at Night’ presenter Dr Maggie Aderin-Pocock joins us in the Dream Restaurant. Does she think that Dark Matter’s evil? Dr Maggie’s new book “The Art of Stargazing’ is published on November 2 by Ebury Publishing. Buy it here. Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 208: Izuka Hoyle | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340009/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 03:00:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340009/</guid><description>Podcast Description ‘Boiling Point’ and ‘Big Boys’ star Izuka Hoyle has put a LOT of thought into her Dream Restaurant. And James has got a message for Stephen Graham…
‘Boiling Point’ the TV series is on BBC One, 9pm on Sundays and on BBC iPlayer.
‘Big Boys’ series 2 is on Channel 4 later this year. Follow Izuka on Instagram @zucchiniboobini
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 207: Nick Frost | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340010/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 03:00:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Want anything from the shop? Nick Frost – star of ‘Shaun of the Dead’, ‘Hot Fuzz’ and ‘Spaced’ – joins us in the Dream Restaurant this week. And a bromance begins…
Nick Frost’s new book ‘A Slice of Fried Gold’ is published by Bonnier on 28 September. Buy it here. Follow Nick on Instagram @FriedGold
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 206: AJ Odudu | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340011/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 03:00:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ever missed a flight? AJ Odudu has. The TV presenter, Strictly star and new host of Big Brother is this week’s dream diner.
‘Big Brother’ is back this October on ITV2 and ITVX.
Follow AJ on Twitter and Instagram @AJOdudu
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.
And go to our website www.</description></item><item><title>Ep 205: Jordan Gray | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 03:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340012/</guid><description>Podcast Description National Comedy Award-winning stand-up and musician Jordan Gray joins us this week. And you’ll never look at a Percy Pig in the same way again… Jordan Gray is on tour now with her Edinburgh Comedy Award-nominated show ‘Is It a Bird?’. For dates and tickets go to jordangraylive.co.uk Listen to Jordan’s podcast ‘Transplaining with Jordan Gray’ wherever you get your podcasts. Follow Jordan on Twitter and Instagram @talkdarkfriend</description></item><item><title>Ep 204: Carol Vorderman | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340013/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 03:00:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340013/</guid><description>Podcast Description I'll have a side dish please, Carol. We're back in National Treash territory as ‘Countdown’s Carol Vorderman orders her dream meal.
‘Carol Vorderman’s Perfect 10 Quiz Book’ is published on 14th September, published by Ebury Press. Buy it here.
Listen to Carol’s podcast ‘Perfect 10 with Carol Vorderman’ here.
Follow Carol on Twitter and Instagram @carolvorders
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 203: Paul Foot | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340014/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 03:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alternative comedy hero Paul Foot discovers the Fifth Flavour in the Dream Restaurant this week. Not everyone will want to try it. Trigger warning: this episode contains chat about vomiting from eating and euthanasia. Paul Foot is on tour with his new show ‘Dissolve’ which has just announced more dates for Spring 2024. For dates and tickets go to paulfoot.tv. Follow Paul on Twitter @paulfoot and Instagram @paulfootcomedy Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.</description></item><item><title>Ep 202: Jimi Famurewa | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340015/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 03:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Author, food critic and Masterchef star Jimi Famurewa is judging the Dream Restaurant this week. Fingers crossed for a good review.
Jimi Famurewa’s book ‘Settlers: Journeys Through the Food, Faith and Culture of Black African London’ is out now in paperback, published by Bloomsbury Continuum. Buy it here.
Follow Jimi on Twitter @Jimfam and Instagram @jimfamished
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 201: Angela Barnes | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340016/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 03:00:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mock the Week and Radio 4 star Angela Barnes is our next booking in the Dream Restaurant. And she likes to be able to hear her drinks. Angela Barnes is on tour with ‘Hot Mess’. For dates and tickets visit angelabarnes.co.uk.
Follow Angela on Twitter @angelabarnes and Instagram @angela_barnsey
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 200: Ed Gamble and James Acaster (with special guest genie Rylan Clark) | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340017/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 03:00:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340017/</guid><description>Podcast Description As we round off another hundo, it’s time to flip the table once again and make Ed and James the guest diners in the dream restaurant. Have their choices changed over the last 100 episodes? And will they exploit as many loopholes as their first attempt? And, once again, the genie is transferring his powers to one of our favourite guests from the last century, Rylan Clark!
A massive thanks to Rylan for being our guest genie.</description></item><item><title>Ep 199: Celya AB | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340018/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 03:00:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340018/</guid><description>Podcast Description French-Algerian stand-up (and former cat-sitter to James) Celya AB has a table booked this week. Bon appétit!
Celya AB’s new solo show ‘Second Rodeo’ is at the Edinburgh Fringe, Pleasance Courtyard, 2-27 August (not 15). Tickets and info.
Follow Celya on Twitter and Instagram @abcelya
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 198: Graham Coxon | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340019/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 03:00:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340019/</guid><description>Podcast Description Give this guest coffee and TV. Blur guitarist Graham Coxon chooses his dream dishes this week.
Blur’s new album ‘The Ballad of Darren’ is out now. Listen and buy it now.
Graham’s band The Waeve’s album is also out now. Listen it buy it now.
Follow Graham on Twitter and Instagram @grahamcoxon
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 197: Jenny Eclair | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340020/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 03:00:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340020/</guid><description>Podcast Description Why would anyone do that? Good question, Jenny Eclair. The Taskmaster star and legendary stand-up is this week’s diner in the Dream Restaurant.
Trigger warning: this episode contains chat about eating disorders and depression. Jenny Eclair is on tour with ‘Sixty Plus (FFS!)’. For dates and tickets visit jennyeclair.com
Listen to Jenny’s podcast ‘Older &amp;amp; Wider’ wherever you listen to podcasts.
Follow Jenny on Twitter @jennyeclair and Instagram @jennyeclair1960</description></item><item><title>Ep 196: Toheeb Jimoh | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340021/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 03:00:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340021/</guid><description>Podcast Description Riceo, Riceo, wherefore art thou Riceo? Kicking off series 10 is ‘Ted Lasso’ star Toheeb Jimoh. Toheeb’s currently starring in ‘Romeo and Juliet’ at the Almeida Theatre until 29 July. Buy tickets here. Follow Toheeb on Twitter @Toheeb_Jimoh and Instagram @toheeb.j Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Series 10 Trailer – Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 03:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340022/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Dream Restaurant starts taking bookings Wed 12 July. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 195: Judi Love | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 03:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340023/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s the last episode of series 9, and who better to eat at the Dream Restaurant than the unprepared and gassy Judi Love. See you next series! Judi Love is on tour with ‘The One Like’. Visit judilove.co.uk for dates and tickets. Follow Judi on Twitter and Instagram @1judilove
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 194: Tim Minchin | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 03:00:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sometimes you have to be a little bit naughty. Arena-filling comedian, Matilda maestro and co-writer of Groundhog Day the musical, Tim Minchin joins us in the Dream Restaurant.
Groundhog Day is playing at the Old Vic Theatre in London until 19 August. Buy tickets here.
Follow Tim on Twitter and Instagram @timminchin
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 193: Arlo Parks | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340025/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 03:00:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mercury Prize-winning musician Arlo Parks gets an in-depth education in the musical genre ‘food rock’ in this week’s episode. Arlo Parks’ new album ‘Soft Machine’ is released on Transgressive Records on 26 May. Buy and stream it here. Arlo Park is on tour this autumn. Go to arloparksofficial.com for dates and tickets. Follow Arlo on Twitter @arloparks and Instagram @arlo.parks Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.</description></item><item><title>Ep 192: Helen Bauer | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340026/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 03:00:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Edinburgh Comedy Award-nominated stand-up, ‘Live at the Apollo’ star and ‘Trusty Hogs’ podcast co-host Helen Bauer is this week’s guest. And she’s so committed to her menu she’s ordered some of it last night.
Trigger warning: there is some talk about compulsive eating. Helen Bauer is going on tour. Visit helenbauer.co.uk for dates and tickets.
Listen to Helen’s podcast with Catherine Bohart, ‘Trusty Hogs’, wherever you listen to podcasts.</description></item><item><title>Ep 191: Paul Feig | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340027/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 03:00:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340027/</guid><description>Podcast Description For the second week on the trot, alcohol is flowing in the Dream Restaurant. Paul Feig – director or ‘Bridesmaids’ and ‘Spy’, creator of ‘Freaks and Geeks’, and cocktail connoisseur – is this week’s guest diner. Paul Feig’s book ‘Cocktail Time!: The Ultimate Guide to Grown-Up Fun’ is out now, published by HarperCollins. Buy it here. Follow Paul on Twitter and Instagram @paulfeig Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.</description></item><item><title>Ep 190: Kiell Smith-Bynoe | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340028/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 03:00:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Grab a whisky, for the first time the Off Menu boys are drinking on the job in, with ‘Ghosts’, ‘Stath Lets Flats’ and ‘Taskmaster’ star Kiell Smith-Bynoe. (Can anyone lend me 30p for a Capri Sun?)
Kiell is currently in ‘Taskmaster’ on Channel 4.
His Channel 4 Blap ‘Red Flag’ is on All 4.
Follow Kiell on Twitter @kfRedhot and Instagram @klayzeflaymz
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.</description></item><item><title>Ep 189: Róisín Murphy | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340029/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 03:00:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Will this week’s guest be tempted by fruit hanging ripe on the tree? Róisín Murphy – musician, record producer and formerly half of Moloko – is our dream diner. Róisín Murphy’s new single ‘CooCool’ is out now, and she has more new music coming soon. She plays the Royal Albert Hall in London on 11 May. Buy tickets here. Follow Róisín on Twitter @roisinmurphy and Instagram @roisinmurphyofficial Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.</description></item><item><title>Ep 188: Alex Jones | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340030/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 03:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340030/</guid><description>Podcast Description One way or another, Alex Jones is going to order her dream meal.
All episodes Alex’s new series ‘Reunion Hotel’ are now on every Thursday on BBC Two at 8pm and available on BBC iPlayer thereafter.
Follow Alex on Twitter @MissAlexJones and Instagram @alexjonesthomson
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 187: Lily Allen | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340031/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 03:00:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sun is in the sky, oh why oh why, would we want to be anywhere else. Lily Allen joins us in the Dream Restaurant this week. Lily Allen stars in ‘Dreamland’ on Sky Atlantic and NOW. She also stars in ‘The Pillowman’ at the Duke of York’s Theatre in London’s West End from 10 June - 2 September. Buy tickets here.
Follow Lily on Twitter and Instagram @lilyallen</description></item><item><title>Ep 186: John Kearns | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340032/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 03:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340032/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Kearnel himself, ‘Taskmaster’ star John Kearns, is this weeks’s dream diner. John Kearns is on tour now with ‘The Varnishing Days’. For tour dates and tickets go to johnkearnscomedy.co.uk John’s podcast ‘Microscope’ is available on Apple Podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts. Follow John on Twitter @johnsfurcoat Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 185: Florence Pugh | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340033/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 03:00:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340033/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s another guest we’ve been trying to book since day one: Florence Pugh – the Oscar-nominated star of ‘Little Women’, ‘Black Widow’ and ‘A Good Person’ – joins us in the Dream Restaurant. And James tries not to bring up ‘Midsommar’ fan theories. SPOILER ALERT: there are ‘Midsommar’ spoilers aplenty. HEALTH WARNING: obviously, never take Calpol (or any other drugs) with alcohol. Obviously. Florence Pugh stars in ‘A Good Person’ which is in cinemas now and on Sky Cinema on 28 April.</description></item><item><title>Ep 184: Nick Mohammed | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340034/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 04:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340034/</guid><description>Podcast Description ‘Ted Lasso’ star and superb character comic Nick Mohammed orders, err, his dream(?) meal this week.
Nick Mohammed is on tour with ‘The Very Best and Worst of Mr Swallow’. For tour dates and tickets visit berksnest.com/nick Follow Nick on Twitter @nickmohammed Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 183: Motsi Mabuse | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340035/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 04:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340035/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode gets a 10(!) from us. Strictly Come Dancing judge Motsi Mabuse is this week’s guest diner. Motsi’s book ‘Finding My Own Rhythm: My Story’ is out now, published by Ebury. Buy it here. Follow Motsi on Instagram @motsimabuse Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.
And go to our website www.</description></item><item><title>Menus To Be Buried With - Judgement Day! | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340036/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 04:00:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Look out! Brett Goldstein, Ped Plambles (Ed Gamble) &amp;amp; The Genie (James Acaster) meet once again for Judgement Day to talk all about their favourite films meals all for Red Nose Day. On the menu this year we have bad dates, erotic meals and a very spicy curry.&amp;nbsp;
This Red Nose Day, let’s come together to raise some smiles – and some money – to tackle issues such as homelessness, mental health problems, and food poverty here in the UK and around the world.</description></item><item><title>Ep 182: Joe Cornish | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340037/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 04:00:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joe Cornish – film writer and director, ‘Lockwood &amp;amp; Co.’ head honcho and the 'Joe' half of Adam &amp;amp; Joe – has a table booked this week.
Joe’s series ‘Lockwood &amp;amp; Co.’ is out now, only on Netflix. Watch it here. Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 181: Cariad Lloyd | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340038/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 04:00:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Cariad Lloyd – improviser extraordinaire, Greifcast host and author of ‘You Are Not Alone’ – gets very specific in the Dream Restaurant this week. Trigger warning: this episode contains talk about grief and death.
Cariad’s book ‘You Are Not Along’ is out now, published by Bloomsbury. Buy it here. Listen to Cariad’s podcast ‘Griefcast’ wherever you listen to podcasts. Follow Cariad on Twitter @ladycariad and Instagram @cariadlloyd Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.</description></item><item><title>Ep 180: Reece Shearsmith | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 04:00:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340039/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Dream Restaurant finally has an address: 9, err, Genie Lane. Oh and also it’s a nest. Reece Shearsmith is this week’s diner.
Trigger warning: this episode contains talk about dieting and weight. Reece Shearsmith is in ‘The Unfriend’ at the Criterion Theatre in London’s West End until 16 April. Tickets and info here.
‘Inside No 9’ is on BBC iPlayer.
Follow Reece on Twitter @ReeceShearsmith
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.</description></item><item><title>Ep 179: Yotam Ottolenghi | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340040/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 04:00:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Another dream guest in the Dream Restaurant. World renowned chef, restaurateur and author Yotam Ottolenghi has a table booked this week. And James just wants to talk about Disney World food. ‘Ottolenghi Test Kitchen: Extra Good Things’, by Yotam Ottolenghi and Noor Murad, is out now, published by Ebury Press. Buy it here. Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive. Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 178: Fern Brady | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340041/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 04:00:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who’s this week’s guest, Fern? ‘It’s me Fern Brady, me Fern Brady!’ The superb stand-up, Taskmaster star-turned-author orders her dream meal.
Trigger warning: this episode contains talk of dieting and calories.
Fern Brady’s book ‘Strong Female Character’ is out on 16 February 2023, published by Octopus. Buy it here.
Follow Fern on Twitter @FernBrady and Instagram @fernfrombathgate
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 177: Kathy Burke | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340042/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 04:00:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340042/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re digging for national treasure, and we’ve found Kathy Burke – a guest we’ve been inviting to the Dream Restaurant since day one.
Kathy Burke’s podcast ‘Where There’s a Will, There’s a Wake’ is out now on all the usual podcast platforms. Listen to it here.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 176: Paul Mescal | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340043/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 04:00:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340043/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Dream Restaurant reopens its doors for series 9, and our first guest is Oscar-nominated and BAFTA-winning actor and star of 'Normal People', Paul Mescal.
Paul Mescal stars in 'Aftersun' which is available to stream now on Mubi.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.
And go to our website www.</description></item><item><title>Series 9 Trailer – Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340044/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 04:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340044/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Dream Restaurant reopens Wed 25 Jan. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2022: Part 2 | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340045/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 04:00:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340045/</guid><description>Podcast Description And here's part two of our 2022 Best Of collection. We’ll be back in the new year! Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.
And go to our website www.offmenupodcast.co.uk for a list of restaurants recommended on the show.
Watch Ed and James's YouTube series 'Just Puddings'. Watch here.</description></item><item><title>Best of 2022: Part 1 | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340046/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 04:00:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340046/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's been another delectable year of Off Menu. And here's part one of our favourite clips of 2022. Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.
And go to our website www.offmenupodcast.co.uk for a list of restaurants recommended on the show.
Watch Ed and James's YouTube series 'Just Puddings'. Watch here.</description></item><item><title>The Christmas Dinner Party (Live at Southbank Centre’s Royal Festival Hall) | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340047/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2022 04:00:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340047/</guid><description>Podcast Description A present from Ed, James and The Great Benito.
Off Menu: The Christmas Dinner Party, recorded live at Southbank Centre’s Royal Festival Hall on 20 December 2022.
Featuring special guests:
Nish Kumar
Rosie Jones
Bob Mortimer
Munya Chawawa
Sindhu Vee
Tim Key
Plus contributions from Claudia Winkleman and Dan Aykroyd. Bob Mortimer's new novel The Satsuma Complex is out now. Buy it here. Tim Key's Festivical Playing Cards. Buy them here.</description></item><item><title>Ep 175: Alex Horne (Christmas Special) | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340048/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 04:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Record a Christmas food podcast. Your time starts now. Watch The Horne Section TV Show on All 4. Watch Taskmaster on All 4. Listen to The Horne Section Podcast. Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.
And go to our website www.offmenupodcast.co.uk for a list of restaurants recommended on the show.</description></item><item><title>Ep 174: Mel Giedroyc (Christmas Special) | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340049/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 04:00:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tidings of comfort and joy to all! Finally, we complete the Mel and Sue set and welcome Mel Giedroyc to the Dream Restaurant for our first Christmas special of 2022. Watch Mel Giedroyc: Unforgivable on Dave and UKTV Play. Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.
And go to our website www.</description></item><item><title>Ep 173: Chris Redd (Live at Just for Laughs Montreal) | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340050/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 04:00:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340050/</guid><description>Podcast Description The third ever live Off Menu, this time across the Atlantic in Canada. With very special guest, Saturday Night Live star and superb stand-up Chris Redd.
Follow Chris on Twitter @ReddSaidIt and Instagram @ChrisReddIs
Recorded by Just for Laughs Comedy Pro. Edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.
And go to our website www.</description></item><item><title>Ep 172: Stanley Tucci | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340051/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 04:00:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340051/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the final episode of series 8, bonafide foodie and global treasure Stanley Tucci joins us in the Dream Restaurant. But will he raise a toast? Stanley Tucci’s book ‘Taste: My Life in Food’ is available now in paperback. Buy it here. ‘Inside Man’ is available on BBC iPlayer. Follow Stanley on Instagram @StanleyTucci Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 171: Chloe Petts | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340052/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 04:00:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Petts wins prizes is this week's episode, as acclaimed stand-up (and Ed’s regular support act) Chloe Petts orders her dream meal. Amazing this episode survived, considering the water spillage. Chloe Petts is on tour with ‘Transience’ in 2023. Visit chloepetts.org for dates and tickets. Follow Chloe on Twitter and Instagram @ChloePetts Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive. Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 170: Babatunde Aléshé | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340053/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 04:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340053/</guid><description>Podcast Description Let’s GO! Stand-up comedian and I'm a Celeb and Celebrity Gogglebox star Babatunde Aléshé orders his dream meal this week. And do NOT piss him off. Babatunde is starring in the current series of I'm a Celebrity… Get Me Out of Here! on ITV
See Babatunde of tour in 2023 with Babahood. For dates and tickets go to his website. Follow Babatunde on Twitter @BabatundeComedy and Instagram @BabatundeComedian</description></item><item><title>Ep 169: Ania Magliano | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340054/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 04:00:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rising comedy star Ania Magliano picks her dream menu, and a new caterpillar-based game in this week’s sugar-filled episode. See Ania Magliano’s show ‘Absolutely No Worries If Not’ at London’s Leicester Square Theatre on Fri 11 Nov. And look our for further dates on Ania's website. Follow Ania on Twitter @AniaMags and Instagram @AniaMagliano Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 168: Alison Spittle | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340055/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 03:00:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wheel of Misfortune podcaster and soup-erb stand-up Alison Spittle has a reservation at the Dream Restaurant this week. Listen to Alison's podcast ‘Wheel of Misfortune’ on BBC Sounds. Follow Alison on Twitter and Instagram @AlisonSpittle
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.
And go to our website www.offmenupodcast.co.uk for a list of restaurants recommended on the show.</description></item><item><title>Ep 167: Rina Sawayama | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340056/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 03:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Will this guest be eating to XS? Hyperpop superstar Rina Sawayama orders her dream meal this week. And James is trying to scare people with olive oil. Rina Sawayama's new album 'Hold the Girl' is out now. Rina is on tour. Head to rina.online for dates and tickets.
Rina's hot sauce 'This Hell' is out now. Buy it here.
Follow Rina on Twitter @rinasawayama and Instagram @rinasonline Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.</description></item><item><title>Ep 166: Paul Chowdhry | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340057/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 03:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Things get spooky – or should we say ‘sinistro’ – in this week’s episode with stand-up and Taskmaster star Paul Chowdhry. Paul Chowdhry is on tour with ‘Family Friendly Comedian (No Children). Buy tickets at paulchowdhry.com. Listen to Paul’s podcast ‘Pudcast’ wherever you listen to podcasts. Follow Paul on Twitter and Instagram @paulchowdhry Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 165: Richard Ayoade | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340058/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 03:00:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340058/</guid><description>Podcast Description BAFTA-winning actor, comedian, writer and filmmaker Richard Ayoade has a table booked this week. And he knows the way to James's heart. Richard Ayoade’s children's book ‘The Book That No One Wanted To Read’ is published on 6th Oct by Walker Books. Buy it here. Follow Richard on Twitter @RichardAyoade Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive. Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Announcement! Off Menu: The Christmas Dinner Party - live show in London - on sale this Wednesday | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340059/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 13:00:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dream Restaurant Announcement!
Off Menu: The Christmas Dinner Party
Live at London’s Southbank Centre, Royal Festival Hall
Tuesday 20 December 2022
Tickets go on sale this Wednesday 5th October 10am from southbankcentre.co.uk
This festive season(ing), Ed Gamble and James Acaster decorate the Dream Restaurant and host the Off Menu Christmas Dinner Party.
Join The Genie and the Maître Dream for some very special festive surprises, for one night only.</description></item><item><title>Ep 164: Richard E Grant | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340060/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 03:00:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340060/</guid><description>Podcast Description No Camberwell Carrots are on the menu in this week’s episode with – yet another national treasure – Richard E Grant. Richard E Grant’s new book ‘A Pocketful of Happiness’ is published in hardback by Simon &amp;amp; Schuster on 29th September. Buy it here. Follow Richard on Twitter @RichardEGrant and Instagram @richard.e.grant Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive. Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 163: Rylan Clark | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340061/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 03:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to the Dream Restaurant Rylan Clark we’ve been expecting you for a long time! A guest we’ve been trying to book since day one, and he doesn’t disappoint. Rylan Clark’s new book ‘Ten: The Decade That Changed My Future’ is published in hardback by Seven Dials on 29th September. Buy it here. Follow Rylan on Twitter and Instagram @Rylan Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive. Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 162: Matt Lucas | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340062/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 03:00:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Do be happy, don't be sad – when you listen to this week’s episode of the Off Menu podcast with special guest, Matt Lucas. Matt Lucas hosts ‘The Great British Bake Off’ which is on Tuesdays, 8pm, Channel 4. Watch it here. Follow Matt Lucas on Twitter and Instagram @RealMattLucas Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive. Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 161: Flo &amp; Joan | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340063/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 03:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gotcha! Musical comedy duo Flo &amp;amp; Joan – aka sisters Nicola and Rosie – order their dream menus this week. Flo &amp;amp; Joan are on tour with ‘Sweet Release’. Go to floandjoan.com for dates Follow Flo &amp;amp; Joan on Twitter and Instagram @floandjoan Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 160: Sir Lenny Henry | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340064/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 03:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340064/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re back in National Treash territory as we welcome our first Knight of the Realm to the Dream Restaurant: Sir Lenny Henry.
Lenny Henry’s ‘Rising to the Surface’ is published by Faber &amp;amp; Faber on 1 September. Buy it here.
Lenny Henry‘s ‘The Book of Legends’ is published by Pan Macmillan on 13 October. Buy it here. Lenny Henry stars in ‘Lord of the Rings: The Rings of Power’ on Prime Video from 2 September.</description></item><item><title>Ep 159: Felicity Ward | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340065/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 03:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Superb stand-up and Live at the Apollo star Felicity Ward has a reservation this week. And James has a guess at what's in a salad. Go to felicityward.com for Felicity’s latest tour dates.
Follow Felicity on Twitter and Instagram @FelicityWard
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.
And go to our website www.</description></item><item><title>Ep 158: Maisie Adam | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340066/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 03:00:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fresh from The Dip, Mock the Week star and superb stand-up Maisie Adam orders her dream meal. What a roller coaster ride of an episode. Maisie Adam is at the Edinburgh Fringe and on tour with ‘Buzzed’. Go to maisieadam.com for dates. Follow Maisie on Twitter and Instagram @MaisieAdam Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 157: Professor Brian Cox | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340067/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 03:00:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can you drink a black hole? Is sand evil? All these questions and more are put to our smartest guest yet, Professor Brian Cox. Professor Brian Cox is on tour with ‘Horizons’. Dates and tickets at briancoxlive.co.uk. Follow Brian on Twitter and Instagram @ProfBrianCox Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 156: Amy Gledhill | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340068/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 03:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340068/</guid><description>Podcast Description In one of the most chaotic episodes ever, rising comedy start – and 1/3 of sketch duo The Delightful Sausage – Amy Gledhill needs a mystery solving. See Amy Gledhill’s debut solo show ‘The Girl Before The Girl You Marry’ at the Edinburgh Fringe this August. Tickets here.
Follow Amy on Twitter @thatgledhill and Instagram @thatamygledhill Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 155: Taron Egerton | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340069/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 03:00:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rocket-man himself Taron Egerton pops into the Dream Restaurant this week. See Taron in 'Black Bird’ on Apple TV+. Follow Taron on Twitter @taronegerton Instagram @taron.egerton
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.
And go to our website www.offmenupodcast.co.uk for a list of restaurants recommended on the show.</description></item><item><title>Ep 154: Esther Manito | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340070/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 03:00:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Live at the Apollo star Esther Manito drops by the Dream Restaurant this week. Hope we've ordered enough lemons.
See Esther Manito’s new show #NotAllMen at the Edinburgh Fringe this August. Tickets here.
Follow Esther Manito on Twitter @Esther_Manito and Instagram @EstherManito
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 153: Joseph Quinn | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340071/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 03:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy series 8! We’re kicking off the season by heading into the Upside Down with Joseph Quinn – aka Stranger Things’s Eddie Munson.
Stranger Things season 4 is available now on Netflix. Follow Joseph Quinn on Instagram @josephquinn Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.
And go to our website www.</description></item><item><title>Series 8 Trailer – Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340072/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 03:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340072/</guid><description>Podcast Description New menu from Wednesday 13 July. Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 152: Paul Hollywood | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340073/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 03:00:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340073/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the last episode of the series, the baking king himself – and James’s nemesis – Paul Hollywood joins us in the dream restaurant. Bon appetit! Paul Hollywood’s new book ‘Bake’ is out on 9th June, published by Bloomsbury. Buy it here. Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 151: Rob Brydon | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340074/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 03:00:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340074/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re back in National Treasure territory, as Rob Brydon – who has eaten a lot of food both on and off camera – joins us in the Dream Restaurant.
See Rob Brydon on tour. Go to robbrydon.live for tickets. Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.
And go to our website www.</description></item><item><title>Off Menu x Percival: Second Helpings | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340075/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 07:25:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340075/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’ve teamed up with the good folk at Percival once again for another official Off Menu clothing collab. Tees, hoodies, shirts, caps - available now at percivalclo.com
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 150: Angela Hartnett | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340076/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 03:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michelin starred chef Angela Hartnett gives James some tips for his chorizo broccoli pasta in today’s episode.
Angela Hartnett’s new book ‘The Weekend Cook’ is out on 26 May, published by Bloomsbury. Buy it here. Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.
And go to our website www.offmenupodcast.co.uk for a list of restaurants recommended on the show.</description></item><item><title>Ep 149: Adam Buxton | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340077/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 03:00:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Podcasting royalty Dr Buckles drops by the Dream Restaurant. And this meal’s on him. Listen to The Adam Buxton Podcast on Acast or whatever you listen on. Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.
And go to our website www.offmenupodcast.co.uk for a list of restaurants recommended on the show.</description></item><item><title>Ep 148: Jarvis Cocker | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340078/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 03:00:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340078/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re opening up the national treasure chest to welcome legendary Pulp frontman, radio DJ and author Jarvis Cocker to the Dream Restaurant. We hope there are no mice in the kitchen. Jarvis Cocker’s book ‘Good Pop, Bad Pop’ is out on 26th May, published by Jonathan Cape. Pre-order it here. Follow Jarvis on Instagram @jarvisbransoncocker Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 147: Sikisa | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340079/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 03:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rising stand-up star Sikisa – aka Twix – has a reservation this week. And she‘s got opinions on sausage rolls. Sikisa’s taking her debut solo show – ‘Life of the Party’ – to the Edinburgh Festival Fringe in August. For tickets head to edfringe.com. Follow Sikisa on Twitter @sikisacomedy and Instagram @twix_choc87
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 146: Jamali Maddix | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340080/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 03:00:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Superb stand-up, Taskmaster anarchist and Hate Thy Neighbour documentary maker Jamali Maddix goes wild at the Dream Restaurant this week. See Jamali in London at the Hackney Empire on 28 May. Tickets here. Follow Jamali on Twitter and Instagram @jamalimaddix Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.
And go to our website www.</description></item><item><title>Ep 145: Kiri Pritchard-McLean | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340081/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 03:00:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340081/</guid><description>Podcast Description In an Off Menu first, comedian and podcaster Kiri Pritchard-McLean returns to the Dream Restaurant. Confused? Best listen…
Kiri Pritchard-McLean is on tour with ‘Home Truths’. For tour dates visit www.kiripritchardmclean.co.uk Listen to Kiri’s podcast ‘All Killa No Filla’ at allkillanofilla.libsyn.com Follow Kiri on Twitter @kiripritchardmc and Instagram @kiri_pritchard_mclean Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive. Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations). Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 144: Josh Thomas | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340082/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 03:00:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Josh Thomas – acclaimed Australian comedian and star of his own Aus and US TV shows – orders his dream meal this week, in the final episode from our trip across the Pond.
Watch Josh’s show ‘Please Like Me’ on Amazon Prime.
Follow Josh Thomas on Twitter and Instagram @joshthomas87
Recorded by Ben Williams and edited by Naomi Parnell for Plosive. Recorded at The Comedy Store, LA. Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 143: Siobhán McSweeney | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340083/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 03:00:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Derry Girls star and Great Pottery Throw Down host Siobhán McSweeney is this week’s diner, welcomed to the Dream Restaurant by Ed and the Genie for McSweeney. Derry Girls returns Tuesday 12 April on Channel 4. Epsiodes will air each Tuesday and be available to catch up on All 4. Watch it here. Follow on Siobhán Twitter and Instagram @siobhni Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive. Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 142: Morgana Robinson | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340084/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 03:00:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Taskmaster champion and award-winning comedy actor Morgana Robinson is next on the bookings list. But who let the stray dogs out? Morgana Robinson stars in Newark Newark which is on Mondays at 9pm on Gold. Watch here. Follow Morgana on Instagram @morgana_robinson.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 141: Asma Khan | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340085/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 04:00:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chef and restaurateur Asma Khan – owner of Darjeeling Express in London, and the first British chef to appear on&amp;nbsp;Netflix’s ‘Chef’s Table’ – is this week’s diner. Asma Khan’s new book ‘Ammu: Indian Home-Cooking To Nourish Your Soul’ is out now, published by Ebury Press. Buy it here. Follow Asma on Twitter @Asma_KhanLDN and Instagram @asmakhanlondon. Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 140: Claudia Jessie | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340086/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2022 04:00:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340086/</guid><description>Podcast Description ‘Bridgerton’ and ‘Line of Duty’ star Claudia Jessie’s travelled down from Brum for her booking at the Dream Restaurant. And she’s brought samosas with her. ‘Bridgerton’ series 2 launches globally on Netflix, March 25. Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive. Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations). Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial. And go to our website www.offmenupodcast.co.uk for a list of restaurants recommended on the show.</description></item><item><title>Menus To Be Buried With - The Resurrection! | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340087/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 01:00:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340087/</guid><description>Podcast Description After bringing the dream restaurant into the afterlife for Red Nose Day last year, Ed Gamble, James Acaster and Brett Goldstein have returned to the land of the living for another edition of Menus To Be Buried With. You have the power to do something incredible this Red Nose Day. Whether it’s a little or a lot, the money you donate will help tackle poverty, take action against violence and bring an end to discrimination.</description></item><item><title>Ep 139: Nadiya Hussain | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340088/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 04:00:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340088/</guid><description>Podcast Description ‘Bake Off’ champion and award-winning TV chef Nadiya Hussain is our guest diner this week. But don’t tell her your recipes, she might put them in her next book.
‘Nadiya x Prestige’ cookware and bakeware range will be available to buy in stores and online at John Lewis and from Prestige’s website from March 14.
Follow Nadiya on Twitter @begumnadiya and Instagram @nadiyajhussain.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.</description></item><item><title>Ep 138: Dane Baptiste | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340089/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 04:00:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340089/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re ordering this episode sunny side up, as stand-up comic and ‘Sunny D’ star Dane Baptiste dines at the dream restaurant. And remember: we’ve all got bellies and we all do sh*ts. Listen to Dane’s podcast ‘Dane Baptiste Questions Everything’ on Acast or wherever you listen to podcasts. Follow Dane on Twitter @danebaptweets and Instagram @danesnaptiste Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 137: Michael Schur | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340090/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 04:00:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340090/</guid><description>Podcast Description ‘Parks and Recreation’ co-creator and ‘The Office’ writer Michael Schur creates his perfect menu this week. But is his dream restaurant a Good Place to be or a Bad Place? Michael Schur’s book ‘How To Be Perfect: The Correct Answers to Every Moral Question’ is out now, published by Quercus. Buy it here. Follow Michael on Twitter @kentremendous. Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive. Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 136: Fatiha El-Ghorri | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340091/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 04:00:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340091/</guid><description>Podcast Description The genie better not mess-up comedian Fatiha El-Ghorri’s order. She’ll punch him in the face and call him stupid. Follow Fatiha on Twitter @fatihaelghorri and Instagram @fatiha.elghorri. Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.
And go to our website www.offmenupodcast.co.uk for a list of restaurants recommended on the show.</description></item><item><title>Ep 135: Tom Davis | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340092/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 04:00:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Big Tom Davis – star of Channel 4’s new crime comedy ‘The Curse’ and officially The David Blaine of Science – joins us for his dream meal this week. And there’s an actual experiment in the studio. Tom Davis stars in ‘The Curse’ which is on Sundays at 10pm on Channel 4. All episodes are available to stream on All 4. Listen to Tom’s podcast ‘Wolf and Owl’ on Acast or wherever you get your podcasts.</description></item><item><title>Ep 134: Charlotte Church | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340093/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 04:00:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340093/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Voice of an Angel herself, Charlotte Church, gets back to nature in the dream restaurant this week. And James is there, getting embarrassed. ‘Charlotte Church’s Dream Build’ airs at 9pm on Tuesdays on Really, also available to stream on discovery+ Follow Charlotte Church on Twitter @charlottechurch and Instagram @therealcharlottechurch Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 133: Tim Key | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340094/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 04:00:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340094/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Off Menu boys are back for a seventh series, and who better to be the first diner than Tim ‘I’ll be mother’ Key? Tim Key’s new book ‘Here We Go Round the Mulberry Bush: An Anthology of Poems and Conversations from Outside’ is published by Utter &amp;amp; Press on 14 February. Pre-order it here.
And buy Tim’s previous book, ‘He Used Thought as a Wife. An Anthology of Poems And Conversations (From Inside)’, here.</description></item><item><title>Series 7 Trailer – Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340095/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 04:00:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dinner is served from Wednesday 26 January.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2021: Part 2 | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340096/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 04:00:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340096/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s part two of our huge best of bonanza. We’ll be back for a new series in 2022. Happy new year! Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.
And go to our website www.offmenupodcast.co.uk for a list of restaurants recommended on the show.
Watch Ed and James's YouTube series 'Just Puddings'.</description></item><item><title>Best of 2021: Part 1 | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340097/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 04:00:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340097/</guid><description>Podcast Description What a delicious year for Off Menu. So much so we’ve split our annual Best of the Year episode into two parts. Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.
And go to our website www.offmenupodcast.co.uk for a list of restaurants recommended on the show.
Watch Ed and James's YouTube series 'Just Puddings'.</description></item><item><title>Ep 132: Harry Hill (Christmas Special) | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340098/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 04:00:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Spreading festive cheer this week is absurdist comedy hero Harry Hill! But which Christmas special is better? There’s only one way to find out… Harry Hill’s autobiography ‘FIGHT!’ is out now. Buy it here. Harry Hill is on tour with ‘Pedigree Fun’ in 2022. Buy tickets here. Harry’s podcast ‘Harry Hill’s Noise’ is available on Apple Podcasts, Spotify and Acast. Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive. Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 131: Sarah Kendall (Christmas Special) | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340099/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340099/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s Chrissstttmasssss! And what better way to get into the festive spirit than with an absolutely disgusting episode of Off Menu with Taskmaster champ Sarah Kendall.
Series 2 of Sarah Kendall’s sitcom ‘Frayed’ is on Sky and NOW in the new year.
Follow Sarah on Twitter @sarah_kendall
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Off Menu x Percival | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340100/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Exciting announcement! We’ve teamed up with the good folk at Percival for an official Off Menu clothing collab. Tees, sweats and hoodies - available now at percivalclo.com
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 130: Bridget Christie | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340101/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340101/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s the final episode of series 6, and who better than Netflix star, Edinburgh Comedy Award-winner and one of the finest comedians in the country – Bridget Christie – to be the dream restaurant’s last customer. That poor squirrel. Bridget Christie’s new show ‘Who Am I?’ is at the Leicester Square Theatre in London, 14-18 Dec. Book tickets here. Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 129: Jason Reitman | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340102/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who ya gonna call? The dream restaurant! Acclaimed film director Jason Reitman – director of ‘Up in the Air’, ‘Juno’ and ‘Ghostbusters: Afterlife’ – joins the Off Menu boys in LA.
Jason Reitman’s ‘Ghostbusters: Afterlife’ is in cinemas on 18 Nov.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 128: Miquita Oliver | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340103/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Like mother like daughter? TV presenter and broadcaster Miquita Oliver has a table booked this week. Hope the restaurant has enough clean vessels.
Miquita presents the Times wine podcast ‘Wine Times’. Listen on Apple Podcasts or Spotify,
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.
And go to our website www.</description></item><item><title>Ep 127: Timothy Spall | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340104/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Like father like son. Another national treasure is in the dream restaurant – legendary actor Timothy Spall orders his perfect meal.
Timothy Spall stars in ‘Spencer’ which is in cinemas this Fri 5th Nov.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.
And go to our website www.offmenupodcast.co.uk for a list of restaurants recommended on the show.</description></item><item><title>Ep 126: Jack Dee | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340105/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to the dream restaurant Jack Dee, we’ve been expecting you for some time! The legendary grump orders his dream meal, but don’t tell Jane. Jack Dee’s new book ‘What’s Your Problem?’ is published on 28th October. Order it here. Follow Jack on Twitter @therealjackdee. Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive. Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations). Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 125: Ed Sheeran | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340106/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Up-and-coming singer-songwriter Ed Sheeran has a table reserved this week. And James is turning his weirdest dial up to 11.
Ed Sheeran’s new album ‘=’ (Equals) is released on 29th October 2021 through Asylum/Atlantic. Pre-order it here.
Follow Ed on Twitter @edsheeran and Instagram @teddysphotos
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 124: Michelle Keegan | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340107/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brassic and Our Girl star (and Bake Off champion) Michelle Keegan picks her dream meal this week. But is she a cheat?
Brassic 3 all episodes available now on Sky and streaming service NOW.
Follow Michelle Keegan on Twitter and Instagram @michkeegan
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 123: Jeff Rosenstock | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340108/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Grab a couple of tallboys! On his way to a root canal, NY-born musician Jeff Rosenstock joins Ed and James in LA (in a pre-pandemic world) to choose his dream menu.
Buy Jeff Rosenstock’s albums on Bandcamp
Follow Jeff on Twitter @jeffrosenstock
Recorded by the Comedy Store LA and edited by Naomi Parnell for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 122: Meera Syal | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340109/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Goodness gracious me, it’s another national treasure in the dream restaurant. Actor-writer Meera Syal joins the Off Menu boys to order her perfect meal.
Meera Syal stars in Sky Original ‘Code 404’, series 2. All episodes available now on Sky Comedy and NOW.
Follow Meera on Twitter @meerasyal
Recorded by Ben Williams and edited by Naomi Parnell for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 121: Sarah Keyworth | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340110/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340110/</guid><description>Podcast Description The genie’s left speechless by comedian, writer and cob-lover Sarah Keyworth in this week’s episode. Speechless.
See Sarah Keyworth live – visit her website for dates: sarahkeyworth.co.uk
Follow Sarah on Twitter @sarahkcomedy and Instagram @sarah_keyworth
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.
And go to our website www.offmenupodcast.co.uk for a list of restaurants recommended on the show.</description></item><item><title>Ep 120: Miriam Margolyes | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340111/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340111/</guid><description>Podcast Description We welcome an absolute national treasure to the dream restaurant this week – Bafta-winning actor, Miriam Margolyes OBE!
Miriam Margolyes’s memoir ‘This Much Is True’ is published on 16 September. Buy it here.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.
And go to our website www.offmenupodcast.co.uk for a list of restaurants recommended on the show.</description></item><item><title>Ep 119: Jamie Oliver | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340112/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Usually it’s the guest that’s shocked by ‘poppadoms or bread’. Not this week, as we welcome to the dream restaurant legendary TV chef Jamie Oliver.
Jamie Oliver’s new book ‘Together’ is out now. Buy it here.
Follow Jamie on Twitter and Instagram @jamieoliver
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 118: Edgar Wright (Live at Royal Festival Hall) | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340113/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340113/</guid><description>Podcast Description The second ever live Off Menu, in front of a sold out crowd at London’s Royal Festival Hall. With very special guest, Hollywood director and Cornetto connoisseur, Edgar Wright!
Watch Edgar Wright’s documentary ‘The Sparks Brothers’ in cinemas or on demand.
Edgar’s new feature film ‘Last Night in Soho’ is in cinemas 29 October.
Follow Edgar on Twitter and Instagram @edgarwright
Recorded by Southbank Centre. Edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.</description></item><item><title>Ep 117: Ainsley Harriott | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340114/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Christmas comes early for Ed and James with the gift they’ve been asking for since day one of Off Menu: Ainsley Harriott in the dream restaurant.
Ainsley’s new book ‘Good Mood Food’ is published on on 9 September. Buy it here.
Follow Ainsley on Twitter and Instagram @ainsleyfoods
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 116: Bob Mortimer | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340115/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340115/</guid><description>Podcast Description We welcome comedy hero Bob Mortimer to the dream restaurant this week. Will a campachoochoo be on the menu?
Bob Mortimer’s autobiography ‘And Away’ is released on 16 September. Buy it here.
Follow Bob on Twitter and Instagram @realbobmortimer
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.
And go to our website www.</description></item><item><title>Ep 115: Isy Suttie (Live at Royal Festival Hall) | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340116/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Aug 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Last month, the Off Menu boys took to the stage at the Southbank Centre’s Royal Festival Hall in London for our first ever live show. Couldn’t be there? Here’s your chance to relive the show. And who better to be our guest for the first live Off Menu than Isy Suttie!
Isy Suttie’s book ‘Jane is Trying’ is out now. Buy it here.
Isy’s podcast ‘The Things We Do For Love’ is available wherever you listen to podcasts.</description></item><item><title>Ep 114: Shaparak Khorsandi | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340117/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340117/</guid><description>Podcast Description Superb stand-up comedian Shaparak Khorsandi joins the comedy rock stars of their generation Ed Gamble and James Acaster this week.
See Shaparak Khorsandi on tour with ‘It Was the 90s!’. Buy tickets at shappi.co.uk
Shaparak’s book ‘Kissing Emma’ is out on 2 Sep. Pre-order it here.
Follow Shaparak on Twitter and Instagram @shappikhorsandi
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 113: Asim Chaudhry | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340118/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340118/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor and writer Asim Chaudhry – aka ‘People Just Do Nothing’s Chabuddy G – has a table booked this week. And there’s a battle of the diet colas.
‘People Just Do Nothing: Big In Japan’ is released in cinemas on 18th August.
Follow Asim Chaudhry on Twitter @AsimC86 and Instagram @asimc
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 112: Simon Amstell | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340119/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian, writer and film director Simon Amstell joins Ed and James in the dream restaurant this week. And James gets so excited he cooks one of the courses. (Plus – we probably need to be clear – in no way do we condone taking illegal substances.) Simon Amstell is on tour with ‘Spirit Hole’ from 8 Sep. Go to simonamstell.com for tickets.
Follow Simon Amstell on Twitter @simonamstell and Instagram @thisissimonamstell</description></item><item><title>Ep 111: Emily Atack | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340120/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340120/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emily Atack – star of ‘The Inbetweeners’ and ‘The Emily Atack Show’ – is this week’s diner. But, unlike her ‘Inbetweeners’ co-star Joe Thomas, there’s not a buried lamb in sight.
The second series of ‘The Emily Atack Show’ on ITV2 kicks off in October., Emily is also on tour from the end of September. Tickets here.
Follow Emily Atack on Twitter @ematack and Instagram @emilyatackofficial
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.</description></item><item><title>Ep 110: Ross Kemp | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340121/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Finally, the documentary everyone’s been waiting for: Ross Kemp On Food. The Bafta-winning journalist, documentary maker, actor, podcaster and, of course, Eastenders’ Grant Mitchell joins Ed and James for a meal in a dream restaurant. But who’s the toughest?
Listen to Ross Kemp’s podcast ‘The Kempcast’ on Apple Podcasts, Acast, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Follow Ross Kemp on Twitter @rosskemp and Instagram @rosskemptv
Extra tickets for Off Menu Live at London’s Royal Festival Hall go on sale Thu 22 July at 10am from southbankcentre.</description></item><item><title>Ep 109: Nicola Coughlan | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340122/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340122/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s time to serve up another series of delicious chat, and who better to kick off series 6 than ‘Bridgerton’ and ‘Derry Girls’ star, Nicola Coughlan! But will she get locked out of the dream restaurant?
Follow Nicola Coughlan on Twitter and Instagram @nicolacoughlan
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Series 6 Trailer – Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340123/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340123/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hungry for more episodes? Series 6 starts Wednesday 14 July.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 108: Dan Aykroyd (Bonus Episode) | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340124/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Surprise! While we’re in the off season, here’s a very special – and very different – bonus episode. Ed and James speak to an actual Ghostbuster and Blues Brother – Dan Aykroyd. Dan kindly agreed to be on the podcast to promote his vodka brand, Crystal Head – and he sure is passionate about it.
We’ll be back properly for series 6 in a few weeks, but for now, bon appétit!</description></item><item><title>Announcement! Off Menu live show in London - on sale this Friday | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340125/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 09:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dream Restaurant Announcement!
Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster – Live
Friday 30th July at London’s Southbank Centre, Royal Festival Hall
Tickets go on sale this Friday 25th June at 10am from southbankcentre.co.uk
For the first time ever, Ed Gamble and James Acaster invite an audience to the dream restaurant for a very special live edition of their smash-hit podcast, Off Menu.&amp;nbsp;
Since launching in December 2018, Off Menu has become one of the biggest podcasts in the country, winning multiple awards, regularly topping the podcast charts and being downloaded over 55 million times.</description></item><item><title>Ep 107: Joe Wicks | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340126/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340126/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s the last episode of the series, and who better to wrap up season 5 than lockdown hero, Joe Wicks! But is he going to mug James off on dessert?
Joe Wicks’s new book ‘Joe’s Family Food’ is published on 10th June. Buy it here.
Listen to Joe’s podcast ‘The Joe Wicks Podcast’ on BBC Sounds.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 106: Josh Gondelman | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340127/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340127/</guid><description>Podcast Description New York-based stand-up and former ‘Last Week Tonight with John Oliver’ writer Josh Gondelman lives up to his reputation as the nicest man in comedy. Just wait till you hear his dessert…
This episode was recorded pre-pandemic in February 2020.
Listen to Josh Gondelman’s podcast ‘Make My Day’ on Apple and Spotify.
Josh Gondelman’s book ‘Nice Try’ is out now. Buy it here.
Follow Josh on Twitter @joshgondelman</description></item><item><title>Ep 105: Big Zuu | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340128/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340128/</guid><description>Podcast Description Grime artist and chef Big Zuu takes a trip around the globe to pick his dream menu. Is he having a nice time, or is that his fake laugh again?
The new series of ‘Big Zuu’s Big Eats’ is on Dave starting Mon 7 Jun.
The ‘Big Zuu’s Big Eats’ cookbook is published 3 Jun.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 104: Martin Freeman | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340129/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 May 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340129/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week’s episode takes An Unexpected Journey as BAFTA-winning actor Martin Freeman – star of ‘The Hobbit’, ‘Sherlock’, ‘Black Panther’ and Sky’s ‘Breeders’ – orders his dream meal. But what about that ‘Fargo’ accent, eh?
Season 2 of ‘Breeders’ will land as a box set on Sky and be available to watch on Sky One and NOW TV from 27th May.
Recorded by Ben Williams and edited by Naomi Parnell for Plosive.</description></item><item><title>Ep 103: Bimini Bon Boulash | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340130/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340130/</guid><description>Podcast Description Release the beast! Bimini Bon Boulash – the breakout star of this year’s ‘Drag Race UK’ – has a table booked this week. And did she mention she’s vegan?
New music from Bimini is coming soon.
Pre-order Bimini’s book ‘A Drag Queen’s Guide to Life’ here.
Follow Bimini on Twitter and Instagram @biminibabes
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 102: Rafe Spall | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340131/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Has James spilt the ketchup? Because he’s got red on him. Actor Rafe Spall – star of ‘Hot Fuzz’, ‘Jurassic World’, ‘The Shadow Line’ and Apple TV+’s ‘Trying’ – is in the dream restaurant this week. And it’s going to be a roadblock event.
Series 2 of ‘Trying’ is streaming globally on Apple TV+ on May 14. Series 1 is available now.
Recorded by Ben Williams and edited by Naomi Parnell for Plosive.</description></item><item><title>Ep 101: Julie Adenuga | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340132/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340132/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re breaking off the next hundred with radio presenter and co-host of MTV’s ‘Catfish UK’, Julie Adenuga! There’s a game that the listeners can get involved with, and Julie and Ed come to blows…
‘Catfish UK’ is on Wednesdays at 9pm, only on MTV.
Follow Julie on Twitter and Instagram @JulieAdenuga.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 100: Ed Gamble and James Acaster (with special guest genie Claudia Winkleman) | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340133/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340133/</guid><description>Podcast Description One hundred! The hundo! The big 1-0-0! In a milestone episode, Ed and James finally reveal their dream meals. And who better for the genie to transfer his powers to than Off Menu fave and this episode’s special guest host, Claudia Winkleman!
A massive thanks to Claudia for being our wish-granter. A HUGE thank you to you, the listeners, for helping us reach 100 episodes – we wouldn't be making the podcast if you weren’t listening.</description></item><item><title>Ep 99: Domhnall Gleeson | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340134/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor and The Strokes fan Domhnall Gleeson – star of ‘Star Wars’, ‘Ex Machina’, ‘Harry Potter’ and brand new Channel 4 sitcom ‘Frank of Ireland’ – is in the dream restaurant for our 99th episode. And Tom Hollander’s sat outside.
‘Frank of Ireland’ airs weekly from Thursday 15th April, 10pm, Channel 4. All eps will also be available to boxset on All 4.
Recorded by and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.</description></item><item><title>Ep 98: Mary Lynn Rajskub | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340135/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comic and actor Mary Lynn Rajskub – aka Chloe from ‘24’ and Gail the Snail from ‘It’s Always Sunny…’ – joins us in LA for this week’s meal. And James absolutely stinks. (This episode was recorded in February 2020, pre-pandemic.)
Watch Mary Lynn’s new special ‘Mary Lynn Rajskub: Live from the Pandemic’ on Vimeo
Follow Mary Lynn on Twitter and Instagram: @MaryLynnRajskub
Recorded by and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.</description></item><item><title>Ep 97: Munya Chawawa | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340136/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340136/</guid><description>Podcast Description Instagram sensation and satirist Munya Chawawa is this week’s guest. But, as he has another restaurant booking to get to, will he leave us wanting more?
Follow Munya on Twitter and Instagram: @munyachawawa
Visit Munya’s website munyachawawa.com
Recorded by and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.
And go to our website www.</description></item><item><title>Off Menu: The Redemption Dinner Party – Second Helpings – Live-Streamed Show – On Sale Now | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340137/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dream Restaurant Announcement!
Off Menu: The Redemption Dinner Party – Second Helpings
Sunday 11 April, 7.30pm (BST) – Live and Online
Still hungry? Ed Gamble and James Acaster re-open the dream restaurant and invite some of Off Menu’s most talked-about guests to The Redemption Dinner Party: Second Helpings. Will the previous podcast guests stick with their outlandish orders, or will they take a once-in-a-meal chance to change their minds?</description></item><item><title>Ep 96: Thanyia Moore | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340138/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340138/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian and ‘Mock the Week’ star Thanyia Moore’s inviting her best pals to her dinner party – but who’s more of a knobhead, Ed or James?
Follow Thanyia on Twitter and Instagram: @ThanyiaMoore
Visit Thanyia’s website thanyiamoore.co.uk
Recorded by and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.
And go to our website www.</description></item><item><title>Ep 95: Rosie Jones | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340139/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hope the corner shop’s still open, because the Genie’s going to need to do some shopping to whip up comedian Rosie Jones’s dream meal.
Listen to Rosie Jones’s podcast ‘Daddy Look at Me’ on Acast or wherever you get your podcasts
Follow Rosie on Twitter and Instagram: @josierones
Recorded by and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Menus To Be Buried With with Ed Gamble, James Acaster and Brett Goldstein | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340140/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340140/</guid><description>Podcast Description Look out, it’s only a crossover episode! Peddy Bambles and The Genie team up with Bradley Goldstein for this Acast Red Nose Day Mashup podcast, all in aid of Comic Relief. This is Off Menu meets Films To Be Buried With. AKA: Menus To Be Buried With.
Donations have the power to help people living incredibly tough lives. If you can, please, head to comicrelief.com/podcastmashup and give now. Or give £5 by texting ‘COMIC’ to 70205.</description></item><item><title>Ep 94: Todd Barry | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340141/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340141/</guid><description>Podcast Description There’s a table ready for New York-based stand-up and ‘Flight of the Conchords’ star Todd Barry this week. And he’s invited a bunch of rappers to the dream restaurant. (This episode was recorded in January 2020 – before the pandemic.)
Watch Todd Barry’s Netflix special ‘Spicy Honey’ and Amazon Prime special ‘The Crowd Work Tour’.
Follow Todd on Twitter and Instagram: @toddbarry
Recorded by Ben Williams and edited by Naomi Parnell for Plosive Productions.</description></item><item><title>Ep 93: Jessica Fostekew | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340142/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340142/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fellow food podcaster and superb stand-up Jessica Fostekew has a table booked, and ethics are being thrown out of the dream restaurant window.
Listen to Jess’s podcast ‘Hoovering’ on Acast or wherever you get your podcasts.
Watch Jess’s stand-up special ‘Silence of the Nans’ on NextUp.
Follow Jess on Twitter and Instagram: @jessicafostekew
Recorded by Ben Williams and edited by Naomi Parnell for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 92: Sue Perkins | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340143/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340143/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a VERY memorable episode, national treasure and former ‘Bake Off’ co-host Sue Perkins discovers an unexpected loophole in the dream restaurant’s ordering process.
Listen to Sue’s podcast ‘Sue Perkins: An hour or so with…’ on Audioboom or wherever you get your podcasts.
Follow Sue Perkins on Twitter @sueperkins
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 91: Joel Kim Booster | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340144/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340144/</guid><description>Podcast Description LA-based comedian and writer Joel Kim Booster has brought his blender to the dream restaurant this week. Is there something about Joels and food? Plus, James gets INCREDIBLY offensive. (This episode was recorded pre-pandemic.)
Listen to Joel Kim Booster’s podcast ‘Urgent Care with Joel Kim Booster and Mitra Jouhari’ wherever you get your podcasts
Follow Joel Kim Booster on Twitter and Instagram @ihatejoelkim
Recorded by Ben Williams and edited by Naomi Parnell for Plosive Productions.</description></item><item><title>Ep 90: Paul Scheer | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340145/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340145/</guid><description>Podcast Description Actor, comedian and ‘How Did This Get Made?’ podcaster Paul Scheer – and a mystery healthy old man – join Ed and James in the dream restaurant this week. This episode was recorded in LA, pre-pandemic, when we had our regular lives.
Listen to Paul’s podcast ‘How Did This Get Made?’ at www.hdtgminfo.com
Follow Paul on Twitter and Instagram @paulscheer
Big thanks to Earwolf for the studio space!</description></item><item><title>Ep 89: Anne-Marie | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340146/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340146/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chart-topping sensation Anne-Marie talks very intimately in the dream restaurant this week. Hopefully there are no strangers nearby.
Anne-Marie’s joint new track with KSI and Digital Farm Animals called ‘Don’t Play’ is out now. Anne-Marie is a judge on ‘The Voice’ on ITV, Saturdays at 8.30pm.
Follow Anne-Marie on Instagram and Twitter @AnneMarie
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 88: Mae Martin | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340147/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340147/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Dream Restaurant opens its doors for series 5, and its first patron is superb comedian and creator/star of ‘Feel Good’, Mae Martin! Ed’s trying to smuggle a ninja star into the kitchen and James reminisces about shrimp.
Watch ‘Feel Good’ on All4 in the UK and on Netflix worldwide.
Follow Mae Martin on Twitter @TheMaeMartin and Instagram @hooraymae. Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.</description></item><item><title>Series 5 Trailer – Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340148/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340148/</guid><description>Podcast Description The fifth course of our podcast tasting menu is nearly on the pass. Series 5 starts Wednesday 27 January.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Off Menu: The Redemption Dinner Party – Live-Streamed Show – On Sale Now | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340149/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2021 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340149/</guid><description>Podcast Description RESCHEDULED DATE: SUNDAY 7 FEBRUARY
Dream Restaurant Announcement!
Off Menu: The Redemption Dinner Party
Sunday 7 February, 7.30pm (GMT) – Live and Online
In a very special live-streamed show, Ed Gamble and James Acaster invite some of Off Menu’s most talked-about guests back to the dream restaurant to re-live their contentious meal choices. Will they stick with their orders, or will they take a once-in-a-meal chance to change their minds?</description></item><item><title>Best of 2020 | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340150/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340150/</guid><description>Podcast Description To mark the end of such a fantastic year for everyone, we revisit our favourite clips from the last 12 months of Off Menu.
We'll be back for series 5 in the new year. Bon appétit!
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.
And go to our website www.</description></item><item><title>Ed and James and Willie and Joe’s Perfect Chocolate Christmas | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340151/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340151/</guid><description>Podcast Description Yes, we made it happen. Willie Harcourt-Cooze and Joe Thomas meet at last for a festive, lamb-based chat with Ed and James. Merry Christmas!
(And this episode was recorded before Tier 4 was announced.)
Buy Willie’s chocolate at www.williescacao.com
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.
And go to our website www.</description></item><item><title>Ep 87: Sarah Millican (Christmas Special) | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340152/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340152/</guid><description>Podcast Description Grab the KFC gravy, it’s another classic Off Menu Christmas Special, and we welcome Sarah Millican to the dream restaurant. And we’ll make sure her meal is piled high on a plate.
Sarah Millican is on tour in 2021/2022 with ‘Bobby Dazzler’. For tour dates and tickets visit sarahmillican.co.uk.
Follow Sarah Millican on Twitter @SarahMillican75 and Instagram @thesarahmillican.
#JoinIn will be happening on Twitter on Christmas Day.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.</description></item><item><title>Ep 86: Russell Howard (Christmas Special) | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340153/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340153/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Festivus! The nation’s sweetheart Russell Howard joins us in the merry dream restaurant for an Off Menu Christmas Special.
The Russell Howard Hour Christmas Special is on Thu 17 Dec at 10pm
Follow Russell Howard on Twitter and Instagram: @russellhoward
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 85: Jo Brand | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340154/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340154/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s the final episode of series 4, and what better way to end the season than with alternative comedy legend (and Bake Off Extra Slice host) Jo Brand? Plus there’s a new verse to James’s Cawston Press chart-topper.
Follow Jo Brand on Instagram: @iamnotjobrand
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 84: Jayde Adams | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340155/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340155/</guid><description>Podcast Description Get the Renniés out, West Country comedian and host of Channel 4 food show ‘Crazy Delicious’ Jayde Adams has a table booked this week. #jaydebangamash
Watch Jayde Adams’s special ‘Serious Black Jumper’ on Amazon Prime.
Watch ‘Crazy Delicious’ on All 4.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 83: Josh Groban | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340156/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340156/</guid><description>Podcast Description Multi-platinum selling singer-songwriter and actor Josh ‘Chirashi Joshie’ Groban joins Ed and James at the bar in the dream restaurant, in another New York recorded episode. Plus we get an appearance from the Coffee Comedian.
Josh Groban’s new album ‘Harmony’ is available on 20 November. Buy and stream it here.
Follow Josh Groban on Twitter and Instagram @joshgroban
Recorded by Ben Williams and edited Naomi Parnell for Plosive Productions.</description></item><item><title>Ep 82: Thomasina Miers | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340157/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340157/</guid><description>Podcast Description Time to crack open the tequila, because ‘Masterchef’ winner and Wahaca co-founder Thomasina Miers is this week’s guest, in another pre-Covid recorded episode.
Find out more about Thomasina Miers at www.thomasinamiers.com
Follow Thomasina on Twitter and Instagram @thomasinamiers
Buy Thomasina’s cook books on her website
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 81: David O’Doherty (Bonus Episode) | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340158/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340158/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ed and James welcome wonderful comedian David O’Doherty to the dream restaurant for this very special live-streamed episode of Off Menu as part of Unmute: The Online Podcast Festival. Hope you’ve got your microwave plugged in.
Follow David O’Doherty on Twitter and Instagram @phlaimeaux
Buy David O’Doherty’s album ‘Live in his Own Car During a Pandemic’ on Bandcamp
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 80: David Cross | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340159/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340159/</guid><description>Podcast Description There’s a table booked for David Cross – legendary US stand-up and star of ‘Mr Show’ and ‘Arrested Development’ – this week. And he’s pre-drinking.
Follow David Cross on Twitter @davidcrosss and Instagram @davidcrossofficial
Watch David Cross’s Netflix special ‘Making America Great Again!’ on Netflix
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 79: Wyatt Cenac | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340160/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340160/</guid><description>Podcast Description NY stand-up and writer Wyatt ‘Uncle Wy Wy’ Cenac joins us in the dream restaurant this week. And there's a whole fuffle over the Bake Off piss-window.
Follow Wyatt Cenac on Instagram and Twitter: @wyattcenac
Watch Wyatt Cenac’s Netflix special ‘Brooklyn’ on Netflix
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 78: Dolly Alderton | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340161/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340161/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s an episode full of Highs and Lows as author, journalist and podcaster Dolly Alderton chooses her dream meal. This episodes comes with sparklers in it, like a Mayfair nightclub cocktail.
Dolly Alderton’s debut novel ‘Ghosts’ is published on 15 Oct 2020. Buy it here
Follow Dolly on Instagram and Twitter: @dollyalderton
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 77: Ovie Soko | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340162/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340162/</guid><description>Podcast Description He might not recognise his Island-mate, but British basketball superstar and ‘Love Island’ contestant Ovie Soko’s picking his dream meal this week. Let’s hope he doesn’t get pied.
Ovie Soko’s book ‘You Are Dope’ is out now. Buy it here.
Follow Ovie on Instagram and Twitter: @oviesoko
Follow Griffin Frenchie on Instagram: @griffinfrenchie
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 76: Claudia Winkleman | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340163/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340163/</guid><description>Podcast Description We give this episode… 10! ‘Strictly Come Dancing’ co-host Claudia Winkleman has booked a table this week, and she really knows her order. Goodbye, thanks for coming, night night.
Claudia Winkleman’s book ‘Quite’ is available from 1st October. Buy it here.
Follow Claudia on Twitter and Instagram @ClaudiaWinkle
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 75: Corey Taylor | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340164/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340164/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s time to Wait and Feed as we welcome Slipknot frontman Corey Taylor – whose debut solo album ‘CMFT’ is released soon – to the dream restaurant. And, boy oh boy, is Ed a happy metalhead.
Corey Taylor’s debut solo album ‘CMFT’ is released on 2nd October. Pre-order here.
Follow Corey Taylor on Twitter: @CoreyTaylorRock
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 74: Anthony Jeselnik | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340165/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340165/</guid><description>Podcast Description In what is surely to become a much-talked about Off Menu episode, US stand-up and Netflix star Anthony Jeselnik joins us in the dream restaurant and questions the Mash King’s authority. Oh and – obviously – this episode was recorded pre-pandemic.
Watch Anthony Jeselnik’s latest Netflix special ‘Fire in the Maternity Ward’.
Follow Anthony on Twitter: @anthonyjeselnik
Recorded by Ben Williams and edited by Naomi Parnell for Plosive Productions.</description></item><item><title>Ep 73: Hari Kondabolu | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340166/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340166/</guid><description>Podcast Description New York born stand-up, writer and actor Hari Kondabolu – who made the acclaimed documentary ‘The Problem with Apu’ – orders his dream meal this week on the Off Menu podcast with James Acaster and Eddie Bagel Lonely.
Rent Hari’s documentary ‘The Problem with Apu’ on Amazon.
Follow Hari on Twitter: @harikondabolu
Recorded by Ben Williams and edited by Naomi Parnell for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 72: Michael McKean | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340167/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340167/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re cranking this episode up to 11 to welcome Michael McKean – star of ‘This Is Spinal Tap’, ‘A Mighty Wind’ and ‘Better Call Saul’ and all round comedy legend – into the dream restaurant.
Watch Michael McKean in ‘Breeders’ on Sky One and NOW TV.
Follow Michael McKean on Twitter: @MJMcKean
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 71: Amy Hoggart | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340168/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340168/</guid><description>Podcast Description ‘Almost Royal’s Poppy and Georgie are reunited! Ed’s former castmate and all-round ‘glutie cutie’ Amy Hoggart joins us in the dream restaurant – which, this week, is in New York City.
Watch ‘It’s Personal with Amy Hoggart’ on TruTV
Follow Amy Hoggart on Twitter: @amy_hoggart
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 70: Andi Oliver | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340169/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340169/</guid><description>Podcast Description Award-winning TV chef and ‘Great British Menu’ judge Andi Oliver makes an order at the dream restaurant and the Off Menu Cinematic Universe expands rapidly. So, what’s for dinner, mummy? (And, yes, she is Miquita Oliver’s mum.)
Andi Oliver’s Wadadli Kitchen ‘One Love’ pop-up opens at the Clapton Country Club in London on 20th August 2020. More info at wadadlikitchen.com
Watch ‘What’s For Dinner, Mummy?’ on Andi’s Instagram: @andioliver</description></item><item><title>Ep 69: Diane Morgan | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340170/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340170/</guid><description>Podcast Description Star of her own BBC Two sitcom ‘Mandy’ and Philomena Cunk herself Diane Morgan joins us in the dream restaurant this week. We’re thrilled, but is she?
Diane Morgan’s sitcom ‘Mandy’ starts on BBC Two, Thursday 13th August, 9.30pm, and will be on BBC iPlayer.
Follow Diane on Twitter: @missdianemorgan
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 68: Gok Wan | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340171/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340171/</guid><description>Podcast Description The genie wants to know how to look good naked, so we’ve invited Gok Wan for a dinner party – and it really is a party.
Gok Wan’s Easy Asian is on Mondays from 10th August, 8pm on Food Network and available on dplay
Follow Gok Wan on Twitter: @therealgokwan
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 67: Aparna Nancherla | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340172/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340172/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian and writer Aparna Nancherla has booked a table in the dream restaurant this week. And, finally, James’s Diet Coke story gets an upgrade.
Follow Aparna Nancherla on Twitter: @aparnapkin
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.
And go to our website www.offmenupodcast.co.uk for a list of restaurants recommended on the show.</description></item><item><title>Ep 66: Louis Theroux | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340173/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340173/</guid><description>Podcast Description Louis Theroux meets a genie and a maître d’ – now that’s a documentary we’d like to see. The filmmaker and author spends a weird weekend in the dream restaurant.
Louis Theroux’s book ‘Gotta Get Theroux This’ is out now in paperback – buy it here
Listen to Louis’s podcast, ‘Grounded with Louis Theroux’, on BBC Sounds, Apple Podcasts or wherever you get your podcasts
Follow Louis Theroux on Twitter @louistheroux and Instagram @officiallouistheroux</description></item><item><title>Ep 65: Romesh Ranganathan | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340174/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340174/</guid><description>Podcast Description The restaurant’s re-opened (with new Covid precautions) and the first guest of series 4 is Romesh Ranganathan! Romesh is in his garage, Ed's in his home and the genie’s in his lamp.
Listen to Romesh’s podcast ‘Hip Hop Saved My Life’ on Acast
Follow Romesh on Twitter and Instagram: @RomeshRanga
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Series 4 Trailer – Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340175/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340175/</guid><description>Podcast Description This restaurant’s a buffet, and we’re going up for a fourth helping. Series 4 starts Wednesday 15th July.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 64: Teri Hatcher | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340176/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340176/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s the final episode of the series, and what better for a season finale than our most prepared guest ever? Teri Hatcher – yes, Lois actual Lane and star of ‘Desperate Housewives’ – drops by the dream restaurant (/our Airbnb), orders her favourite meal and indulges Ed’s medieval chatter.
Follow Teri Hatcher on Twitter @HatchingChange and Instagram @officialterhatcher
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Ep 63: Jen Brister | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340177/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340177/</guid><description>Podcast Description Wonderful stand-up comedian and author Jen Brister joins us in the dream restaurant for the penultimate episode of series 3. Topics include Itsu orders, small plates etiquette and corn flower woes.
Follow Jen Brister on Twitter: @JenBrister
Buy Jen’s book ‘The Other Mother’ from Waterstones
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>#TheShowMustBePaused | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340178/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340178/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are not releasing an episode of Off Menu today.
In solidarity with protestors worldwide and the Black Lives Matter movement, instead use the time you would spend listening to us to donate, support and get educated.
Find resources, reading material and ways to donate at:
blacklivesmatters.carrd.co
theshowmustbepaused.com
blacklivesmatter.com
actblue.com/donate/bailfunds
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 62: Ivo Graham | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340179/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340179/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian, Eton alumnus and water fanatic Ivo Graham joins us in the dream restaurant. (And there’s a special cameo from Edward Easton.)
Follow Ivo Graham on Twitter: @ivograham
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.
And go to our website www.offmenupodcast.co.uk for a list of restaurants recommended on the show.</description></item><item><title>Ep 61: Reggie Watts | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340180/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340180/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s the most relaxed dream restaurant yet, as this week’s guest is Reggie Watts – comedian, musician and James Corden band leader. This episode was recorded on bean bags in Reggie’s LA studio.
Watch Reggie Watts’ Netflix special ‘Spatial’.
Follow Reggie on Twitter: @reggiewatts
Recorded by Ben Williams and edited by Naomi Parnell for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 60: Emily V Gordon | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340181/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340181/</guid><description>Podcast Description Academy Award nominee Emily V Gordon – co-writer of ‘The Big Sick’ – joins us in the dream restaurant on her visit to London town. And she has a cracking celeb story.
Watch ‘The Big Sick’ on Amazon Prime Video.
Listen to Emily’s podcast ‘Staying In with Emily &amp;amp; Kumail’ on Stitcher, Apple Podcasts, Acast and Spotify.
Follow Emily on Twitter: @emilyvgordon
Recorded by Ben Williams and edited by Naomi Parnell for Plosive Productions.</description></item><item><title>Ep 59: Roisin Conaty (Bonus Episode) | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340182/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340182/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s another lockdown live-streamed episode, with guest Roisin Conaty! WARNING: the sound quality is terrible. If you watched the live-stream you’ll know that, technically, it was a disaster. We’ve tried our best. It’s a bonus episode!
The live-stream was for the Cosmic Shambles Network’s Stay at Home Festival, which is raising money for artists who have had their entire livelihoods taken away by the pandemic. You can watch the full live-stream on YouTube here.</description></item><item><title>Ep 58: Susie Essman | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340183/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340183/</guid><description>Podcast Description Curb Your Enthusiasm star Susie Essman drops by the dream restaurant and Ed and James are hoping they get called fat f**ks.
Watch Susie Essman in Curb Your Enthusiasm on Sky Comedy and NOW TV.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.
And go to our website www.</description></item><item><title>Ep 57: Simon Rogan | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340184/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340184/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chef Simon Rogan – whose Lake District restaurant L’Enclume has two(!) Michelin stars – joins us in the dream restaurant this week. And the hangover trilogy is finally complete.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
For more info on Simon Rogan and his restaurants visit his website.
Follow Simon Rogan on Twitter: @simon_rogan
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 56: Jean Grae | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340185/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340185/</guid><description>Podcast Description The multitalented Jean Grae – NY-based musician, rapper, producer, actress – is this week’s guest. And there’s no real need for the dream restaurant, as Jean’s cooking everything.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Buy Jean Grae’s music on Bandcamp or listen on Spotify
Follow Jean Grae on Twitter: @JeanGreasy
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 55: Natasha Leggero and Moshe Kasher | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340186/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340186/</guid><description>Podcast Description So many firsts in this week’s LA-recorded episode with comedians Natasha Leggero and Moshe Kasher: our first married couple in the dream restaurant, the first competitive menus, and James’s first sip of coffee in god knows how long.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
For latest news from Natasha and Moshe visit natashaleggero.com and moshekasher.</description></item><item><title>Ep 54: Sam Carter | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340187/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340187/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ed’s not the only metalhead in the dream restaurant this week, as Sam Carter – lead singer of Architects – chooses his dream menu. And he proves the rule: the heavier the band, the more documentaries they watch.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Architects’ latest album ‘Holy Hell’ is out now.
Follow Sam Carter and Architects on Twitter: @samarchitects / @architectsuk</description></item><item><title>Ep 53: Richard Herring (Bonus Episode) | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340188/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340188/</guid><description>Podcast Description We live-streamed a very special lockdown episode of Off Menu with guest Richard Herring for the Cosmic Shambles Network’s Stay at Home Festival, which is raising money for artists who have had their entire livelihoods taken away by the pandemic.
You can watch the full live-stream on YouTube here. And, if you have the means to, please donate to the Stay at Home Festival fund here.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.</description></item><item><title>Ep 52: Sara Pascoe | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340189/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340189/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is the dream restaurant dog-friendly? It is now, as Sara Pascoe wants to bring her pooch for her magical meal.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Sara Pascoe’s book ‘Sex Power Money’ is out now, and listen to her podcast of the same name.
Follow Sara Pascoe on Twitter: @sarapascoe
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 51: Paul F. Tompkins | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340190/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340190/</guid><description>Podcast Description We’re in sunny Los Angeles and our first Hollywood guest is podcasting king and ‘Bojack Horseman’ star Paul F. Tompkins!
Recorded by Devon Bryant at Earwolf. Edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Listen to Paul F. Tompkins’s podcast ‘The Neighborhood Listen’ on Stitcher.
Follow Paul F. Tompkins on Twitter: @PFTompkins
Thanks to Earwolf for the studio space!</description></item><item><title>Ep 50: Joe Thomas | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340191/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340191/</guid><description>Podcast Description Joe Thomas – star of ‘The Inbetweeners’, ‘Taskmaster’ and play ‘What’s in a Name?’ that he does such a great job at promoting – takes a seat in the dream restaurant to order an emotional roller coaster of a meal.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Joe Thomas stars in ‘What’s in a Name?’ which is on tour.</description></item><item><title>Ep 49: Catherine Cohen | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340192/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340192/</guid><description>Podcast Description New York-based comedian and Edinburgh Best Newcomer winner Catherine Cohen invites Ed and James to her Manhattan apartment to record what is probably the most chaotic Off Menu yet.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Catherine Cohen brings her award-winning show ‘The Twist…? She’s Gorgeous!’ to Bush Hall, 11-13 March. Tickets here.
Catherine’s podcast ‘Seek Treatment’ is on Apple Podcasts or wherever you get your podcasts.</description></item><item><title>Ep 48: Arabella Weir | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340193/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340193/</guid><description>Podcast Description 'The Fast Show' star Arabella Weir drops in to the dream restaurant this week. Will she be ordering Posh Nosh?
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Arabella Weir is on tour with her show 'Does My Mum Loom Big In This?' – go to arabellaweir.co.uk for tour dates
Follow Arabella Weir on Twitter: @arabellaweir</description></item><item><title>Ep 47: Ronny Chieng | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340194/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340194/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Off Menu team are in NYC and this week’s guest – ‘The Daily Show’ correspondent Ronny Chieng – is worried about how we’re funding the trip.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Watch Ronny Chieng’s Netflix special ‘Asian Comedian Destroys America!’
For Ronny’s Melbourne food recommendations go to imokwithanything.com
Follow Ronny Chieng on Twitter (@ronnychieng) and Instagram (@ronnychieng).</description></item><item><title>Ep 46: Noah Schnapp | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340195/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340195/</guid><description>Podcast Description Uh oh, let’s hope the dream restaurant doesn’t get trapped in the Upside Down, because ‘Stranger Things’ star Noah Schnapp is this week’s guest. And this meal is fancy.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Noah Schnapp stars in ‘Waiting for Anya’ which is released in UK cinemas on Friday 21 February.
Follow Noah Schnapp on Twitter (@noah_schnapp) and Instagram (@noahschnapp).</description></item><item><title>Ep 45: Katherine Ryan | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340196/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340196/</guid><description>Podcast Description TV’s Katherine Ryan – the hardest working person in comedy – drops by the dream restaurant this week, and she’s brought gifts! What a couple of lucky boys.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Watch Katherine Ryan’s stand-up specials on Netflix.
Follow Katherine Ryan on Twitter @Kathbum.
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 44: Armando Iannucci | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340197/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340197/</guid><description>Podcast Description The genie waiter’s in the thick of it when Armando Iannucci requests a table. And the writer-director of ‘The Personal History of David Copperfield’ is not against pasta.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
‘The Personal History of David Copperfield’ is in cinemas now and ‘Avenue 5’ is on Sky One and NOW TV.</description></item><item><title>Ep 43: Anthony Head | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340198/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340198/</guid><description>Podcast Description After a brief renovation, the restaurant’s now open for series 3, and our first guest is national treasure and star of Netflix’s ‘The Stranger’ Anthony Head! And what a holy meal it is.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
All episodes of ‘The Stranger’ are on Netflix from January 30th. Watch here.
Follow Anthony Head on Twitter @AnthonySHead.</description></item><item><title>Series 3 Trailer – Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340199/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340199/</guid><description>Podcast Description The third course of Off Menu – the dessert course? – starts this Wednesday, 29th January 2020. Stay hungry!
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Best of 2019 | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340200/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340200/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's the end of the decade, and the end of the first year of Off Menu. It's time to reminisce and take a look back at the best bits of the podcast so far.
We'll be back for series 3 very soon – stay hungry!
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 42: Greg Davies (Christmas Special) | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340201/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340201/</guid><description>Podcast Description A second Christmas miracle! The Taskmaster himself Greg Davies joins us in the dream restaurant for another festive special. So let's start the meal with the well-known phrase, 'I'm hard, let's eat'.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Greg Davies on Twitter @gdavies.
Watch his sitcom 'Man Down' and his stand-up special 'You Magnificent Beast' on Netflix.</description></item><item><title>Ep 41: Joe Lycett (Christmas Special) | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340202/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340202/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's a Christmas miracle! Joe Lycett joins us in the dream restaurant for a surprise festive special. If these three formed a boyband they'd be called Glazing Squad.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Joe Lycett on Twitter @joelycett
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.
And go to our website www.offmenupodcast.co.uk for a list of restaurants recommended on the show.</description></item><item><title>Ep 40: Kumail Nanjiani | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340203/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340203/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's the last episode of series two! And what a treat we have for the season finale: Kumail Nanjiani – star of 'Silicon Valley', upcoming Marvel movie 'The Eternals' and the Oscar-nominated 'The Big Sick' – closes the series with his emotionally-dead meal.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Kumail Nanjiani on Twitter @kumailn</description></item><item><title>Ep 39: Mike Skinner | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340204/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340204/</guid><description>Podcast Description There's a table booked for The Streets frontman Mike Skinner this week. Will he pick plenty of scrambled eggs and plenty of fried tomato? Let's ask Carl Jung…
Recorded by Ben Williams and edited by Naomi Parnell for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Mike Skinner has new music coming soon. Follow Mike on Twitter: @MikeSkinnerLtd.
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 38: Kemah Bob | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340205/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340205/</guid><description>Podcast Description Texas-born stand-up Kemah Bob – who runs the FOC It Up Comedy Club – joins us in the dream restaurant this week. She likes honesty in the kitchen, James is hungover, and we ask: do genies jizz?
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Kemah Bob on Twitter and Instagram @kemahbob.
And find out more about the FOC It Up Comedy Club on Facebook.</description></item><item><title>Ep 37: Tom Allen | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340206/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340206/</guid><description>Podcast Description The always dapper Tom Allen – incredible comedian and host of 'Bake Off: The Professionals' and 'The Apprentice: You're Fired' – is this week's dinner guest. And boy oh boy does he have some shocking tales to tell. Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Tom Allen on Twitter @tomallencomedy and Instagram @tomindeed.
Watch Tom on 'The Apprentice: You're Fired', Wednesdays, 10pm, BBC Two.</description></item><item><title>Ep 36: Evelyn Mok | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340207/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340207/</guid><description>Podcast Description Swedish-raised, London-based comedian and podcaster Evelyn Mok has a table booked this week. Expect podcast firsts and a lot of talk of pee and poo (sorry).
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Evelyn co-hosts the Rice To Meet You podcast with Nigel Ng. Listen and subscribe on Apple Podcasts, Spotify and Audioboom.
Follow Evelyn on Twitter and Instagram: @EvelynMok.</description></item><item><title>Ep 35: Daisy May Cooper | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340208/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340208/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bafta-winning star of ‘This Country’ Daisy May Cooper is this week’s dinner guest. Buffet techniques are compared, the dark side of Rugrats is discussed, and the genie gets tricked. Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Daisy's book ‘This Is This Country’ is out now, published by Trapeze. Buy the book here.
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 34: Sophie Duker | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340209/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340209/</guid><description>Podcast Description Edinburgh Comedy Award Best Newcomer nominee Sophie Duker has a table booked this week. Tears flow, secrets are revealed and the rice battle continues. Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Sophie Duker's show 'Venus' is at London's Soho Theatre, 29 Oct-2 Nov. More info at sohotheatre.com.
Follow Sophie on Twitter: @sophiedukebox.
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 33: Jess Phillips MP | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340210/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340210/</guid><description>Podcast Description Order, order! The podcast gets political as MP Jess Phillips orders her dream meal. Will her menu get the genie's vote?
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Jess Phillips MP's new book, 'Truth to Power: 7 Ways to Call Time on B.S.', is out this week. Buy it here. Follow Jess on Twitter: @JessPhillips.</description></item><item><title>Ep 32: Catherine Bohart | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340211/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340211/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian Catherine Bohart – as seen on 'The Mash Report' and 'Roast Battle' – is in the dream restaurant this week. Things get rude, Catherine's meal is flipped on its head and the genie is hungover. Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Catherine Bohart plays the Soho Theatre in London, 30 Sep-5 Oct. Visit the Soho Theatre website for more details.</description></item><item><title>Off Menu supports #PODSTRIKE | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340212/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340212/</guid><description>Podcast Description Off Menu is supporting the global climate strike on Friday 20th September, organised by Greta Thunberg and the UK Student Climate Network.
Young people have woken up much of the world with their powerful Fridays for Future school strikes for the climate. As we deal with devastating climate breakdown and hurtle towards dangerous tipping points, young people are calling on millions of us across the planet to disrupt business as usual by joining the global climate strikes on September 20, just ahead of a UN emergency climate summit, and again on September 27.</description></item><item><title>Ep 31: Marcus Samuelsson | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340213/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340213/</guid><description>Podcast Description Top chef Marcus Samuelsson – the man behind Red Rooster in Harlem and Shoreditch, MARCUS Montreal and Marcus B&amp;amp;P – takes a break from the kitchen and lets the genie cook in the dream restaurant. And, for Samuelsson, location is key.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Red Rooster Shoreditch is now open – find out more here.</description></item><item><title>Ep 30: Cerys Matthews | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340214/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340214/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode could be a case for Mulder and Scully. Musician, 6 Music DJ and wild cook Cerys Matthews has a table booked in the dream restaurant.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Cerys Matthews's new book ‘Where the Wild Cooks Go’ is out now. Buy it here.
Cerys is also on tour – visit Penguin Live for more details.</description></item><item><title>Ep 29: Jay Rayner | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340215/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340215/</guid><description>Podcast Description Restaurant expert Jay Rayner – The Observer’s food critic, Masterchef judge and author of ‘My Last Supper’ – has a table booked this week. Ed has strong opinions about Jay's dessert, James doesn’t understand jokes and Jay suggests he invented the podcast.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Footsteps by Lauren.
Jay Rayner’s new book ‘My Last Supper’ is out this week.</description></item><item><title>Ep 28: Serge Pizzorno | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340216/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340216/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sergio Pizzorno – aka Serge from Kasabian, aka the SLP – orders his dream meal this week. Let's just hope there are no magicians nearby…
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Serge's debut solo album, 'The SLP', is released this week. Buy the album here.
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.
And go to our website www.</description></item><item><title>Ep 27: Jordan Banjo | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340217/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340217/</guid><description>Podcast Description 'Diversity' dancer Jordan Banjo is this week's diner, and he's the restaurant's jumpiest guest yet. Plus James gets another new nickname.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
See Jordan in Diversity's 10th Anniversary Tour. For tickets visit Ticketmaster.
Follow Jordan on Twitter: @Jordan_Banjo
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.
And go to our website www.</description></item><item><title>Ep 26: Kerry Godliman | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340218/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340218/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kerry Godliman – 'Taskmaster' champion and 'Derek' star – pops in to the dream restaurant this week. We're off on holiday to eat this meal, but James has forgotten to tell Kerry something. Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
See Kerry Godliman in 'After Life' on Netflix, check out her website www.kerrygodliman.com, and follow her on Twitter @KerryAGodliman.</description></item><item><title>Ep 25: Loyle Carner | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340219/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340219/</guid><description>Podcast Description Loyle Carner – Mercury-nominated hip hop artist – orders his dream meal this week. He talks about his Chilli Con Carner cookery school for teenagers with ADHD, Ed opens up about his relationship and James gets angry about an Oscar winner.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Loyle Carner is touring the UK throughout October and November.</description></item><item><title>Ep 24: Sian Clifford | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340220/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340220/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emmy-nominated 'Fleabag' star Sian Clifford picks her dream meal this week. Loopholes are exploited, there's a detailed water order, and James tells a very boring story. Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Sian Clifford on Twitter @SiansUniverse and Instagram @SiansStillSpace
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.
And go to our website www.</description></item><item><title>Ep 23: Dynamo | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340221/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340221/</guid><description>Podcast Description The genie has some conjuring competition this week as the restaurant welcomes its first magician guest – it's Dynamo! Plus there's an update on Ed's superpowers and James gets a new nickname.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Follow Dynamo on Twitter and Instagram: @DynamoMagician
www.dynamomagician.com
Follow Off Menu on Twitter and Instagram: @offmenuofficial.</description></item><item><title>Ep 22: Suzi Ruffell | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340222/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340222/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week's guest is stand-up sensation (and regular eating buddy of Ed and James) Suzi Ruffell! We're asking the big questions – like why don't athletes drink sparkling water? – and a new tongue-twister is created. Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Suzi Ruffell is performing at the Edinburgh Fringe in August and is touring the UK in the autumn.</description></item><item><title>Ep 21: Dara O Briain | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340223/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340223/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's the grand re-opening of the magical restaurant, and our first guest in Series 2 is Dara O Briain! Not only does the 'Mock the Week' host talk us through his dream meal, he gets even with Aisling Bea and explains what helps him write all those jokes.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography and design) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Series 2 Trailer – Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340224/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340224/</guid><description>Podcast Description New series, new menus. The magical restaurant is back in business and ready for bookings. Series 2 starts 10th July 2019.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Ep 20: Rose McGowan | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340225/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340225/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the final episode of the series, Rose McGowan – actor, activist, author and model – orders her dream meal. And, when it comes to food, she has superpowers…
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography) and Amy Browne (illustrations)
Rose McGowan's book 'Brave' is available now. Buy it here.
Ed Gamble records his special at the Leicester Square Theatre on 12 May.</description></item><item><title>Ep 19: Gemma Cairney | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340226/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340226/</guid><description>Podcast Description We welcome Gemma Cairney – BBC radio DJ, author and presenter – to the dream restaurant this week. And it's not just a meal, it's a party.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography) and Amy Browne (illustrations)
Listen to Gemma Cairney's BBC podcast 'The Leisure Society'.
Ed Gamble records his special at the Leicester Square Theatre on 12 May. See the Leicester Square Theatre website for details.</description></item><item><title>Ep 18: Desiree Burch | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340227/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340227/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week's guest is comedian Desiree Burch – star of Netflix's upcoming 'Flinch'. The podcast gets hacked, Desiree knows the way to James's heart, and we find out what's in the dream restaurant's bathroom.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography) and Amy Browne (illustrations)
Desiree Burch stars in 'Flinch' which comes to Netflix soon, and she has a new special on Comedy Central in the near future.</description></item><item><title>Ep 17: Victoria Coren Mitchell | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340228/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340228/</guid><description>Podcast Description Victoria Coren Mitchell – 'Only Connect' host, writer and professional poker player – is this week's diner. She gets introduced to teddy bear ham, talks very British holidays and reveals her dinner party secret. Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography) and Amy Browne (illustrations)
'Only Connect' is on BBC Two, Mondays, 7.30pm. Ed Gamble is on tour. See his website for full details.</description></item><item><title>Ep 16: Jamie Demetriou | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340229/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340229/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jamie Demetriou – comedian, actor and writer extraordinaire – has booked a table this week. His meal's so good, not even a marmalade sandwich made by Paddington himself makes the cut. Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography) and Amy Browne (illustrations)
You can watch Jamie Demetriou's excellent sitcom 'Stath Lets Flats' on All 4 and look out for series 2 on Channel 4 later this year.</description></item><item><title>Ep 15: Sindhu Vee | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340230/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340230/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week's guest is Sindhu Vee – Edinburgh Comedy Award-nominated stand-up, Radio 4 regular and Live at the Apollo star. When it comes to food, she knows what she wants. And, yet again, Ed makes some vulgar jokes.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography) and Amy Browne (illustrations)
Sindhu Vee is currently on tour. Check out www.sindhuvee.com for info and tickets.</description></item><item><title>Ep 14: Jack McBrayer | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340231/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340231/</guid><description>Podcast Description We welcome '30 Rock's Jack McBrayer – the most polite man in showbusiness – to the restaurant this week. James tells a sexy story, Ed cracks some crass jokes and Jack has a lot of foods explained to him.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography) and Amy Browne (illustrations)
Jack McBrayer is currently starring in the musical 'Waitress' at the Aldephi Theatre in London's West End.</description></item><item><title>Ep 13: Phil Wang | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340232/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340232/</guid><description>Podcast Description 'Taskmaster' star Phil Wang – everyone's favourite Wang – visits the restaurant this week. Let's just hope he doesn't roast Ed again.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography) and Amy Browne (illustrations)
Check out Phil Wang's latest live dates are philwang.co.uk.
Ed Gamble is on tour. See his website for full details.
James Acaster is on tour. See his website for full details.</description></item><item><title>Ep 12: Josie Long | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340233/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340233/</guid><description>Podcast Description Comedian, filmmaker and James's former boss Josie Long visits the restaurant this week. The genie's on his best behaviour, Ed definitely isn't into tantric sex, and everyone has a lot of fun telling dad jokes.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography) and Amy Browne (illustrations)
Josie Long is on tour with Jonny &amp;amp; The Baptists and Grace Petrie with The Lefty Scum tour.</description></item><item><title>Ep 11: Krishnan Guru-Murthy | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340234/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340234/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have we got NEWS for you! Channel 4's Krishnan Guru-Murthy orders his dream meal this week. Ed and James introduce the newsreader to a popular fast food, James realises he's been mispronouncing a drink and Ed learns how to wash a paella pan.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography) and Amy Browne (illustrations)
Krishnan Guru-Murthy's podcast 'Ways to Change the World' is on Apple Podcasts, Acast, Spotify and all the others.</description></item><item><title>Ep 10: Lou Sanders | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340235/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340235/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hugely talented comedian Lou Sanders chooses her dream meal this week. Well, she struggles to choose. Can she take some of the heat off Joel Dommett?
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography) and Amy Browne (illustrations)
Lou Sanders’s acclaimed show ‘Shame Pig’ plays London’s Soho Theatre, 25-28 Feb, and she’s on tour from 24 Feb till 5 June. Check her website for details.</description></item><item><title>Ep 9: Selasi Gbormittah | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340236/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340236/</guid><description>Podcast Description Oh boy, Selasi Gbormittah – ‘The Great British Bake Off’s most relaxed contestant ever – is this week’s guest. But before getting to dessert he picks his favourite savoury dishes. Plus James gives a burger chain a kicking, Ed talks marathon prep and Selasi’s surprised by a well-known fact of life.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography) and Amy Browne (illustrations)</description></item><item><title>Ep 8: Tom Kerridge | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340237/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340237/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's the magical restaurant's first chef guest! The Michelin-starred Tom Kerridge orders his dream meal. Will he stick to his healthy regime, or will it be an 'off day'? We also learn more about the genie waiter's backstory and James tries to embarrass Ed in some *bonus content* – so keep listening until the end.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography) and Amy Browne (illustrations)</description></item><item><title>Ep 7: Lolly Adefope | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340238/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jan 2019 04:00:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340238/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, there’s a table ready for talented comedian and actor Lolly Adefope. Comfort food is the order of the day, we learn about Ed’s teenage wine hobby and – FINALLY – a debate happens on: who has the best fries?
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography) and Amy Browne (illustrations)
Lolly Adefope has roles in two US TV shows coming out this year: ‘Miracle Workers’ on TBS starting 12 February and ‘Shrill’ on Hulu streaming 15 March.</description></item><item><title>Ep 6: Joel Dommett | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340239/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340239/</guid><description>Podcast Description Handsome boy Joel Dommett – off of Netflix and ‘I’m a Celeb…’ – orders his dream meal this week. Or does he? Ed and James aren’t too happy about his choices…
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography) and Amy Browne (illustrations)
Watch Joel’s stand-up special on Netflix in ‘Comedians of the World’ and follow him on Twitter @JoelDommett.
Ed Gamble is on tour in 2019.</description></item><item><title>Ep 5: Aisling Bea | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340240/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340240/</guid><description>Podcast Description Not only does Aisling Bea order her dream meal, the comedian and actor treats the restaurant to Hollywood anecdotes and introduces us to rappers Yung Coconut, Big Gulp and Tiny Bites.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography) and Amy Browne (illustrations)
Watch Aisling’s stand-up on Netflix in ‘The Comedy Line-Up’ and follow her on Twitter @WeeMissBea.
Ed Gamble is on tour in 2019.</description></item><item><title>Ep 4: Nish Kumar (Christmas Special) | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340241/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Dec 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340241/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's Boxing Day, we're feeling festive, and everyone's best friend Nish Kumar has popped in to order his favourite Christmas meal. Plus we need your help to #BringBackKumarsCobbler
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography) and Amy Browne (illustrations).
Nish Kumar is on tour in 2019 starting 25 January. See his website for full details.
Ed Gamble is on tour in 2019.</description></item><item><title>Ep 3: Richard Osman | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340242/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340242/</guid><description>Podcast Description Richard Osman – off of ‘Pointless’, ‘House of Games’ and ‘Taskmaster’ – is this week’s guest, bringing with him fascinating food thoughts and memories. Plus, he picks on Ed and picks holes in the format.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography) and Amy Browne (illustrations)
Follow Richard Osman on Twitter: @richardosman.
Ed Gamble is on tour in 2019. See his website for full details.</description></item><item><title>Ep 2: Grace Dent | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340243/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340243/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ordering their dream menu this week is the Guardian's restaurant critic Grace Dent, so the pressure's really on for the genie waiter. The food writer talks to Ed Gamble and James Acaster about the tastiest things she's ever eaten, how the other half dine and what the chef really means when they say they're 'playful'.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography) and Amy Browne (illustrations)</description></item><item><title>Ep 1: Scroobius Pip | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340244/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340244/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's the grand opening of the magical restaurant and the first guest through the doors is Mr Podcast himself, Scroobius Pip. The rapper, podcaster, actor and record label owner talks Ed Gamble and James Acaster through his dream meal, gives advice on pizza hut thriftiness and introduces his own food invention, the Meadsy Base.
Recorded and edited by Ben Williams for Plosive Productions.
Artwork by Paul Gilbey (photography) and Amy Browne (illustrations).</description></item><item><title>Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster – Trailer | Off Menu with Ed Gamble and James Acaster</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3609340245/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 18:12:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3609340245/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to the restaurant. Take a seat. May we take your coat? Ed Gamble and James Acaster introduce their brand new podcast Off Menu.
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>