<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Therapy Crouch on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/the-therapy-crouch/</link><description>Recent content in The Therapy Crouch on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 06:30:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/the-therapy-crouch/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Therapy Crouch Guide To Christmas Gifting | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720001/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 06:30:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Abbey and Pete join forces with Klarna for this special edition of The Therapy Crouch, packed full of tips and tricks (plus the odd fail from Pete) for gifting and hosting this Christmas.&amp;nbsp;
&amp;nbsp;
What’s Pete’s tried and tested present buying strategy? What has Abbey got in store for him over the festive period? And who is the real grinch of the Clancy / Crouch household
Hosted on Acast.</description></item><item><title>The Therapy Crouch made some new friends....and they do not disappoint | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 06:30:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720002/</guid><description>Podcast Description The moment you’ve all been waiting for has finally arrived! The Therapy Crouch has waited almost a year for this very special moment and boy was it worth it…
This week, we are joined by fellow podcasters and new best friends, James Buckley and Clair Buckley!&amp;nbsp;
It’s fair to say that this is a bit of a milestone for the podcast and nothing was off the table in this no holds barred chat, from how to pity a girl into bed to James’ truly teeth woes.</description></item><item><title>'Tis The Season | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720003/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 02:30:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720003/</guid><description>Podcast Description As Christmas approachs Pete and Abbey are getting into the festive spirit, by discussing their holiday joys and pet peeves from Christmas prep to how to do presents. After a trip to Bicester Village this week, Pete and Ab discuss each others contradicting shopping styles.
With plenty of your Agony Ab's and Weekly Whines we are back to give you fantastic(ish) advice. To contact us: Email: thetherapycrouch@gmail.com Instagram: https://www.</description></item><item><title>When good intentions backfire SPECTACULARLY | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 06:30:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720004/</guid><description>Podcast Description After their recent break away from the kids to ‘disconnect and reconnect’ Abbey and Pete are back with tales of when even the best of intentions can backfire with hilarious results.&amp;nbsp;
Thailand in the depths of monsoon season? Sounds like the perfect opportunity for Abbey to tear through three books and avoid talking to Pete at all costs…&amp;nbsp;
In our weekly whine (or shine) club, we hear from a couple who have had the picture perfect proposal in nowhere else than the big apple itself as well as a woman who is convinced her husband has taken up whistling as a full time hobby just to drive her round the bend.</description></item><item><title>Surprise, Surprise | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720005/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 06:30:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ahead of Pete’s long anticipated surprise holiday for him and Abbey, the pair sit down to talk about some of the more memorable - and even more forgettable - surprises they’ve pulled off for each other.&amp;nbsp;
Not wanting to be outdone by the Therapy Crouch team, we also hear from our listeners who have provided some of their best and worse surprises over the year, from days out being a zookeeper to spiteful exes with a taste for Bridget Jones.</description></item><item><title>Therapy Crouchfest | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720006/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 06:30:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720006/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s episode of The Therapy Crouch, Abbey and Peter take a while to take stock ofter the roaring success that was Crouchfest.&amp;nbsp;
Never ones to take themselves too seriously, the gang talk all things fancy dress, gameshow parodies, music and everything in between.&amp;nbsp;
Abbey also gives insight into their ‘Sunday Monday’ experience - a rare treat when the house is normally jam packed with four kids.&amp;nbsp;
In the Agony Abs, we hear from a listener who is feeling pressured into going on a rather expensive family group holiday as well as a young couple who are struggling to decide if they want to have another baby, secure their nest or blow it all on the big day!</description></item><item><title>Here comes the Bride(maid) | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720007/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 06:30:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720007/</guid><description>Podcast Description It has been a big week for Abbey - she finally popped her bridesmaid’s cherry for none other than her BFF Holly.&amp;nbsp;
But before they spill the beans on the wedding of the year, they reminisce on what has been a rather eventful week. From halloween face paint fails to a Geoff Clancy fashion faux pas there is plenty to be unravelled here.&amp;nbsp;
Abbey and Pete also take a surprising detour from the pod topic and reminisce on some of their school school day pranks and performances which brings a lot of happy memories flooding back.</description></item><item><title>Happy Halloween!! | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720008/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 06:30:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Keeping in the spirit of the spookiest day of the year, Abbey and Peter have donned their best outfits and are talking all things fright night.&amp;nbsp;
Before delving into everything that gives them the heebie jeebies though, we have a recap on what could have potentially been the best week of Abbey’s life……so far.&amp;nbsp;
There is some big name dropping in this week’s podcast, with Madonna, Frankie Dettori, Mick Hucknall of Simply Rouge and Mr Micky Mouse himself all getting honourable mentions.</description></item><item><title>Mischief Week | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720009/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 05:30:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720009/</guid><description>Podcast Description It is a one week countdown to Halloween and in honour of the Scouse tradition of Mizzy night, Abbey and Peter are getting their spook on!
Fresh off the back of her first ever hen do - Abbey has had her own mischief weekend away with the girls and has left Pete to a weekend of paw patrol performances with the little ones.&amp;nbsp;
The pair also reminisce on some of their old antics around the spookiest time of year - eggs-be-athrowin and apples-be-adunkin!</description></item><item><title>I AM NOT A FISH | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720010/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 05:30:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Tuesday! With the official Therapy Crouch book now on sale, Abbey and Peter have had a busy week of promo, sitting down on the one show couch, this morning and anywhere else that will have them.&amp;nbsp;
For this reason, we sat down in a hotel in London which shared an uncanny resemblance to a budget Chinese restaurant/brothel.&amp;nbsp;
This week, Abbey and Pete are talking about how they are currently trying to reconnect with one another.</description></item><item><title>Guilty Pleasures | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720011/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720011/</guid><description>Podcast Description After the ribena-gate of last week, tune in to see if Ralphie made it to a second week in the Crouch family household.&amp;nbsp;
This week, the Abbey and Peter are chatting about all things guilty pleasures. After hearing about a recent TikTok trend, Abbey is desperate to stay down with the kids and expose all the things that men secretly love but hate to admit, what could go wrong….</description></item><item><title>Doggystyle | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 16:42:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720012/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s pod, Peter finally admits his love love for the young pup!! As expected, Abbey is less than magnanimous in success but there is no love lost between the pair.&amp;nbsp;
In the weekly whine club, one of our golf widow listeners has been in touch, much to the detriment of the big man, and we also hear from a young scaffolder who’s struggling to enjoy a day evening off even on a cold wet Tuesday underneath the spotlights.</description></item><item><title>The Therapy Crouch Guide To Better Holidays | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 05:30:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720013/</guid><description>Podcast Description British Airways Holidays are making it so much easier to enjoy your holidays without the stress. All their holidays are ATOL protected, they offer a 24hr helpline should you need them when you’re away and allow you to book with a low deposit. You can enjoy flexible payments until you fly*, and can even use Avios points towards your holiday too! Plus, all their holidays include a 23kg baggage allowance per person, so no surprises when you book.</description></item><item><title>Role Models | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720014/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 05:30:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Abbey and Peter are back with a bang this week where they sit down and discuss some of the big influences they have had in their lives that have helped them get where they are today.&amp;nbsp;
We hear about some of their favourite school teachers, parents and family members which are often the unsung heroes of people’s success!&amp;nbsp;
In weekly whine club, Abbey’s obsession with the new cavapoo, Optimus, is already driving Pete to the edge of insanity before it has arrived but Abbey is in no mood to take any of his SH*T.</description></item><item><title>Love Thy House | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 05:30:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Abbey and Peter sit down this week and talk all things grand designs. Abbey is well known for her love of a pet project/doer upper and is on hand to give some top tips on how to spruce up your interiors without breaking the bank!&amp;nbsp;
Pete also has some very interesting suggestions on how he would improve their current home and relives some childhood fantasies when weighing up the idea of creating a soft play area for the kids.</description></item><item><title>Back to School! | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 05:30:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720016/</guid><description>Podcast Description With term time back upon us, Abbey and Peter sit down to reflect on their summer holidays and their mixed emotions now that the little ones have gone back to school.&amp;nbsp;
The gang have some tips on how to get back into the swing of things if you have fallen out of routine and some other pearls of wisdom on how to make the most of your time away from the kids.</description></item><item><title>Holiday Ep Pt 2 | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720017/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 05:30:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720017/</guid><description>Podcast Description We are back and live from sunny Portugal with the gang discussing all things fashion!&amp;nbsp;
Abbey is on hand to give some tips on how to bring your man up from a strong 4 to a 6.5, and Pete spills the beans on how to achieve the Amalfi coast-chic look he has been known to rock.&amp;nbsp;
We also learn of the perils of drinking tap water and Pete has some very questionable Dad jokes that make an appearance.</description></item><item><title>Moving Abroad | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720018/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 01:00:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720018/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s Therapy Crouch, Abbey and Peter take a trip down memory lane and go on holiday to where The Therapy Crouch began.
If you could move abroad where would you go and why? Would you move to a quiet American raunch? Or would you prefer a beautiful house secluded in a Spanish mountain range? Today Peter &amp;amp; Abbey discuss their preferences on where they could move to and the countries which are on their travel list.</description></item><item><title>Bonus: Abbey Almost Gets The Boot | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720019/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 10:54:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720019/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this extra special episode of the pod, courtesy of Acast Creative and WhatsApp from Meta, Abbey and Pete switch phones and dive deep into their chats. Golf gets cancelled, Pete wins the &amp;ldquo;Champion&amp;rsquo;s Shield&amp;rdquo; and Abbey almost get’s the boot. So get comfy, enjoy the episode, and remember to lock your chats!!!
Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Beige Flags | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720020/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 05:30:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720020/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s Therapy Crouch, Abbey and Peter are discussing one of the hottest new TikTok trends that is….Beige Flags.&amp;nbsp;
Does your boyfriend rely on a waiter’s recommendations to make his food choices? Or ever found yourself on a date with someone who uses well known sayings in slightly the wrong context? Well you are not alone! Today the gang go through some of the most well known beige flags around as well as some of their own for each other.</description></item><item><title>And they call it, Puppy Love | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720021/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 05:30:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720021/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s episode of The Therapy Crouch, Abbey and Peter are discussing all things young love.&amp;nbsp;
With their own daughter approaching dating age, the gang reflect on some of their own young love experiences. Abbey reminisces on getting caught telling porky pies so she could sneak out without a chaperone whilst Pete cringes at some of his Dad’s antics when he was young and on the pull.&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>To Dream The Impossible Dream | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720022/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 05:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720022/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s Therapy Crouch, Abbey and Peter take a while to sit down and discuss some of their dreams and aspirations both as a pair of youngsters and now as one of the UK’s most prominent power couples.&amp;nbsp;
We hear about Abbey’s early days in Genie Queen -&amp;nbsp;Liverpool’s answer to the Sugababes - and a young football protege with dreams of scoring 100 premier league goals and becoming the nation’s Podfather in the process.</description></item><item><title>Freaky Friday | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 07:17:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720023/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s Therapy Crouch, Abbey and Peter embrace their inner Jamie Lee Curtis and Lindsey Lohan and ponder one of life’s great questions…..what would you do if you found yourself in a Freaky Friday situation?&amp;nbsp;
They look at which one of their heroes they would most like to switch with, what would be the first thing they’d do if they found themselves in the other’s body (parental guidance advised) and Peter answers a very tricky question regarding his mum and Abbey’s own Freaky Friday experience.</description></item><item><title>The Language of Love | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720024/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 05:30:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720024/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome back to this week’s Therapy Crouch! Today Abbey and Peter are on the couch to talk about their respective ‘love languages’&amp;nbsp;
If the terms ‘Words of Affirmation, Gift giving, Touch, Acts of Service, and Quality Time’ leave you feeling a bit confuddled then have no fear we have got you covered.&amp;nbsp;
Abbey’s questionable math skills are also called into question after one of our dear listeners writes in to celebrate one of his wife’s recent achievements as well as what to do when your best friend wants to order dominoes for their wedding breakfast.</description></item><item><title>Friends with (no) benefits | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720025/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 05:30:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720025/</guid><description>Podcast Description ADVISORY CONTENT WARNING: Unfortunately, our mics dropped out for the last 10 mins of this week’s episode so we apologise for the last 5 minutes…
Welcome to this week’s episode of the Therapy Crouch!
This week, Abbey has had some life affirming news and it has encouraged the gang to discuss all things friendship group related.&amp;nbsp;
Ever found yourself stuck with a talkative boring Norman at a wedding? Or had the dreaded experience of when two of your close friends split up and you don’t know which one to keep?</description></item><item><title>The Roaring 30's | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720026/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 05:30:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720026/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s episode of The Therapy Crouch we have some big news…….
Our book The Therapy Crouch: In Search of a Happy (N)Ever After is out on October 12th. To preorder your copy got to https://lnk.to/therapycrouch where you will find links to a limited number of signed copies, the audio book and more.
In the rest of the podcast, Abbey and Peter are on hand to discuss how to handle turning the big 3 0!</description></item><item><title>Glasto...Part 2 | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720027/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 05:30:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720027/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s the one you have all been waiting for! After a rather hectic Glastonbury experience, a slightly worse for wear Therapy Crouch is here to dish the dirt on what went down at Worthy Farm.&amp;nbsp;
The gang battle through some rather self-inflicted hangovers and lift the lid on their Glastonbury experience - expect a lot of Elton John chat, Abbey’s step count and the avoidance of the dreaded long drop….</description></item><item><title>Father's Day | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720028/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 05:30:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Tuesday! On this week’s Therapy Crouch, Abbey and Peter sit down and have a chat about their recent Father’s Day festivities, with Pete having put in a slightly underwhelming performance on Mother’s Day, is it likely Abbey pulled out all the stops for him this year? There is only one way to find out!&amp;nbsp;
To kick things off, Abbey and Peter share with us some of their favourite Dad jokes (that’s rubbish jokes, not jokes about Dads, Peter)&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>Glastonbury...Part 1 | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720029/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome back to The Therapy Crouch! This week, your favourite couple take a sit down to spill the beans on all their Glastonbury planning and preparations. We have got some interesting ideas on how we can help Pete go incognito in the crowd (wig suggestions welcome) and Abbey gives a breakdown on how she is going to give Sir Elton John himself a run for his money when it comes to outfit changes.</description></item><item><title>T’is the (birthday) season | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720030/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 05:00:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720030/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s your favourite time of the week again! Today, Abbey and Peter are back on The Therapy Crouch to discuss their very busy birthday scheduling, Spring has certainly sprung!&amp;nbsp;
Off the back of a rather large weekend in her hometown of Liverpool its safe to say the pair are still feeling slightly worse for wear but the main question is was it all worth it? We will let you be the judge.</description></item><item><title>The Rulebreakers | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720031/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 05:00:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720031/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s episode of The Therapy Crouch, Abbey and Peter discuss their differing attitudes when it comes to parenting styles - expect fun dad and house management vibes.&amp;nbsp;
And it isn’t just Abbey and Pete’s parenting styles that we get a glimpse into, but you guys as well! We hear from a couple whose attempts at confiscating their child’s Peppa Pig tablet backfired with some hilarious results.&amp;nbsp;</description></item><item><title>They Call Me The Godfather | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720032/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 05:00:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome back to The Therapy Crouch! On this week’s episode Abbey and Peter are on hand to share some pearls of wisdom on what makes a good godparent, and some top tips on how to expertly navigate a thanks but no thanks conversation with your nearest and dearest.&amp;nbsp;
In Agony Ab, Abbey and Peter are on hand to help when your better half suddenly decides to take up the gym 10 years too late and we hear from Louis, one of our international listeners who needs some advice on how to make the first move!</description></item><item><title>Sticky Icky | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720033/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 05:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720033/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s episode of The Therapy Crouch, there is no messing around in the Crouch family household as Abbey and Peter lift the lid on some of their biggest icks.&amp;nbsp;
For those of you unfamiliar with the term, an ick, as described by Urban Dictionary is:&amp;nbsp;
‘Something someone does that is an&amp;nbsp;instant&amp;nbsp;turn-off for you, making you&amp;nbsp;instantly hate the&amp;nbsp;idea of being with them romantically.’
And boy, have we got some icks for you….</description></item><item><title>The Power Shift | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720034/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 05:00:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720034/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s episode of The Therapy Crouch, Abbey and Peter take a little revisit one of the more contentious topics from a previous episode - the power shift that happens when a couple decides to put a ring on it.&amp;nbsp;
With Pete claiming that golf trips and nights out with the lads swiftly becomes a thing of the past, Abbey decides to call bullsh*t….big time.&amp;nbsp;
With the help of you, the listener, Abbey also decides to put together her own ‘Good Househusband Guide’ with some do’s and don’s included if you want to maintain your happy wife, happy life.</description></item><item><title>Youth is Wasted on the Young | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720035/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720035/</guid><description>Podcast Description It’s your favourite part of the week again! Therapy Crouch is back with a bang and this week Abbey and Peter lift the lid on some of their misspent youth activities.&amp;nbsp;
Expect tales of underage discos enough to whip you up into a FRENZY and lessons how not to pull a sicky when you are battling your first hangover.&amp;nbsp;
Agony Ab is on hand to provide some much needed guidance and comic relief for what to do when your husband has some interesting locations he likes to spend a penny or, even worse, thinks they’re the next Whitney Houston.</description></item><item><title>Runway Ready | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720036/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 04:00:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720036/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s episode of The Therapy Crouch, by popular demand, Abbey opens the door on what helped shape her career as one of Britain’s Next Top Models.&amp;nbsp;
It’s safe to say this journey was not all plain sailing, with plenty of high points, low points and laughs along the way.&amp;nbsp;
We also hear Pete’s opinions on the change in power dynamic once you put a ring on it and why ‘Airport Ab’ is a force to be reckoned with on a family holiday.</description></item><item><title>Half Term from Hell | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720037/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 04:00:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Happy Therapy Crouch release day! In this week’s episode Abbey and Peter talk about their rather eventful Easter break spent with their nearest and dearest….as well as their four kids.&amp;nbsp;
With Pete pondering why the little ones get such a long time off for Easter when Jesus himself only took 3 days, Abbey lets loose on some of their less-than-wholesome strolls in the park and trips to the beach.</description></item><item><title>Keeping Up Appearances | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720038/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 04:00:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720038/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today's episode of The Therapy Crouch, Abbey and Peter are recovering from their recent getaway for a friend's 30th birthday party.&amp;nbsp;
Having friend's 10-15 years younger than you when you're approaching the wrong side of 40 clearly takes it toll. Although we do hear about how hangover days without kids running round the house can hit another level as well as the tricks and techniques you can do to keep up with the young ones.</description></item><item><title>Calm Down, Calm Down | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720039/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 04:00:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720039/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s episode of the Therapy Crouch, we are going full Scouse power and taking a look at Abbey’s Liverpudlian roots.&amp;nbsp;
In Weekly Whine Club, we hear how Mother’s Day in casa de Crouch went down (expect some fireworks) and the extraordinary lengths Peter has to go to for a simple slice of chocolate in his own home.&amp;nbsp;
Abbey also gives a crash course in some of her favourite Scouse lingo and we learn why should never call someone’s meat antwacky.</description></item><item><title>Neurotic Parents | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720040/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 04:04:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720040/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s episode of the Therapy Crouch, Abbey and Peter discuss their differing parent styles…what could go wrong?&amp;nbsp;
We also hear about their recent appearance on the Jonathan Ross show and why there seems to be a huge problem with rimming in the Crouch household.&amp;nbsp;
Agony Ab is also back with a bang giving some great and some not so great advice out to you, our dear listeners.</description></item><item><title>The Doctor Will See You Now | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720041/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 23:15:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720041/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a slight change of gear for the Therapy Crouch team, Abbey and Peter sit&amp;nbsp;down with Natali Kelly and Dr Jeffrey Braithwaite to discuss endometriosis - a condition which affects 1 in 10 women - during national Endometriosis awareness month.&amp;nbsp;
Discover more about the symptoms and treatments of the disease and how we can all do more to raise awareness.&amp;nbsp;
In Agony Ab, we learn about the perils of watching a blue movie with your phone connected to the family bluetooth speaker, and why you should always leave the lights on when going for a midnight pee at your new in-laws house.</description></item><item><title>Top O’ the Mornin to Ya | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720042/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 00:15:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720042/</guid><description>Podcast Description In honour of St Patrick, the Therapy Crouch goes international and takes the team too Dublin.&amp;nbsp;
Expect plenty of Guinness, Irish stew and questionable footwear chat.&amp;nbsp;
In Agony Ab, we hear from one of our listeners whose boyfriend’s hairline is in desperate need of a trip to Turkey, and learn why Bondi Rescue and Home and Away may not be the best research tools used if you are planning to emigrate to Australia.</description></item><item><title>The Big Day | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720043/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 00:38:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720043/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s episode we finally get an invite to the celebrity wedding event of the year - albeit 12 years too late.&amp;nbsp;
Abbey, being a trend setter as always, is rocking a what she describes as a ‘Unitard’ but Peter more aptly labels as a giant baby grow.&amp;nbsp;
We hear about Pete’s questionable decision making on the eve of his big day and why you should never let a bunch of scousers near your wedding day golf buggy.</description></item><item><title>Wedding Planning | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720044/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:05:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720044/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s episode, we get an exclusive invite to the planning behind the wedding of the decade. From pre match nerves, to Elton John’s florist - learn more about the planning of the most important day of Abbey’s life (and probably Pete’s as well).&amp;nbsp;
We also hear how Abbey feels how she has made a load of new friends since starting the podcast and why Peter is still struggling to show his face in the bakery after THAT famous incident.</description></item><item><title>Will You Marry Me? | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720045/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 00:15:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720045/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Abbey and Peter provide a schooling session on how to nail the perfect proposal (spoiler: It does not involve chemtrails) Weekly Whine club is also back, with Abbey and Peter going a bit more upmarket to celebrate the roaring success that is The Therapy Crouch! We learn why you can't trust Abbey to keep a clean car and how Peter is considering taking up a career modelling fake tan.</description></item><item><title>I WANT BONO! | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720046/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 10:08:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720046/</guid><description>Podcast Description On today’s episode, Abbey and Peter shed light on all the things they have in common, from nights in watching boxsets to nights out on the tiles.... and even their taste in men. The pair also bond over their shared appreciation for all things Bono and Barry from Eastenders. In the Weekly Whine Club, we learn why having a Victoria Secret’s model as a wife may not be as glamorous as it sounds and, rather ironically, that poor punctuality is one of Abbey’s pet hates.</description></item><item><title>The Holiday Episode | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720047/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 00:01:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720047/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, The Therapy Crouch is streaming live and direct from sunny Portugal where Pete and Abbey are away with the kids. Abbey and Pete reminisce some of their most memorable moments from being on holiday over the years, including fights with paparazzi, near death experiences and going undercover in Barcelona. Agony Ab is also back with a bang - with Abbey giving fashion tips on what to wear to a kinky rave and how to pass gas discretely when you’re in a new relationship.</description></item><item><title>The Therapy Crouch - Oh GROW UP! | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720048/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:15:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720048/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this week’s episode, Abbey and Peter give us a glimpse into what life in the public eye is really like. From the glitz and the glam to the sh*t and the sham, sit back and relax whilst we lift the lid on life as a celeb in 2023. This week also sees the return of the hotly anticipated ‘Weekly Whine Club’, so get your glasses and other half at the ready and find out what’s been grinding our gears recently.</description></item><item><title>The Therapy Crouch - What To Expect When You're Expecting | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720049/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720049/</guid><description>Podcast Description In today’s episode, Abbey and Pete discuss what to expect when you’re expecting. Abbey opens up on some of the issues they experienced when getting pregnant for the first time and offers advice to any listeners who find themselves in a similar situation. Pete is also on hand to provide guidance to the partners who are trying to navigate their way through hormones, weird cravings and strange demands. Sit yourself down, grab a prawn sandwich and enjoy this week’s episode of The Therapy Crouch!</description></item><item><title>The Therapy Crouch - You May As Well Move In Then | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720050/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 00:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720050/</guid><description>Podcast Description On this week’s episode, Pete provides a lesson on exactly how not to ask the love of your life to move in with you. Learn more about Peter’s revolutionary invention, ‘The Squat Box’ and why you should never leave your home movie collection lying around when your future wife and mother-in-law are coming round for tea.
From Pet Detectives to interior design clashes, no stone is left unturned on The Therapy Crouch.</description></item><item><title>The Therapy Crouch - First Dates | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720051/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 00:05:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720051/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the opening episode of their new podcast series, The Therapy Crouch, Abbey and Peter take a trip down memory lane and shed light on their early days dating, as well as advice on how to keep the spark alive once you settle down.&amp;nbsp;
Stay tuned for some questionable chat up lines, trips to monkey island, and advice on how to avoid entering your overdraft on the first date…</description></item><item><title>Welcome to The Therapy Crouch | The Therapy Crouch</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2867720052/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 14:04:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2867720052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to the Therapy Crouch! The brand new couples therapy podcast from Abbey Clancy and Peter Crouch. Join us on our weekly episodes where we will be exploring the trials and tribulations experienced by us, and you the listener, as we navigate our way through complex relationships. Enter into our safe space where nothing is off limits and expect some tears, tantrums and plenty of laughs along the way.</description></item></channel></rss>