<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Global Story on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/the-global-story/</link><description>Recent content in The Global Story on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 09:50:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/the-global-story/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The clash between antisemitism and free speech on US college campuses | The Global Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3170030017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3170030017/</guid><description>Podcast Description There is a row about antisemitism raging in US colleges. After widespread protests against Israel’s bombing of Gaza, Republicans in Congress have accused universities of not doing enough to combat hate speech targeting Jewish students. We look at the battle between free speech and hate speech with the BBC's North America Correspondent Nomia Iqbal and US National Digital Reporter Mike Wendling.
The Global Story brings you trusted insights from BBC experts around the world, with Katya Adler.</description></item><item><title>Is South Africa living up to Nelson Mandela's legacy? | The Global Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3170030001/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3170030001/</guid><description>Podcast Description BBC Special Correspondent Fergal Keane reported on the end of apartheid with his South African producer Milton Nkosi. Thirty years after the transition from apartheid to a democratic South Africa, the two of them have taken a trip around the country to visit the people they interviewed then, to see how life has turned out. They hear of the disillusionment but also the glimmers of hope. The Global Story brings you trusted insights from BBC experts around the world, with Katya Adler.</description></item><item><title>Why are Afghan refugees stuck on the US-Mexico border? | The Global Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3170030002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3170030002/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two years after the Taliban stormed Kabul, thousands of people from Afghanistan tried to escape to the United States. Now many of them are stuck on the US-Mexico border. We hear about the difficult journeys they made to get there and why the crisis at the border is affecting people across the world. In this episode we speak with our US West Coast reporter Regan Morris and our South Asia and Afghanistan correspondent Yogita Limaye.</description></item><item><title>What happened to Hong Kong’s pro-democracy protesters? | The Global Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3170030003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3170030003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Forty-seven of Hong Kong’s pro-democracy campaigners have been in jail for more than a thousand days since the government’s crackdown on the movement in 2019. Ahead of their verdict, we examine whether there is still room to protest in Hong Kong, how the national security law has affected the region and what it could mean for Taiwan. We delve into the story with the BBC’s Asia Pacific editor Celia Hatton, and our Hong Kong-based correspondent Danny Vincent.</description></item><item><title>What's going on with the UK Royal Family? | The Global Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3170030004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3170030004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Reported differences between members of the British Royal Family have complicated the beginning of the reign of King Charles III. We examine whether or not the departure of Harry and Meghan from the royal fold following a highly publicised racial row is likely to leave a lasting impact on the British monarchy, and how it has affected the attitude of the public towards those inside Buckingham Palace. We delve into the story with BBC Royal Correspondent Jonny Dymond, and our Los Angeles-based correspondent David Willis.</description></item><item><title>Inside Trump’s legal strategy | The Global Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3170030005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 09:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3170030005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Former US President Donald Trump has been criminally indicted four times and will have a series of trials to attend in 2024 as he pursues a comeback bid for the White House. In total, Trump faces 91 felony charges, including 44 federal and 47 state charges. He denies all the charges. What is his strategy, and what do these cases mean for his presidential campaign? We unpack all the legal complexities surrounding Trump with the BBC’s Nada Tawfik and CBS News Chief Election &amp;amp; Campaign correspondent Robert Costa.</description></item><item><title>Will Argentina's new president nicknamed 'The Madman' deliver his radical promises? | The Global Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3170030006/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3170030006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Javier Milei is far from your average politician. His critics call him ‘El Loco’, meaning The Madman and he certainly plays up to that reputation having claimed that he ‘hears voices’ and frequently ‘talks to his dead dog.’ Milei ran his campaign mostly on TikTok where he became known for his fiery and sometimes wild campaign promises. He has claimed he was going to shut down the central bank and axe a whole host of government departments.</description></item><item><title>What we know about Hamas and its military capacity | The Global Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3170030007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 09:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3170030007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Israel has vowed to eliminate the perpetrators of the October 7th attack, which killed more than 1,200 people and saw around 240 taken hostage. Hamas - which governs the Palestinian territory of Gaza and is viewed as a terrorist organisation by many western governments – has been the target of unprecedented force from Israeli military. So, what damage has been done? And is it really possible to defeat the group?</description></item><item><title>A risky escape from North Korea | The Global Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3170030008/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 09:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3170030008/</guid><description>Podcast Description North Koreans are forbidden from making contact with the outside world. But what happens when one family decides they want to leave?
Our Seoul Correspondent Jean Mackenzie tells us the story of one defector who we're calling Mr Kim. He and his relatives made a dangerous escape from the tyrannical state in a boat and are now adjusting to life in South Korea.
The Global Story brings you trusted insights from BBC experts around the world, with Katya Adler.</description></item><item><title>Elon Musk’s global satellite ambition | The Global Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3170030009/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3170030009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Elon Musk is the world's richest person. He leads Tesla, Twitter and SpaceX and he owns half the satellites in Earth’s lower orbit; with over 5,000 already operating in space. They make up a global internet constellation called Starlink, which is set to grow rapidly in the coming years. We explore how big his ambitions for space are with our science correspondent Jonathan Amos and our North America technology reporter James Clayton.</description></item><item><title>Could Europe defend Ukraine on its own? | The Global Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3170030010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 09:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3170030010/</guid><description>Podcast Description With the war in Ukraine dragging on, continuing military aid has become a contentious political issue in the United States. So, if support from Kyiv’s biggest military backer was to waver, could its other allies make up the difference? The BBC’s defence correspondent Jonathan Beale and Berlin correspondent Jessica Parker assess whether there is the political will and military capacity for Europe to defend Ukraine on its own. The Global Story brings you trusted insights from BBC experts around the world, with Katya Adler.</description></item><item><title>Is Europe a hotbed for the far-right? | The Global Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3170030011/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3170030011/</guid><description>Podcast Description After populist politician Geert Wilders wins the most seats in the Netherlands election, we ask if his success is part of a broader European pattern. We also explore why voters are turning away from mainstream politics with our correspondent in the Netherlands, Anna Holligan, and Professor Timothy Garton Ash.
The Global Story brings you trusted insights from BBC experts around the world, with Katya Adler. We’re keen to hear from you, wherever you are in the world.</description></item><item><title>Inside COP28: a climate summit in an oil state, a BBC exclusive and a UAE fightback | The Global Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3170030012/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 09:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3170030012/</guid><description>Podcast Description World leaders are arriving in Dubai for COP28 – the most significant annual climate summit. The BBC’s climate editor, Justin Rowlatt, takes us behind the scenes of the summit and talks us through the expectations, and the fallout of a BBC investigation pointing out that the UAE planned to use climate talks to make oil deals. The Global Story brings you trusted insights from BBC experts around the world, with Katya Adler.</description></item><item><title>How did tiny Qatar become a global hostage negotiator? | The Global Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3170030013/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 09:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3170030013/</guid><description>Podcast Description How has a small country in the Middle East managed to become a key player in the negotiations between Israel and Hamas? Today, with the BBC’s security correspondent Frank Gardner, and BBC Monitoring’s Jaidaa Taha in Cairo.
The Global Story brings you trusted insights from BBC experts around the world, with Katya Adler. We’re keen to hear from you, wherever you are in the world. #TheGlobalStory We want your ideas, stories and experiences to help us understand and tell The Global Story.</description></item><item><title>Joe Biden’s ageing brain | The Global Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3170030014/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3170030014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Democrat Joe Biden, 81, is America’s oldest president. His chief rival, Republican Donald Trump, is 77. Polls consistently show voters are more worried that Mr Biden lacks “mental sharpness.” Today, why President Biden’s age matters, with our Medical Editor, Fergus Walsh, and our Special Correspondent in Washington, Katty Kay. The Global Story brings you trusted insights from BBC experts around the world, with Katya Adler. We’re keen to hear from you, wherever you are in the world.</description></item><item><title>Israel-Gaza conflict: The social media battles | The Global Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3170030015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 09:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3170030015/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Global Story brings you trusted insights from BBC experts around the world. Today, why the battle on your social media feed matters, with our Chief International Correspondent, Lyse Doucet, and our Disinformation &amp;amp; Social Media Correspondent, Marianna Spring.
It’s been seven weeks since Hamas, which governs Gaza and is labelled a terrorist group by the US and many other western governments, murdered 1200 people in southern Israel. Israel’s response has left Gaza in ruins - an emphatic symbol of its military prowess.</description></item><item><title>Introducing The Global Story | The Global Story</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/3170030016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 12:09:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/3170030016/</guid><description>Podcast Description A brand new podcast to help you cut through the headlines. Starts 27 November 2023, with Katya Adler. Insight you can trust from our BBC experts around the world. One big story, Monday to Friday. Helping you make sense of the news. Get in touch: theglobalstory@bbc.com #TheGlobalStory
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>