<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>After Dark: Myths, Misdeeds &amp; the Paranormal on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/after-dark-myths-misdeeds-the-paranormal/</link><description>Recent content in After Dark: Myths, Misdeeds &amp; the Paranormal on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 03:00:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/after-dark-myths-misdeeds-the-paranormal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Palmer the Poisoner: Victorian England's Doctor of Death | After Dark: Myths, Misdeeds &amp; the Paranormal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2317510024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 03:00:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2317510024/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a century of poisoners, William Palmer stands out as the prince of them all. Charles Dickens called him "the greatest villain that ever stood in the Old Bailey".
Maddy tells Anthony the story this week, whisking us back to Victorian England and the Staffordshire town of Rugeley where Palmer plied his trade. A town where Maddy's ancestor happened to be working as the chemist at the time....</description></item><item><title>Why Do People Kill at Christmas? | After Dark: Myths, Misdeeds &amp; the Paranormal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2317510001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 03:00:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2317510001/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;nbsp;Why do people kill in the season of goodwill? Why are we fascinated when they do? And what does it say about us?
Professor David Wilson, leading criminologist and bestselling author, joins Maddy and Anthony for this Christmas Special edition.
David's latest book is "Murder at Home: how our safest space is where we're most in danger".
Edited by Tom Delargy, Produced by Freddy Chick, Senior Producer is Charlotte Long</description></item><item><title>Ghost That Solved Its Own Murder: Red Barn Murder | After Dark: Myths, Misdeeds &amp; the Paranormal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2317510002/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 03:00:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2317510002/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Red Barn Murder in 1827 was ground zero for true crime podcasts. It become one of the first cases to explode in the media and caused a national sensation. It had everything - sex, murder and a ghost that revealed the location of its own corpse. What more could Britain's budding army of armchair detectives want?
Huge thanks to Una McIlvenna for her beautiful (and historically accurate)&amp;nbsp;recording of the ballad the 'Murder of Maria Marten'.</description></item><item><title>The Ghost of Anne Boleyn | After Dark: Myths, Misdeeds &amp; the Paranormal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2317510003/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 03:00:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2317510003/</guid><description>Podcast Description We talk the ghost of Anne Boleyn, Queen of England before Henry VIII chopped off her head, with the marvellous Tracy Borman.
Where can Anne Boleyn's ghost be seen? What form does it take? And why does she haunt us so? Get ready for carriages pulled by headless horses, spooky palaces, a weird floating cylinder thing...and a single moment in history that has haunted England, and now Britain's, imagination for hundreds of years.</description></item><item><title>Hellfire Club: Sex, Scandal &amp; Satanism in Georgian England | After Dark: Myths, Misdeeds &amp; the Paranormal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2317510004/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 03:00:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2317510004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sex, Satanism and Scandal surrounded the Hellfire Club that operated out of a network of caves in the country estate of 18th century aristocrat Francis Dashwood. The most powerful men in the country came to Dashwood's underground lair. Rumours swirled of everything from orgies to human sacrifice and Satanic spirits. But was it all as diabolical as it seemed?
Maddy tells Anthony the story this week.
Produced by Freddy Chick and Charlotte Long.</description></item><item><title>Amelia Dyer: Victorian Baby Farm Killer | After Dark: Myths, Misdeeds &amp; the Paranormal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2317510005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 03:00:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2317510005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Some estimates have it that Amelia Dyer killed more than 400 babies. It's hard to say for sure because so few victims were recovered. She was a phantom that grew up in a very dark corner of Victorian society where helpless mothers were given with no better options but to give their babies to 'baby farmers'.
Anthony tells Maddy this painful history.
Edited and produced by Freddy Chick. Senior Producer is Charlotte Long.</description></item><item><title>The Real Origins of Witches | After Dark: Myths, Misdeeds &amp; the Paranormal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2317510006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 03:00:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2317510006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Have you ever wondered what the ancient origins of witchcraft is? How did the black-hat-broomstick stereotype emerge? And what causes the waves of witch trials throughout history, right up to the present day?
Ronald Hutton is back on After Dark to discuss the history of the witch, in an episode from our sister podcast, Betwixt the Sheets. This podcast was mixed and produced by Stuart Beckwith. The senior producer was Charlotte Long.</description></item><item><title>Victorian Death Photography: Postmortem Posers | After Dark: Myths, Misdeeds &amp; the Paranormal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2317510007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 03:00:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2317510007/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Victorians created the unsettling art of death photography - posing their deceased love ones in family portraits as if they were alive. How did they manage to make corpses strike poses? Why did they want to?
Maddy and Anthony are joined by Brandy Schillace, author of Death’s Summer Coat - What Death and Dying Cal Tell Us about Life and Living to flick through the strangest, and most moving, of family photo albums.</description></item><item><title>Mother Shipton: Tudor Prophetess of England's Doom | After Dark: Myths, Misdeeds &amp; the Paranormal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2317510008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 03:00:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2317510008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Did a Tudor prophetess correctly predict the English Civil War, the Crimean War, the sinking of the Titanic, World War One and the end of days? And what does she have to do with turning teddy bears into stone?
Find out as Maddy and Anthony discuss Mother Shipton's life, legend and legacy.
Written by Maddy Pelling
Edited and produced by Freddy Chick. Senior producer is Charlotte Long.
Discover the past with exclusive history documentaries and ad-free podcasts presented by world-renowned historians from History Hit.</description></item><item><title>The Real Witch Hunts: Persecution &amp; Panic | After Dark: Myths, Misdeeds &amp; the Paranormal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2317510009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 03:00:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2317510009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Witch hunts blazed across Europe from the 1400s right into the 1700s. Their terror has been burned into the collective memory. But how accurate are the pictures we have in our heads?
For this episode, Anthony and Maddy are joined by Suzannah Lipscomb, host of Not Just the Tudor. She helps them delve deep into the realities of witches and witch trials in Early Modern Europe.
Edited by Joseph Knight and produced by Annie Coloe and Rob Weinberg</description></item><item><title>The Man Who Hanged Nazis: Albert Pierrepoint | After Dark: Myths, Misdeeds &amp; the Paranormal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2317510010/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 03:00:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2317510010/</guid><description>Podcast Description For Albert Pierrepoint, execution was a family affair. His father and uncle were hangmen and from the 1940s until the late 1950s Albert was Britain's "Number One" executioner. Which meant he was the one sent to hang the Nazis who ran the Bergen-Belsen concentration camp at the end of the war.
Who was Albert Pierrepoint? What does it take to be able to execute hundreds of people? And what is 'The Drop'?</description></item><item><title>Ghost Fetishes: From Ancient World to Victorians | After Dark: Myths, Misdeeds &amp; the Paranormal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2317510011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 03:00:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2317510011/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is spectrophilia? Well, it's a fetish for ghosts (as well as mirrors), so being turned on by anything lurking in the non-physical realm. What are the historic origins of this fetish and phenomenon? And what real life stories can be told of it?
Maddy and Anthony talked with Kate Lister, wonderful host of our sister podcast Betwixt the Sheets.
This podcast was edited by Siobhan Dale and produced by Stuart Beckwith.</description></item><item><title>Origins of the Loch Ness Monster | After Dark: Myths, Misdeeds &amp; the Paranormal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2317510012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 03:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2317510012/</guid><description>Podcast Description What lurks beneath the dark waters of Loch Ness? The legendary monster? A piece of Celtic folklore? A warning of the Nazis' rise to power? A fraudster?
Today Anthony and Maddy are examining grainy photographs, picking over descriptions of monsters and trying to work out what it all means.
Written by Anthony Delaney
Edited by Tom Delargy. Produced by Freddy Chick. Senior Producer is Charlotte Long.
This episode contains sound effects from Zapsplat.</description></item><item><title>Guy Fawkes &amp; the 1605 Gunpowder Plot | After Dark: Myths, Misdeeds &amp; the Paranormal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2317510013/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 03:55:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2317510013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Other countries celebrate their victories and independence. But in Britain, we celebrate a bungling terrorist from the 17th century. Why? Who was Guy Fawkes? What was the Gunpowder Plot? And why must we Remember, Remember the 5th of November?
Maddy Pelling and Anthony Delaney are joined by historian and author Steven Veerapen - author of (among other titles) Of Blood Descended: An Anthony Blanke Tudor Mystery: https://birlinn.co.uk/product/of-blood-descended/
Produced by Charlotte Long and Freddy Chick.</description></item><item><title>Hammersmith Ghost: How to Murder a Poltergeist | After Dark: Myths, Misdeeds &amp; the Paranormal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2317510014/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 03:00:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2317510014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Can it be murder if you think you're killing a ghost? In 1804 the London suburb of Hammersmith was being terrorised by a ghost. One man set out to hunt down whoever, or whatever, this was. He almost swung from the end of a rope for his troubles.
Join Anthony and Maddy for this ghostly Halloween episode.
Written by Maddy Pelling.
Edited by Tom Delargy. Produced by Freddy Chick.</description></item><item><title>Hauntings, Hangings &amp; a Beast: Bodmin Jail | After Dark: Myths, Misdeeds &amp; the Paranormal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2317510015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 02:00:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2317510015/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bodmin Jail can claim to be one of the most haunted buildings in Britain. Perhaps that's because of all the hangings that took place here. Or the postmortem punishment the jail dolled out to prisoners. Or perhaps it is because it's in Cornwall - land of giants, beasts and all things otherworldly.
Maddy and Anthony are joined by Jess Marlton, manager of Bodmin Jail, to talk about life, death and afterlife at this unique 18th century prison.</description></item><item><title>Last Witch of Scotland | After Dark: Myths, Misdeeds &amp; the Paranormal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2317510016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 02:00:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2317510016/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1727, Janet Horne of the Highland community of Dornoch became the last person in Britain to be tried and executed for witchcraft.
As the poet Edwin Morgan put it; They tarred her and feathered her, bound her and barrelled her burning in the peat-smoke, while the good folk of Dornoch paused briefly for a look.
But maybe the events aren’t quite as black and white as they seem?</description></item><item><title>Banshees: Ireland's Harbinger of Death | After Dark: Myths, Misdeeds &amp; the Paranormal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2317510017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 02:00:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2317510017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today Siobhán McSweeney (Derry Girls) joins Anthony Delaney and Maddy Pelling for the story of the Banshee. In Irish folklore the Banshee heralds the death of a family member, usually by shrieking, or keening. Anthony tells us a story about one dying man - Charles Bunworth d.1772 - who was called to his death by a Banshee's wailing cries.
Written by Anthony Delaney.
Edited by Tom Delargy.
Senior Producer is Charlotte Long.</description></item><item><title>HMS Terror: Cursed Arctic Expedition | After Dark: Myths, Misdeeds &amp; the Paranormal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2317510018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 02:08:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2317510018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Was ever a ship more aptly named? In 1845, HMS Terror (and its forgettably named sister ship HMS Erebus) set off from Victorian Britain. Their quest was to discover the fabled Northwest passage through the Arctic ice. The crew were heroes in waiting. Yet by the end the rules that govern life on board Royal Navy vessels collapsed into chaos and cannibalism.
Maddy tells Anthony this story about life in the Royal Navy, Arctic winters, badly written poetry, and the thin line that separates us from horror.</description></item><item><title>Burke &amp; Hare: Scotland’s Most Notorious Serial Killers | After Dark: Myths, Misdeeds &amp; the Paranormal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2317510019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 02:06:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2317510019/</guid><description>Podcast Description They’re the most famous grave-robbers in the world…except they never actually robbed any graves. Discover the true story of Burke and Hare’s murderous rampage through the streets of Edinburgh, all to serve the needs of the city’s scientific minds.
Anthony tells Maddy the unnerving details about the infamous 19th century serial-killing duo.
Written by Anthony Delaney. Edited by Tom Delargy. Producer is Freddy Chick. Senior Producer is Charlotte Long</description></item><item><title>Goriest Murders in Ancient Rome: From Gladiators to Flesh Eating Fish | After Dark: Myths, Misdeeds &amp; the Paranormal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2317510020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 02:04:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2317510020/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode is a bloody delight: from flesh-eating fish and humiliating deaths inside sacks, to a deadly re-enactment of the Icarus myth. For a culture that is seen as an emblem of civilisation (whatever that means), the Romans expended a lot of creative energy on inventing new ways to kill people. And our guest today knows them all!
Anthony Delaney and Maddy Pelling are joined by the one and only Emma Southon author of A Fatal Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum.</description></item><item><title>The Origins of Halloween | After Dark: Myths, Misdeeds &amp; the Paranormal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2317510021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 02:02:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2317510021/</guid><description>Podcast Description From its prehistoric origins until today, Halloween has always had the Shiver of Terror running through it. First as a pagan festival of Winter-the-Bringer-of-Death. Then as a Catholic holy day dedicated to lost Souls in purgatory. Now as a celebration of horrifyingly bad fancy dress!
Maddy and Anthony speak to the one-and-only Professor Ronald Hutton, a national treasure who is the author of too many wonderful books to list here.</description></item><item><title>The Murders That Shocked Georgian London | After Dark: Myths, Misdeeds &amp; the Paranormal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2317510022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 02:00:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2317510022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Laundress-turned-murderess, Sarah Malcolm horrified Georgian London in 1733 when she was found guilty of killing three women she worked for while they slept. For wealthy Georgians this was a nightmare come true: a servant killing the household they served. Sarah became a celebrity killer and was painted by none other than William Hogarth while she sat in jail.
Anthony Delaney tells Maddy Pelling this dark history.
Written by Anthony Delaney.</description></item><item><title>Welcome to After Dark: Myths, Misdeeds &amp; the Paranormal | After Dark: Myths, Misdeeds &amp; the Paranormal</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2317510023/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 02:00:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2317510023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Introducing After Dark: Myths, Misdeeds &amp;amp; the Paranormal, the podcast that takes you to the shadiest corners of the past, unpicking history’s spookiest, strangest, and most sinister stories.
Meet your hosts, historians Anthony Delaney and Maddy Pelling, who will be taking a look at the darker side of history. From haunted pubs and Houdini, to witch trials and weird UFO sightings.
New episodes every Monday and Thursday, from Monday 16th October.</description></item></channel></rss>