<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Empire on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/empire/</link><description>Recent content in Empire on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 02:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/empire/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Rise of Islam | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860110/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860110/</guid><description>Podcast Description With the Sassanian Empire defeated and the Byzantine Empire exhausted, there is a power vacuum in the centre of the world. Both of these superpowers have drained their resources fighting each other over the past 30 years, consuming many of the great cities of antiquity. To the south, on the Arabian peninsula, a new power was rising that would come to take advantage of their weakness. A power that would change the course of history.</description></item><item><title>The Last Great War of Antiquity | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860109/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860109/</guid><description>Podcast Description Eurasia is divided into two great superpowers. Khusrow II rules the Sassanian Empire. Maurice, the last of the Justinian dynasty, rules their mighty rivals, the Byzantines. When he is overthrown, Khusrow looks to capitalise upon the chaos, invades his neighbour, and begins to sweep through Byzantine territory. The clash that follows over the next 30 years consumes the two empires and leads to the end of antiquity. Listen as William and Anita discuss this titanic war for the world.</description></item><item><title>How Persian Religion Changed the World | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860108/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Three great religions have come out of Persia and all of them have influenced world history. First there was Zoroastrianism, the first monotheistic religion, which had significant influence over Christianity, Judaism, and Islam. Then there was Mithraism. It began in Persia but, through conquest, it filtered into the Roman pantheon. As a result, there are shrines to it as far away as Hadrian’s Wall. Lastly, there is Manichaeism. The religion that is fundamentally rooted in the struggle between good and evil, which is itself a Zoroastrian idea.</description></item><item><title>Alexander the Great: Defeating Darius | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860105/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Darius has already been defeated by Alexander. His wife has been kidnapped and has now died in childbirth. The omens sent by the gods bode ill for him. Yet, the two are ready to face off at Gaugamela. Will Darius be the first commander to defeat Alexander in battle, or will he fall like all those before him? Listen as William and Anita tell the story of the end of the Achaemenid Empire.</description></item><item><title>Alexander the Great: The Conquest of Persia | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860104/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860104/</guid><description>Podcast Description Darius III rules Persia and he has already demonstrated his heroism and skill in battle. The Empire itself, despite having been through a period of court intrigue, was stable. Yet, coming through their western border, originally from Macedonia, was a young man bent on conquering the whole world. His name, Alexander the Great. Listen as William and Anita retell one of the greatest stories in history.
For bonus episodes, ad-free listening, reading lists, book discounts, a weekly newsletter, and a chat community.</description></item><item><title>Salamis: Athens’ Revenge | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860106/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Leonidas and the 300 have been defeated at Thermopylae, leaving the way to Athens open. With the Persians advancing, many Athenians flee to the island of Salamis in the hope it will give them shelter. From there, they see flames lick the sky as the Persians burn Athens. But their leader, Themistocles, has readied the fleet for one last battle with Xerxes. Listen as William and Anita are once again joined by Lloyd Llewellyn-Jones to discuss the Battle of Salamis and the end of the Persian invasion of Greece.</description></item><item><title>The Battle of Salamis: Athens’ Revenge | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860103/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Leonidas and the 300 have been defeated at Thermopylae, leaving the way to Athens open. With the Persians advancing, many Athenians flee to the island of Salamis in the hope it will give them shelter. From there, they see flames lick the sky as the Persians burn Athens. But their leader, Themistocles, has readied the fleet for one last battle with Xerxes. Listen as William and Anita are once again joined by Lloyd Llewellyn-Jones to discuss the Battle of Salamis and the end of the Persian invasion of Greece.</description></item><item><title>Thermopylae: Xerxes, Leonidas, and the 300 | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860102/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860102/</guid><description>Podcast Description August 480BC; the might of the Persian army, roughly 100,000 soldiers, face down a few thousand Greeks, led by Leonidas and his brave 300. In light of their overwhelming advantage, an embassy of Xerxes asks the Spartans to lay down their weapons. Their response, &amp;lsquo;come and get them&amp;rsquo;. Listen as William and Anita are joined by Paul Cartledge to discuss the heroic last stand of Leonidas and the 300 at Thermopylae.</description></item><item><title>Marathon and the Rise of Greece | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860107/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ionia has revolted and so Darius turns his gaze away from India and towards Greece. He crushes the rebellion, quelling all resistance. He then looks to take much of the Greek mainland and many city states acquiesce before his envoys, but not the Athenians. So the might of the Persian army land at Marathon, ready to face down the belligerent Greeks. What follows is one of history’s most famous battles.</description></item><item><title>The Battle of Marathon and the Rise of Greece | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860001/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ionia has revolted and so Darius turns his gaze away from India and towards Greece. He crushes the rebellion, quelling all resistance. He then looks to take much of the Greek mainland and many city states acquiesce before his envoys, but not the Athenians. So the might of the Persian army land at Marathon, ready to face down the belligerent Greeks. What follows is one of history’s most famous battles.</description></item><item><title>Darius the Great: Ruling from India to the Mediterranean | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860002/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860002/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Persian Empire that Darius took control of was already mighty and powerful; his predecessor, Cambyses, had conquered Egypt, further expanding its territory. But it was under Darius it reached its zenith. Stretching all the way from the Mediterranean in the west to India in the east, from the Gulf of Oman in the south to southern Russia in the north, Persia under Darius was truly a global superpower.</description></item><item><title>Cyrus the Great: Building the First Superpower | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860003/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Born the son of a khan, a tribal chieftain, Cyrus would go on to be a titanic figure of world history. He took Persia from being a minor regional power to the first superpower the world has ever seen. Conquering all of modern day Iran, then Turkey, and finally defeating the power of the day, Babylon: Cyrus undoubtedly deserves the sobriquet of the Great. Listen as William and Anita are joined by Lloyd Llewellyn-Jones to discuss the life of the founder of the Persian Empire, Cyrus the Great.</description></item><item><title>Series 5: Empires of Iran | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860004/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860004/</guid><description>Podcast Description Persia was the first great superpower. The empire built by Cyrus, Darius, Xerxes and the rest of the Achaemenids stretched from India in the east to the Mediterranean in the west, from Russia in the north to the Gulf of Oman in the south. It laid the foundation for empires of the future. It was destroyed by Alexander the Great, but Iran has risen many times since. In this series we&amp;rsquo;ll look at the ancient Persian empire, but also their successors; the Sassanians, who fought against Rome, in a vast war that eventually led to the Rise of Islam; then the Saffavids, during whose rule Shi&amp;rsquo;ism took root in Iran; and we&amp;rsquo;ll end with the Iranian Revolution and the way it laid the foundations for political islam and much of the politics that drives the Middle-east today.</description></item><item><title>The History of Putin's War | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860005/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vladimir Putin invaded Ukraine on 24th February 2022, but how did we get to this point? After the brutality of the Second World War, Ukraine was completely under the control of Moscow. Then in the 1980s, with Chernobyl as the catalyst, the Ukrainian nationalist movement regained momentum and on 24th August 1991 declared independence. This was never accepted by Russia and all the tension, discord, and conflict since then has led us to the devastating war of today.</description></item><item><title>Welcome to the Empire Club | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860006/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ladies and gentlemen, we give you the Empire Club. Do you want bonus episodes? Do you want discounts on the books mentioned in the weeks podcast? Do you want reading lists? Do you want ad-free listening? Well now you can. All you need to do is join the Empire Club to access all of these benefits and more.
Sign up at https://empirepod.supportingcast.fm/
Twitter: @Empirepoduk
Email: empirepoduk@gmail.com
Goalhangerpodcasts.com
Producer: Callum Hill Exec Producer: Jack Davenport + Neil Fearn Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>The Bloody History of Russia &amp; Ukraine | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860007/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860007/</guid><description>Podcast Description The history of Russia and Ukraine has been irrevocably entwined for centuries. When the Bolsheviks took over and Civil War erupted across the Russian Empire, Ukraine was one of the bloodiest centres of the conflict. Antisemitic pogroms and wanton violence destroyed whole communities. Then during the 1930s Russia inflicted upon Ukraine one of the deadliest famines in history, the death toll is estimated to be around 4m. Listen as William and Anita are joined by Pulitzer-winning historian Anne Applebaum to discuss the traumatic history of Russia and Ukraine.</description></item><item><title>Murdering the Romanovs: The End of a Dynasty | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860008/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860008/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dawn breaks on 16th July 1918. For Nicholas, Alexandra, and the rest of the Romanov family this is just another day in exile. They sit down for breakfast - today it is eggs - and then go about their usual business. The Romanovs had been out in the cold ever since Nicholas II&amp;rsquo;s abdication over a year earlier. First they had lived in their own home, then they were moved to Siberia.</description></item><item><title>Killing Rasputin | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Born in Siberia to a peasant family, Rasputin was an incredibly charismatic, physically striking, and politically savvy figure. He was a holy man, a mystic, who found his way to the centre of Imperial Russian power. Once he met Nicholas and Alexandra, he gained a central place in the court as the only man who could stop the tsarevich, Alexei, from bleeding. As his influence grew, his reputation among the Russian aristocracy declined.</description></item><item><title>Lenin and The Rise of the Bolsheviks | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860010/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860010/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Tsar has abdicated and the provisional government rules Russia, but Petrograd is overflowing with revolutionaries who want more radical change. Lenin has returned from exile and is looking to seize power for the Bolsheviks. Their momentum is growing and with Russia still in the First World War, Kerensky and the provisional government&amp;rsquo;s authority is draining away. Listen as William and Anita are once again joined by the great Antony Beevor to discuss the October Revolution and the Bolsheviks&amp;rsquo; consolidation of power in the civil war.</description></item><item><title>The Russian Revolution: Overthrowing the Tsar | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860011/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860011/</guid><description>Podcast Description Russian politics is fast destabilising. Strikes, assassinations, and famines have made Russia increasingly turbulent at the turn of the century. Revolutionary politics is on the rise, as is dissatisfaction with the tsar. When compounded by the strains of the defeat in the Russo-Japanese War, the nation stands on the verge of implosion. And on Europe&amp;rsquo;s horizon is the Great War&amp;hellip; Listen as William and Anita are joined by the great Antony Beevor to discuss the build-up to the revolution and the events of February 1917.</description></item><item><title>The Final Act of the Great Game | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860012/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Fearing Russian designs on the region, the eyes of the British turn towards Tibet. Francis Younghusband, the Victorian adventurer and elite player of the Great Game, and Lord Curzon decide that with the Russians distracted by their conflict in Manchuria, now is the time to seize the territory. This is their chance to one-up their imperial rival. In this classic tale of the Great Game, British and Russian officers face each other down in far-off mountain ranges, before things take a darker turn as a British expedition sets off a cycle of violence.</description></item><item><title>The Russo-Japanese War: Asia Strikes Back | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860013/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860013/</guid><description>Podcast Description 1905 was one of the most pivotal moments in history. Japan, the supposedly weaker Asian power, overwhelmingly defeated the mighty Russian Empire. The effects of this rippled through the 20th century, inspiring nationalism across Asia. The Indian independence movement, through figures like Gandhi, Nehru, and Tagore, took direct inspiration from it, as did Chinese nationalists like Sun Yat-Sen. Russia was equally rocked by this disastrous defeat, putting it well on the road to revolution.</description></item><item><title>Tolstoy: War and the Russian Empire | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860014/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tolstoy was one of the greatest writers of all time. His books have constructed how we think about Russian imperial history. But he was not just an observer, he was also a participant. As a young man, Tolstoy fought in several of Russia&amp;rsquo;s imperial wars– against the Chechens and the Ottoman Turks, then against both the French and the British in the Crimea. As he matured he grew far more critical of Russian Empire building and lamented the futility of war and conquest.</description></item><item><title>Crushing the Khans: Russia Seizes the Centre of the World | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860015/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860015/</guid><description>Podcast Description As the other European empires were consolidating their holdings in Asia, Russia took 1.5million square miles of territory. Moving south from the Orenburg line, the Russian Empire swallowed up the Khanates of Central Asia with minimal casualties to their own troops. Depicting the citizens of Kokhand, Khiva, and Bokhara as insolent and inferior, this conquest serves as one of classic European colonialism. Listen as William and Anita delve into the story of the conquest of Central Asia.</description></item><item><title>The Russian Conquest of America | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860016/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the 18th century Vitus Bering went from Russia&amp;rsquo;s east coast and landed in America. Over the next 150 years, Russia colonised more and more land, first taking Alaska and then working down America&amp;rsquo;s west coast, eventually claiming areas as far south as California. Whilst this venture did fail, this failure was not inevitable. Listen as William and Anita are joined by Owen Matthews to discuss the most improbable story of Russia and its (almost successful) attempts to colonise large parts of America.</description></item><item><title>A Tale of Two Nurses: Seacole &amp; Nightingale | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860017/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860017/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Lady with the Lamp, the great nurse who forever changed public health for the better: Florence Nightingale lives large in the national consciousness. Mary Seacole, however, has been largely forgotten by history, even though she too played a significant role in the Crimean War. Both were lauded by the press. Both were famous in Britain upon their return. Remarkable forces of will, both were women ahead of their time.</description></item><item><title>The Charge of the Light Brigade | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860018/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860018/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Crimean War continues to drag on. The allies&amp;rsquo; siege of Sevastopol is grinding to a stalemate. The Russians seek to counterattack to tip the balance back in their favour. As they make gains at Balaclava, the British cavalry undertake one of the most tragically heroic actions in British history: the Charge of the Light Brigade. Listen as William and Anita are joined by Orlando Figes to discuss the end of the Crimean War, the impact it had upon Russia, and the shadow it still casts today.</description></item><item><title>Crimea: The War on Repeat | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860019/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860019/</guid><description>Podcast Description A slow grind of sieges and massacres. Long distance bombardments and gruelling inch-by-inch trench warfare. Battles for Sevastopol, Odessa, and control of the Black Sea. Is it 1853 or 2023? The parallels between the Crimean War and what is happening now in Ukraine are startling. Listen as William and Anita are joined by Orlando Figes to discuss this totemic 19th century clash and all of its modern-day resonances.</description></item><item><title>The Graveyard of Empires | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860020/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860020/</guid><description>Podcast Description After the calamitous retreat from Kabul left thousands of British dead, the East India Company wants revenge. They will call upon the Army of Retribution which will leave Afghanistan, once the Crossroads of Civilisation, a desolate wasteland. But once the last sepoy has descended the Khyber Pass, who will rule Afghanistan - and how will the Russians respond? Listen as William and Anita finish the story of the First Anglo-Afghan War and discuss whether Afghanistan really is the Graveyard of Empires, and whether China will be the next foreign power to burn its fingers in the Afghan furnace.</description></item><item><title>1842: The Retreat from Kabul | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860021/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860021/</guid><description>Podcast Description As the British occupation of Kabul collapses, the troops flee. What follows is one of the darkest events in British imperial history. A treacherous journey through mountain passes in crippling winter conditions leaves the British at the mercy of the Afghan forces. Over 15,000 men, women, and children leave the capital, legend says only one man survives. Listen as William and Anita discuss the bloody, brutal, first retreat from Kabul.</description></item><item><title>Invading Afghanistan: The Return of a King | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860022/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860022/</guid><description>Podcast Description It is 1839 and Britain has declared its intention: to invade Afghanistan and return Shah Shuja to the throne. Despite its vast size, the British invasion force is not impressive. Overstocked with luxuries and understocked with necessities, how will it fare as it enters the Bolan Pass and the inhospitable terrain of Afghanistan? Listen as William and Anita tell the Return of a King.
Twitter: @Empirepoduk
Email: empirepoduk@gmail.com</description></item><item><title>The Battle of the Spies | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860023/</guid><description>Podcast Description The rivalry between Russia and Britain continues to grow as both of their attentions begin to centre more and more on Afghanistan. In a bid to gain influence in the region, both empires send young, daring spies to infiltrate the region. Alexander Burnes and Jan Prosper Vitkevich will both battle to gain the upper hand. Listen as William and Anita discuss these two spies and their thrilling roles in the Great Game.</description></item><item><title>The Great Game Begins | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860024/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860024/</guid><description>Podcast Description It will all begin on the banks of the River Niemen. Tsar Alexander forms a pact with Napoleon; the Russian Empire, along with the French, will try to take control of British India. The British increasingly become nervous about losing their prized possession and hostile towards Russia. What will follow has come to be known as the Great Game in Britain and the Tournament of Shadows in Russia. It is the ultimate imperial rivalry; Britain and Russia, the two greatest powers of the day, vying for control of the centre of the world.</description></item><item><title>The Empress &amp; The General | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860025/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860025/</guid><description>Podcast Description With her reign in peril in three separate arenas, Catherine begins to turn her attention to a young soldier, Grigory Potemkin. What follows is one of the great partnerships (and love affairs) of history. Together, they consolidate her rule then rapidly expand; seizing vast parts of modern Ukraine, annexing Crimea, building Kherson and Sevastopol, and taking the Russian Empire to its apogee. Listen as William and Anita are joined by Simon Sebag Montefiore for the final time as they tell the tale of the Russian Empire’s finest moment.</description></item><item><title>Catherine the Great: The Golden Age | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860026/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860026/</guid><description>Podcast Description Not a drop of Russian blood. A woman in a world ruled by men. A loveless marriage to a man who lacked even a shred of empathy. The odds were always stacked against Catherine the Great when she arrived from Prussia. But this German Princess and child of the Enlightenment was a political genius who possessed charm, beauty and impeccable people skills. All these were needed as she rose to power to become Empress of Russia and ushered in a golden age.</description></item><item><title>Peter the Great: The First Emperor | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860027/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860027/</guid><description>Podcast Description A giant of Russian history, and a giant of a man. Peter the Great, standing at 6'8, established Russia as the world power that it is today and is famously one of Vladimir Putin&amp;rsquo;s inspirations. He expanded Russia&amp;rsquo;s borders, modernised the state, and built St Petersburg from a swamp. Yet with all this, he still found time for drunken debauchery of the most absurd level; he enjoyed dwarf-throwing, wheelbarrow racing, and creating the position of Archdeacon Fuck-Off for his ministers.</description></item><item><title>Ivan the Terrible and the Founding of Russia | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860028/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Subjected, downtrodden, brutalised. The principality of Muscovy had long suffered at the hands of the Mongols. But as their overlords weaken, their ruler, Ivan the Great, begins to lead the Muscovites to freedom. Come 1533, it is time for his descendant, Ivan the Terrible to rule. A man known to enjoy hanging people by their ribs, and drowning people under river ice, will his taste for torture throw everything into chaos?</description></item><item><title>Series 4: The Russian Empire and the Great Game | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860029/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860029/</guid><description>Podcast Description The story of the Russian Empire spans centuries and continents. It is one of tsars and revolutionaries. Sex and power. Invasions and conquests. In the new season, William and Anita will explore the roots, deeds, and legacy of one the largest empires to ever exist. From the first Russian invasion of Ukraine, to the birth of Asian nationalism, with the original retreat from Kabul in between; this will leave you stunned.</description></item><item><title>Nazis, reparations, and laws 'just for the English to see' | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860030/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Did the Nazis use slave labour? Should Britain pay reparations? What is the origin of the Portuguese phrase &amp;lsquo;just for the English to see&amp;rsquo;? What was the role of Islam in abolition? Listen as William and Anita answer these questions and more&amp;hellip;
Twitter: @Empirepoduk
Email: empirepoduk@gmail.com
Goalhangerpodcasts.com
Producer: Callum Hill Exec Producer: Jack Davenport + Neil Fearn Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Haitian Revolution, Dutch royals, and what happened to the Caribs? | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860031/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860031/</guid><description>Podcast Description What happened to the Caribs, the indigenous people of the Caribbean? Why did indentured labour become so prominent? What is the current Dutch monarchy&amp;rsquo;s approach to slavery? Did Native Americans keep slaves? Listen as William and Anita answer your questions.
This episode is sponsored by BetterHelp. Give online therapy a try at betterhelp.com/empirepod.
Twitter: @Empirepoduk
Email: empirepoduk@gmail.com
Goalhangerpodcasts.com
Producer: Callum Hill Exec Producer: Jack Davenport + Neil Fearn Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>A Reckoning with Slavery | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860032/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Slavery may have been abolished in 1838, but its legacy lives on in Britain today. A lot of the nation benefited financially from the trade, none more so than the slaveholders who were compensated during abolition. Today, William and Anita are joined by Alex Renton, whose family were such beneficiaries. Listen as he argues that slavery is not ancient history: it&amp;rsquo;s a bit of our past that still haunts the present in real and tangible ways.</description></item><item><title>The Long Death of Slavery | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860033/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emancipations are never clean, they don&amp;rsquo;t happen overnight. Instead, they are long, drawn-out, messy processes that leave many still oppressed. Listen as William and Anita are joined by Kris Manjapra to discuss the century of emancipations and their legacy.
This episode is sponsored by BetterHelp. Give online therapy a try at betterhelp.com/empirepod.
Twitter: @Empirepoduk
Email: empirepoduk@gmail.com
Goalhangerpodcasts.com
Producer: Callum Hill Exec Producer: Jack Davenport + Neil Fearn Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Slavery's Demise | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860034/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860034/</guid><description>Podcast Description The slave trade has been abolished, but the number of slaves within the British Empire remains colossal. Thomas Fowell Buxton, the Elephant, has taken the mantle of leadership from William Wilberforce with one singular aim: the complete abolition of slavery. But how will he fare against the West India Interest? Listen as William and Anita are once again joined by Michael Taylor to discuss how much of the British establishment united to try and block his efforts.</description></item><item><title>Wilberforce and the Fight for Freedom | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860035/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860035/</guid><description>Podcast Description The abolition movement is growing in Britain, at its helm are two men. William Wilberforce leads the campaign in parliament and Thomas Clarkson powers it from the grassroots. Their combined might will win a great victory in the abolition of the slave trade in 1807. Listen as William Dalrymple and Anita Anand are joined by Michael Taylor to tell this story.
This episode is sponsored by BetterHelp. Give online therapy a try at betterhelp.</description></item><item><title>When the Enslaved Took on Napoleon | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860036/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Napoleon is emperor of France. Having consolidated his rule at home, he starts to look abroad and to the re-institution of slavery. His eyes set upon Haiti, where Toussaint L’Ouverture, the Black Spartacus, leads his army of freed slaves. How will this titanic clash play out?
This episode is sponsored by BetterHelp. Give online therapy a try at betterhelp.com/empirepod.
Twitter: @Empirepoduk
Goalhangerpodcasts.com
Producer: Callum Hill Exec Producer: Jack Davenport + Neil Fearn Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>The Black Spartacus | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860037/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860037/</guid><description>Podcast Description &amp;lsquo;A courageous chief only is wanted. Where is he, that great man whom nature owes to her vexed, oppressed and tormented children? Where is he? He will appear, doubt it not; he will come forth and raise the sacred standard of liberty.&amp;rsquo;
Saint-Domingue, the most lucrative colony in the world, is fuelled by the exploitation of 500,000 slaves. But the waves of the French Revolution are washing up on its shores: dreams of liberty, equality, fraternity are spreading on the plantations.</description></item><item><title>Creating Sierra Leone: The Land of the Free | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860038/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860038/</guid><description>Podcast Description These former slaves have fought valiantly for the British and have been promised a new life. With things not working out in North America, eyes turn toward Africa. Could their homeland, from which they had been so brutally torn, offer sanctuary? Listen as William and Anita are again joined by Maya Jasanoff to talk about the attempts to create a colony in Sierra Leone.
This episode is sponsored by BetterHelp.</description></item><item><title>When Slaves Fought for the British Empire | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860039/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860039/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Boston Tea Party has occurred. War has broken out on the American continent. The British need to bolster their forces to keep hold of the 13 colonies, but to whom do they turn? Their own slaves. Listen as William and Anita are joined by Maya Jasanoff to discuss the slaves who fought for the British in the America War of Independence and how they were rewarded afterwards.</description></item><item><title>The Black Abolitionist | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860040/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860040/</guid><description>Podcast Description Olaudah Equiano: slave, free man, captive, abolitionist, public figure, entrepreneur, successful author, family man. His life is one of the most extraordinary tales of ups and down, with more happening to him in one lifetime than happens in ten average ones. Listen as William and Anita discuss it.
Sign up to The Knowledge here: www.theknowledge.com/empire/
LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/empire
This episode is sponsored by BetterHelp. Give online therapy a try at betterhelp.</description></item><item><title>Britain's Most Famous Slave | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860041/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860041/</guid><description>Podcast Description Olaudah Equiano is Britain&amp;rsquo;s most famous slave. In many ways he lived the life which many slaves did, but in others he was totally unique. A brilliant man with extraordinary abilities, listen as William and Anita discuss the life of Olaudah Equiano.
Sign up to The Knowledge here: www.theknowledge.com/empire/
LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/empire
This episode is sponsored by BetterHelp. Give online therapy a try at betterhelp.com/empirepod.
Twitter: @Empirepoduk</description></item><item><title>Francis Barber: Abolition, the Navy, and the Enlightenment | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860042/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Francis Barber is established in Dr Johnson&amp;rsquo;s household. He is his servant, but he is more than that. Their relationship is more akin to father-son, than master-servant. So how did this impact Dr Johnson? And will things remain this way? Listen as William and Anita are once again joined by Peter Moore to discuss the second part of Francis Barber&amp;rsquo;s life
Sign up to The Knowledge here: www.theknowledge.com/empire/</description></item><item><title>Dr Johnson's Black Heir | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860043/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860043/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr Johnson is one of the most famous Brits to ever exist. A raucous, genius of a giant, he is remembered for writing the dictionary. Much less is known about his black servant and heir, Francis Barber. Listen as William and Anita are joined this week by Peter Moore to discuss the life of Francis Barber.
Sign up to The Knowledge here: www.theknowledge.com/empire/
LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/empire
This episode is sponsored by BetterHelp.</description></item><item><title>Tacky's Revolt: An Atlantic Slave War | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860044/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860044/</guid><description>Podcast Description The stage is set. It&amp;rsquo;s 1760 and the enslaved people of Jamaica are ready to rise up. It will begin with Tacky. William and Anita are again joined by Vincent Brown, Professor at Harvard and co-founder of Timestamp Media, to discuss the climax of Tacky&amp;rsquo;s Revolt.
Sign up to The Knowledge here: www.theknowledge.com/empire/
LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/empire
This episode is sponsored by BetterHelp. Give online therapy a try at betterhelp.</description></item><item><title>Tacky's Revolt: Causes of the Rebellion | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860045/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860045/</guid><description>Podcast Description What was life like for enslaved people on the plantations? How did white people treat their slaves? What economic model did plantation owners operate on? William and Anita are joined this week Vincent Brown, Professor at Harvard and co-founder of Timestamp Media, to discuss Tacky&amp;rsquo;s Revolt and in this episode they focus upon the horrific circumstances that slaves had to endure.
**TRIGGER WARNING: this episode contains graphic descriptions of the brutal treatment of slaves, do not listen with children.</description></item><item><title>The Fall of the Royal African Company | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860046/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860046/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Royal African Company has a monopoly on the trading of slaves, given directly by the Stuarts. But the Glorious Revolution sweeps in and they are deposed. How will The Company fare? And, more importantly, how will this affect the transatlantic slave trade? Listen to William and Anita to find out.
Sign up to The Knowledge here: www.theknowledge.com/empire/
LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/empire
This episode is sponsored by BetterHelp. Give online therapy a try at betterhelp.</description></item><item><title>Royal African Company: Slavery Inc | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860047/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860047/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Royal African Company was at the heart of England&amp;rsquo;s involvement in the transatlantic slave trade. From its inception to the abolition of the trade, it was responsible for shipping more enslaved people across the Atlantic than any other organisation. Join William and Anita as they discuss the beginnings of the transatlantic slave trade and the company at the centre of it.
Sign up to The Knowledge here: www.</description></item><item><title>Barbary Corsairs: Raiding the British isles | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860048/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Slave raids on the south coast of Britain. Islamic executioners from Exeter. North African pirates in the Mediterranean. The Barbary slave trade is quite extraordinary. Listen this week as William and Anita are joined by Nabil Matar to discuss it.
Sign up to The Knowledge here: www.theknowledge.com/empire/
LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/empire
This episode is sponsored by BetterHelp. Give online therapy a try at betterhelp.com/empirepod.
Twitter: @Empirepoduk
Goalhangerpodcasts.com
Producer: Callum Hill Exec Producer: Jack Davenport + Neil Fearn Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>The Slave who Ruled | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860049/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Born in Ethiopia, 1548, Malik Ambar was taken from his people at the age of 12 and sold into slavery. First he was sold to an owner in Baghdad, where he converted to Islam, but he ended up in India, on the Deccan plateau. From there, his star rose, eventually to become ruler of the Sultanate Ahmadnagar and the arch-rival of the Mughal Empire. Listen as William and Anita are joined by Manu Pillai to discuss this extraordinary figure.</description></item><item><title>Vikings: Slavs to Slaves | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860050/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860050/</guid><description>Podcast Description Indian beads found on a Viking in Britain, how did this come to be? The story includes the origin of the word slave, a surprising trade, and a horrific funeral ritual. Listen this week as Anita and William are joined by Cat Jarman to discuss the Viking slave trade.
***Tickets for the live show can be bought at the following link from 9am on Wednesday 10th May: https://robomagiclive.com/empire-podcast-live/.</description></item><item><title>Rome: A Slave Society | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860051/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860051/</guid><description>Podcast Description Was Rome a slave society? Did Caesar really take a million Gauls captive? And what is the real story of Spartacus? Listen as William and Anita are joined by Mary Beard to discuss slavery in Ancient Rome.
***Tickets for the live show can be bought at the following link from 9am on Wednesday 10th May: https://robomagiclive.com/empire-podcast-live/.
Sign up to The Knowledge here: www.theknowledge.com/empire/
LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/empire
This episode is sponsored by BetterHelp.</description></item><item><title>The Dawn of Everything | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860052/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is slavery hardwired into society? Is hierarchy inevitable? Who built the pyramids? Listen as William and Anita are joined by David Wengrow to discuss slavery in the world’s most ancient civilizations.
Sign up to The Knowledge here: www.theknowledge.com/empire/
LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/empire
This episode is sponsored by BetterHelp. Give online therapy a try at betterhelp.com/empirepod.
Twitter: @Empirepoduk
Goalhangerpodcasts.com
Producer: Callum Hill Exec Producer: Jack Davenport Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Series 3: The History of Slavery | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860053/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860053/</guid><description>Podcast Description One series ends, another dawns. With the Ottomans now behind us, we move on to the history of slavery. Listen as William and Anita discuss what will be covered in the next series, why they want to do it, and tease a few of the jaw-dropping facts to come.
Sign up to The Knowledge here: www.theknowledge.com/empire/
LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/empire
This episode is sponsored by BetterHelp. Give online therapy a try at betterhelp.</description></item><item><title>Rebels Against the Raj | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860054/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Annie Besant. BG Horniman. Satyanada Stokes. Madeleine Slade. What do they call have in common? They were all Rebels Against the Raj. Listen as Anita and William are joined by Ram Guha to discuss what this means.
Sign up to The Knowledge here: www.theknowledge.com/empire/
LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/empire
This episode is sponsored by BetterHelp. Give online therapy a try at betterhelp.com/empirepod.
Twitter: @Empirepoduk
Goalhangerpodcasts.com
Producer: Callum Hill Exec Producer: Jack Davenport Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>The Mau Mau, the court case, and the hidden documents | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860055/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860055/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Mau Mau emergency began in 1952. Over the next eight years, the British abused thousands of Kenyans; detaining them, torturing them, murdering them. Yet, when Caroline Elkins published her book detailing this in 2005, she was slated for a lack of documentary evidence. Now, one court case and one incredible discovery later, she has been proved totally right. Join William and Anita as they are joined by Caroline Elkins to tell the story in this very special bonus episode of Empire.</description></item><item><title>Successors to the Romans, progressive harems, and living Ottomans | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860056/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Did the Ottomans see themselves as the successors to the Roman Empire? Was the Ottoman harem more progressive than others? How tolerant was the Ottoman Empire? And where are the descendants of the Empire today? Listen as William and Anita answer these questions and more in the very last episode in this series on the Ottomans.
Sign up to The Knowledge here: www.theknowledge.com/empire/
LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/empire
This episode is sponsored by BetterHelp.</description></item><item><title>The Legacy of the Ottomans, Queen of the Desert, and giant turbans | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860057/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860057/</guid><description>Podcast Description How did Ataturk view the Ottomans? What is the status of the Ottoman Empire today? Who was Gertrude Bell? And how did Ottomans wear such big turbans? Listen as William and Anita answer your questions in our end of series Q&amp;amp;A.
LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/empire
This episode is sponsored by BetterHelp. Give online therapy a try at betterhelp.com/empirepod.
Twitter: @Empirepoduk
Goalhangerpodcasts.com
Producer: Callum Hill Exec Producer: Jack Davenport Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>The Birth of Saudi Arabia | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860058/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860058/</guid><description>Podcast Description A Saud. A Bin Laden. A Philby. They all, along with the discovery of oil and a BBC demon, come together in the birth of the modern state of Saudi Arabia. Join William and Anita as they are joined by Steve Coll to discuss Ibn Saud and the creation of Saudi Arabia. LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/empire
This episode is sponsored by BetterHelp. Give online therapy a try at betterhelp.</description></item><item><title>The Fiery End of the Ottoman Empire | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860059/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860059/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Greeks are retreating to Smyrna in the face of Ataturk’s victory. The city, once one of the jewels of the Ottoman kingdom, is set to face devastation hitherto unknown. William and Anita are once again joined by Giles Milton as they discuss the catastrophe that occurred in Smyrna in 1922 and the central role this played in the collapse of the Ottoman Empire.
To hear Giles&amp;rsquo; podcast - Cover Up: Ministry of Secrets - on the great unsolved Cold War mystery of Lionel &amp;lsquo;Buster&amp;rsquo; Crabb, follow this link: https://listen.</description></item><item><title>The Rise of Ataturk | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860060/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860060/</guid><description>Podcast Description The First World War is over. There is unrest across Anatolia, exacerbated by the Greek invasion coming through Smyrna. Turkish forces are swelling to fight back against the Greeks, and at their head&amp;hellip; Mustafa Kemal. Otherwise known as Ataturk. Join William and Anita this week as they are twice joined by Giles Milton to discuss the events of Smyrna in 1922 and the rise of Ataturk.
LRB Empire offer: lrb.</description></item><item><title>Origins of the Israel-Palestine Conflict | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860061/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860061/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Balfour Declaration was published on the 9th November 1917. It stated the intent of the British government to create a Jewish homeland in Palestine. This week, William and Anita are joined by Tom Segev to discuss the declaration and the ensuing British mandate for Palestine.
LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/empire
This episode is sponsored by BetterHelp. Give online therapy a try at betterhelp.com/empirepod.
Twitter: @Empirepoduk
Goalhangerpodcasts.com
Producer: Callum Hill Exec Producer: Jack Davenport Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Lawrence of Arabia and the Arab Revolt | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860062/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860062/</guid><description>Podcast Description Often understood through Peter O’Toole’s iconic display, who really was Lawrence of Arabia? His role in the First World War and the Arab Revolt had a defining effect on the Middle-East. Listen as William and Anita are joined by Anthony Sattin to discuss his life.
LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/empire
This episode is sponsored by BetterHelp. Give online therapy a try at betterhelp.com/empirepod.
Twitter: @Empirepoduk
Goalhangerpodcasts.com
Producer: Callum Hill Exec Producer: Jack Davenport Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Sykes-Picot: Carving up the Middle-East | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860063/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860063/</guid><description>Podcast Description 3 characters. 2 nations. 1 disastrous deal. The Sykes-Picot agreement is often blamed as the cause for much of the unrest in the Middle-East today, but what was it exactly? Listen as William and Anita are joined by James Barr to discuss this historic agreement to carve up the Middle-East.
LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/empire
This episode is sponsored by BetterHelp. Give online therapy a try at betterhelp.com/empirepod.
Twitter: @Empirepoduk</description></item><item><title>The Armenian Genocide: Death Marches | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860064/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860064/</guid><description>Podcast Description The secret orders have been given. The Armenian community is to be destroyed. Ordered to march across the desert, to unsupplied camps in Deir ez-Zor. Listen as William and Anita are, for the final time, joined by Eugene Rogan to discuss the end of the Genocide and its aftermath. LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/empire
This episode is sponsored by BetterHelp. Give online therapy a try at betterhelp.com/empirepod.
Twitter: @Empirepoduk</description></item><item><title>The Armenian Genocide: Road to the Deportations | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860065/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860065/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Armenian community has ancient, deep roots in Anatolia. But from the late 19th century onwards, violence and forced deportations at the hands of the Ottoman Empire puts them in doubt. Listen as William and Anita are once again joined by Eugene Rogan as they discuss one of the most tragic events of world history.
LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/empire
This episode is sponsored by BetterHelp. Give online therapy a try at betterhelp.</description></item><item><title>Gallipoli: Death at the Cliff Edge | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860066/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860066/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Great War has begun. The British want to open supply lines through the Black Sea to support their Russian allies. Therefore they must take the Gallipoli peninsula. Cue one of the most famous events of the First World War. Listen as William and Anita are again joined by Eugene Rogan to discuss the attempts to take Gallipoli and the brutal fighting that ensued.
LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/empire</description></item><item><title>The Sick Man of Europe | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860067/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860067/</guid><description>Podcast Description The winds of nationalism are blowing through Ottoman territory in the Balkans. Unrest is rife and the Empire is bankrupt. The young sultan Abdülhamid is at the helm. Listen as William and Anita are joined by Eugene Rogan to discuss whether the Ottoman Empire really was the sick man of Europe in the run-up to the First World War.
LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/empire
This episode is sponsored by BetterHelp.</description></item><item><title>Lady Mary: Our Woman in Constantinople | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860068/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860068/</guid><description>Podcast Description She was a pioneering scientist, proto-feminist, and letter writer extraordinaire. Lady Mary Wortley Montagu escaped a marriage to Clotworthy Skeffington to become one of history&amp;rsquo;s most incredible women. Listen this week as William and Anita are joined by Katie Hickman to tell the tale of her life.
IRC link: https://www.rescue.org/uk DEC link: https://donation.dec.org.uk/turkey-syria-earthquake-appeal
LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/empire
This episode is sponsored by BetterHelp. Give online therapy a try at betterhelp.</description></item><item><title>The Greatest Ottoman Adventurer | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860069/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860069/</guid><description>Podcast Description Evliya Çelebi travelled for 41 years. He documented his adventures, which included interactions with vampires, humans transforming into chickens, and dervishes riding rhinos. Listen as William and Anita are joined by Caroline Finkel to discuss this man and the vivid descriptions he provided of the Ottoman Empire.
This episode was recorded before the devastating earthquake hit Turkey and Syria. Our thoughts are with those who have been affected.</description></item><item><title>Conquering the Night: The History of Coffee | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860070/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Coffee is everywhere today, but where does it come from? Was it originally a sex drug? What is the connection between Starbucks and a medieval goat herder? Why are coffee houses political? Listen as Anita and William are joined by Cemal Kafadar to discuss the history of the substance.
LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/empire
Twitter: @Empirepoduk
Goalhangerpodcasts.com
Producer: Callum Hill Exec Producer: Jack Davenport Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Sultanas to Slaves: Voices from the Harem | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860071/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860071/</guid><description>Podcast Description What was life like for women in the Ottoman Empire? Was the Sultanate of Women the golden era? What was the role of the Harem? Listen as William and Anita are joined by Bettany Hughes to discuss the role of women in the Ottoman Empire.
LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/empire
Twitter: @Empirepoduk
Goalhangerpodcasts.com
Producer: Callum Hill Exec Producer: Jack Davenport Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Tudors and the Turks | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860072/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Slave raids in Cornwall. Englishmen spying for the venetians. The East India Trading Companies’ older brother. Join William and Anita this week as they discuss the relationship between Britain and the Ottoman Empire, all of which centre around the Levant Company.
LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/empire
Twitter: @Empirepoduk
Goalhangerpodcasts.com
Producer: Callum Hill Exec Producer: Jack Davenport Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Battle of Lepanto | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860073/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dawn breaks on the 7th October 1571 over the Gulf of Patras. On this day, the Holy League will face down the Ottomans in one of the most pivotal battles in Ottoman history. Listen as William and Anita are once again joined by Barnaby Rogerson to discuss the Battle of Lepanto, its significance, and whether it really was the last crusade.
LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/xempire
Twitter: @Empirepoduk
Goalhangerpodcasts.com</description></item><item><title>The Siege of Cyprus | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860074/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Selim II leads the Ottomans. Marco Brigadin the Venetians. They will clash over the island of Cyprus. But who will be victorious, and who will be defeated (and flayed)? The two sides meet on this mediterranean island in the run-up to one of the greatest naval battles in history - the Battle of Lepanto. Listen as William and Anita are joined by Barnaby Rogerson to discuss the Ottoman siege of Cyprus, as they set the stage for Thursday&amp;rsquo;s episode on the Battle of Lepanto.</description></item><item><title>Suspicion and Sorrow in Suleiman's Court | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860075/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Murdered love interests, intellectual curiosity, incredible barbarity, and body doubles all make an appearance in this week’s episode. Listen as William and Anita are once again joined by Marc Baer to discuss the remainder of Suleiman the Magnificent’s rule. To get your free two week trial for Find my past, go to www.findmypast.co.uk and sign up. LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/xempire Twitter: @Empirepoduk Goalhangerpodcasts.com Producer: Callum Hill Exec Producer: Jack Davenport Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Suleiman the Magnificent | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860076/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2022 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Who is Selim the Grim? How does a slave come to be one of the most powerful members of Suleiman’s court? How does Suleiman anger the Christian powers? Listen as William and Anita are joined by Marc Baer to discuss the rule of Suleiman the Magnificent, in particular his love interests and the very Game of Thrones-style intrigue they create.
To get your free two week trial for Find my past, go to www.</description></item><item><title>The Fall of Constantinople | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860077/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860077/</guid><description>Podcast Description The biggest gun in history. A giant underwater chain. A previously unconquerable fortress. Inspirational leaders. Join William and Anita as they discuss the extraordinary story of 1453 and the Fall of Constantinople.
To get your free two week trial for Find my past, go to www.findmypast.co.uk and sign up. LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/xempire Twitter: @Empirepoduk Goalhangerpodcasts.com Producer: Callum Hill Exec Producer: Jack Davenport Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>The First of the Ottomans | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860078/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 02:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860078/</guid><description>Podcast Description How did the Ottomans seize the Balkans? Who is their first leader? How did the fourth crusade pave the way for their rise to power? Join William and Anita as they, along with Peter Frankopan, detail the birth of the Ottoman Empire, discuss its founder, Osman I, and set the scene for 1453.
To get your free two week trial for Find my past, go to www.findmypast.co.uk and sign up.</description></item><item><title>Byzantium and the Rise of the Turks | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860079/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860079/</guid><description>Podcast Description The lights are dimmed. A hush has fallen. The curtain is rising. Season two of Empire is here. Our topic? The Ottoman Empire. In the opening episode, Anita and William are joined by Peter Frankopan to discuss Byzantium and the rise of the Seljuk Turks. LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/xempire Twitter: @Empirepoduk Goalhangerpodcasts.com Producer: Callum Hill Exec Producer: Jack Davenport Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Series 2: The Ottoman Empire | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860080/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 01:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860080/</guid><description>Podcast Description How did an Empire that stretched over thousands of miles and over half a millennium impact the world we live in today? William and Anita explain the focus for the second series of the Empire, which will focus on the Ottoman Empire. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Nationhood, the Indian constitution, and the railways | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860081/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join William and Anita for the second part of this week’s special question time bonanza where they answer all of your queries. In this episode they discuss the impact Jallianwala Bagh had upon Indian nationhood, the influence that Britain had upon the writing of the Indian constitution, and whether the railways did benefit India.
To get your free two week trial for Find my past, go to www.findmypast.co.uk and sign up.</description></item><item><title>Federal India, indentured labour, and naked yogis | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860082/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860082/</guid><description>Podcast Description This week, Anita and William are doing two episodes in which they answer all of your questions about Empire. Join William and Anita today as they discuss whether partition was inevitable, why the British never settled India, what the best books on Empire are, and much much more.
To get your free two week trial for Find my past, go to www.findmypast.co.uk and sign up. LRB Empire offer: lrb.</description></item><item><title>The Empire Implodes | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860083/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860083/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the finale of our series on the British in India, William and Anita are joined by Sathnam Sanghera. With him they discuss the legacies of the Empire: how has it affected the politics, curriculum, and national institutions of modern Britain?
To get your free two week trial for Find my past, go to www.findmypast.co.uk and sign up. LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/empire Twitter: @Empirepoduk Goalhangerpodcasts.com Producer: Callum Hill Exec Producer: Jack Davenport Learn more about your ad choices.</description></item><item><title>Rishi Sunak's Ancestry: Indians in East Africa | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860084/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860084/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Anita and William are joined by Mahmood Mamdani to discuss the East African Indian diaspora. How did Indians come to live in East Africa? Why did so many move to Britain? What was the role of Idi Amin in all of this?
To get your free two week trial for Find my past, go to www.findmypast.co.uk and sign up. LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/empire Twitter: @Empirepoduk Goalhangerpodcasts.</description></item><item><title>Partition | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860085/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860085/</guid><description>Podcast Description The line has been drawn. India and Pakistan have been divided. Mountbatten and Radcliffe have left. But how will ordinary people caught up in this geopolitical event fare? Listen as William and Anita are joined by Kavita Puri to discuss the impact partition had on real lives.
http://www.projectdastaan.org/
To get your free two week trial for Find my past, go to www.findmypast.co.uk and sign up. LRB Empire offer: lrb.</description></item><item><title>The Last Viceroy of India | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860086/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860086/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Anita and William are joined by Alex von Tunzelmann to discuss Lord Louis Mountbatten, the last Viceroy of India. Listen in to hear all about his superstar marriage to Edwina Ashley, his relationships with key figures such as Nehru and Jinnah, and the role he played in the partition of India. To get your free two week trial for Find my past, go to www.findmypast.co.uk and sign up.</description></item><item><title>Muhammad Ali Jinnah | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860087/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Listen as William and Anita discuss the life of Muhammad Ali Jinnah. They will discuss the pivotal role he played in the creation of Pakistan, his rivalry with Gandhi, and the vision he had for his nation&amp;rsquo;s future. Plus, we are very fortunate to be joined at the end by the wonderful Ayesha Jalal.
To get your free two week trial for Find my past, go to www.findmypast.co.uk and sign up.</description></item><item><title>The Patient Assassin | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860088/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join William and Anita as they discuss the life of Udham Singh, who is as much man as he is myth. Coming from nothing, he killed a leopard with a knife as a toddler, then joined the revolutionary Ghadar Party, smuggled himself across the US-Mexico border, and on 13th March 1940 committed his most infamous act…
To get your free two week trial for Find my past, go to www.</description></item><item><title>Sophia: Princess, Suffragette, Revolutionary | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860089/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join William and Anita as they discuss the extraordinary life of Princess Sophia. Her story includes a debut at Buckingham Palace, a meeting with Gandhi, fierce involvement in the suffragette movement, and the First World War.
LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/empire
Twitter: @EmpirePodUk
goalhangerpodcasts.com
Producer: Callum Hill Exec Producer: Jack Davenport Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Queens and the Koh-i-Noor | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860090/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860090/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join William and Anita for the final episode in their series on the Koh-i-Noor diamond. This remarkable story includes Prince Albert’s inadvertent creation of Britain’s first sauna, an elderly Duke of Wellington cutting the diamond, and the contemporary significance of the Koh-i-Noor.
LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/empire Twitter: @empirepoduk Goalhangerpodcasts.com
Producer: Callum Hill Exec Producer: Jack Davenport Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Killing for the Koh-i-Noor | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860091/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Divide and rule, a man described as Brian Blessed but ‘with a bigger, bushier, blacker beard’, and a whole lot of regicide. Join Anita and William as they continue to take us through the rip-roaring history of the Koh-i-Noor diamond.
LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/empire Twitter: @EmpirePodUk goalhangerpodcasts.com
Producer: Callum Hill Exec Producer: Jack Davenport Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Curse of the Koh-i-Noor | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860092/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860092/</guid><description>Podcast Description Intense paranoia, palatial looting, and murder. Join Anita and William as they discuss the bloody origins of The Curse of the Koh-i-Noor.
Twitter: @EmpirePodUk Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Koh-i-Noor Diamond | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860093/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860093/</guid><description>Podcast Description A single stone has been fought over for at least 250 years by four different empires, and now sits in the Queen Consort&amp;rsquo;s crown as part of the British royal family&amp;rsquo;s Crown Jewels. William and Anita trace the murky history of one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most famous diamonds. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Mahatma Gandhi | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860094/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860094/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the latest episode of Empire, William and Anita are joined by Ram Guha to explore the incredible life and story of Mahatma Gandhi.
LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/empire
Email: empirepoduk@gmail.com Instagram: @EmpirePodUK Twitter: @EmpirePodUK
goalhangerpodcasts.com Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Queen Elizabeth II &amp; Empire (with David Olusoga) | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860095/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Anita and Willie are joined by David Olusoga for a special episode of Empire, where they discuss the Queen, the Commonwealth, the future of the monarchy and the long shadow of Empire.
LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/empire
Email: empirepoduk@gmail.com Instagram: @EmpirePodUK Twitter: @EmpirePodUK
goalhangerpodcasts.com Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Jallianwala Bagh Massacre | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860096/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860096/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the latest episode of Empire, Willie and Anita dive into the story of the Jallianwala Bagh massacre, alongside Professor Kim Wagner. Plus a discussion as to whether analysing the darker parts of a country’s history is the same as talking it down.
LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/empire
Email: empirepoduk@gmail.com Instagram: @EmpirePodUK Twitter: @EmpirePodUK
goalhangerpodcasts.com Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Between Two Massacres: 1857-1919 | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860097/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860097/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join William and Anita for the latest episode of Empire, which picks up in the aftermath of the 1857 Rebellion and the establishment of the British Raj. The episode covers the birth of Gandhi, the arrival of Michael O&amp;rsquo;Dwyer, Indian soldiers in the First World War, and the lead up to the Jallianwala Bagh massacre.
LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/empire Twitter: @EmpirePodUk goalhangerpodcasts.com Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>Mutiny, Uprising, and Rebellion | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860098/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860098/</guid><description>Podcast Description In 1857 tensions in Company-controlled India came to a head in what the British called &amp;lsquo;The Indian Mutiny&amp;rsquo;, now referred to in India as the First War of Independence. The uprising and bloody reprisals sent shockwaves through the Empire, ended the rule of the East India Company, and led to the creation of the Raj.
LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/empire Twitter: @EmpirePodUk goalhangerpodcasts.com Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.</description></item><item><title>Company Rule in India | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860099/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 01:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Emerging victorious from the Battles of Plassey and Buxar, The East India Company cements its grip on power in India.
Join Anita and William as they discuss the nature, horrors, and key figures of &amp;lsquo;Company Rule&amp;rsquo; in India at its height in the early 19th Century.
LRB Empire offer: lrb.me/empire Twitter: @EmpirePodUk goalhangerpodcasts.com Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The East India Company | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860100/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860100/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to Empire, a brand new history podcast hosted by William Dalrymple and Anita Anand.
The first series looks at the British in India: The East India Company, The Raj, Gandhi, Independence and Partition.
In the opening episode, William and Anita discuss the rise of The East India Company, exploring how a small corporation founded in Tudor England - with only a handful of employees - came to rule India.</description></item><item><title>Trailer | Empire</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8785860101/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 13:19:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8785860101/</guid><description>Podcast Description How do empires rise? Why do they fall? And how have they shaped the world around us today?
William Dalrymple and Anita Anand explore the stories, personalities and events of empire over the course of history.
The first series looks at the British in India, covering the East India Company, the Raj, Gandhi, Independence and Partition. Learn more about your ad choices. Visit podcastchoices.com/adchoices
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>