<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Corny - The last Irishman in the NFL on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/corny-the-last-irishman-in-the-nfl/</link><description>Recent content in Corny - The last Irishman in the NFL on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:55:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/corny-the-last-irishman-in-the-nfl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>4th Quarter - The Future | Corny - The last Irishman in the NFL</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2432990001/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:55:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2432990001/</guid><description>Podcast Description In our final episode, the spotlight is on Corny as he faces the most significant kick of his illustrious career on the grandest stage of the NFL. The question looms: Can he deliver the goods, or will time prove to be his adversary in this high-stakes moment?
As we bid farewell to a football legend with Corny's retirement from the NFL, the episode also turns its gaze toward the promising future of Irish talent in the league.</description></item><item><title>3rd Quarter - The Pro | Corny - The last Irishman in the NFL</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2432990002/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2432990002/</guid><description>Podcast Description In Episode 3, witness Neil's triumphant return to the top tier of the NFL, donning the colors of the young and dynamic Tampa Bay Buccaneers. As he contributes to the team's success, a pivotal moment unfolds, solidifying his place in Bucs history.
However, the plot thickens as Neil's journey takes an unexpected turn. A twist of fate brings him face to face with Jim Hanifan, coach of the St.</description></item><item><title>2nd Quarter - The Draft | Corny - The last Irishman in the NFL</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2432990003/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2432990003/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode follows Corny's gripping journey as he grapples with the challenges of a new life in the USA. Join him as he struggles to acclimatize to unfamiliar surroundings and then shift dramatically from soccer to college football.
Hear how his resilience in the face of adversity and his determination to redefine his path culminates in a thrilling twist as Corny transitions from college football to the pinnacle of sports – being drafted into the NFL.</description></item><item><title>1st Quarter - The Scholarship | Corny - The last Irishman in the NFL</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2432990004/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2432990004/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, we unravel Neil's extraordinary journey from Clondalkin, Dublin, to the USA. Discover the tight familial bonds that shaped him and the pivotal soccer scholarship decision that altered his life forever. Join us for a captivating tale of family, choices, and the unexpected turns that define a lifetime. Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trailer | Corny - The last Irishman in the NFL</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/2432990005/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/2432990005/</guid><description>Podcast Description It's been 40 years since an Irishman played in the NFL and his story has been untold... until now!
Meet Neil O'Donoghue, the 6-foot 6 Dublin native who kicked his way to the top of American Football. His journey takes us from the heart of Ireland to arenas of American football.
This is a resurrection of a forgotten hero from an era of fierce competition and unbreakable spirit.</description></item></channel></rss>