<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Peter Attia Drive on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/the-peter-attia-drive/</link><description>Recent content in The Peter Attia Drive on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 09:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/the-peter-attia-drive/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>#283 ‒ Gut health &amp; the microbiome: improving and maintaining the microbiome, probiotics, prebiotics, innovative treatments, and more | Colleen Cutcliffe, Ph.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000326/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000326/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Colleen Cutcliffe is an expert in molecular biology and co-founder of Pendulum Therapeutics, a company working to develop treatments for a variety of diseases by targeting the microbiome. In this episode, Colleen delves into the complexity of the microbiome, how it is tested, and how it changes over time.</description></item><item><title>#282 - AMA #54: Magnesium: risks of deficiency, how to correct it, supplement options, potential cognitive and sleep benefits, and more | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000001/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000001/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter tackles essential questions about magnesium, beginning with the important roles it plays in the body and why maintaining proper levels is crucial. Peter discusses the harms of magnesium deficiency, how to determine if you're deficient, potential causes of deficiency, and how diet and supplementation can be used to increase magnesium levels.</description></item><item><title>#281 ‒ Longevity drugs, aging biomarkers, and updated findings from the Interventions Testing Program (ITP) | Rich Miller, M.D., Ph.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000002/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Richard Miller is a professor of pathology and the Director of the Center for Aging Research at the University of Michigan, as well as a previous guest on The Drive. In this episode, Rich provides an update on the exciting work of the Interventions Testing Program (ITP), an initiative designed to assess potential life-extending interventions in mice.</description></item><item><title>#280 ‒ Cultivating happiness, emotional self-management, and more | Arthur Brooks Ph.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000003/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Arthur Brooks is a social scientist, professor at Harvard University, columnist for The Atlantic, and bestselling author. In this episode, Arthur returns to the podcast to discuss his new book, Build the Life You Want. He delves into the nuanced concept of happiness, differentiating between momentary feelings and overall wellbeing.</description></item><item><title>The world’s most important doctor to millions in the war-torn and remote villages of Sudan | Tom Catena, M.D. (#40 rebroadcast) | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000004/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000004/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
To support Tom’s mission and work, please visit: https://africanmissionhealthcare.org/donation/catena/.
In this episode, Tom Catena, a missionary physician who runs Mother of Mercy Hospital in the Nuba Mountains in Sudan, describes some of his extraordinary work as the only doctor in a remote, war-torn region of Africa. In terms of individual lives saved, you could argue that there is no other person on the front lines doing more than Tom.</description></item><item><title>#279 - AMA #53: Metabolic health &amp; pharmacologic interventions: SGLT-2 inhibitors, metformin, GLP-1 agonists, and the impact of statins | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000005/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000005/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter explores various pharmacologic tools commonly utilized to improve metabolic health and treat diabetes, including SGLT-2 inhibitors, metformin, and GLP-1 agonists. He examines the available data on these drugs, assessing their comparative effectiveness and their potential in the context of lifestyle interventions.</description></item><item><title>#278 ‒ Breast cancer: how to catch, treat, and survive breast cancer | Harold Burstein, M.D., Ph.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000006/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000006/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Harold (Hal) Burstein is an internationally renowned breast cancer expert. In this episode, Hal discusses a broad range of topics related to breast cancer, starting with the intricacies of breast anatomy and the endocrinological factors at play. He covers the spectrum of breast cancer, from precancerous lesions to invasive breast cancer, classifying these conditions into a helpful framework.</description></item><item><title>#277 ‒ Food allergies: causes, prevention, and treatment with immunotherapy | Kari Nadeau, M.D., Ph.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000007/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000007/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Kari Nadeau is a physician scientist with expertise in treating food allergies. In this episode, Kari first explains the fascinating workings of the immune system, exploring how it adeptly defends against bacteria and viruses but how the same system can lead to food allergies. She proceeds to explore the complexities of food allergies, detailing their typical developmental patterns, underscoring the significance of preventative approaches like early exposure, and highlighting the potentially life-threatening nature of severe food allergies.</description></item><item><title>#276 ‒ Special episode: Peter answers questions on longevity, supplements, protein, fasting, apoB, statins, and more | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000008/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
In this special episode of The Drive, Peter discusses a variety of topics, breaking away from the typical deep-dive format to explore a wide range of common questions submitted by listeners. Peter tackles subjects like the viability of living to 120 and beyond, addressing some of the optimistic theories regarding achievement of this remarkable feat.</description></item><item><title>#275 - AMA #52: Hormone replacement therapy: practical applications and the role of compounding pharmacies | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000009/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000009/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
In this "Ask Me Anything" (AMA) episode, the discussion zeroed in on the practical application of hormone replacement therapy in women. Peter walks through the signs, symptoms, and hormonal changes in women approaching – and going through – menopause. He provides an overview of the FDA-approved HRT formulations and explains how women might go about choosing the right option for themselves.</description></item><item><title>#274 - Performance-enhancing drugs and hormones: risks, rewards, and broader implications for the public | Derek: More Plates, More Dates | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000010/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000010/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
We discuss:
Derek’s interest in weightlifting and experimentation with anabolic steroids at a young age [3:15]; Derek’s experience acquiring steroids from underground labs and the potential long-term fertility concerns early in his bodybuilding career [12:00]; The backstory on More Plates, More Dates and Derek’s unique ability to blend scientific knowledge with personal observation [17:00]; Growth hormone – from extreme use-cases to the more typical – and the misconception that it’s the “elixir of life” [21:30]; Growth hormone 101: definition, where it comes from, and the challenges of measuring it [28:45]; Does exogenous growth hormone compromise one’s ability to make endogenous growth hormone?</description></item><item><title>#273 ‒ Prostate health: common problems, cancer prevention, screening, treatment, and more | Ted Schaeffer, M.D., Ph.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000011/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000011/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Ted Schaeffer is an internationally recognized urologist who specializes in prostate cancer. In this episode, Ted delves deep into the realm of prostate health, starting with strategies for vigilance and effective management of the issues that can arise with aging, including urinary symptoms, prostatitis, pelvic pain, and prostate inflammation.</description></item><item><title>#272 ‒ Rapamycin: potential longevity benefits, surge in popularity, unanswered questions, and more | David Sabatini, M.D., Ph.D. and Matt Kaeberlein, Ph.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000012/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000012/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
In this episode of The Drive, Peter welcomes guests David Sabatini and Matt Kaeberlein, two world-leading experts on rapamycin and mTOR. David and Matt begin by telling the fascinating story of the discovery of rapamycin and its brief history as a pharmacological agent in humans. They then unravel the function of mTOR, a central regulator of numerous biological processes, and they discuss the pathways through which rapamycin exerts its potential benefits on lifespan.</description></item><item><title>#271 - AMA #51: Understanding and improving your metabolic health | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000013/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000013/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter dives deep into the critical topic of metabolic disease. He first sheds light on how poor metabolic health drives up the risk of developing other chronic diseases such as cardiovascular disease, cancer, neurodegenerative disease, and overall mortality. He explores the array of metrics and tests used to assess metabolic health, underscoring his preferred methodologies utilized with patients.</description></item><item><title>#270 ‒ Journal club with Andrew Huberman: metformin as a geroprotective drug, the power of belief, and how to read scientific papers | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000014/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000014/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Andrew Huberman, Professor of Neurobiology at Stanford University and host of the Huberman Lab podcast joins us in a special journal club episode. Peter and Andrew each present a recent paper that sparked their interests, delving into the findings, dissecting their significance, discussing potential confounders and limitations, and exploring remaining questions.</description></item><item><title>#269 - Good vs. bad science: how to read and understand scientific studies | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000015/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
This special episode is a rebroadcast of AMA #30, now made available to everyone, in which Peter and Bob Kaplan dive deep into all things related to studying studies to help one sift through the noise to find the signal. They define various types of studies, how a study progresses from idea to execution, and how to identify study strengths and limitations.</description></item><item><title>#268 ‒ Genetics: testing, therapy, editing, association with disease risk, autism, and more | Wendy Chung, M.D., Ph.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000016/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Wendy Chung is a board-certified clinical and molecular geneticist with more than 25 years of experience in human genetic disease research. In this episode, Wendy delves deep into the world of genetics by first exploring the historical landscape of genetics prior to decoding the human genome, contrasting it with what we know today thanks to whole genome and exome sequencing.</description></item><item><title>#267 ‒ The latest in cancer therapeutics, diagnostics, and early detection | Keith Flaherty, M.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000017/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000017/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Keith Flaherty is the director of clinical research at the Massachusetts General Hospital Cancer Center and a previous guest on The Drive. In this episode, Keith first delves into the statistics on cancer's prevalence as we age, underscoring the significance of finding effective treatments and early detection methodologies.</description></item><item><title>#266 - AMA #50: Genetics: how they impact disease risk, what you can do about it, testing, and more | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000018/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000018/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
In this "Ask Me Anything" (AMA) episode, Peter delves into the realm of genetics, unraveling its connection to disease and emphasizing the value of understanding one's genetic risks. He elucidates essential background knowledge on genetics before delving into the myriad reasons why individuals might consider genetic testing.</description></item><item><title>#265 - Time, productivity, and purpose: insights from Four Thousand Weeks | Oliver Burkeman | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000019/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000019/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Oliver Burkeman is the author of The New York Times best-seller Four Thousand Weeks: Time Management for Mortals. In this episode, Oliver delves into the pervasive idea that time can be mastered, exploring whether maximizing productivity is an attainable goal or a perpetual trap. He discusses the allure of attempting to control time—and, therefore, the future—and shares his personal journey of experimenting with diverse time management techniques that failed to deliver the emotional satisfaction he sought.</description></item><item><title>#264 ‒ Hip, knee, ankle, and foot: common injuries, prevention, and treatment options | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000020/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000020/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Adam Cohen is an orthopedic surgeon with expertise in sports medicine. In this episode, Adam breaks down the anatomy of the lower extremities: the hip, knee, ankle, and foot. He explains in detail the common injuries, sources of pain, and what leads to the development of arthritis.</description></item><item><title>#263 ‒ Concussions and head trauma: symptoms, treatment, and recovery | Micky Collins, Ph.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000021/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Michael “Micky” Collins is an internationally renowned expert in sports-related concussions and a consultant for multiple professional sports organizations. In this episode, Mickey first explains the definition and diagnosis of a concussion, as well as the diverse signs and symptoms associated with different types of concussions. He discusses the risk factors that contribute to increased susceptibility and/or severity of concussions in certain individuals, emphasizes the significance of prompt treatment, and uses case studies to illustrate the latest in treatment protocols and recovery process.</description></item><item><title>#262 - AMA #49: Heart rate recovery, strength training, rucking, kidney function, and brain health | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000022/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000022/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter's Weekly Newsletter
In this "Ask Me Anything" (AMA) episode, Peter goes into depth on the topic of brain health, starting with how Alzheimer's disease is diagnosed, the significance of blood-based biomarkers in diagnosis, and what the various APOE gene variants mean in terms of a person's risk of developing Alzheimer's disease.</description></item><item><title>#261 ‒ Training for The Centenarian Decathlon: zone 2, VO2 max, stability, and strength | Peter Attia, M.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000023/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
In this special episode filmed live in front of readers of Outlive, Peter answers questions revolving around his concept of the centenarian decathlon. He starts by defining the “marginal decade” and how that shapes his training for the events and activities that make up his personal centenarian decathlon.</description></item><item><title>Cancer screening with full-body MRI scans and a seminar on the field of radiology | Rajpaul Attariwala, M.D., Ph.D. (#61 rebroadcast) | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000024/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
In this episode, radiologist/engineer, Raj Attariwala, explains how he was able to apply his engineering background to create a unique MRI scanner that is capable of constructing whole-body images with a resolution that is unmatched in the industry. Peter and Raj discuss the implications of such a robust, radiation-free imaging tool on the early detection of cancer.</description></item><item><title>#260 ‒ Men’s Sexual Health: why it matters, what can go wrong, and how to fix it | Mohit Khera, M.D., M.B.A., M.P.H. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000025/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000025/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Mohit Khera is a world-renowned urologist with expertise in sexual medicine and testosterone therapy. In this episode, Mohit provides a comprehensive overview of male sexual health. He begins with an in-depth exploration of erectile dysfunction, shedding light on its prevalence across different age groups, diagnostic methods, and its intriguing connection to cardiovascular disease.</description></item><item><title>#259 - Women's sexual health: Why it matters, what can go wrong, and how to fix it | Sharon Parish, M.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000026/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000026/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter's Weekly Newsletter
Sharon Parish is a Professor of Medicine in Clinical Medicine and Clinical Psychiatry at Weill Cornell Medical College and a prominent sexual medicine specialist who has been practicing for 30 years. In this episode, Sharon tackles the topic of women's sexual health, including the conditions associated with decreased sexual function and desire and available treatment options.</description></item><item><title>#258 - AMA #48: Blood pressure—how to measure, manage, and treat high blood pressure | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000027/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000027/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter delves into the critical subject of blood pressure, which is one of the three primary causes of atherosclerosis, along with high apoB and smoking. He begins by unraveling the nature of high blood pressure, its prevalence, and why it often goes undiagnosed.</description></item><item><title>#257 ‒ Cognitive decline, neurodegeneration, and head injuries: mitigation and prevention strategies, supplements, and more | Tommy Wood, M.D., Ph.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000028/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000028/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Tommy Wood is an Assistant Professor of Pediatrics at the University of Washington, where he studies brain injury and how lifestyle choices and environmental factors contribute to brain health, cognitive function, and chronic disease. In this episode, Tommy delves into the complexities of age-related cognitive decline and explores interventions to counteract it.</description></item><item><title>#256 ‒ The endocrine system: exploring thyroid, adrenal, and sex hormones | Peter Attia, M.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000029/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000029/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
In this special episode of The Drive, Peter provides a comprehensive overview of the various endocrine systems: the thyroid system, the adrenal system, and the sex hormone system (for both men and women). He walks through the basic biology and the feedback cycles that regulate the production of these hormones and discusses the various options for the treatment of hormone deficiencies.</description></item><item><title>#255 ‒ Latest therapeutics in CVD, APOE’s role in Alzheimer’s disease and CVD, familial hypercholesterolemia, and more | John Kastelein, M.D., Ph.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000030/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000030/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
John Kastelein is a renowned expert in lipoprotein metabolism and atherosclerotic cardiovascular disease (ASCVD) research. In this discussion, John delves deep into familial hypercholesterolemia (FH), a genetic disorder characterized by high levels of LDL cholesterol in the blood that increases the risk of developing heart disease. He covers its definition, genetic underpinnings, and clinical identification.</description></item><item><title>#254 - AMA #47: Cold therapy: pros, cons, and its impact on longevity | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000031/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000031/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter delves deep into the data surrounding different forms of cold therapy, including cold water immersion, cryotherapy, and cold showers, aiming to unveil the potential benefits and drawbacks associated with cold therapy. He dissects the studies examining the effects of cold therapy on delayed onset muscle soreness (DOMS), activation of brown adipose tissue, and its potential impact on mood and as a therapeutic approach for depression.</description></item><item><title>#253 ‒ Hormone replacement therapy and the Women’s Health Initiative: re-examining the results, the link to breast cancer, and weighing the risk vs reward of HRT | JoAnn Manson, M.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000032/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000032/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
JoAnn Manson is a world-renowned endocrinologist, epidemiologist, and Principal Investigator for the Women’s Health Initiative (WHI). In this episode, she dives deep into the WHI to explain the study design, primary outcome, confounding factors, and nuanced benefits and risks of hormone replacement therapy (HRT). JoAnn reflects on how a misinterpretation of the results, combined with sensationalized headlines regarding an elevated risk of breast cancer, led to a significant shift in the perception and utilization of HRT.</description></item><item><title>#252 ‒ Latest insights on Alzheimer’s disease, cancer, exercise, nutrition, and fasting | Rhonda Patrick, Ph.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000033/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000033/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Rhonda Patrick, Ph.D., is a scientist with expertise in the areas of aging, cancer, and nutrition who translates complex scientific topics into actionable insights on her podcast, Found My Fitness. In this episode, Rhonda provides her latest thinking as it relates to Alzheimer's disease including the possibility of a vascular hypothesis as well as the factors that can impact disease risk such as type 2 diabetes, blood pressure, omega supplementation, exercise, sauna, and more.</description></item><item><title>The impact of stress on our physical and emotional health | Robert Sapolsky, Ph.D. (#51 rebroadcast) | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000034/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000034/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
In this episode, Robert Sapolsky, Ph.D., discusses the widespread impact of stress on our physical and emotional health as well as the mechanisms by which it can precipitate chronic illness, dementia, depression, and more. He also provides insight into the factors that contribute to the stress response (and our ability to handle it) such as social rank, personality, environment, and genetics.</description></item><item><title>#251 - AMA #46: Optimizing brain health: Alzheimer's disease risk factors, APOE, prevention strategies, and more | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000035/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000035/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter goes into depth on the topic of brain health, starting with how Alzheimer's disease is diagnosed, the significance of blood-based biomarkers in diagnosis, and what the various APOE gene variants mean in terms of a person's risk of developing Alzheimer's disease.</description></item><item><title>#250 ‒ Training principles for longevity | Andy Galpin, Ph.D. (PART II) | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000036/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000036/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Andy Galpin is a Professor of Kinesiology at California State University at Fullerton, where he studies muscle adaptation and applies his research to work with professional athletes. In this episode, Andy returns to the podcast and continues the conversation about training for longevity. He examines the training practices of powerlifters, Olympic weightlifters, Strongmen/women, CrossFit athletes, and sprinters in order to extract insights that can be applied to the individual wanting to optimize for longevity.</description></item><item><title>#249 ‒ How the brain works, Andrew’s fascinating backstory, improving scientific literacy, and more | Andrew Huberman, Ph.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000037/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000037/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Andrew Huberman is a Professor of Neurobiology at Stanford University and host of the Huberman Lab podcast. In this episode, Andrew begins with a fascinating discussion about the brain, including the role of the prefrontal cortex in adjusting your ruleset to match your setting, the neural circuitry underlying the ability of stress to limit creativity and problem-solving, the effect of belief on physiology and performance, and more.</description></item><item><title>#248 ‒ OUTLIVE book: A behind-the-scenes look into the writing of this book, motivation, main themes, and more | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000038/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Order OUTLIVE
View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
After more than six years of research, planning, and writing, Peter’s book, Outlive: The Science and Art of Longevity, is officially available as of March 28th. In this episode, Peter sits down with co-author Bill Gifford to provide a behind-the-scenes look into the writing process, including the motivation for making it happen, how the book evolved over the course of the writing process, and why certain topics were chosen (and omitted).</description></item><item><title>#247 ‒ Preventing cardiovascular disease: the latest in diagnostic imaging, blood pressure, metabolic health, and more | Ethan Weiss, M.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000039/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000039/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Ethan Weiss is a preventative cardiologist at UCSF, an entrepreneur-in-residence at Third Rock Ventures, where he is working on a project related to cardiometabolic disease, and a previous guest on The Drive. In this episode, Ethan compares and contrasts the diagnostic imaging tools, CAC (coronary artery calcium score) and CTA (CT angiography), used to image plaque—including the latest in CTA software—and how these tools inform our understanding of ASCVD risk and guide clinical decision-making.</description></item><item><title>#246 - AMA #45:  Pros and cons of GLP-1 weight loss drugs and metformin as a geroprotective agent | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000040/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000040/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter focuses the discussion on two topics getting a lot of attention recently. He first dives deep into GLP-1 agonists, most notably semaglutide and tirzepatide, which originally came to market as diabetes drugs but are now being studied and prescribed for weight loss.</description></item><item><title>#245 ‒ Overcoming trauma, finding inner peace, and living a meaningful and fulfilling life | Lewis Howes | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000041/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000041/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Lewis Howes is a New York Times best-selling author, entrepreneur, speaker, and host of the popular podcast, The School of Greatness. In this episode, Lewis opens up about the various hardships and traumatic events he experienced starting at a very young age and reveals the valuable lessons he learned as he worked through those traumas to improve his emotional health.</description></item><item><title>#244 ‒ The history of the cell, cell therapy, gene therapy, and more | Siddhartha Mukherjee | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000042/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000042/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Siddhartha Mukherjee is an oncologist, Pulitzer Prize-winning author, and previous guest on The Drive. In this episode, Sid discusses many of the subjects of his latest book, The Song of the Cell, including the incredible discovery of the cell and how it transformed medicine. He explains the evolutionary drive to go from single-cell to multicellular life and unpacks the four different types of cell-based therapies and the problems they are attempting to solve.</description></item><item><title>#243 ‒ The fentanyl crisis and why everyone should be paying attention | Anthony Hipolito | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000043/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000043/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Anthony Hipolito is a sheriff’s deputy in Hays County, Texas with over 24 years of experience in law enforcement. In this episode, Anthony discusses his work to spread awareness about illicit fentanyl use and the drastic increase in accidental overdoses, especially in young people. Anthony explains the deadly nature of fentanyl, including how many counterfeit drugs are now being laced with deadly doses of fentanyl.</description></item><item><title>#242 - AMA #44: Peter’s historical changes in body composition with his evolving dietary, fasting, and training protocols | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000044/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000044/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter reviews the last 12+ years of his DEXA scan results revealing the changes to his body composition, lean muscle mass, visceral adipose tissue, and more. He explains how his body composition and blood biomarkers were impacted by the various dietary approaches (ketosis, fasting, high protein, etc.</description></item><item><title>#241 ‒ Living intentionally, valuing time, prioritizing relationships, and more keys to a rich life | Ric Elias (Part 2) | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000045/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000045/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Ric Elias, the founder of Red Ventures and previous guest on The Drive, returns to discuss his evolving insights on time, relationships, parenting, and how to make the most of the gift of life. In this episode, he reflects on the changes he’s made since his near-death experience during the crash landing of Flight 1549 on the Hudson River in 2009.</description></item><item><title>#240 ‒ The confusion around HDL and its link to cardiovascular disease | Dan Rader, M.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000046/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000046/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Dan Rader is a Professor at the Perelman School of Medicine at the University of Pennsylvania, where he conducts translational research on lipoprotein metabolism and atherosclerosis with a particular focus on the function of high-density lipoproteins (HDLs). In this episode, Dan goes in-depth on HDL biology, including the genesis of HDL, its metabolism, function, and how this relates to atherosclerotic cardiovascular disease (ASCVD).</description></item><item><title>#239 ‒ The science of strength, muscle, and training for longevity | Andy Galpin, Ph.D. (PART I) | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000047/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000047/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Andy Galpin is a Professor of Kinesiology at California State University at Fullerton, where he studies muscle adaptation and applies his research to work with professional athletes. In this episode, Andy sets the foundation for the conversation by discussing the anatomy, microanatomy, and physiology of the muscle, including explaining what it actually means to undergo hypertrophy of the muscle.</description></item><item><title>#238 – AMA #43: Understanding apoB, LDL-C, Lp(a), and insulin as risk factors for cardiovascular disease | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000048/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000048/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter answers questions related to the leading cause of death in both men and women—atherosclerotic cardiovascular disease (ASCVD). He highlights the most important risk factors for ASCVD, such as apoB, LDL, hyperinsulinemia, and Lp(a), and explains the mechanism by which they confer risk and how these factors are interrelated.</description></item><item><title>#237 ‒ Optimizing life for maximum fulfillment | Bill Perkins | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000049/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000049/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Bill Perkins is one of the world’s most successful hedge fund managers and entrepreneurs, and the author of the bestseller, Die With Zero. In this episode, Bill unpacks the Die With Zero philosophy which challenges conventional thinking related to the balance between health, wealth, and time—the three variables important for fulfillment.</description></item><item><title>#236 ‒ Neurodegenerative disease: pathology, screening, and prevention | Kellyann Niotis, M.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000050/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000050/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Kellyann Niotis is a neurologist specializing in risk reduction strategies for the prevention or slowing of neurodegenerative disorders. In this episode, Kellyann provides an overview of the various diseases associated with neurodegeneration, including, but not limited to, Alzheimer’s disease, Lewy body dementia, and Parkinson’s disease. She goes in-depth on Parkinson’s disease, explaining its pathology, role in movement capacity, very early warning signs, and the role of anxiety and sleep.</description></item><item><title>James Clear: Building &amp; Changing Habits (#183 rebroadcast) | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000051/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000051/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
James Clear is the author of the New York Times bestseller Atomic Habits. His extensive research into human behavior has helped him identify key components of habit formation and develop the “Four Laws of Behavioral Change.” In this episode, James provides insights into how both good and bad habits are formed, including the influence of genetics, environment, social circles, and more.</description></item><item><title>#235 ‒ Training principles for mass and strength, changing views on nutrition, creatine supplementation, and more | Layne Norton, Ph.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000052/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000052/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Layne Norton holds a Ph.D. in nutritional sciences and is a physique coach, natural bodybuilder and powerlifter, and two-time previous podcast guest. In this episode, Layne discusses his training as a powerlifter and shares training principles that non-powerlifters can apply to improve muscle strength and mass. Layne goes in-depth on creatine supplementation, including the benefits for lean mass and strength, and addresses the common arguments against its regular usage.</description></item><item><title>#234 ‒ Chris Hemsworth on Limitless, longevity, and happiness | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000053/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000053/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Chris Hemsworth, best known for his role as Thor in the Marvel movies, joins Peter to discuss his recent work in the docuseries called Limitless. In the docuseries, Chris undertook extreme challenges to explore his physical and emotional limits and gain insights into longevity. In this episode, Chris discusses these many challenges—from fasting to arctic swims to 100-foot rope climbs—as well as the insights that he gained from each.</description></item><item><title>#233 - AMA #42: Optimizing sleep - bedtime routine, molecule regimen, sleep trackers, sauna, &amp; more | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000054/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000054/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter answers a number of questions on optimizing sleep. He describes his pre-bedtime routine, how he utilizes a sauna, and his current regimen of medicines and supplements for improving sleep time and quality. He goes in depth on each of the molecules that have shown promise in boosting sleep, including their mechanisms of action as well as any noteworthy contraindications.</description></item><item><title>#232 ‒ Shoulder, elbow, wrist, and hand: diagnosis, treatment, and surgery of the upper extremities | Alton Barron, M.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000055/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000055/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Alton Barron is an orthopedic surgeon specializing in the shoulder, elbow, and hand. In this episode, Alton breaks down the anatomy of the upper extremities and discusses the most common injuries associated with this area of the body. He explains in detail how he examines the shoulder, elbow, and hand to find the source of the pain and lays out the non-surgical and surgical treatment options as well as the factors that determine whether surgery is appropriate.</description></item><item><title>A masterclass on insulin resistance—mechanisms and implications | Gerald Shulman, M.D., Ph.D. (#140 rebroadcast) | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000056/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000056/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Gerald Shulman is a Professor of Medicine, Cellular &amp; Molecular Physiology, and the Director of the Diabetes Research Center at Yale. His pioneering work on the use of advanced technologies to analyze metabolic flux within cells has greatly contributed to the understanding of insulin resistance and type 2 diabetes.</description></item><item><title>#231 - AMA #41: Medicine 3.0, developments in the field of aging, healthy habits in times of stress, and more | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000057/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000057/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter answers a wide variety of questions, starting with a discussion on the evolution of medicine and the hopeful transition to “Medicine 3.0.” Peter recounts his unique career path and explains how he assesses risk and utilizes frameworks for decision-making.</description></item><item><title>#230 ‒ Cardiovascular disease in women: prevention, risk factors, lipids, and more | Erin Michos, M.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000058/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000058/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Erin Michos is an internationally-known leader in preventive cardiology and women’s cardiovascular health. In this episode, Erin discusses current trends in cardiovascular disease (CVD) through the lens of female biology and the observation that major adverse cardiac events in both sexes are on the rise. She walks through risk factors including LDL-cholesterol, apoB, and Lp(a) and makes the case for the importance of early preventative measures.</description></item><item><title>#229 ‒ Understanding cardiovascular disease risk, cholesterol, and apoB | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000059/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000059/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
In this special episode of The Drive, we have pulled together a variety of clips from previous podcasts about cardiovascular disease to help listeners understand this topic more deeply, as well as to identify previous episodes which may be of interest. In this episode, Peter highlights the importance of understanding cardiovascular disease and why early intervention is critical.</description></item><item><title>#228 ‒ Improving body composition, female-specific training principles, and overcoming an eating disorder | Holly Baxter, APD | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000060/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000060/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Holly Baxter is an accredited practicing dietician (APD), competitive bodybuilder, fitness and nutrition educator, and coach. In this episode, Holly discusses her experience as an athlete and competitive bodybuilder. She also opens up about her struggles with mental health, her long battle with an eating disorder, and the important steps she’s taken in her road to recovery.</description></item><item><title>#227 - AMA #40: Body composition, protein, time-restricted feeding, fasting, DEXA scans, and more | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000061/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000061/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter discusses the importance of understanding body composition and explains how to interpret the most important metrics revealed by a DEXA scan, such as lean muscle tissue mass, visceral adiposity tissue mass, bone mineral density, and more. He discusses common concerning trends in these metrics as well as strategies to address them.</description></item><item><title>#226 ‒ The science of happiness | Arthur Brooks, Ph.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000062/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000062/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Arthur Brooks is a social scientist, professor at Harvard University, a columnist for The Atlantic, and the bestselling author of From Strength to Strength. In this episode, Arthur explains how intelligence changes as we get older, and how to take advantage of this to maximize our happiness and success.</description></item><item><title>#225 ‒ The comfort crisis, doing hard things, rucking, and more | Michael Easter, MA | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000063/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000063/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Michael Easter is the author of the bestseller, The Comfort Crisis. He’s also a journalist, Professor of Journalism at UNLV, and a leading voice on how humans can integrate modern science and evolutionary wisdom for improved health, meaning, and performance in life and at work. In this episode, Michael first talks about his upbringing, including his parents' struggle with alcoholism, his father leaving when he was young, and how these things impacted Michael's own struggle with alcoholism.</description></item><item><title>#224 ‒ Dietary protein: amount needed, ideal timing, quality, and more | Don Layman, Ph.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000064/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000064/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Don Layman is a Professor of Food Science and Human Nutrition at the University of Illinois Urbana-Champaign. He has spent the past 40 years investigating the role of dietary protein in muscle protein synthesis. In this episode, Don describes how his decades of research have shaped his thinking around protein, muscle, anabolic factors, metabolism, and more.</description></item><item><title>#223 - AMA #39: The Centenarian Decathlon, zone 2, VO2 max, and more | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000065/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000065/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter describes what it means to exercise with the goal of longevity in mind, including his personal goals, exercise framework, and how he is optimizing for what he refers to as the “Centenarian Decathlon.” He explains the various types of cardiovascular training and how to partition your time between intensity levels (i.</description></item><item><title>#222 ‒ How nutrition impacts longevity | Matt Kaeberlein, Ph.D | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000066/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000066/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Dr. Matt Kaeberlein is a globally recognized expert on the biology of aging and recurring on The Drive. In this episode, Matt explains his research findings on nutrition as it relates to aging and longevity, including the results from his recent review article in Science. From there, he and Peter dive deep into the literature on calorie restriction (CR), explaining the nuance, benefits for lifespan and healthspan, and potential downsides of CR.</description></item><item><title>#221 ‒ Understanding sleep and how to improve it | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000067/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000067/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
In this special episode of The Drive, we have pulled together a variety of clips from previous podcasts with sleep expert Dr. Matthew Walker to help listeners understand this topic more deeply, as well as to identify which previous episodes featuring Matt may be of interest. In this episode, Matt gives an overview of why we sleep, the stages of sleep, and sleep chronotypes, and he provides tips to those looking to improve their total sleep and sleep efficiency.</description></item><item><title>#220 ‒ Ketamine: Benefits, risks, and promising therapeutic potential | Celia Morgan, Ph.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000068/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000068/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Celia Morgan is a Professor of Psychopharmacology at the University of Exeter who has authored numerous publications on the potential therapeutic uses of ketamine in mental healthcare. In this episode, Celia dives deep into the neurobiology of ketamine, how it affects users, and how it differs from other, more classical psychedelics (LSD, MDMA, PCP, and psilocybin).</description></item><item><title>#219 ‒ Dialectical behavior therapy (DBT): skills for overcoming depression , emotional dysregulation, and more | Shireen Rizvi, Ph.D., ABPP | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000069/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000069/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Shireen Rizvi is a Professor of Clinical Psychology and Psychiatry at Rutgers University, where she is also the Director of the Dialectical Behavior Therapy Clinic. This episode focuses specifically on dialectical behavior therapy (DBT), a skills-based technique which was originally developed to treat borderline personality disorder (BPD) and has since been adapted to treat depression and other mental health conditions, as well as to help people who have difficulty with emotional regulation and self-destructive behaviors.</description></item><item><title>#218 - AMA #38: Can you exercise too much? | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000070/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000070/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter dives deep into the question of whether there is such a thing as “too much exercise.” He explores the theoretical “J-curve” relationship between exercise and longevity, whereby mortality risk declines with increasing activity levels only to see an uptick above a certain exercise volume threshold.</description></item><item><title>#217 ‒ Exercise, VO2 max, and longevity | Mike Joyner, M.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000071/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000071/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Mike Joyner is a physician-researcher and one of the world’s leading experts on human performance and exercise physiology. In this episode, Mike discusses how to combat age-related declines in health and fitness levels by using various modes of exercise to improve lifespan and healthspan. Mike explains the impact of exercise on the autonomic nervous system, blood pressure, heart rate, heart rate variability, heart rate recovery, and max heart rate.</description></item><item><title>#216 - Metabolomics, NAD+, and cancer metabolism | Josh Rabinowitz, M.D., Ph.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000072/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000072/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Josh Rabinowitz is a Professor of Chemistry and Integrative Genomics at Princeton University, where his research focuses on developing a quantitative, comprehensive understanding of cellular metabolism through the study of metabolites and their fluxes. In this episode, Josh focuses the discussion on three main topics: metabolomics, NAD (and its precursors), and cancer metabolism.</description></item><item><title>#215 - The gut-brain connection | Michael Gershon, M.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000073/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000073/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Mike Gershon is a Professor of Pathology and Cell Biology at Columbia University and has been at the forefront of studying neural control of the gut for the past 60 years. In this episode, Mike gives a tour de force on the pathways of gut-brain communication but first sets the stage with an overview of gastrointestinal tract development and anatomy.</description></item><item><title>#214 - AMA #37: Bone health—everything you need to know | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000074/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000074/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter dives deep into the topic of bone health and explains why this is an important topic for everyone, from children to the elderly. He begins with an overview of bone mineral density, how it's measured, how it changes over the course of life, and the variability between sexes largely due to changes in estrogen levels.</description></item><item><title>#213 ‒ Liquid biopsies and cancer detection | Max Diehn, M.D. Ph.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000075/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000075/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Max Diehn is a Professor of Radiation Oncology at Stanford and a clinical radiation oncologist specializing in lung cancer. Max’s research focuses on developing novel methods for detecting circulating tumor DNA in the blood of cancer patients and on elucidating the molecular pathways and genes associated with cancer.</description></item><item><title>Earning the gift of life | Ric Elias (#79 rebroadcast) | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000076/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000076/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
In this episode, Ric Elias, founder of Red Ventures, opens up about the fateful day he knew for certain that he was going to die as a passenger on US Airways Flight 1549. Ric dives deep into how that day impacted his life, greatly changed his perspective, and improved his relationship with his family and the broader community.</description></item><item><title>#212 - The neuroscience of obesity | Stephan Guyenet, Ph.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000077/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000077/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Stephan Guyenet is a neuroscientist focused on the neuroscience of obesity and energy homeostasis. He is the author of the book, The Hungry Brain and founder/director of Red Pen Reviews. In this episode, Stephan explains how obesity has changed phenotypically over the course of human history as well as what might explain the dramatic increase in prevalence of obesity in the last few decades.</description></item><item><title>#211 - AMA #36: Fruits &amp; vegetables—everything you need to know | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000078/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000078/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter discusses the nutritional profiles of various fruits and vegetables as a means of assessing their relative value. He explains the difference between eating them vs. drinking them, how processing fruits and vegetables can change their properties, and how one’s current state of health affects nutrition strategy when it comes to fruits and vegetable consumption.</description></item><item><title>#210 - Lp(a) and its impact on heart disease | Benoît Arsenault, Ph.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000079/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000079/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Benoît Arsenault is a research scientist focused on understanding how lifestyle and genetic factors contribute to cardiovascular disease risk. In this episode, the discussion casts a spotlight on Lp(a)—the single most important genetically-inherited trait when it comes to atherosclerotic cardiovascular disease (ASCVD) risk. Benoît explains the biology of Lp(a), how it’s inherited, the importance of measuring Lp(a) levels, and the diseases most associated with high Lp(a).</description></item><item><title>#209 ‒ Medical mistakes, patient safety, and the RaDonda Vaught case | Marty Makary, M.D., M.P.H. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000080/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000080/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Marty Makary is a surgeon, public policy researcher, and author of the New York times best-sellers Unaccountable and The Price We Pay. In this episode, Marty dives deep into the topic of patient safety. He describes the risk of medical errors that patients face when they walk into the hospital and how those errors take place, and he highlights what amounts to an epidemic of medical mistakes.</description></item><item><title>The Art of Stability | Beth Lewis (Ep. #131 Rebroadcast) | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000081/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000081/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Beth Lewis is a former professional dancer and a self-described “educator of movement” who has an unmatched ability to assimilate information and customize training plans from multiple training systems. In this episode, Beth describes how she identifies problematic movement patterns and postures to help individuals relieve pain, avoid injury, and move better within all types of exercise.</description></item><item><title>#208 - Tragedy, grief, healing, and finding happiness | Kelsey Chittick | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000082/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000082/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Kelsey Chittick is the author of Second Half: Surviving Loss and Finding Magic in the Missing. In this episode, Kelsey describes her long healing process following the sudden death of her husband, former NFL player Nate Hobgood-Chittick. She describes her life with Nate before and after football, including her premonitions that something was off about Nate and the subsequent finding that he suffered from chronic traumatic encephalopathy (CTE).</description></item><item><title>#207 - AMA #35: "Anti-Aging" Drugs — NAD+, metformin, &amp; rapamycin | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000083/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000083/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter is joined by special guest, Dr. Matt Kaeberlein. Together they answer many questions around the field of aging with an emphasis on three specific molecules—NAD, metformin, and rapamycin—and their purported geroprotective qualities. They first discuss aging biomarkers and epigenetic clocks before breaking down the advantages and limitations of the most common experimental models being used today to study aging and pharmacological possibilities for extending lifespan.</description></item><item><title>#206 - Exercising for longevity: strength, stability, zone 2, zone 5, and more | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000084/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000084/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
In this special episode of The Drive, we have pulled together a variety of clips from previous podcasts about exercise to help listeners understand this topic more deeply, as well as to identify previous episodes which may be of interest. In this episode, Peter discusses his framework for exercise, what he’s really optimizing for, and how to train today to be prepared for a good life at age 100.</description></item><item><title>#205 - Energy balance, nutrition, &amp; building muscle | Layne Norton, Ph.D. (Pt.2) | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000085/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000085/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Layne Norton holds a Ph.D. in nutritional sciences and is a physique coach, natural bodybuilder, and previous guest on The Drive. In the first half of this episode, Layne dives deep into the topic of energy balance, including the role that macronutrients and calories play in weight loss.</description></item><item><title>#204 - Centenarians, metformin, and longevity | Nir Barzilai, M.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000086/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000086/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
Nir Barzilai, Director of the Institute for Aging Research at the Albert Einstein College of Medicine, is back for his third appearance on The Drive. In this episode, Nir divulges insights into lifespan and healthspan through the lens of his extensive research on centenarians as well as the latest from the TAME trial (Targeting/Taming Aging with Metformin), a multi-center study investigating the concept that the multi-morbidities of aging can be delayed in humans.</description></item><item><title>#203 - AMA #34: What Causes Heart Disease? | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000087/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000087/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter dives deep into the topic of atherosclerotic cardiovascular disease (ASCVD)—the number one killer in the developed world. Peter argues for the importance of paying attention to and understanding ASCVD given its ubiquity and inevitability. He goes into great detail about the development of atherosclerosis and how it can take hold at a very early age, the role of cholesterol, and the causal factors of ASCVD that determine prevention strategies.</description></item><item><title>#202 - Peter on nutrition, disease prevention, sleep, and more — looking back on the last 100 episodes | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000088/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000088/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Sign Up to Receive Peter’s Weekly Newsletter
In this second edition of the “Strong Convictions, Loosely Held” episode, Peter discusses topics on which his thoughts have evolved as a result of his interviews with podcast guests and other information he’s gained since episode 100. Peter covers topics including cancer therapy and screening, as well as prevention strategies for cardiovascular disease and Alzheimer’s disease.</description></item><item><title>In remembrance of Sarah Hallberg, D.O., M.S. (Ep. #162 Rebroadcast) | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000089/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000089/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Episode Description:
Today’s episode of The Drive is a rebroadcast of the conversation with Sarah Hallberg (released on May 17th, 2021). It's with great sadness that we report that Sarah recently lost her battle with lung cancer, and as such we've decided to republish her episode to honor her amazing work in challenging the status quo in the treatment of metabolic disease.</description></item><item><title>#201 - Deep dive back into Zone 2 | Iñigo San-Millán, Ph.D. (Pt. 2) | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000090/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000090/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Episode Description:
Iñigo San-Millán is an internationally renowned applied physiologist and a previous guest on The Drive. His research and clinical work focuses on exercise-related metabolism, metabolic health, diabetes, cancer metabolism, nutrition, sports performance, and critical care. In this episode, Iñigo describes how his work with Tour de France winner Tadej Pogačar has provided insights into the amazing potential of elite athletes from a performance and metabolic perspective.</description></item><item><title>#200 - AMA #33: Hydration—electrolytes, supplements, sports drinks, performance effects, and more | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000091/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Become a Member to Listen to the Full Episode
View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Episode Description:
In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter discusses all things related to hydration, starting with how water is distributed in the body and the important concept of tonicity. He explains the difference between dehydration and volume depletion and their respective health consequences and implications. He describes the different conditions which affect our daily water needs, as well as the signs of dehydration and how it can affect performance.</description></item><item><title>#199 - Running, overcoming challenges, and finding success | Ryan Hall | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000092/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000092/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Episode Description:
Ryan Hall is the fastest American ever to run the marathon (2:04:58) and half marathon (59:43) and is the author of the book Run the Mile You’re In. In this episode, Ryan discusses his amazing successes and epic failures during his remarkable running career and what he's learned through these experiences. Ryan explains not only the physical aspects of running - including his training routine, fueling regimen, and recovery process - but he also emphasizes the mental aspect of the sport.</description></item><item><title>#198 - Eye health—everything you need to know | Steven Dell, M.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000093/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000093/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Episode Description:
Steven Dell is an ophthalmologist, current Medical Director of Dell Laser Consultants, and a leader in refractive eye surgery with over 20 patents to his name. In this episode, Steven explains the anatomy and functional mechanics of the eye and how they relate to common variations in vision. He discusses changes in vision that occur with aging, the fundamentals of different types of vision loss, and provides an in-depth look into the various treatments and procedures available for corrective eye surgery.</description></item><item><title>#197 - The science of obesity &amp; how to improve nutritional epidemiology | David Allison, Ph.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000094/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000094/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Episode Description:
David Allison is an award-winning scientific writer who has been at the forefront of obesity research for the last 20 years. Currently the Dean of the Indiana University School of Public Health, he has also authored many publications on statistical and research methodology and how to improve research rigor and integrity. David’s focus on evidence and data brings forth an interesting discussion of what we know (and don’t know) about the science of obesity.</description></item><item><title>#196 - AMA #32: Exercise, squats, deadlifts, BFR, and TRT | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000095/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000095/</guid><description>Podcast Description Become a Member to Listen to the Full Episode
View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Episode Description:
In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter shares his current workout regimen and how he incorporates blood flow restriction (BFR). He walks through the mechanics and fundamentals of some of his favorite lifts including squats, deadlifts, and hip thrusters and stresses the relative importance of each in the context of longevity.</description></item><item><title>#195 - Freedom, PTSD, war, and life through an evolutionary lens | Sebastian Junger | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000096/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000096/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Episode Description:
Sebastian Junger is an award-winning journalist, documentary filmmaker, and New York Times best-selling author. In this wide-ranging discussion, Sebastian shares stories from his time as a war reporter and how it shaped his understanding of the psychological effects of combat, including the sacred bond of soldiers, the forces that unify a tribe, and the psychological mechanisms that protect humans from painful experiences.</description></item><item><title>#194 - How fructose drives metabolic disease | Rick Johnson, M.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000097/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000097/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Episode Description:
Rick Johnson, Professor of Nephrology at the University of Colorado and a previous guest on The Drive, returns for a follow-up about unique features of fructose metabolism, and how this system that aided the survival of human ancestors has become potentially hazardous based on our culture’s dietary norms. In this episode, Rick explains how the body can generate fructose from glucose and how circulating glucose and salt levels can activate this conversion.</description></item><item><title>#193 - AMA #31: Heart rate variability (HRV), alcohol, sleep, and more | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000098/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000098/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Episode Description:
In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter and Bob first answer a variety of questions related to heart rate variability (HRV): what it means, why it matters, and how to measure, interpret, and potentially elevate it. Next, they dive deep into the topic of alcohol, beginning with a discussion on the negative impact that it can have on sleep.</description></item><item><title>#192 - COVID Part 2: Masks, long COVID, boosters, mandates, treatments, and more | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000099/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000099/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Episode Description:
This episode is a follow-up to our recent COVID-19 podcast with Drs. Marty Makary and Zubin Damania (aka ZDoggMD). Here, we address many of the listener questions we received about our original discussion. In addition to Marty and ZDoggMD, we are also joined by Dr. Monica Gandhi, an infectious disease specialist and Professor of Medicine at the University of California, San Francisco.</description></item><item><title>#191 - Revolutionizing our understanding of mental illness with optogenetics | Karl Deisseroth M.D., Ph.D. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000100/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000100/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Episode Description:
Karl Deisseroth is a world-renowned clinical psychiatrist, neuroscientist, and author of Projections: A Story of Human Emotions. In the episode, Karl explains his unique career path that led to the development of optogenetics—a revolutionary technique that uses specialized light-sensitive ion channels to precisely control the activity of select populations of neurons. Karl provides a concise overview of how optogenetics works and how it can be used to better understand mental illness, to identify the neurons responsible for specific behaviors, and to guide development of new treatments.</description></item><item><title>#190 - Paul Conti, M.D.: How to heal from trauma and break the cycle of shame | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000101/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000101/</guid><description>Podcast Description View the Show Notes Page for This Episode
Become a Member to Receive Exclusive Content
Episode Description:
Paul Conti, a returning guest on The Drive, is a practicing psychiatrist and recent author of Trauma: The Invisible Epidemic: How Trauma Works and How We Can Heal From It, in which he offers valuable insights on healing from trauma. In this episode, Paul explains how his personal experience with trauma and his many years seeing patients have shaped his understanding of trauma’s impact on the brain, its common patterns and manifestations, and how often people don't recognize the implications of trauma in their own life.</description></item><item><title>#189 - COVID-19: Current state of affairs, Omicron, and a search for the end game | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000102/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000102/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Peter sits down with Drs. Marty Makary and Zubin Damania (aka ZDoggMD), both previous guests on The Drive. Marty is a Johns Hopkins professor and public health researcher and ZDoggMD is a UCSF/Stanford trained internist and the founder of Turntable Health. This episode, recorded on December 27, 2021, was in part inspired by some of the shoddy science and even worse messaging coming from top officials regarding COVID-19.</description></item><item><title>Iñigo San Millán, Ph.D.: Zone 2 Training and Metabolic Health (Ep. #85 Rebroadcast) | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000103/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s episode of The Drive is a rebroadcast of the conversation with Iñigo San Millán, (released on December 23rd, 2019). This episode with Iñigo was one of the most popular discussions to date and is a prelude to an upcoming follow-up discussion in 2022.
In this episode, Dr. Iñigo San Millán, Assistant Professor at the University of Colorado School of Medicine, explains the crucial role of mitochondrial function in everything from metabolic health to elite exercise performance.</description></item><item><title>#188 - AMA #30: How to Read and Understand Scientific Studies | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000104/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000104/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter and Bob dive deep into all things related to studying studies to help one sift through all the noise to find the signal. They define the various types of studies, how a study progresses from idea to execution, and how to identify study strengths and limitations. They explain how clinical trials work, as well as the potential for bias and common pitfalls to watch out for.</description></item><item><title>#187 - Sam Apple: The Warburg Effect—Otto Warburg’s cancer metabolism theory | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000105/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000105/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sam Apple is the author of the book Ravenous: Otto Warburg, the Nazis, and the Search for the Cancer-Diet Connection, published in May 2021. In this episode, Sam describes the fascinating life story of Otto Warburg, a Nobel Prize-winning scientist who, despite being both Jewish and gay, survived Nazi Germany because of his valuable research on cellular metabolism and cancer. Sam describes Warburg’s observation that cancer cells consume large amounts of glucose anaerobically – a phenomenon subsequently known as the “Warburg Effect” – and relates how Warburg’s seminal work on this topic was largely forgotten after the discovery of oncogenes, only to regain relevance decades later within the field of cancer biology.</description></item><item><title>#186 - Patrick Radden Keefe: The opioid crisis—origin, guilty parties, and the difficult path forward | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000106/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Patrick Radden Keefe is an award-winning staff writer at The New Yorker and the bestselling author of Empire of Pain: The Secret History of the Sackler Dynasty. In this episode, Patrick tells the story of the Sackler family and Purdue Pharma - makers of the pain management drug OxyContin, providing the backdrop for the ensuing opioid epidemic and public health crisis. He reveals the implicit and sometimes explicit corruption of all parties involved in the development, approval, and marketing of OxyContin, leading to a cascade of unintended consequences including addiction and death.</description></item><item><title>#185 - Allan Sniderman, M.D.: Cardiovascular disease and why we should change the way we assess risk | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000107/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Allan Sniderman is a highly acclaimed Professor of Cardiology and Medicine at McGill University and a foremost expert in cardiovascular disease (CVD). In this episode, Allan explains the many risk factors used to predict atherosclerosis, including triglycerides, cholesterol, and lipoproteins, and he makes the case for apoB as a superior metric that is currently being underutilized. Allan expresses his frustration with the current scientific climate and its emphasis on consensus and unanimity over encouraging multiple viewpoints, thus holding back the advancement of metrics like apoB for assessing CVD risk, treatment, and prevention strategies.</description></item><item><title>Rick Johnson, M.D.: Metabolic Effects of Fructose (Ep. #87 Rebroadcast) | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000108/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today’s episode of The Drive is a rebroadcast of the conversation with Rick Johnson (originally released January 6th, 2020). This episode was one of the most popular discussions to-date and is a prelude to an upcoming follow-up discussion which will be coming out in February 2022 along with the release of Rick’s new book.
In this episode, Rick Johnson, professor of nephrology at the University of Colorado, explains how his research into the causes of blood pressure resulted in a change of research direction to focus more on how fructose has such profound metabolic effects.</description></item><item><title>#184 - AMA #29: GLP-1 Agonists—The Future of Treating Obesity? | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000109/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000109/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter and Bob discuss all things related to GLP-1 agonists—a class of drugs that are gaining popularity for the treatment of obesity. They cover the discovery of these peptides, their physiology, and what it is they do in their natural state. Next, Peter and Bob break down a recently published study which showed remarkable results for weight loss and other metabolic parameters using a once-weekly injection of the GLP-1 agonist drug semaglutide, also known as Ozempic, in overweight and obese patients.</description></item><item><title>#183 - James Clear: Building &amp; changing habits | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000110/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000110/</guid><description>Podcast Description James Clear is the author of the New York Times bestseller Atomic Habits. His extensive research into human behavior has helped him identify key components of habit formation and develop the “Four Laws of Behavioral Change.” In this episode, James provides insights into how both good and bad habits are formed, including the influence of genetics, environment, social circles, and more. He points to changes one can make to cultivate more perseverance and discipline and describes the profound impact habits can have when tying them into one’s self-identity.</description></item><item><title>#182 - David Nutt: Psychedelics &amp; Recreational Drugs | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000111/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000111/</guid><description>Podcast Description David Nutt is a psychiatrist and a neuroscientist at Downing College, Cambridge. His research focuses on illicit drugs—their harm, classification, and potential for therapeutic use in psychiatry. In this episode, David discusses his framework for assessing the potential harm caused by common recreational drugs and explains how they are regulated, which is oftentimes misaligned with actual risk. He describes in detail the neurobiology, mechanisms of action, and addiction potential of alcohol, opiates, cocaine, and methamphetamine and contrasts those with psychedelics, which have been given a similar regulatory classification despite their relatively low risk of harm and their numerous potential therapeutic uses.</description></item><item><title>#181 - Robert Gatenby, M.D.: Viewing cancer through an evolutionary lens and why this offers a radically different approach to treatment | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000112/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000112/</guid><description>Podcast Description Robert (Bob) Gatenby is a radiologist who specializes in exploring theoretical and experimental models of evolutionary dynamics in cancer and cancer drug resistance. He has developed an adaptive therapy approach for treating cancer which has shown promise in improving survival times with less cumulative drug use. In this episode, Bob explains what brought him into medicine, his search for organizing principles from which to understand cancer, and the mathematical modeling of other complex systems that led him to model the dynamics of tumor cell changes in cancer.</description></item><item><title>#180 - AMA #28: All things testosterone and testosterone replacement therapy | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000113/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000113/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter and Bob discuss all things related to testosterone: what happens when testosterone levels are low, and the potential benefits and risks of testosterone replacement therapy (TRT). They explain the physiology of testosterone, how it works, and how its level changes over the course of a person's life. They have a detailed discussion about existing literature, which reveals vast potential structural, functional, and metabolic benefits of testosterone replacement therapy.</description></item><item><title>#179 - Jeremy Loenneke, Ph.D.: The science of blood flow restriction—benefits, uses, and what it teaches us about the relationship between muscle size and strength | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000114/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000114/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jeremy Loenneke has a Ph.D. in exercise physiology, a Master’s in nutrition and exercise, and is currently the director of the Kevser Ermin Applied Physiology Laboratory at the University of Mississippi, where he focuses his research on skeletal muscle adaptations to exercise in combination with blood flow restriction (BFR). In this episode, Jeremy explains the science of BFR and the mechanisms by which BFR training can produce hypertrophy using low loads.</description></item><item><title>#178 - Lance Armstrong: The rise, fall, and growth of a cycling legend | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000115/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000115/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lance Armstrong is a legendary figure in professional cycling having won seven consecutive Tour de France titles but also a controversial figure facing scrutiny for the use of performance enhancing drugs. In this episode, Lance takes us through his meteoric rise to one of the most famous athletes in the world and his equally accelerated fall from grace. Lance describes how he persevered through his brutal diagnosis of testicular cancer before rattling off a historic run of seven consecutive Tour de France titles all while facing tremendous scrutiny for his alleged use of performance enhancing drugs such as EPO and cortisone.</description></item><item><title>#177 - Steven Rosenberg, M.D., Ph.D.: The development of cancer immunotherapy and its promise for treating advanced cancers | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000116/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000116/</guid><description>Podcast Description Steve Rosenberg is the Chief of Surgery at the National Cancer Institute, a position he has held continuously for the past 47 years. Steve is a pioneer in the field of immunotherapies for cancer and a recipient of nearly every major award in science. In this episode, Steve discusses his inspiration for devoting his career to cancer research and describes his keen observation of two cases of spontaneous cancer remission, driving him to learn how to harness the immune system to treat cancer.</description></item><item><title>#176 - AMA #27: The importance of muscle mass, strength, and cardiorespiratory fitness for longevity | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000117/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000117/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter and Bob discuss the longevity benefits from greater cardiorespiratory fitness (CRF) and greater muscle mass and strength. Conversely, they dive deep into the literature showing a rapid increase in morbidity and mortality risk as fitness levels decline with age. They also try to tease out the relative contributions of CRF, muscle mass, and strength. Additionally, they discuss the impact of fasting on muscle mass, the potential tradeoffs to consider, and finish by discussing why it’s critical to maximize your fitness level.</description></item><item><title>#175 - Matt Kaeberlein, Ph.D.: The biology of aging, rapamycin, and other interventions that target the aging process | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000118/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000118/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matt Kaeberlein is globally recognized for his research on the biology of aging and is a previous guest on The Drive. In this episode, Matt defines aging, the relationship between aging, chronic inflammation, and the immune system, and talks extensively about the most exciting molecules for extending lifespan. He discusses the current state of the literature of testing rapamycin (and rapalogs) in animals and humans, including Matt’s Dog Aging Project, and provides insights into how we can improve future trials by conceptualizing risk, choosing better endpoints, and working with regulators to approve such trials.</description></item><item><title>#174 - Lawrence Wright: The 20th anniversary of the 9/11 attacks: reflections on how they happened, and lessons learned and not learned | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000119/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000119/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lawrence Wright is the author of The Looming Tower: Al-Qaeda and the Road to 9/11 which won the 2007 Pulitzer Prize for general nonfiction and was named one of Time's top 100 books of all time. In this episode, released just before the 20th anniversary of the September 11th attacks, Lawrence and Peter discuss the book and the lasting impact of that day. Lawrence reflects on his personal experiences on that day and how he was first drawn into reporting on the attacks.</description></item><item><title>#173 - AMA #26: Continuous glucose monitors, zone 2 training, and a framework for interventions | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000120/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000120/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter and Bob answer numerous follow-up questions to recently discussed deep-dive topics such as the use of continuous glucose monitors and getting the most from zone 2 exercise. They also discuss the incredible feats of cyclists in the Tour de France through the lens of the amazing performance physiology required from these athletes. Additionally, Peter ties the conversation together by sharing his foundational framework when considering different interventions, even in the absence of data from a randomized controlled trial.</description></item><item><title>#172 - Esther Perel: The effects of trauma, the role of narratives in shaping our worldview, and why we need to accept uncomfortable emotions | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000121/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000121/</guid><description>Podcast Description Esther Perel is a psychotherapist and New York Times bestselling author who is an expert on modern relationships. In this episode, Esther describes how being a child of parents who narrowly survived the Holocaust shaped and influenced her perspectives and ultimately led to her to a career in therapy. She discusses how the generational differences in parenting, among other things, led to the rise of individualism with a focus on happiness and self-esteem to the detriment of our relationships and sense of community.</description></item><item><title>#171 - Steve Austad, Ph.D.: The landscape of longevity science: making sense of caloric restriction, biomarkers of aging, and possible geroprotective molecules | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000122/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000122/</guid><description>Podcast Description Steve Austad is a distinguished professor of biology at the University of Alabama and director of one of the Nathan Shock Centers of Excellence in aging biology. Steve's current research seeks to understand the underlying causes of aging, specifically with a long-term goal of developing medical interventions that slow the age-related decay of human health. In this episode, Steve tells Peter about his unusual childhood and stints as a cab driver and lion tamer.</description></item><item><title>#170 - AMA #25: Navigating the complexities and nuances of cancer screening | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000123/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000123/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter and Bob dive deep into cancer screening, including why it’s important, what you need to know about a test, and Peter’s approach with patients. They specifically discuss various screening methods, explain important terms like sensitivity and specificity, and how layering and stacking different tests in tandem can improve predictive values. They conclude with a discussion on one of the more exciting screening tools, diffusion-weighted MRI, and how it’s changing the cancer screening landscape.</description></item><item><title>#169 - Katherine Eban: COVID-19 Lab Leak: Examining all sides of the debate and discussing barriers to a full investigation | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000124/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000124/</guid><description>Podcast Description Katherine Eban is an award-winning investigative journalist who previously appeared on The Drive to discuss the widespread fraud in the generic drug industry. In this episode, she discusses the content of her recent Vanity Fair article, which examined the evidence for the theory that the COVID-19 pandemic resulted from a virus lab escape as opposed to a natural virus that came from an animal host. Katherine and Peter walk through the evidence for both theories as well as discuss the long and troubling history of dangerous lab leaks and safety concerns about the Wuhan Institute of Virology.</description></item><item><title>#168 - Hugh Jackman: Reflections on acting, identity, personal transformation, and the significance of being Wolverine | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000125/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000125/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hugh Jackman is an award-winning actor and an overall fascinating and introspective individual. In this episode, Hugh reflects upon his acting career, including how he navigated many tough decisions that led to important professional turning points for him. Peter and Hugh have an intimate discussion related to handling professional criticism, self-identity, spirituality, raising kids, and the role that past trauma often plays in extremely driven individuals. Hugh gives the inside scoop on some of his most well-known character roles and explains how he finds the energy to consistently perform.</description></item><item><title>#167 - Gary Taubes: Bad science and challenging the conventional wisdom of obesity | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000126/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000126/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gary Taubes is an investigative science and health journalist and a best-selling author. In this podcast, Gary explains how he developed a healthy skepticism for science as he was transitioning from being a physics major to beginning as a science journalist. He talks about how he was particularly drawn to sussing out “pathologic science,” telling the stories behind his books on the discovery of the W and Z bosons and cold fusion, emphasizing the need for researchers to perform a thorough background analysis.</description></item><item><title>#166 - Patricia Corby, D.D.S.: Importance of oral health, best hygiene practices, and the relationship between poor oral health and systemic disease | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000127/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000127/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dr. Patricia Corby is Associate Professor of Oral Medicine and Associate Dean of Translational Research at Penn Dental Medicine. Her work focuses on the importance of providing dental services alongside critical public healthcare services, like cancer treatment. In this episode, Pat provides an overview of dental anatomy, the importance of oral hygiene to overall health, and the association of poor oral health and systemic diseases like cancer and diabetes.</description></item><item><title>#165 - AMA #24: Deep dive into blood glucose: why it matters, important metrics to track, and superior insights from a CGM | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000128/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000128/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter and Bob dive deep into blood glucose and why it matters so much with respect to metabolic health and longevity. They explain the need to pay close attention to metrics like average blood glucose, glucose variability, and peak glucose numbers. Additionally, Peter explains why he encourages all his patients, even nondiabetics, to utilize a continuous glucose monitor (CGM) which gives important insights that traditional lab testing and metrics consistently miss.</description></item><item><title>#164 - Amanda Smith, M.D.: Diagnosing, preventing, and treating Alzheimer’s disease, and what we can all learn from patients with dementia | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000129/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000129/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amanda Grant Smith is a geriatric psychiatrist with decades of experience treating patients with dementia and Alzheimer's disease. In this episode, Amanda shares how she developed a passion for geriatric psychiatry as a means to support dementia patients. She explains how to recognize, define, and diagnose dementia—a process that still remains somewhat elusive. They also talk about the significance of ApoE genotype and compare the various forms of dementia including differentiating between Alzheimer’s disease and Lewy body dementia.</description></item><item><title>#163 - Layne Norton, Ph.D.: Building muscle, losing fat, and the importance of resistance training | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000130/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000130/</guid><description>Podcast Description Layne Norton is a physique coach, a natural professional bodybuilder and powerlifter, and holds a Ph.D. in nutritional sciences. In this episode, Layne explains how he became interested in weightlifting and fitness both professional and academically. He provides insights into preventing and managing injuries while using consistency and determination to boost his professional success in bodybuilding and powerlifting. Peter and Layne also review the science of body composition and what’s really driving muscle growth, including the role of nutrition, supplements, and a number of important and misunderstood hormones important to muscle protein synthesis.</description></item><item><title>#162 - Sarah Hallberg, D.O., M.S.: Challenging the status quo of treating metabolic disease, and a personal journey through a grim cancer diagnosis | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000131/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000131/</guid><description>Podcast Description Sarah Hallberg is the Medical Director at Virta Health and a physician who has spent nearly two decades treating patients with obesity and type 2 diabetes. In the first half of this episode, Sarah discusses how she became a huge believer in the efficacy of carbohydrate restriction for the treatment of type 2 diabetes through her research and clinical experience. Sarah challenges the common beliefs about the role of dietary fat and carbohydrate on the plasma makeup of fatty acids and triglycerides.</description></item><item><title>#161 - AMA #23: All Things Nicotine: deep dive into its cognitive and physical benefits, risks, and mechanisms of action | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000132/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000132/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter and Bob dive deep into nicotine, a complicated and interesting molecule that has effects on both the brain and the body. They analyze the results of the studies that describe nicotine’s cognitive benefits and potential for inducing weight loss. They talk about a smoking cessation technique called nicotine replacement therapy and give a full breakdown of the various routes of administration, dosing, and safety.</description></item><item><title>#160 - Paul Offit, M.D.: The latest on COVID-19 vaccines and their safety, herd immunity, and viral variants | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000133/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000133/</guid><description>Podcast Description Paul Offit is a pediatrician specializing in infectious diseases and an expert in virology and vaccine development. He currently serves on the FDA committee evaluating COVID-19 vaccines. In this episode, Paul’s second appearance on The Drive, he provides an update on all the SARS-CoV-2 vaccines currently deployed, explains why the concerns raised around the mRNA vaccines are not legitimate, and offers his view on the prospects and timeframe of reaching herd immunity.</description></item><item><title>#159 - Peter Hotez, M.D., Ph.D.: Evolution of the anti-vaccine movement, the causes of autism, and COVID-19 vaccine state of affairs | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000134/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000134/</guid><description>Podcast Description Peter Hotez is an internationally recognized physician-scientist in neglected tropical diseases and vaccine development. In this episode, they first follow up on the podcast episode (#158) with Brian Deer (the investigative journalist who exposed the complex and disturbing story behind the infamous 1998 Lancet paper by Andrew Wakefield linking the MMR vaccine and autism) with a broader discussion about the origin and evolution of the anti-vaccine movement. They explore some of the specific claims being made around vaccine additives, the timing of when vaccines are given, and claims about issues with the HPV vaccine specifically.</description></item><item><title>#158 - Brian Deer: A tale of scientific fraud—exposing Andrew Wakefield and the origin of the belief that vaccines cause autism | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000135/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000135/</guid><description>Podcast Description Brian Deer is an award-winning investigative journalist best known for his coverage of the pharmaceutical industry. In this episode, he and Peter discuss the content of his book, The Doctor Who Fooled the World: Science, Deception, and the War on Vaccines, which exposes the complex and disturbing story behind the infamous 1998 Lancet paper by Andrew Wakefield linking the MMR vaccine and autism. Brian explains how doctors led by Wakefield, a lawyer, and an anti-vaccination parents’ group worked together on a study to validate their preconceived belief that the MMR vaccine caused autism.</description></item><item><title>#157 - AMA #22: Losing fat and gaining fat: the lessons of fat flux | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000136/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2021 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000136/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter and Bob take a deep dive into fat flux. They define the major players that impact the flow of fat entering and exiting a fat cell, which determines how much fat a person carries. They discuss the significant influence that insulin has on the net fat balance and explore common strategies, such as fasting and low-carb diets, that have efficacy in the liberation and oxidation of fat from fat cells.</description></item><item><title>#156 - Jake Muise: Humanely harvesting axis deer while alleviating its impact on Hawaii’s vulnerable ecosystems | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000137/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000137/</guid><description>Podcast Description Jake Muise is an avid hunter, environmentalist, and advocate for the preservation of Hawaii’s natural resources. He is the founder of Maui Nui Venison, a company which actively manages Hawaii’s imbalanced population of axis deer by harvesting them as a food resource. In this episode, Jake tells his unbelievable backstory growing up in Northern Alberta before landing in Hawaii on a volleyball scholarship where he fell in love with the islands and the people.</description></item><item><title>#155 - Chris Sonnenday, M.D.: The history, challenges, and gift of organ transplantation | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000138/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000138/</guid><description>Podcast Description Chris Sonnenday is the Transplant Center Director for Michigan Medicine. As Peter’s senior resident while at Johns Hopkins, Chris made a lasting impression on him with his remarkable leadership and ability to maintain his humanity through the stressors of that challenging environment. In this episode, Chris tells the incredible backstory of the history of transplant medicine, focusing on the kidney and the liver. He discusses the surgical and immunologic developments that launched the field forward, but also lays out the challenges ahead for the field, such as the rising prevalence of chronic kidney and liver failure.</description></item><item><title>#154 - Steve Levitt, Ph.D.: A rogue economist’s view on climate change, mental health, the ethics of experiments, and more | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000139/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000139/</guid><description>Podcast Description Steven Levitt is a professor of economics at the University of Chicago and the co-author of the bestselling book Freakonomics and its two sequels. In this episode, Steve discusses his unlikely path to a career in economics and his view of the current state, and limitations, of the field. He also gives his unique perspective on contemporary issues including climate change, mental health in education, how to evaluate whether an experiment is ethical, decision making, horse racing, and much more.</description></item><item><title>#153 - AMA #21: Deep dive into olive oil, high-intensity exercise, book update, and more | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000140/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000140/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter and Bob take a deep dive into olive oil. They explore the history of olive oil, discuss observational data that led to the hypothesis that olive oil is a healthier alternative to many other fats, and they explain the classification of olive oil types —including what to look for in a high-quality “extra virgin” olive oil. Peter and Bob round out the discussion with a “two-minute drill,” in which Peter answers questions from subscribers.</description></item><item><title>#152 - Michael Rintala, D.C.: Principles of Dynamic Neuromuscular Stabilization (DNS) | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000141/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000141/</guid><description>Podcast Description Michael Rintala is a sports medicine chiropractor and one of only 18 international instructors teaching dynamic neuromuscular stabilization (DNS) for the Prague School of Rehabilitation. This episode focuses on understanding DNS, including the foundational principles and how it relates to human motor development. Michael also shares the most common injuries and issues he sees in patients in his practice, such as postural problems and back pain, and how the movements of a DNS program are used to avoid injury, maintain longevity, and improve sports performance.</description></item><item><title>#151 - Alex Hutchinson, Ph.D.: Translating the science of endurance and extreme human performance | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000142/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000142/</guid><description>Podcast Description Alex Hutchinson is a sports science journalist, author of the book Endure—which explores the science of endurance and the real limits of human performance—and former competitive runner for the Canadian national team. In this episode, Alex tells the story of his “aha moment” during a meaningless track meet that catapulted his running career and seeded his interest in the power of the mind. He then explains the science behind VO2 max, the difference between maximum aerobic capacity and efficiency, and extracts insights from examples of extreme human performance, such as the recent attempts to break the 2-hour mark in the marathon.</description></item><item><title>#150 - Senator Bill Frist, M.D.: A modern Renaissance man's journey through science, politics, and business | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000143/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000143/</guid><description>Podcast Description Bill Frist is a nationally acclaimed heart and lung transplant surgeon, former U.S. Senate Majority Leader, and is actively engaged in health policy and education reform. In this episode, Bill takes us through his long and varied career in medicine, politics, and business, which includes establishing the organ transplantation program at Vanderbilt as well as rising from the lowest-ranked member of the U.S. Senate to the Majority Leader in two terms.</description></item><item><title>#149 - AMA #20: Simplifying the complexities of insulin resistance: how it's measured, how it manifests in the muscle and liver, and what we can do about it | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000144/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000144/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter and Bob discuss all things related to insulin resistance by revisiting the important points made in the fascinating, yet quite technical, episode of The Drive with Gerald Shulman. They devote the entire discussion to understanding the condition known as insulin resistance, how it’s measured, how it manifests in the muscle and liver, and ultimately, what we can do about it.</description></item><item><title>#148 - Richard Miller, M.D., Ph.D.: The gold standard for testing longevity drugs: the Interventions Testing Program | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000145/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000145/</guid><description>Podcast Description Richard Miller is a professor of pathology and the Director of the Center for Aging Research at the University of Michigan. He is one of the architects of the NIA-funded Interventions Testing Programs (ITPs) animal study test protocol. In this episode, Rich goes through the results of the long list of molecules tested by the ITP—including rapamycin, metformin, nicotinamide riboside, an SGLT-2 inhibitor called canagliflozin, and more. Many of the discussed outcomes have had surprising outcomes—both positive and negative findings.</description></item><item><title>#147 - Hussein Yassine, M.D.: Deep dive into the “Alzheimer’s gene” (APOE), brain health, and omega-3s | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000146/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000146/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hussein Yassine is a physician and researcher who studies brain lipid utilization in the context of finding preventative measures for cognitive impairment, specifically Alzheimer’s disease (AD). In my conversation with Hussein, we begin with a fundamental coursework in brain biology—including its architecture and energy systems. We go on to discuss what these systems look like when something goes wrong and cognitive decline ensues. We talk about the evolutionary origins of the ApoE genotype, with specific attention to the ApoE4 allele and its association with AD.</description></item><item><title>#146 - Guy Winch, Ph.D.: Emotional first aid and how to treat psychological injuries | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000147/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000147/</guid><description>Podcast Description Guy Winch is a psychologist, author, and co-host of the Dear Therapist podcast. In this episode, Guy speaks to the commonality of the human condition with relatable stories from his decades of therapy sessions as well as his own experience with incessant rumination in the early days of his private practice. He shares insights on what he sees as an epidemic of rumination that leads to career burnout, the consequences of social comparison heightened by social media, and the psychological impact of not recognizing success.</description></item><item><title>#145 - AMA #19: Deep dive on Zone 2 training, magnesium supplementation, and how to engage with your doctor | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000148/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000148/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter and Bob take a deep dive into zone 2 training. They begin with a detailed definition of zone 2 and continue by discussing the importance of adding it to your exercise regimen. They talk about how to program zone 2 training, including intensity, frequency, and duration, and metrics for tracking improvement. Additionally, they provide a detailed overview of all things related to magnesium supplementation.</description></item><item><title>#144 - Phil Maffetone: Optimizing health and performance through maximal aerobic function | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000149/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000149/</guid><description>Podcast Description Phil Maffetone is an author, health practitioner, and coach with decades of experience helping everyone from amateurs to world-class athletes optimize their health and performance. In this episode, Phil explains the importance of developing the aerobic system, defines maximum aerobic function (MAF), and explains how to determine your MAF heart rate. He then demonstrates how to integrate that into a training protocol which is designed to help people move faster at a sub maximum heart rate and increase fat utilization as the primary source of fuel—emphasizing the importance of nutrition on one's capacity to oxidize fat.</description></item><item><title>#143 - John Ioannidis, M.D., D.Sc.: Why most biomedical research is flawed, and how to improve it | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000150/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000150/</guid><description>Podcast Description John Ioannidis is a physician, scientist, writer, and a Stanford University professor who studies scientific research itself, a process known as meta-research. In this episode, John discusses his staggering finding that the majority of published research is actually incorrect. Using nutritional epidemiology as the poster child for irreproducible findings, John describes at length the factors that play into these false positive results and offers numerous insights into how science can course correct.</description></item><item><title>#142 - Robert Abbott: The Bobby Knight story—a cautionary tale of unchecked anger, ego, and winning at all costs | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000151/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000151/</guid><description>Podcast Description Robert Abbott is a six-time Emmy award winner and the director of “The Last Days of Knight,” the behind-the-scenes documentary of legendary coach Bobby Knight, and the events that led to his termination from Indiana University. In this episode, Robert takes us through his investigative journey, which revealed cautionary tales of a winning at all costs environment—how pain often gets left in the wake of unchecked anger, ego, and perfectionism.</description></item><item><title>#141 - AMA #18: Deep dive: sugar and sugar substitutes | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000152/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000152/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter and Bob talk all about sugar and sugar substitutes and provide a way to think about sugar consumption. The conversation begins by defining the various forms of sugar, delineating between added sugar and naturally occurring sugar, and describing the important variables that determine the potential for metabolic damage from consumption. They then take a dive deep into three main categories of sugar substitutes—non-nutritive sweeteners, alcohol sugars, and leaving allulose, in a class by itself—including the safety profile of each, impact on blood sugar and insulin, side-effects, taste preferences, and more.</description></item><item><title>#140 - Gerald Shulman, M.D., Ph.D.: A masterclass on insulin resistance—molecular mechanisms and clinical implications | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000153/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000153/</guid><description>Podcast Description Gerald Shulman is a Professor of Medicine, Cellular &amp; Molecular Physiology, and the Director of the Diabetes Research Center at Yale. His pioneering work on the use of advanced technologies to analyze metabolic flux within cells has greatly contributed to the understanding of insulin resistance and type 2 diabetes. In this episode, Gerald clarifies what insulin resistance means as it relates to the muscle and the liver, and the evolutionary reason for its existence.</description></item><item><title>#139 - Kristin Neff, Ph.D.: The power of self-compassion | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000154/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000154/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kristin Neff is a Professor of Educational Psychology at the University of Texas, author, and a leading expert on mindful self-compassion. In this episode, she shares how developing a self-compassion and mindfulness practice was the most effective tool for relieving her own suffering, and provides strategies and tactics to improve self-compassion and well-being.
We discuss:
The life crisis that turned Kristin to mindfulness and self-compassion (3:30); How mindful self-compassion relieved Kristin’s feelings of self-judgement, and the psychology that says we all have the capacity for self-compassion (9:45); Peter’s history of self-criticism and his personal practice of self-compassion (17:15); The problem with prioritizing self-esteem over self-compassion, and how self-compassion produces a more stable version of self-worth (20:15); An argument for self-compassion over self-criticism for optimizing performance (26:15); How and when to introduce self-compassion to children (31:45); Learning her son had autism—a personal story of how Kristin used mindfulness and self-compassion (36:45); Self-compassion for cases of childhood trauma, PTSD, and overcoming a “fear of compassion” (44:00); The relationship between self-compassion and physical health (49:30); Distinguishing between self-compassion and self-pity, and the three necessary components self-compassion (52:30); Why self-criticism comes from a desire to be safe, the circular pattern of self-judgment, and self-compassion as the ultimate motivator (55:45); Potential role of a self-compassion practice for addiction and other maladaptive behaviors (58:45); Clinical applications and practical uses of self-compassion (1:01:30); Why you don’t need to meditate to learn mindfulness and self-compassion (1:04:45); Kristin’s personal meditation practice (1:08:40); Resources for learning self-compassion (1:11:45); and More.</description></item><item><title>#138 - Lauren Miller Rogen and Richard Isaacson, M.D.: Alzheimer’s disease prevention—patient and doctor perspectives | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000155/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000155/</guid><description>Podcast Description Peter is joined by writer, director, actress, and founder of HFC, Lauren Miller Rogen, and previous podcast guest and director of the Alzheimer’s Prevention Clinic at Weill Cornell Medicine and New York-Presbyterian, Dr. Richard Isaacson. In this episode, Lauren tells the heartbreaking story of watching members of her family succumb to Alzheimer’s disease (AD) which motivated her to proactively address her own risk with Richard’s guidance. Richard discusses the various genetic and lifestyle factors that influence the risk of AD and uses Lauren’s unique situation to explain how he diagnoses patients and personalizes care.</description></item><item><title>#137 - Paul Offit, M.D.: An expert perspective on COVID-19 vaccines | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000156/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000156/</guid><description>Podcast Description Paul Offit is a pediatrician specializing in infectious diseases and an expert in virology and vaccine development. He currently serves on the FDA committee overseeing and evaluating COVID-19 vaccines. In this episode, Paul discusses the strategies and major companies pursuing a vaccine against the SARS-CoV-2 virus. He gets into the nuances of the vaccine approval process and its implications for COVID-19 vaccine outlook. Paul also explains potential risks, reveals his own confidence level in safety, and gives insight into protection against reinfection with vaccination.</description></item><item><title>#136 - AMA #17: Body composition methods tour de force, insulin resistance, and Topo Chico | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000157/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Nov 2020 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000157/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter and Bob discuss different methods to evaluate body composition. They explore ways of measuring body fat, delineating between subcutaneous and visceral fat, and go over best strategies for improving body composition and optimizing health. They also discuss insulin resistance using a patient case study that highlights interventions capable of reversing the condition. Finally, Peter addresses his level of concern about a recent Consumer Report finding that Topo Chico had the highest levels of a class of synthetic chemicals (PFAS) of all the carbonated bottled waters tested.</description></item><item><title>#135 - BJ Miller, M.D.: How understanding death leads to a better life | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000158/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000158/</guid><description>Podcast Description BJ Miller is a hospice and palliative care specialist on a quest to reframe our relationship with death. In this episode, BJ begins with how his own brush with death radically shifted his perspective and ultimately forged his path towards palliative care and helping patients integrate and understand their life in a meaningful way. BJ recounts several moving stories from his patients, which reveal important lessons about overcoming the fear of death, letting go of regret, and what’s most important in life.</description></item><item><title>#134 - James O’Keefe, M.D.: Preventing cardiovascular disease and the risk of too much exercise. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000159/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000159/</guid><description>Podcast Description James O’Keefe is a preventative cardiologist and bestselling author of The Forever Young Diet and Lifestyle. In this episode, James discusses cardiac physiology and what makes the human heart susceptible to disease. He provides evidence for what supports his approach to exercise--elucidating both positive and negative kinds of exercise for heart health. He also discusses the role of nutrition, specific nutrients, and pharmacological interventions to support heart and brain longevity.</description></item><item><title>#133 - Vinay Prasad, M.D., M.P.H: Hallmarks of successful cancer policy | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000160/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000160/</guid><description>Podcast Description Vinay Prasad is a practicing hematologist-oncologist who doubles as a “meta-researcher,” studying the quality of medical evidence, health policy, and clinical trials. In this episode, Vinay discusses the differences in clinical treatment from the existing medical evidence, often leading to useless, or even harmful, outcomes for patients. With a focus in oncology, he takes a deep dive into the field’s structural problems, which include the disconnect between progress and funding, drug costs, and financial conflicts of interest.</description></item><item><title>#132 - AMA #16: Exploring hot and cold therapy | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000161/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000161/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter and Bob explore the quality of evidence for hot and cold therapy. In the discussion, they evaluate the safety, efficacy, and opportunity costs of various hot and cold therapy protocols, and Peter ultimately considers the addition of dry sauna to his longevity toolkit. Once again, Bob Kaplan, Peter’s head of research, will be asking the questions. If you’re not a subscriber and listening on a podcast player, you’ll only be able to hear a preview of the AMA.</description></item><item><title>#131 - Beth Lewis: The Art of Stability: Learning about pain, mitigating injury, and moving better through life | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000162/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000162/</guid><description>Podcast Description Beth Lewis is a former professional dancer and a self-described “educator of movement” who has an unmatched ability to assimilate information and customize training plans from multiple training systems. In this episode, Beth takes us through how she identifies problematic movement patterns and postures to help individuals relieve pain, avoid injury, and move better within all types of exercise. She explains how movement is in fact a trainable skill and provides suggestions for what people can add to their exercise routine to benefit their health and longevity.</description></item><item><title>#130 - Carol Tavris, Ph.D. &amp; Elliot Aronson, Ph.D.: Recognizing and overcoming cognitive dissonance | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000163/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000163/</guid><description>Podcast Description Renowned social psychologists Carol Tavris and Elliot Aronson are the co-authors of Mistakes Were Made (But Not By Me), a book which explores the science of cognitive biases and discusses how the human brain is wired for self-justification. In this episode, Carol and Elliot discuss how our desire to reconcile mental conflicts adversely affects many aspects of society. The two give real-world examples to demonstrate the pitfalls in attempts to reduce mental conflict, or dissonance.</description></item><item><title>#129 - Tom Dayspring, M.D.: The latest insights into cardiovascular disease and lipidology | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000164/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000164/</guid><description>Podcast Description World-renowned lipidologist Tom Dayspring returns to give an update on the current thinking in lipidology as a follow-up to his 2018 five-part podcast series. In this episode, Tom discusses the growing consensus that atherogenic lipoproteins are essential drivers of atherosclerotic vascular disease. Tom further emphasizes apolipoprotein B (apoB) and lipoprotein(a) (Lp(a)). He provides insights into risk assessment, including which lab metrics to use, how to interpret them, and the appropriate therapeutic targets.</description></item><item><title>#128 – Irene Davis, Ph.D.: The evolution of the foot, running injuries, and minimalist shoes | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000165/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000165/</guid><description>Podcast Description Irene Davis is the founding Director of the Spaulding National Running Center at the Harvard Medical School. In this episode, Irene describes how her research of biomechanics and clinical work with running injuries, as well as research by others, has shaped her views on maintaining body alignment and foot health. Irene discusses her argument for the role of modern footwear in running-related injuries and how minimalist footwear helps resolve the subsequent biomechanical issues.</description></item><item><title>#127 - AMA #3 with sleep expert, Matthew Walker, Ph.D.: Fasting, gut health, blue light, caffeine, REM sleep, and more | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000166/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000166/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this special episode, Matthew Walker returns for his third AMA episode to provide his expert insight into numerous sleep-related questions directly from listeners. He explains how he adjusted his hypotheses on topics like blue light and caffeine, and why he is more bullish on the importance of REM sleep. Matt also answers questions about sleep wearables, how fasting affects sleep, how sleep deprivation impacts gut health, and magnesium as a sleep aid.</description></item><item><title>#126 – Matthew Walker, Ph.D.: Sleep and immune function, chronotypes, hygiene tips, and addressing questions about his book | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000167/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000167/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, sleep expert Matthew Walker returns by popular demand to dive deeper into many sleep-related topics, starting with what we’ve learned about sleep through the lens of the COVID-19 pandemic and how sleep impacts the immune system. He then covers topics such as how dreaming affects emotional health, the different sleep chronotypes, the best sleep hygiene tips, and the pros and cons of napping. Matthew finishes by addressing several of the errors that readers have pointed out in his book, Why We Sleep.</description></item><item><title>#125 - John Arnold: The most prolific philanthropist you may not have heard of | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000168/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000168/</guid><description>Podcast Description John Arnold is widely regarded as the greatest natural gas trader of all time, but in his late 30’s he walked away from it all and turned full-time philanthropist. He and his wife have committed to strategically give away most of their vast fortune in their lifetime and are already doing so at a staggering pace of nearly a half billion dollars a year. In this episode, John explains his quest to address the most challenging social programs plaguing the country, including criminal justice, health care policy, and K-12 education.</description></item><item><title>#124 - AMA #15: Real-world case studies—metabolic dysregulation, low testosterone, menopause, and more | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000169/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000169/</guid><description>Podcast Description As a follow up to AMA #14 where Peter explained his framework for analyzing labs, this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode focuses on a number of real-world case studies exploring metabolic dysregulation, low testosterone, menopause, hypothyroidism, elevated uric acid, and more. From the examples discussed, you can follow along how our clinical team goes about interpreting diagnostic measures and applying relevant research findings. Once again, Bob Kaplan, Peter’s head of research, will be asking the questions.</description></item><item><title>#123 - Joan Mannick, M.D. &amp; Nir Barzilai, M.D.: Rapamycin and metformin—longevity, immune enhancement, and COVID-19 | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000170/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000170/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Joan and Nir discuss their extensive research into rapamycin (including the category of analogs to rapamycin known as rapalogs) and metformin, respectively. Based on his work with metformin, Nir shares how he believes it could be a pro-longevity drug and the clinical trial he’s leading to test this belief. Joan discusses her work with rapalogs, their ability to suppress the immune system as well as provide immune-enhancement, and the clinical trials she has led that inform her insights.</description></item><item><title>#122 - Lori Gottlieb: Understanding pain, therapeutic breakthroughs, and keys to enduring emotional health | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000171/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000171/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lori Gottlieb is a psychotherapist and the bestselling author of Maybe You Should Talk to Someone. In this episode, Lori extracts important lessons from her experiences as both a therapist and a patient. The stories Lori shares has provided her the material for insights into living a more fulfilling life. In our conversation, Lori also dispels some misconceptions about therapy, explains the process of big therapeutic breakthroughs, and reveals the most important steps for enduring emotional health.</description></item><item><title>#121 - Azra Raza, M.D.: Why we're losing the war on cancer | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000172/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000172/</guid><description>Podcast Description Azra Raza is a physician, scientist, author, and outspoken advocate for reconfiguring the current model of research in cancer. In this episode, Azra discusses the content of her book, The First Cell, which takes a critical look at the outdated models being used to study cancer resulting in a lack of progress in survival rates for cancer patients. Azra offers a solution which focuses on early detection and prevention, and she concludes with an optimistic outlook for the future of cancer research.</description></item><item><title>#120 - AMA with Dom D’Agostino, Ph.D., Part II of II: Ketosis for cancer and chronic disease, hyperbaric oxygen therapy, and the effect of ketosis on female health | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000173/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000173/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part 2 of this special AMA episode, ketosis expert Dom D’Agostino once again joins Bob Kaplan, Peter’s Head of Research, to discuss the impact of ketosis on various chronic diseases as well as the latest research on the metabolic management of cancer. Dom also discusses the numerous applications of hyperbaric oxygen therapy, provides insights into the application of ketosis on female health and performance, and much more. If you’re not a subscriber and listening on a podcast player, you’ll only be able to hear a preview of the AMA.</description></item><item><title>#119 - Terry Real: Breaking the cycle of shame, anger, and depression | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000174/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000174/</guid><description>Podcast Description Terry Real, a renowned family therapist and best-selling author, helps people create the connections they desire in their relationships. In this episode, Terry describes how his upbringing with an abusive father forged his path to become a therapist, develop his Relational Life Therapy (RLT) framework, and write I Don't Want to Talk About It—a book that reveals the hidden legacy of male depression. Terry discusses the link between childhood trauma and the deep-rooted shame, anger, and depression, which can result in feeling disconnected.</description></item><item><title>#118 - Lloyd Klickstein, M.D., Ph.D.: Rapamycin, mTOR inhibition, and the biology of aging | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000175/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000175/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lloyd Klickstein is the Chief Science Officer at resTORbio, a biopharmaceutical company that develops medications to target the biology of aging. In this episode, Lloyd discusses his company’s clinical application of rapamycin and its derivatives. He also elucidates details of his 2014 paper—a paper that greatly influenced Peter’s perspective of rapamycin in the context of longevity. Peter and Lloyd go on to discuss the dose-dependent effect of rapamycin on immune function and compare rapamycin, fasting, and caloric restriction.</description></item><item><title>#117 - Stanley Perlman, M.D., Ph.D.: Insights from a coronavirus expert on COVID-19 | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000176/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000176/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Stanley Perlman shares insights from his impressive career studying coronaviruses—both the common and more deadly ones, like MERS and SARS. In comparing preceding coronaviruses with SARS-CoV-2, Stanley discusses how other coronaviruses can aid our current understanding of, and be used to infer about, COVID-19. He also gives his thoughts on durable immunity, therapeutic strategies, and future outbreak preparedness. We discuss: His background and early work with coronaviruses [2:45]; The coronavirus family—various types, common traits, and scientific understanding [9:00]; The origin of viruses, animal to human transmission, R_0, immunity, and more [17:45]; Insights from the 2002 SARS outbreak [28:30]; Insights from the 2012 MERS outbreak [35:00]; Comparing SARS-CoV-2 to MERS, SARS, and other coronaviruses [42:00]; COVID-19 survivor potential for long-term damage [53:30]; Using the current pandemic for lessons on future preparedness [57:00]; Genetic drift and the potential for long-term immunity to COVID-19 [1:07:00]; Prevention and treatment strategies for COVID-19 and future diseases [1:22:30]; Alternative hypothesis to the origin of SARS-CoV-2 [1:32:30]; Determining durable immunity to COVID-19 and what a successful vaccine looks like [1:34:30]; and More.</description></item><item><title>#116 - AMA with Dom D’Agostino, Ph.D., Part I of II: Ketogenic diet, exogenous ketones, and exercise | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000177/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000177/</guid><description>Podcast Description Back by very popular demand for a special AMA episode, ketosis expert Dom D’Agostino joins Bob Kaplan, Peter’s Head of Research, to address many lingering questions about the ketogenic diet, exogenous ketones, and exercise for overall health. Dom also shares valuable insights from his personal experience with training, supplements, intermittent fasting, and other nutritional strategies to optimize his own health and performance. If you’re not a subscriber and listening on a podcast player, you’ll only be able to hear a preview of the AMA.</description></item><item><title>#115 - David Watkins, Ph.D.: A masterclass in immunology, monoclonal antibodies, and vaccine strategies for COVID-19 | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000178/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000178/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, David Watkins, professor of pathology at George Washington University, shares how insights from his HIV and Zika virus research could apply to SARS-CoV-2 protection strategies. David introduces monoclonal antibodies as an intervention to prevent and treat COVID-19 infection, and also discusses how they could be used as a hedge to vaccine development. Additionally, David’s immunology tutorial explains the innate and adaptive immune systems and their differentiated responses to viral infection.</description></item><item><title>#114 - Eileen White, Ph.D.: Autophagy, fasting, and promising new cancer therapies | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000179/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000179/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Eileen White, Chief Scientific Officer at the Rutgers Cancer Institute, describes the fundamental role of autophagy in the maintenance of health and prevention of neurodegeneration, cancer, and other diseases. She also goes into detail about the paradoxical finding that autophagy may benefit an existing cancer cell and help it to survive—a discovery leading to new possibilities in cancer therapy. We also discuss fasting (and molecules that induce autophagy) and the critical need to decode the proper fasting “dose” in order to improve human health.</description></item><item><title>#113: Normative errors—a conversation with my daughter about current events | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000180/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000180/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, I sit down with my daughter to discuss the brutal death of George Floyd, and the aftermath we are watching unfold. Though I have no expertise in race relations, law enforcement, or police brutality, I do have some knowledge in the training of physicians, and it is that training of doctors that I’ve been thinking about lately as it may offer one small insight into this crisis.</description></item><item><title>#112 - Ned David, Ph.D.: How cellular senescence influences aging, and what we can do about it | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000181/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000181/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ned David is the co-founder of Unity Biotechnology, a company developing senolytic medicines—molecules that target and destroy senescent cells in the human body. In this episode, Ned explains the science of cellular senescence and how it impacts the aging process. Ned discusses how senolytics may delay, prevent, treat, or even reverse age-related diseases, including cancer, cardiovascular disease, and neurodegenerative disease. As a serial entrepreneur, Ned also provides advice on how to transform a simple idea into the creation of a company.</description></item><item><title>#111 - AMA #14: What lab tests can (and cannot) inform us about our overall objective of longevity | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000182/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000182/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter explains his framework for understanding what lab tests can (and cannot) inform us as it pertains to overall longevity, with a specific focus on atherosclerosis, cancer, Alzheimer’s disease, and the physical body. Additionally, Peter shares details into two patient case studies around cardiovascular disease, including how the lab results influenced his diagnosis and treatment plan for the patients. Once again, Bob Kaplan, Peter’s head of research, will be asking the questions.</description></item><item><title>#110 - Lew Cantley, Ph.D.: Cancer metabolism, cancer therapies, and the discovery of PI3K | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000183/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000183/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Lew Cantley, Professor of cancer biology and Director of the Sandra and Edward Meyer Cancer Center at Weill Cornell Medical College in NYC, walks us through his amazing discovery of phosphoinositide 3-kinase (PI3K) and the implications for the care of patients with cancer. He explains various combinations of therapies being tested and used, including the possibility of pairing prescriptive nutritional therapies to increase the efficacy of drugs like PI3K inhibitors.</description></item><item><title>#109 - John Dudley: The beauty in archery, the love of practice, and a model system for life | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000184/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000184/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, professional archer, John Dudley, shares the many insights he’s gleaned through the process of not only becoming an elite competitor of archery but also an exceptional teacher. John describes how his desire for improvement has cultivated a sheer love of practice, and how pursuing mastery helped put into context how archery is an amazing model system for life. Additionally, John discusses the often misunderstood nature of hunting, but also makes the case as to why one should consider trying archery even if there is no desire to hunt.</description></item><item><title>#108 - AMA #13: 3-day fasting, exogenous ketones, autophagy, and exercise for longevity | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000185/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000185/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter explains some observations he’s noticed since switching to a 3-day fasting cycle from the longer fasts, the various things he’s measuring, and some helpful tips for getting through a prolonged fast. He also discusses the role of exogenous ketones in fasting and ketogenic diets as well as their impact on autophagy, specifically. Finally, Peter provides some practical advice for those looking to fit exercise for longevity into their busy life.</description></item><item><title>#107 - John Barry: 1918 Spanish flu pandemic—historical account, parallels to today, and lessons | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000186/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000186/</guid><description>Podcast Description n this episode, John Barry, historian and author of The Great Influenza: The Story of the Deadliest Pandemic in History, describes what happened with the 1918 Spanish flu pandemic, including where it likely originated, how and why it spread, and what may have accounted for the occurrence of three separate waves of the virus, each with different rates of infection and mortality. While the current coronavirus pandemic pales in comparison to the devastation of the Spanish flu, John highlights a number of parallels that can be drawn and lessons to be learned and applied going forward.</description></item><item><title>#106 - Amesh Adalja, M.D.: Comparing COVID-19 to past pandemics, preparing for the future, and reasons for optimism | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000187/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000187/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, infectious disease and pandemic preparedness expert, Amesh Adalja, M.D., puts the current pandemic into context against previous coronaviruses as well as past influenza pandemics. Amesh also provides his interpretation of the evolving metrics which have contributed to big variations in modeling predictions, whether this will be a seasonally recurring virus, and perhaps most importantly—how we can be better prepared for the inevitable future novel virus. Finally, Amesh explains where he sees positive trends which give him reasons for optimism.</description></item><item><title>#105 - Paul Conti, M.D.: The psychological toll of a pandemic, and the societal problems it has highlighted | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000188/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000188/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, psychiatrist Paul Conti, M.D. discusses the impact of the fear and uncertainty surrounding the COVID-19 pandemic and the resulting stress, anxiety, and trauma it may impart on the population. Paul examines how this situation has highlighted the challenges we face at the societal level as well as the individual level, and stresses the importance of seeking absolute truth above personal truth and taking action as individuals as a means to combat many of these pervasive problems.</description></item><item><title>#104 - COVID-19 for kids with Olivia Attia | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000189/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000189/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Peter sits down with his daughter to answer questions from her and other kids about COVID-19.
We discuss:
What is a virus? [1:45]; How did this version of coronavirus (SARS-CoV-2) start? [4:30]; How does COVID-19 compare to SARS and MERS (previous coronaviruses)? [6:00]; Will COVID-19 come back again after we resolve the current issue? [7:15]; When will kids go back to school? [7:45]; How has the US surpassed China in total cases, and how could we have been better prepared for this?</description></item><item><title>#103 - Looking back on the first 99 episodes: Strong Convictions, Loosely Held | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000190/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000190/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, originally recorded to be the 100th episode of The Drive, Peter discusses topics that he has changed his mind about since starting the podcast as a result of preparing for interviews as well as from the actual conversations. Peter also reviews some of his favorite moments from the first 99 episodes, shares what books he’s currently reading, and much more. Initially scheduled to be released as episode 100, this was delayed due to recent podcasts covering COVID-19.</description></item><item><title>#102 - Michael Osterholm, Ph.D.: COVID-19—Lessons learned, challenges ahead, and reasons for optimism and concern | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000191/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000191/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Michael Osterholm, Director of the Center for Infectious Disease Research and Policy at the University of Minnesota and author of Deadliest Enemy: Our War Against Killer Germs, provides an overview on the COVID-19 pandemic in regards to what has happened to date, what we’ve learned about how the disease spreads, and his optimism and pessimism about what potentially lies ahead. Michael gives his take on the true case fatality rate, why it differs around the world, and which underlying conditions, such as obesity, impact risk of severe illness and death.</description></item><item><title>#101 - Ryan Holiday: Finding stillness amidst chaos | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000192/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000192/</guid><description>Podcast Description Ryan Holiday, bestselling author and author of Daily Stoic, discusses practical ways to find stillness and apply the insights of stoic philosophy in the midst of COVID-19 chaos. Ryan discusses the importance of taking back a feeling of control, the benefits of structure and routine, and the idea of being prepared for anything.
We discuss:
Using times of adversity to evaluate and reflect how you’ve set up and prioritized your life [2:30];</description></item><item><title>#100 - Sam Harris, Ph.D.: COVID-19—Comprehending the crisis and managing our emotions | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000193/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 16:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000193/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Sam Harris, neuroscientist, author, and host of the Making Sense Podcast, joins Peter to discuss this unprecedented coronavirus (COVID-19) crisis. The discussion includes the important distinction between COVID-19 and influenza, the impact on the economy, the dire situation in New York, and the challenge of creating a safe and effective vaccine. Additionally, Sam brings insights from his extensive meditation practice to help those struggling with stress, anxiety, and fear in this extraordinary situation.</description></item><item><title>#99 - Peter Hotez, M.D., Ph.D.: Continuing the conversation on COVID-19 | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000194/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 23:49:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000194/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Dr. Peter Hotez M.D., Ph.D., Dean for the National School of Tropical Medicine Baylor College of Medicine, returns to continue the conversation on COVID-19. Dr. Hotez informs us on how we can gauge the number of infected people, behaviors to reduce the probability of becoming infected, and the inconsistency of hospitalizations among young adults between different countries. Dr. Hotez underscores the continued uncertainty in many virus-related developments, but ends with some points of optimism.</description></item><item><title>Qualy #129 - Evolutionary reasons to sleep | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000195/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000195/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode of The Qualys is from podcast #47 – Matthew Walker, Ph.D., on sleep – Part I of III: Dangers of poor sleep, Alzheimer’s risk, mental health, memory consolidation, and more.
The Qualys is a subscriber-exclusive podcast, released Tuesday through Friday, and published exclusively on our private, subscriber-only podcast feed. Qualys is short-hand for “qualifying round,” which are typically the fastest laps driven in a race car—done before the race to determine starting position on the grid for race day.</description></item><item><title>#97 - Peter Hotez, M.D., Ph.D.: COVID-19: transmissibility, vaccines, risk reduction, and treatment | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000196/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000196/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Dr. Peter Hotez M.D., Ph.D., Dean for the National School of Tropical Medicine Baylor College of Medicine, shares his expertise on viral disease and how it applies specifically to the coronavirus disease (COVID-19) and the virus that causes it (SARS-CoV-2). Dr. Hotez informs us about the current state of disease progression, which has many unknowns, but has thus far been greatly determined by the delayed response time and lack of testing.</description></item><item><title>Qualy #125 - Hierarchies in healthcare, physician burnout, and a broken system | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000197/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000197/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode of The Qualys is from podcast #37 – Zubin Damania, M.D.: Revolutionizing healthcare one hilariously inspiring video at a time.
The Qualys is a subscriber-exclusive podcast, released Tuesday through Friday, and published exclusively on our private, subscriber-only podcast feed. Qualys is short-hand for “qualifying round,” which are typically the fastest laps driven in a race car—done before the race to determine starting position on the grid for race day.</description></item><item><title>#96 - David Epstein: How a range of experience leads to better performance in a highly specialized world | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000198/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000198/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, David Epstein, best-selling author of Range and The Sports Gene, discusses the evidence around the most effective ways to improve long-term performance and learning in our specialties, our sports, our careers, and our lives. David makes a compelling case that a range of experiences and skills are more likely to lead to expert performance compared to early specialization, and offers an in-depth critique of the much-publicized 10,000-Hour Rule.</description></item><item><title>Qualy #121 - The “art” of longevity: the challenge of preventative medicine and understanding risk | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000199/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000199/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode of The Qualys is from podcast #52 – Ethan Weiss, M.D.: A masterclass in cardiovascular disease and growth hormone – two topics that are surprising interrelated.
The Qualys is a subscriber-exclusive podcast, released Tuesday through Friday, and published exclusively on our private, subscriber-only podcast feed. Qualys is short-hand for “qualifying round,” which are typically the fastest laps driven in a race car—done before the race to determine starting position on the grid for race day.</description></item><item><title>#95 - Luke Bennett, M.D.: The emotional, cognitive, and physical demands that make Formula 1 a unique and special sport | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000200/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000200/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Luke Bennett, Medical and Sports Performance Director for Hintsa Performance, explains the ins and outs of Formula 1 with a focus on the behind-the-scenes human element, and what makes it so emotionally, cognitively, and physically demanding for the drivers as well as the many team members. Luke first talks about his fascinating background with the Royal Flying Doctor Service in Australia, which lead to his current position with Hintsa working closely with F1 drivers to improve their health and performance despite jet-lag and sleep constraints due to an unrivaled travel schedule.</description></item><item><title>Qualy #120 - What is the difference between ketone salts and esters? | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000201/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000201/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode of The Qualys is from podcast #05 – Dom D’Agostino, Ph.D.: ketosis, n=1, exogenous ketones, HBOT, seizures, and cancer.
The Qualys is a subscriber-exclusive podcast, released Tuesday through Friday, and published exclusively on our private, subscriber-only podcast feed. Qualys is short-hand for “qualifying round,” which are typically the fastest laps driven in a race car—done before the race to determine starting position on the grid for race day.</description></item><item><title>#94 - Mark Hyman, M.D.: The impact of the food system on our health and the environment | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000202/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000202/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Mark Hyman, M.D., director of the Cleveland Clinic Center for Functional Medicine and the author of Food Fix, discusses that if we can fix the food system, we can solve many big problems—namely the chronic disease/obesity epidemic, the rising costs of healthcare, as well as the big problems facing the environment. Mark first briefly lays out the health consequences of processed food with a focus on the gut microbiome.</description></item><item><title>Qualy #116 - Dealing with anger in spots where you know it’s coming | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000203/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000203/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode of The Qualys is from podcast #34 – Sam Harris, Ph.D.: The transformative power of mindfulness.
The Qualys is a subscriber-exclusive podcast, released Tuesday through Friday, and published exclusively on our private, subscriber-only podcast feed. Qualys is short-hand for “qualifying round,” which are typically the fastest laps driven in a race car—done before the race to determine starting position on the grid for race day. The Qualys are short (i.</description></item><item><title>#93 - AMA with Jason Fried: Work-life balance, avoiding burnout, defining success, company culture, and more | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000204/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000204/</guid><description>Podcast Description In my first interview with Jason Fried, Jason explained his overall philosophy about work-life balance and how exactly he optimizes for efficiency. For this special follow-up AMA, we've decided to release the full episode to everyone (including non-subscribers), so all can hear Jason answer questions from listeners that dive deeper into topics such as work-life balance, the role of luck versus hard work in success, specifics around Basecamp’s unique process-oriented approach to projects, 4-day work weeks, practical tips for people searching for the right company culture, tips on writing and parenting, and a whole bunch more.</description></item><item><title>Qualy #109 - How does one select the right physician as a patient? | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000205/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000205/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode of The Qualys is from podcast #04 – AMA #1: alcohol, best lab tests, wearables, finding the right doc, racing, and more.
The Qualys is a subscriber-exclusive podcast, released Tuesday through Friday, and published exclusively on our private, subscriber-only podcast feed. Qualys is short-hand for “qualifying round,” which are typically the fastest laps driven in a race car—done before the race to determine starting position on the grid for race day.</description></item><item><title>92 - AMA #12: Strategies for longevity (which don't require a doctor) | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000206/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000206/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter explains the various levers one can pull to affect longevity with a specific focus on the strategies and tactics one can implement that do not require the help of a physician. Once again, Bob Kaplan, Peter's head of research, will be asking the questions. If you’re not a subscriber and listening on a podcast player, you’ll only be able to hear a preview of the AMA.</description></item><item><title>Qualy #106 - Does LDL cause heart disease? | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000207/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000207/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode of The Qualys is from podcast #03 – Ron Krauss, M.D.: a deep dive into heart disease.
The Qualys is a subscriber-exclusive podcast, released Tuesday through Friday, and published exclusively on our private, subscriber-only podcast feed. Qualys is short-hand for “qualifying round,” which are typically the fastest laps driven in a race car—done before the race to determine starting position on the grid for race day. The Qualys are short (i.</description></item><item><title>#91 – Eric Topol, M.D.: Can AI empower physicians and revolutionize patient care? | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000208/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000208/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Dr. Eric Topol, founder and director of the Scripps Research Translational Institute, shares how artificial intelligence and deep learning is currently impacting medicine and how it could transform the healthcare industry, not only in terms of the technological advancements, but also in restoring the patient-doctor relationship for better patient outcomes and experiences. We also discuss Eric’s rich and fascinating career in cardiology as well as his involvement as one of the first outspoken researchers to question the cardiovascular safety of Vioxx.</description></item><item><title>Qualy #102 - Is the food industry still saying that all calories contribute equally to adiposity and insulin resistance? | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000209/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000209/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode of The Qualys is from podcast #14 – Robert Lustig, M.D., M.S.L.: fructose, processed food, NAFLD, and changing the food system.
The Qualys is a subscriber-exclusive podcast, released Tuesday through Friday, and published exclusively on our private, subscriber-only podcast feed. Qualys is short-hand for “qualifying round,” which are typically the fastest laps driven in a race car—done before the race to determine starting position on the grid for race day.</description></item><item><title>#90 - Ryan Holiday: Stillness, stoicism, and suffering less | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000210/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000210/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Ryan Holiday, author of Stillness is the Key, shares the profound impact that stoic philosophy has had on his personal life and his career as a successful writer. Ryan stresses the importance of stillness in a modern world set up to encourage the opposite and lays out the best strategies to develop stillness in your life. He also explains the destructive nature of being driven by ego, as well as the perils of jealousy and anger, and provides practical steps you can take to avoid those harmful states.</description></item><item><title>Qualy #99 - The steroid controversy: Mark’s use of them and Peter’s perspective | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000211/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000211/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode of The Qualys is from podcast #28 – Mark and Chris Bell: steroids, powerlifting, addiction, diet, training, helping others, documentaries, and living your best life.
The Qualys is a subscriber-exclusive podcast, released Tuesday through Friday, and published exclusively on our private, subscriber-only podcast feed. Qualys is short-hand for “qualifying round,” which are typically the fastest laps driven in a race car—done before the race to determine starting position on the grid for race day.</description></item><item><title>#89 - AMA #11: All things fasting | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000212/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000212/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter answers a wide range of fasting-specific questions from subscribers. Peter starts by defining the various fasting protocols, details his own personal fasting regimen, explains his revised plan for 2020, and provides a ton of value to anyone interested in fasting. Once again, Bob Kaplan, Peter's head of research, will be asking the questions. If you’re not a subscriber and listening on a podcast player, you’ll only be able to hear a preview of the AMA.</description></item><item><title>Qualy #94 - Comparing the two broad types of meditation, and Peter’s favorite meditation apps | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000213/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000213/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode of The Qualys is from podcast #34 – Sam Harris, Ph.D.: The transformative power of mindfulness.
The Qualys is a subscriber-exclusive podcast, released Tuesday through Friday, and published exclusively on our private, subscriber-only podcast feed. Qualys is short-hand for “qualifying round,” which are typically the fastest laps driven in a race car—done before the race to determine starting position on the grid for race day. The Qualys are short (i.</description></item><item><title>Qualy #89 - Cortisol and healthy aging | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000214/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000214/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode of The Qualys is from podcast #31 – Navdeep Chandel, Ph.D.: metabolism, mitochondria, and metformin in health and disease.
The Qualys is a subscriber-exclusive podcast, released Tuesday through Friday, and published exclusively on our private, subscriber-only podcast feed. Qualys is short-hand for “qualifying round,” which are typically the fastest laps driven in a race car—done before the race to determine starting position on the grid for race day.</description></item><item><title>#87 - Rick Johnson, M.D.: Fructose—The common link in high blood pressure, insulin resistance, T2D, &amp; obesity? | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000215/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000215/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Rick Johnson, Professor of Nephrology at the University of Colorado, explains how his research into the causes of blood pressure resulted in a change of research direction to focus more on how fructose has such profound metabolic effects. Rick discusses the relationship between salt and high blood pressure, provides a masterclass into uric acid, and expertly reveals the mechanisms and pathways by which sugar (specifically fructose) can profoundly impact metabolic health.</description></item><item><title>Qualy #85 - The past, present, and future of medicine, hospitals, and healthcare | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000216/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000216/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode of The Qualys is from podcast #06 – D.A. Wallach: music, medicine, longevity, and disruptive technologies.
The Qualys is a subscriber-exclusive podcast, released Tuesday through Friday, and published exclusively on our private, subscriber-only podcast feed. Qualys is short-hand for “qualifying round,” which are typically the fastest laps driven in a race car—done before the race to determine starting position on the grid for race day. The Qualys are short (i.</description></item><item><title>#86 - Damon Hill: Overcoming loss, achieving success, and finding one's identity | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000217/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000217/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Damon Hill, 1996 Formula 1 World Champion, opens up about his personal struggles with depression, feelings of inadequacy, loss of identity, and his ultimate path to healing following his remarkable racing career. Damon’s life was given a tragic jolt at 15 years of age when his father and legendary F1 driver Graham Hill died suddenly—the common string that ties together so much of his life and has forged so much of who he is to this day.</description></item><item><title>Qualy #82 - What is the most common first presentation of heart disease? | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000218/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000218/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode of The Qualys is from podcast #03 – Ron Krauss, M.D.: a deep dive into heart disease.
The Qualys is a subscriber-exclusive podcast, released Tuesday through Friday, and published exclusively on our private, subscriber-only podcast feed. Qualys is short-hand for “qualifying round,” which are typically the fastest laps driven in a race car—done before the race to determine starting position on the grid for race day. The Qualys are short (i.</description></item><item><title>#85 - Iñigo San Millán, Ph.D.: Mitochondria, exercise, and metabolic health | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000219/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000219/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Dr. Iñigo San Millán, Assistant Professor at the University of Colorado School of Medicine, explains the crucial role of mitochondrial function in everything from metabolic health to elite exercise performance. Iñigo provides a masterclass into the many different energy system pathways, the various fuel sources (including the misunderstood lactate), the six zones of exercise training, and the parameters he uses to measure metabolic health. Additionally, he highlights the power of zone 2 training in its ability to act as a powerful diagnostic tool, and perhaps more importantly as a treatment for mitochondrial and metabolic dysfunction.</description></item><item><title>Qualy #80 - The four pillars of charity: water that helped it overcome the stigma of nonprofits and become successful | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000220/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000220/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode of The Qualys is from podcast #25 – Scott Harrison: transformation, finding meaning, and taking on the global water crisis.
The Qualys is a subscriber-exclusive podcast, released Tuesday through Friday, and published exclusively on our private, subscriber-only podcast feed. Qualys is short-hand for “qualifying round,” which are typically the fastest laps driven in a race car—done before the race to determine starting position on the grid for race day.</description></item><item><title>#84 - AMA #10: Low testosterone, hypothyroidism, building muscle (and preserving it while fasting) | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000221/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000221/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter answers a wide range of questions from subscribers. Bob Kaplan, Peter’s head of research, asks the questions. If you’re not a subscriber and listening on a podcast player, you’ll only be able to hear a preview of the AMA.
If you’re a subscriber, you can now listen to this full episode on your private RSS feed. You can also listen to this full episode on our website at the AMA #10 show notes page.</description></item><item><title>Qualy #73 - How can we change the food system when 10 companies control almost 90 percent of the calories we consume in the US? | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000222/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000222/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode of The Qualys is from podcast #14 – Robert Lustig, M.D., M.S.L.: fructose, processed food, NAFLD, and changing the food system.
The Qualys is a subscriber-exclusive podcast, released Tuesday through Friday, and published exclusively on our private, subscriber-only podcast feed. Qualys is short-hand for “qualifying round,” which are typically the fastest laps driven in a race car—done before the race to determine starting position on the grid for race day.</description></item><item><title>#83 - Bill Harris, Ph.D.: Omega-3 fatty acids | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000223/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000223/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Bill Harris, Ph.D. in human nutrition and expert on omega-3 fatty acids, sets the table by clearly defining the families of fatty acids (saturated, monounsaturated, polyunsaturated) before diving into the current landscape of polyunsaturated fat (omega-6 and omega-3) with a particular focus on EPA and DHA (the two main elements of fish oil supplements). Bill gives a historical overview, updates us on the latest science related to the health benefits, and provides plenty of insights as to how we should think about increasing our EPA and DHA intake.</description></item><item><title>Qualy #69 - Advice to parents and kids for creating a sustainable environment that’s going to prevent them from running into metabolic problems | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000224/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000224/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode of The Qualys is from podcast #14 – Robert Lustig, M.D., M.S.L.: fructose, processed food, NAFLD, and changing the food system.
The Qualys is a subscriber-exclusive podcast, released Tuesday through Friday, and published exclusively on our private, subscriber-only podcast feed. Qualys is short-hand for “qualifying round,” which are typically the fastest laps driven in a race car—done before the race to determine starting position on the grid for race day.</description></item><item><title>#82 - Mark Messier: Leadership, personal growth, and performing under pressure | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000225/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000225/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Mark Messier, six-time Stanley Cup champion, shares the most valuable lessons he picked up over 25+ years of professional hockey resulting in one of the longest and most decorated careers in hockey history. Mark shares what lead to his unique brand of humble leadership, how he was able to get talented individuals to effectively work as a team, the importance of maturing and evolving as a person, and how he was able to stay calm and perform at his best under enormous amounts of pressure.</description></item><item><title>Qualy #65 - The three laws of medicine — Law #1: A strong intuition is much more powerful than a weak test | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000226/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000226/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode of The Qualys is from podcast #32 – Siddhartha Mukherjee, M.D., Ph.D.: new frontiers in cancer therapy, medicine, and the writing process. The Qualys is a subscriber-exclusive podcast, released Tuesday through Friday, and published exclusively on our private, subscriber-only podcast feed. Qualys is short-hand for “qualifying round,” which are typically the fastest laps driven in a race car—done before the race to determine starting position on the grid for race day.</description></item><item><title>#81 - Debra Kimless, M.D. &amp; Steve Goldner, J.D.: Cannabis – the latest science on CBD &amp; THC | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000227/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000227/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Dr. Debra Kimless and Steve Goldner share their knowledge on the science, policy, and market evolution of medicinal cannabis. We start with the differences between THC and CBD, how they work in the body, and how they act on the brain. We discuss the many potential benefits of using CBD, THC, hemp in the various forms of administration (smoking, vaping, edibles, oils, etc.) as well as some of the safety issues including the recent uptick in incidents of hospitalization and death linked to vaping.</description></item><item><title>Qualy #61 - Rapamycin in cancer treatment | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000228/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000228/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode of The Qualys is from podcast #10 – Matt Kaeberlein, Ph.D.: rapamycin and dogs — man’s best friends? — living longer, healthier lives and turning back the clock on aging and age-related diseases.
The Qualys is a subscriber-exclusive podcast, released Tuesday through Friday, and published exclusively on our private, subscriber-only podcast feed. Qualys is short-hand for “qualifying round,” which are typically the fastest laps driven in a race car—done before the race to determine starting position on the grid for race day.</description></item><item><title>#80 - Celebrity AMA #1: Fasting, rapamycin, performance vs. longevity, and more | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000229/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000229/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this special, bonus celebrity AMA episode, Peter answers questions from former Olympians and past guests, Apolo Ohno and Sasha Cohen, on a wide range of subjects including fasting, learning, training for performance versus longevity, and much more. This bonus AMA is available in full to everyone.
Apolo's questions begin [1:45];
Why women may have a harder time fasting, and tips for those who are struggling [2:10];
Is there any place for fasting as part of a nutritional strategy in adolescents?</description></item><item><title>Qualy #57 - A primer on NAD+/NADH, its effect on lifespan/healthspan, and a review of the supplements | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000230/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000230/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode of The Qualys is from podcast #02 – Rhonda Patrick, Ph.D.: the performance and longevity paradox of IGF-1, ketogenic diets and genetics, the health benefits of sauna, NAD+, and more.
The Qualys is a subscriber-exclusive podcast, released Tuesday through Friday, and published exclusively on our private, subscriber-only podcast feed. Qualys is short-hand for “qualifying round,” which are typically the fastest laps driven in a race car—done before the race to determine starting position on the grid for race day.</description></item><item><title>#79 - Ric Elias: Earning the gift of life | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000231/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000231/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Ric Elias, founder of Red Ventures, opens up about the fateful day he knew for certain that he was going to die as a passenger on US Airways Flight 1549. Ric dives deep into how that day impacted his life, greatly changed his perspective, and improved his relationship with his family and the broader community. We also talk about his incredible role as CEO of an enormous company, his remarkable work in philanthropy, and all the wisdom he has acquired in his extraordinary life.</description></item><item><title>Qualy #53 - Screening for prostate cancer | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000232/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000232/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode of The Qualys is from podcast #39 – Ted Schaeffer, M.D., Ph.D.: How to catch, treat, and survive prostate cancer. The Qualys is a subscriber-exclusive podcast, released Tuesday through Friday, and published exclusively on our private, subscriber-only podcast feed. Qualys is short-hand for “qualifying round,” which are typically the fastest laps driven in a race car—done before the race to determine starting position on the grid for race day.</description></item><item><title>#78 - Sasha Cohen: The price of achievement, and redefining success | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000233/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000233/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Sasha Cohen, former US Olympic figure skater, discusses the most challenging things about life as an Olympian—the pressures, the expectations, years of sacrifice, but worst of all a loss of identity post-career resulting in many former Olympians suffering from depression. We begin by talking about everything that led up to her unforgettable moment from the 2006 Olympics, and how she handled herself so beautifully in the face of disaster.</description></item><item><title>Qualy #52 - Insights about berberine | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000234/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000234/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode of The Qualys is from podcast #26 – AMA #3: supplements, women’s health, patient care, and more.
The Qualys is a subscriber-exclusive podcast, released Tuesday through Friday, and published exclusively on our private, subscriber-only podcast feed. Qualys is short-hand for “qualifying round,” which are typically the fastest laps driven in a race car—done before the race to determine starting position on the grid for race day. The Qualys are short (i.</description></item><item><title>#77 – AMA #2 with sleep expert, Matthew Walker, Ph.D.: short sleep mutants, optimal sleep environment, sleep apnea, &amp; rapid fire questions | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000235/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000235/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this special episode, Matthew Walker returns for his second AMA episode where he provides his expert insight on numerous sleep-related questions directly from listeners. He answers a wide range of questions from the gene that causes the short sleeping phenotype, to the ideal sleeping position, to the optimal temperature for best sleep, to how fasting affects sleep, plus a full dissertation on sleep apnea, and much, much more.</description></item><item><title>Qualy #46 - Rapamycin’s effects on cancer, cardiovascular disease, and neurodegeneration | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000236/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000236/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode of The Qualys is from podcast #09 – David Sabatini, M.D., Ph.D.: rapamycin and the discovery of mTOR — the nexus of aging and longevity?.
The Qualys is a subscriber-exclusive podcast, released Tuesday through Friday, and published exclusively on our private, subscriber-only podcast feed. Qualys is short-hand for “qualifying round,” which are typically the fastest laps driven in a race car—done before the race to determine starting position on the grid for race day.</description></item><item><title>#76 - Kyle Kingsbury: Finding meaning, depression, and psychedelics | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000237/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000237/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Kyle Kingsbury, retired UFC fighter and director of human optimization at Onnit, discusses the purpose and meaning that football and MMA gave him but which also acted as a distraction from his inner demons. Kyle opens up about his use of PEDs (steroids, testosterone, HGH) in college and talks about some of the misconceptions around them. Next, Kyle talks about his battle with depression and a close call with suicide that lead to life-changing experiences with psilocybin and ayahuasca—which really became the turning point in his own journey towards being more emotionally healthy, finding inner peace, and being a better husband and father.</description></item><item><title>Qualy #43 - What are Peter’s thoughts on fasting and ketosis for females? | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000238/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000238/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode of The Qualys is from podcast #26 – AMA #3: supplements, women’s health, patient care, and more.
The Qualys is a subscriber-exclusive podcast, released Tuesday through Friday, and published exclusively on our private, subscriber-only podcast feed. Qualys is short-hand for “qualifying round,” which are typically the fastest laps driven in a race car—done before the race to determine starting position on the grid for race day. The Qualys are short (i.</description></item><item><title>#75 - David Light: Zantac recall due to cancer concerns – what you need to know | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000239/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000239/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, David Light, CEO of Valisure (the company which alerted the FDA to the Zantac cancer concerns), explains the story behind the recent recalls by manufacturers of ranitidine, a common heartburn medication, sold under the trade name Zantac, due to a potential link to increased cancer risk. David breaks down all the evidence, the role of his unique pharmacy company which tests all its drugs before being dispensed to consumers, and the reason behind the FDA’s tempered reaction to the alarming study results.</description></item><item><title>Qualy #38 - Finding meaning in struggle and why we are less happy than ever (David Foster Wallace) | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000240/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000240/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode of The Qualys is from podcast #15 – Paul Conti, M.D.: trauma, suicide, community, and self-compassion.
The Qualys is a subscriber-exclusive podcast, released Tuesday through Friday, and published exclusively on our private, subscriber-only podcast feed. Qualys is short-hand for “qualifying round,” which are typically the fastest laps driven in a race car—done before the race to determine starting position on the grid for race day. The Qualys are short (i.</description></item><item><title>#74 – Jason Fried: Optimizing efficiency and work-life balance | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000241/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000241/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Jason Fried, co-founder of Basecamp, shares his beliefs around achieving business success in a modern world which tends to disproportionately focus on the massive success stories (the outliers). Jason gives his honest take on companies like WeWork, Uber, and Lyft that may give off the appearance of wild success but may instead provide an example of the dangers of perverse incentives. We get into Jason’s backstory, and how his affinity for optimizing efficiency and production in the workplace culminated with the creation of Basecamp, his very successful web-based project management software business.</description></item><item><title>Qualy #33 - How silent bravado and incessant striving can lead to a functional (and actual) death, and why Paul is critical of the current state of psychiatry | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000242/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000242/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode of The Qualys is from podcast #15 – Paul Conti, M.D.: trauma, suicide, community, and self-compassion.
The Qualys is a subscriber-exclusive podcast, released Tuesday through Friday, and published exclusively on our private, subscriber-only podcast feed. Qualys is short-hand for “qualifying round,” which are typically the fastest laps driven in a race car—done before the race to determine starting position on the grid for race day. The Qualys are short (i.</description></item><item><title>#73 - AMA #9: NAD &amp; metformin, fat-burning zone, creatine, estrogenization of men, emergency kit for cold &amp; flu, and more | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000243/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000243/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter answers a wide range of questions from subscribers. Bob Kaplan, Peter’s head of research, asks the questions. If you’re not a subscriber and listening on a podcast player, you’ll only be able to hear a preview of the AMA.
If you’re a subscriber, you can now listen to this full episode on your private RSS feed. You can also watch (or listen) to this full episode on our website at the AMA #9 show notes page.</description></item><item><title>#72 - Dan Harris: 10% happier – meditation, kindness, and compassion | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000244/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000244/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Dan Harris, correspondent for ABC News and co-founder of the Ten Percent Happier meditation app, speaks openly about his struggles with self-centeredness, addiction, depression, emotional volatility, and the deep-rooted insecurities that drove him to career success. He tells the story of how a panic attack on live TV lead him down a path of self-discovery culminating in a meditation practice which has since transformed his life—in terms of his own personal suffering, his relationships with those closest to him, and his ability to be kind and compassionate (which has its own selfish advantages).</description></item><item><title>Qualy #26 - What is Peter looking to achieve and monitor with his blood glucose monitor? | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000245/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000245/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode of The Qualys is from podcast #26 – AMA #3: supplements, women’s health, patient care, and more.
The Qualys is a subscriber-exclusive podcast, released Tuesday through Friday, and published exclusively on our private, subscriber-only podcast feed. Qualys is short-hand for “qualifying round,” which are typically the fastest laps driven in a race car—done before the race to determine starting position on the grid for race day. The Qualys are short (i.</description></item><item><title>#71 - Katherine Eban: Widespread fraud in the generic drug industry | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000246/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000246/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Katherine Eban, investigative journalist and author of Bottle of Lies, illuminates the prevalence of fraud in generic drug manufacturing which brings into question the idea that generics are identical to brand-name drug as we are lead to believe. Katherine walks us through how this widespread corruption came to be, including the shocking story of one particularly egregious (and unfortunately not uncommon) example of an Indian drug company, Ranbaxy, whose business model was completely dependent on falsifying data in their drug applications to the FDA.</description></item><item><title>Qualy #24 - What are the “ABCs” of Alzheimer’s prevention? | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000247/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000247/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode of The Qualys is from podcast #18 – Richard Isaacson, M.D.: Alzheimer’s prevention.
The Qualys is a subscriber-exclusive podcast, released Tuesday through Friday, and published exclusively on our private, subscriber-only podcast feed. Qualys is short-hand for “qualifying round,” which are typically the fastest laps driven in a race car—done before the race to determine starting position on the grid for race day. The Qualys are short (i.</description></item><item><title>#70 - David Sinclair, Ph.D.: How cellular reprogramming could slow our aging clock (and the latest research on NAD) | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000248/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000248/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, David Sinclair, Ph.D., a Professor in the Department of Genetics at Harvard Medical School and co-Director of the Paul F. Glenn Center for the Biological Mechanisms of Aging, returns to the podcast to discuss the content of his new book, Lifespan: Why We Age - and Why We Don’t Have To. This conversation focuses on the biological mechanisms involved in what David terms the Information Theory of Aging which provides insights into the “clock” that determines our aging and to what degree it can be manipulated.</description></item><item><title>Qualy #19 - A unifying theory of aging | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000249/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000249/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode of The Qualys is from podcast #27 – David Sinclair, Ph.D.: Slowing aging – sirtuins, NAD, and the epigenetics of aging.
The Qualys is a subscriber-exclusive podcast, released Tuesday through Friday, and published exclusively on our private, subscriber-only podcast feed. Qualys is short-hand for “qualifying round,” which are typically the fastest laps driven in a race car—done before the race to determine starting position on the grid for race day.</description></item><item><title>#69 - Ronesh Sinha, M.D.: Insights into the manifestation of metabolic disease in a patient population predisposed to metabolic syndrome, and what it teaches us more broadly | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000250/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000250/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Dr. Ronesh Sinha, a physician, author, and educator based in Silicon Valley, shares his many insights into metabolic illness that he has gleaned from his South Asian patient population. In this conversation we focus on hyperinsulinemia, insulin resistance, metabolic dysregulation, inflammation, blood pressure, obesity, etc. and ways to address them with nutrition, sleep, exercise, stress management, and more. We also take a deep dive into insulin resistant phenotypes, evolutionary theory and geographic determinants of insulin resistance which provides insight into the genetic architecture and pathophysiology of metabolic syndrome.</description></item><item><title>Qualy #16 - How much does cognitive activity ward off cognitive decline? | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000251/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000251/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode of The Qualys is from podcast #18 – Richard Isaacson, M.D.: Alzheimer’s prevention.
The Qualys is a subscriber-exclusive podcast, released Tuesday through Friday, and published exclusively on our private, subscriber-only podcast feed. Qualys is short-hand for “qualifying round,” which are typically the fastest laps driven in a race car—done before the race to determine starting position on the grid for race day. The Qualys are short (i.</description></item><item><title>#68 - Marty Makary, M.D.: The US healthcare system—why it’s broken, steps to fix it, and how to protect yourself | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000252/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000252/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Marty Makary, Johns Hopkins surgeon and NYT bestselling author, discusses his ambitious attempt to fix the broken U.S. healthcare system through educating the public, changing the lexicon, encouraging radical transparency in pricing, and more. We go in detail into the main drivers of inflated health care costs, the money games being played making it hard to understand, and the unfortunate system structure that has resulted in one in five Americans finding themselves in medical debt collections which can ruin the lives of people and families seeking basic medical care.</description></item><item><title>Qualy #9 - The importance of exercise for brain health | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000253/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000253/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode of The Qualys is from podcast #02 – Rhonda Patrick, Ph.D.: the performance and longevity paradox of IGF-1, ketogenic diets and genetics, the health benefits of sauna, NAD+, and more.
The Qualys is a subscriber-exclusive podcast, released Tuesday through Friday, and published exclusively on our private, subscriber-only podcast feed. Qualys is short-hand for “qualifying round,” which are typically the fastest laps driven in a race car—done before the race to determine starting position on the grid for race day.</description></item><item><title>#67 - AMA #8: DNA tests, longevity genes, metformin, fasting markers, salt, inflammation, and more | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000254/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000254/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter answers a wide range of questions from subscribers. Bob Kaplan, Peter’s head of research, asks the questions. If you’re not a subscriber and listening on a podcast player, you’ll only be able to hear a preview of the AMA.
If you’re a subscriber, you can now listen to this full episode on your private RSS feed. You can also watch (or listen) to this full episode on our website at the AMA #8 show notes page.</description></item><item><title>Qualy #6 - What are the best lab tests to request specifically for longevity | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000255/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000255/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode of The Qualys is from podcast #04 – AMA #1: alcohol, best lab tests, wearables, finding the right doc, racing, and more.
The Qualys is a subscriber-exclusive podcast, released Tuesday through Friday, and published exclusively on our private, subscriber-only podcast feed. Qualys is short-hand for “qualifying round,” which are typically the fastest laps driven in a race car—done before the race to determine starting position on the grid for race day.</description></item><item><title>#66 - Vamsi Mootha, M.D.: Aging, type 2 diabetes, cancer, Alzheimer’s disease, and Parkinson’s disease – do all roads lead to mitochondria? | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000256/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000256/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Dr. Vamsi Mootha, an expert in mitochondrial biology and investigator at the Howard Hughes Medical Institute, shares his breadth of knowledge on the mitochondrion organelle: its history, function, genome architecture, and his research of rare mitochondrial dysfunction. Vamsi is currently focused on finding clinical treatments for the 300-some identified rare disorders, but in this work there is a wealth of potential implications in the context of longevity and chronic disease.</description></item><item><title>Qualy #1 - What are Peter's thoughts on alcohol consumption and health? | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000257/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000257/</guid><description>Podcast Description Today's episode of The Qualys is from podcast #04 – AMA #1: alcohol, best lab tests, wearables, finding the right doc, racing, and more.
The Qualys is a subscriber-exclusive podcast, released Tuesday through Friday, and published exclusively on our private, subscriber-only podcast feed. Qualys is short-hand for “qualifying round,” which are typically the fastest laps driven in a race car—done before the race to determine starting position on the grid for race day.</description></item><item><title>#65 - Rick Doblin, Ph.D.: MDMA— the creation, scheduling, toxicity, therapeutic use, and changing public opinion of what is possibly the single most important synthetic molecule ever created by our species | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000258/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000258/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Rick Doblin, founder and executive director of MAPS, discusses MDMA, a molecule that has (at a minimum) revolutionary therapeutic benefits for PTSD, but arguably could have, at the highest order, a lasting impact on humanity’s ability to peacefully coexist. Rick details the history of MDMA, what lead to its unfortunate criminalization, and his lifelong work trying to protect MDMA (and other psychedelics) from criminalization (and his subsequent attempt to decriminalize it).</description></item><item><title>#64 - Zol Kryger, M.D.: Navigating the sometimes shady world of plastic surgery—understanding potential complications of common procedures and how to reduce your risk by choosing the right doctor and asking the right questions | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000259/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000259/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, board-certified plastic surgeon, Zol Kryger, enlightens us about the frighteningly loose laws regulating the industry of plastic surgery, paving the way for a majority of cosmetic procedures being performed by doctors that are not board-certified plastic surgeons. We talk about some of the very serious complications that can occur even in “minimally invasive” procedures, where the incidence rate is only increased by the flood of non-certified doctors who want to offer these procedures to augment their income.</description></item><item><title>#63 - AMA #7: Exercise framework, deadlifting, lower back pain, blood pressure, nootropics, CGM, and more | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000260/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000260/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter answers a wide range of questions from subscribers. Bob Kaplan, Peter’s head of research, asks the questions. If you’re not a subscriber and listening on a podcast player, you’ll only be able to hear a preview of the AMA.
If you’re a subscriber, you can now listen to this full episode on your private RSS feed. You can also watch (or listen) to this full episode on our website at the AMA #7 show notes page.</description></item><item><title>#62 - Keith Flaherty, M.D.: Deep dive into cancer—History of oncology, novel approaches to treatment, and the exciting and hopeful future | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000261/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000261/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Keith Flaherty, director of clinical research and targeted cancer therapy at Massachusetts General Hospital, shares his vast wealth of knowledge in cancer starting with the history of treatment from chemotherapy to radiation to surgical therapy and where those methodologies seemed to have leveled off. He also walks us through the timeline of advancements (and lack there of) from when the War on Cancer was declared in the 1970s, through the sequencing of the entire human genome, and all the way to today.</description></item><item><title>#61 - Rajpaul Attariwala, M.D., Ph.D.: Cancer screening with full-body MRI scans and a seminar on the field of radiology | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000262/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000262/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, radiologist/engineer, Raj Attariwala, explains how he was able to apply his engineering background to create a unique MRI scanner that is capable of constructing whole-body images with a resolution that is unmatched in the industry. Peter and Raj discuss the implications of such a robust, radiation-free imaging tool on the early detection of cancer. They dive deep into cancer screening and define terms such as sensitivity and specificity that are necessary to really understand this complex space.</description></item><item><title>The one-year anniversary episode with Olivia Attia: Reflecting on the past year and looking forward to exciting times ahead | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000263/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000263/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this anniversary episode, Olivia, Peter's daughter who initially kicked off The Drive podcast with her sneak peek episode, returns to ask Peter the tough questions on how the podcast is going, what he has learned along the way (and how he plans to make it better), what exciting things are in store for the future, and plenty more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>#60 - Annie Duke, decision strategist: Poker as a model system for life—how to improve decision making, use frameworks for learning, and apply ‘backcasting’ to boost your odds for future success | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000264/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000264/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, former World Series of Poker champion and author, Annie Duke, explains how poker is a pertinent model system for decision making in the real world, a system which blends imperfect information with some unknown percentage of both luck and skill. We go through the decision-making matrix, and how we spend most of our energy focusing on just one of the four quadrants at the expense of the learning opportunities that come from the other 75% of situations.</description></item><item><title>#59 - Jason Fung, M.D.: Fasting as a potent antidote to obesity, insulin resistance, type 2 diabetes, and the many symptoms of metabolic illness | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000265/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000265/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Jason Fung, nephrologist and best-selling author, shares his experiences utilizing an individualized approach to fasting to successfully treat thousands of overweight, metabolically ill, and diabetic patients, and why being a doctor who specializes in kidney disease gives him a unique insight into early indications of metabolic disease. We also have a great discussion on insulin resistance where Jason makes the case that we should actually think of hyperinsulinemia as the underlying problem.</description></item><item><title>#58 – AMA with sleep expert, Matthew Walker, Ph.D.: Strategies for sleeping more, sleeping better, and avoiding things that are disrupting sleep | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000266/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000266/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the first three parts of our series with sleep expert Matthew Walker, Matt revealed the many reasons why we need sleep as well as the many short- and long-term dangers of not sleeping enough. In this special AMA episode, Matt comes back to provide a dissertation on listener’s questions about HOW to sleep. He answers questions from subscribers that largely focus on the practical and tactical ways we can improve our sleep in terms of duration, quality, consistency, and avoidance of the common things that are standing in the way the best sleep possible.</description></item><item><title>#57 – Rick Rubin, legendary music producer: collaborating with sensitive psyche of greatest living musicians, and his personal story of weight loss and spiritual quest | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000267/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000267/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Rick Rubin, legendary music producer and co-founder of Def Jam Records and American Recordings, discusses his early foray into music production which started as a hobby as a teenager and ultimately turned into a Grammy award-winning career that produced revolutionary changes in the music industry. Rick has worked with the likes of the Beastie Boys, Red Hot Chili Peppers, and Johnny Cash, just to name a small fraction.</description></item><item><title>#56 - Jocko Willink, retired Navy SEAL, Part II of II: Sleep, fasting, raising kids, discipline, taking ownership, and the impact of war | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000268/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000268/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the second installment of this 2 part series, Jocko shares his sleep routine and attitude towards sleep, we talk about his meals (and occasional indulgences), his experience with fasting, and touch briefly on his workout routine. Jocko explains his approach to leading a family, instilling values in his kids, and working with others who may not share your same principles. We also find out what prompted Jocko to make discipline the underpinning principle of his life, when it might make sense to quit, and the philosophical topics such as free will, mindset, and whether or not you can change someone.</description></item><item><title>#55 - Jocko Willink, retired Navy SEAL, Part I of II: objective, strategy &amp; tactics, leadership, protocols, dealing with death, and applying the many lessons learned from war | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000269/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000269/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part 1 of this 2 part series, Jocko Willink, retired Navy SEAL, discusses some of his most important lessons learned from his time commanding some of the world’s most expert special forces operators including the importance of understanding the objective and strategy (and then tactics) of a mission, why humility is the greatest trait a leader can have (and certain times when it’s not), as well as the necessity of having proper protocols in place to deal with whatever comes your way.</description></item><item><title>#54 – Kevin Sayer, CEO of Dexcom: Continuous glucose monitors – impact of food, sleep, and stress on glucose, the unmatched power of CGM to drive behavioral change, and the exciting future of CGM | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000270/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000270/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Kevin Sayer, CEO of Dexcom, discusses the remarkable benefits of a continuous glucose monitor for the diabetes population. Peter shares his own invaluable insights he’s learned from wearing a CGM including the impact of sleep and stress on glucose as well as the unmatched power of a CGM to drive behavioral change. Kevin also reveals some of the exciting partnerships and future advancements of their products benefiting not only those with type 1 and 2 diabetes, but also for the growing community of people interested in optimizing health and wellness.</description></item><item><title>#53 - AMA #6: Fasting framework, vitamin supplementation, antioxidants, time management, problem-solving, and more | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000271/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000271/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter answers a wide range of questions from readers and podcast listeners. Bob Kaplan, Peter’s head of research, asks the questions. If you’re listening on a podcast player, you’ll be able to hear a preview of the AMA.
If you’re a subscriber, you can watch or listen to this full episode on our website at the AMA #6 show notes page. PLEASE NOTE: We are currently building a private RSS feed that will allow subscribers to listen uninterrupted on the podcast player of their choice.</description></item><item><title>#52 - Ethan Weiss, M.D.: A masterclass in cardiovascular disease and growth hormone - two topics that are surprising interrelated | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000272/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000272/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Ethan Weiss, Hopkins trained preventative cardiologist at UCSF, discusses two topics that on the surface may seem unrelated which is cardiovascular disease, and the role of growth hormone and IGF in disease. Ethan provides a masterclass in everything from acute coronary syndrome to all of the complex nuances around stent placement, as well as how calcium scores and results from CT angiograms shape his treatment of patients.</description></item><item><title>The Ayrton Senna Episode (re-release): Celebrating the greatest driver in Formula 1 history and the cautionary tales of driven individuals | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000273/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000273/</guid><description>Podcast Description To celebrate the life of the legendary Formula 1 driver Ayrton Senna, 25 years to the day of his tragic death, we are re-releasing this bonus episode. In this episode, Peter and med school colleague (and brilliant psychiatrist) Paul Conti reminisce on their favorite moments in Formula 1 history, their deep admiration for the late Ayrton Senna, and the remarkable careers of their favorite drivers. Paul also helps to illuminate the psychological components that made the luminary drivers great, and the cautionary lessons we can take from their incredible lives.</description></item><item><title>#51 - Robert Sapolsky, Ph.D.: The pervasive effect of stress - is it killing you? | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000274/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000274/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Robert Sapolsky, Ph.D., discusses the widespread impact of stress on our physical and emotional health as well as the mechanisms by which it can precipitate chronic illness, dementia, depression, and more. He also provides insight into the factors that contribute to the stress response (and our ability to handle it) such as social rank, personality, environment, and genetics. Lastly, we discuss how our behavior is altered in the face of stress and how that not only has a pervasive effect on a personal level, but also on society as a whole in how we interact with each other.</description></item><item><title>#50 - AMA #5: calcium scores, centenarian olympics, exercise, muscle glycogen, keto, and more | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000275/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000275/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter answers a wide range of questions from readers and podcast listeners. Bob Kaplan, Peter’s head of research, asks the questions. If you’re listening on a podcast player, you’ll be able to hear a preview of the AMA.
If you’re a subscriber, you can watch or listen to this full episode on our website at the AMA #5 show note’s page.</description></item><item><title>#49 – Matthew Walker, Ph.D., on sleep – Part III of III: The penetrating effects of poor sleep from metabolism to performance to genetics, and the impact of caffeine, alcohol, THC, and CBD on sleep | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000276/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000276/</guid><description>Podcast Description In the final part of this 3 part series, Matthew Walker, professor of neuroscience at UC Berkeley and expert on sleep, discusses the omnipresent effects of insufficient sleep on everything from metabolism, appetite, athletic performance, decision-making, productivity, leadership, mental health, genetics, memory, and more. We also discuss the impact of caffeine and alcohol on sleep quality, the efficacy of sleep aids such as THC and CBD, and much more.</description></item><item><title>#48 – Matthew Walker, Ph.D., on sleep – Part II of III: Heart disease, cancer, sexual function, and the causes of sleep disruption (and tips to correct it) | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000277/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000277/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part 2 of this 3 part series, Matthew Walker, professor of neuroscience at UC Berkeley and expert on sleep, describes the preponderance of evidence linking poor sleep to cardiovascular disease, cancer, and sexual function. He also details the impact of cortisol on our nervous system contributing to sleep disturbances and insomnia as well as the efficacy and risks associated with the most common sleeping pills. Matthew also describes the sleep needs of teenagers and urgently lays the case that we should reconsider school start times.</description></item><item><title>#47 – Matthew Walker, Ph.D., on sleep – Part I of III: Dangers of poor sleep, Alzheimer's risk, mental health, memory consolidation, and more. | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000278/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000278/</guid><description>Podcast Description In part 1 of this 3 part series, Matthew Walker, professor of neuroscience at UC Berkeley and expert on sleep, describes the different stages and cycles of sleep, including what he calls the 4 pillars of sleep, and how they contribute to memory consolidation and numerous important pathways to mental health. We also get into the dangers of chronic sleep deprivation, such as the development of dementia, and the more acute dangers of sleep deprivation like fatal car crashes which are most often caused by drowsy driving.</description></item><item><title>#46 - Chris Masterjohn, Ph.D.: Navigating the many pathways to health and disease - NAD and sirtuins, methylation, MTHFR and COMT, choline deficiency and NAFLD, TMAO, creatine, and more | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000279/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000279/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Chris Masterjohn, entrepreneur, independent researcher, and doctorate in nutrition, elucidates the latest research on the risk and benefits of NAD supplements, and shares his personal intuition on the topic. We also dive deep into choline deficiency and its role in the rising prevalence of nonalcoholic fatty liver disease. From there, Chris enlightens us on the importance of methylation, a simple yet profoundly important biochemical process affecting our physical and mental health.</description></item><item><title>#45 - AMA #4: sleep, jet lag protocol, autophagy, metformin, and more | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000280/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000280/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, the first subscriber-only edition, Peter answers a wide range of questions from readers and podcast listeners. Bob Kaplan, Peter’s head of research, asks the questions.
As a reminder, AMAs are for subscribers only. If you want to subscribe, you can learn more about the benefits at https://peterattiamd.com/subscribe. If you are a subscriber, you can watch or listen to this in full on the show notes portion of our website.</description></item><item><title>#44 - Jeremy Schaap, ESPN journalist: upsets, doping, triumphs, and the importance of sports | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000281/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000281/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Jeremy Schaap, preeminent journalist at ESPN, discusses two of the most incredible upsets in boxing history, both of which Jeremy has expertly covered during his illustrious career, most recently culminating in the 30 for 30 special, 42 to 1. We also discuss his infamous Bobby Knight interview, his coverage of the doping scandals in baseball and cycling, as well as the pressures of following in his father’s enormous footsteps who taught him the importance of fairness in journalism.</description></item><item><title>#43 - Alan Bauman, M.D.: The science of male and female hair restoration - how to protect, enhance, and restore the appearance and health of the hair and scalp | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000282/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000282/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Alan Bauman, certified hair transplantation surgeon and hair restoration expert, discusses both male and female pattern hair loss, the science behind what drives it, and what that tells us about prevention and restoration. Having treated over 20,000 patients, Alan shares his invaluable insights into what works and what doesn’t in terms of the non-surgical treatment options. We also go into great detail about the more invasive approaches like PRP, and of course, hair transplantation, a procedure which Alan has refined over the years into a proprietary method that seems to produce unbelievable results.</description></item><item><title>#42 - Avrum Bluming, M.D., and Carol Tavris, Ph.D.: Controversial topic affecting all women—the role of hormone replacement therapy through menopause and beyond—the compelling case for long-term HRT and dispelling the myth that it causes breast cancer | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000283/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000283/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Avrum Bluming, hematologist, medical oncologist, and emeritus clinical professor at USC and Carol Tavris, social psychologist and author of Mistakes Were Made (But Not By Me), discuss their collaboration on their recent book, Estrogen Matters. Their book takes on the very polarizing and confusing topic of hormone replacement therapy for women suffering with symptoms of menopause. In many ways, the story and history of HRT is in striking parallel to the bad science that led up to the dietary guidelines being set forth in 1980.</description></item><item><title>#41 - Jake Kushner, M.D.: How to thrive with type 1 diabetes and how everyone can benefit from the valuable insights | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000284/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000284/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Jake Kushner, pediatric endocrinologist specializing in helping people with type 1 diabetes, discusses the best strategies to live and thrive with T1D, especially as it relates to diet and exercise. We also discuss why many patients who control their blood sugar with high amounts of exogenous insulin are at a substantially higher risk than people who can control their blood sugar at lower levels of insulin.</description></item><item><title>#40 - Tom Catena, M.D.: The world’s most important doctor – to nearly a million patients – saving countless lives in the war-torn and remote villages of Sudan | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000285/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000285/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Tom Catena, a missionary physician who runs Mother of Mercy Hospital in the Nuba Mountains in Sudan, describes some of his extraordinary work as the only doctor in a remote, war-torn region of Africa. In terms of individual lives saved, you could argue that there is no other person on the front lines doing more than Tom. Additionally, we explore the manner in which the Nuba people die, which is in striking contrast the ubiquity of chronic disease and self-harm in the west, despite the extreme poverty and unimaginable suffering experienced by the Nuba people.</description></item><item><title>#39 - Ted Schaeffer, M.D., Ph.D.: How to catch, treat, and survive prostate cancer | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000286/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000286/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Ted Schaeffer, Professor and Chair of the Department of Urology at Northwestern (youngest chairman in the country), presents the roadmap for the best way to screen for, and treat, prostate cancer. We also get into the “mass screening” controversy and all the risks involved with treatment. In addition, we discuss our evolving understanding of cancer and the most exciting areas of research to come. We discuss:</description></item><item><title>#38 - Francisco Gonzalez-Lima, Ph.D.: Advancing Alzheimer’s disease treatment and prevention – is AD actually a vascular and metabolic disease? | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000287/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000287/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Francisco Gonzalez-Lima, a Professor of Neuroscience and Pharmacology &amp; Toxicology, explains the vascular hypothesis of Alzheimer’s disease which says the central problem is a progressive neuronal energy crisis of impaired blood flow to the brain and impaired mitochondrial respiration. He walks us through the ways we can intervene in this process and also shares details of the exciting future of Alzheimer’s treatment and prevention.
We discuss:</description></item><item><title>#37 - Zubin Damania, M.D.: Revolutionizing healthcare one hilariously inspiring video at a time | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000288/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000288/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Zubin Damania, a.k.a. Zdogg MD, a Stanford trained physician and founder of Turntable Health, discusses his evolution from disillusioned doctor suffering burnout to leading the charge for a radical shift in how we practice medicine. We also go down the rabbit hole on all sorts of juicy topics from meditation to nutrition to the nature of consciousness itself.
We discuss: Med school antics [7:00]; Hierarchies in healthcare, physician burnout, and a broken system [20:15]; Why Zubin left medicine, and what lead to the ZdoggMD persona [31:30]; Peter’s tough decision to leave medicine [44:00]; Benefits and challenges of meditation [54:15]; Zdogg’s theory of consciousness [1:11:30]; Nutrition: Peter’s current strategy with patients [1:31:00]; The anti-vaccine dispute [1:38:15] The common thread of all “diets”, the obesity epidemic, and Peter’s dream experiment [1:44:30]; Do we have free will?</description></item><item><title>#36 - Eric Chehab, M.D.: Extending healthspan and preserving quality of life | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000289/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000289/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Dr. Eric Chehab, orthopedic surgeon and sports medicine specialist, explains the measures we can take to live better and maintain our physical health through exercise and the avoidance of common injuries that prove to be the downfall for many. He also provides valuable insight for those weighing their treatment options from physical therapy to surgery to stem cells. We discuss:
Favorite bands, musicians, and concerts [3:30]; Eric’s upbringing, biggest influences, college life, and teaching overseas [12:45]; Eric’s training, fellowship with the New York Giants, and the risk vs.</description></item><item><title>#35 - Nir Barzilai, M.D.: How to tame aging | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000290/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000290/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Nir Barzilai, director of the Institute for Aging Research and expert in the genetics of longevity, discusses the evidence that metformin and rapamycin have anti-aging properties and how his TAME study aims to support this hypothesis in humans. Additionally, he describes the role of genetics in lifespan/healthspan and how it might affect important pathways such as IGF and insulin sensitivity.
We discuss:
Nir’s background and interest in aging and endocrinology [3:30]; History of metformin, and understanding the mechanism [11:15]; Attempting to define insulin resistance [21:15]; Metformin as a possible anti-aging drug [48:45]; The TAME trial: Targeting Aging with MEtformin [57:45]; Why Nir believes metformin can slow aging [1:16:30]; The genetic gift of centenarians [1:28:00]; IGF/GH and its impact on aging and chronic diseases [1:34:15]; Genetics/epigenetics of centenarians, gene sequencing, CETP-VV, Lp(a) [1:49:15]; Should you be taking HGH?</description></item><item><title>#34 - Sam Harris, Ph.D.: The transformative power of mindfulness | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000291/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000291/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Sam Harris, neuroscientist, author, and host of the Waking Up Podcast, walks us through the profound, yet practical, ways that meditation can transform our lives. Additionally, he helps to define the types of meditation and clarifies potential misconceptions with terms like happiness, pain, and suffering.
We discuss:
The transformative moment that led to Peter reaching out to Sam [3:45]; Comparing the two broad types of meditation, and Peter’s favorite meditation apps [7:45]; The pleasure of a concentrated mind, meditating with pain, and the difference between pain and suffering [13:15]; What it means to be happy, and how to break out of our default state [23:15]; The disease of distraction, why humans suffer, the limitation of happiness, and letting go of anger with mindfulness [31:00]; The challenge of learning mindfulness, the benefit of silent retreats, and Sam’s first experience in solitude as a teenager [54:15]; Sam’s life-altering experience with MDMA [1:03:00]; Mettā meditation a.</description></item><item><title>#33 - Rudy Leibel, M.D.: Finding the obesity gene and discovering leptin | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000292/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000292/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Dr. Rudy Leibel, an expert in Clinical Molecular Genetics and Genomics at Columbia University, discusses his role in the remarkable scientific story of discovering leptin. He also gets into the genetics of obesity, as well as a broader discussion of the causes and effects of obesity, energy expenditure, and metabolism.
We discuss:
Rudy’s background, interest in obesity, and trying to understand the role and impact of adipose tissue [4:15]; Finding the first evidence of leptin by studying obese mice [23:30]; Zucker rats, and the push/pull theories of obesity [34:45]; A breakthrough in obesity research, and closing in on leptin [45:45]; Understanding leptin in humans [1:03:30]; What Prader–Willi syndrome teaches us about body weight regulation [1:09:45]; Leptin and the broad condition of obesity, metabolic consequences of weight reduction, and Peter’s self-experiments [1:18:00]; How is appetite being regulated?</description></item><item><title>#32 - Siddhartha Mukherjee, M.D., Ph.D.: new frontiers in cancer therapy, medicine, and the writing process | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000293/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2018 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000293/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Siddhartha Mukherjee, oncologist, researcher, and author of the Pulitzer Prize-winning book “The Emperor of All Maladies: A Biography of Cancer,” discusses his writing process, his thoughts about medicine, cancer, immunotherapy, and his recent collaboration on a study combining a ketogenic diet with a drug in mice that provided remarkable and encouraging results.
We discuss:
Sid’s background [5:00]; How Sid and Peter met [6:00]; Sid’s Pulitzer Prize-winning book: The Emperor of All Maladies [8:00]; Sid’s writing process: the tenets of writing [12:30]; Our struggle to find preventable, human, chemical carcinogens of substantial impact [23:30]; The three laws of medicine — Law #1: A strong intuition is much more powerful than a weak test [26:30]; Law #2 of medicine: “Normals” teach us rules; “outliers” teach us laws [32:00]; Law #3 of medicine: For every perfect medical experiment, there is a perfect human bias [35:00]; The excitement around immunotherapy [38:15]; The story of Gleevec [46:00]; How does the body's metabolic state affect cancer?</description></item><item><title>#31 - Navdeep Chandel, Ph.D.: metabolism, mitochondria, and metformin in health and disease | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000294/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000294/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Nav Chandel, a professor of medicine and cell and molecular biology at Northwestern University, discusses the role of mitochondria and metabolism in health and disease. Nav also provides insights into the mitochondria as signaling organelles, antioxidants, and metformin’s multifaceted effects on human health, among many topics related to well-being.
We discuss:
What got Nav interested in mitochondria [5:00]; Reactive oxygen species (ROS) [16:00]; Antioxidants: helpful or harmful?</description></item><item><title>#30 - Thomas Seyfried, Ph.D.: Controversial discussion—cancer as a mitochondrial metabolic disease? | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000295/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000295/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Thomas Seyfried, a cancer researcher and professor of biology at Boston College, discusses a controversial view of cancer as a mitochondrial metabolic disease. Many topics related to the causes, treatments, and prevention of cancer are covered in this in-depth conversation.
We discuss:
How Tom got interested in cancer research [9:00]; Calorie-restricted ketogenic diets, fasting, and epileptic seizures [18:30]; Otto Warburg and the Warburg effect [30:45]; Germline mutations, somatic mutations, and no mutations [42:00]; Mitochondrial substrate level phosphorylation: Warburg’s missing link [51:30]; What is the structural defect in the mitochondria in cancer?</description></item><item><title>#29 - Apolo Anton Ohno: 8-time Olympic medalist – extreme training, discipline, pursuing perfection, and responding to adversity | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000296/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000296/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, 8-time Olympic medalist, Apolo Ohno, discusses the lessons he’s learned from his remarkable career in speed skating and the extreme physical and mental training — and determination — required to reach greatness.
We discuss:
Apolo’s childhood with his single dad, early success in sports, and falling in love with skating [7:30]; The differences between inline and ice skating, and short- &amp; long-track speed-skating, and the evolution of the clap skate [21:00]; The mental game and the physical game: intense training and mindset [29:30]; Apolo’s early success in short-track that led to an amazing opportunity and his reluctance to go for it [40:15]; Early days at Lake Placid, first experience on the world stage, and a little self-sabotage [56:45]; Tough love parenting, making a commitment, training like Rocky, and developing the mindset of a fighter [1:17:30]; 2002 Olympics, winning his first medal, and rising above the sport [1:32:45]; Apolo’s evolving training and body composition throughout his Olympic career [2:05:15]; Going into the Lion’s Den to learn from Korean skaters and making a radical and risky change that led to his most successful Olympic games [2:12:45]; Apolo’s tumultuous relationship with South Korea, from hatred to respect to admiration [2:29:00]; Applying lessons learned through training, adjusting to life after skating, and the struggles many athletes face transitioning to retirement [2:46:30]; The final years of Apolo’s career: intense focus, crazy training, mental fortitude, and resiliency [2:57:30]; Officially retiring and contemplating a comeback [3:16:15]; Where does Apolo want to be in 10 years?</description></item><item><title>#28 - Mark and Chris Bell: steroids, powerlifting, addiction, diet, training, helping others, documentaries, and living your best life | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000297/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000297/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Mark and Chris Bell discuss their love of powerlifting, their unbelievable personal records, and what prompted the making of their now iconic film, Bigger, Stronger, Faster. They also very openly discuss steroid use, their tragic family history with addiction, the many inspirations that lead to their multifaceted success, and their dedication to having a positive impact on others in fitness and life.
We discuss:
The impact of Bigger, Stronger, Faster, how it got made, and how it challenged Peter’s set of beliefs regarding steroids [4:45]; Chris’s personal story of addiction and how he’s using his experience to help others [17:30]; Importance of sharing your struggle, and the danger of comparing yourself to others [28:00]; Early life, their love of pro wrestling and what motivated Brothers Bell to be great?</description></item><item><title>#27 - David Sinclair, Ph.D.: Slowing aging – sirtuins, NAD, and the epigenetics of aging | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000298/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000298/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, David A. Sinclair, Ph.D., a Professor in the Department of Genetics at Harvard Medical School and co-Director of the Paul F. Glenn Center for the Biological Mechanisms of Aging, provides insight into why we age and how to slow its effects based on his remarkable work on the role of sirtuins and NAD in health and diseases. He also presents the case that stabilizing the epigenetic landscape may be the linchpin in counteracting aging and disease.</description></item><item><title>#26 - AMA #3: supplements, women’s health, patient care, and more | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000299/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000299/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this “Ask Me Anything” (AMA) episode, Peter answers a wide range of questions from readers and podcast listeners. Bob Kaplan, Peter’s head analyst, asks the questions.
This also marks the first video release of the podcast. You can find it on YouTube (https://youtu.be/kzs7GgxR_FQ) and the website (peterattiamd.com/ama03).
If you have any questions for the next AMA, please submit them to the AMA section on the website (peterattiamd.com).</description></item><item><title>#25 - Scott Harrison: transformation, finding meaning, and taking on the global water crisis | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000300/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000300/</guid><description>Podcast Description We discuss:
How Scott and Peter met [3:45]; Scott’s tragic family story that shaped his life and altered his trajectory [8:00]; High school years, rebellion, and music [30:30]; Life as a club promoter, drug use, soul-searching, and a change of heart [41:30]; Mercy Ships [1:15:00]; The amazing transformations of Mercy Ships and the parallels to his own transformation [1:28:00]; Leveraging the art of storytelling to raise money and awareness while fighting temptations to fall into his previous life [1:33:30]; Discovering the water crisis that lead to charity: water [1:46:45]; How the lack of trust in nonprofits can cripple charities [1:54:00]; The four pillars of charity: water that helped it overcome the stigma of nonprofits and become successful [2:01:00]; Where to learn more about Scott’s work and charity: water [2:12:30]; Scott’s book recommendations [2:14:30]; and More.</description></item><item><title>#24 - Tom Dayspring, M.D., FACP, FNLA – Part V of V: Lp(a), inflammation, oxLDL, remnants, and more | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000301/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000301/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this five-part series, Thomas Dayspring, M.D., FACP, FNLA, a world-renowned expert in lipidology, and one of Peter's most important clinical mentors, shares his wealth of knowledge on the subject of lipids. In Part V, Peter and Tom talk about inflammation, endothelial health, and oxidative stress as they pertain to cardiovascular disease, and our attempts to monitor them using biomarkers. They also discuss a couple of very important risk factors that too few people (and doctors) know about.</description></item><item><title>#23 - Tom Dayspring, M.D., FACP, FNLA – Part IV of V: Statins, ezetimibe, PCSK9 inhibitors, niacin, cholesterol and the brain | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000302/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000302/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this five-part series, Thomas Dayspring, M.D., FACP, FNLA, a world-renowned expert in lipidology, and one of Peter's most important clinical mentors, shares his wealth of knowledge on the subject of lipids. In Part IV, Peter and Tom review the history and current use of drugs to prevent cardiovascular disease. They also discuss why some drugs appear to be more effective than others, an in-depth conversation about niacin, cholesterol and brain health, and the futility of using CKs (creatinine kinase) and liver function tests to identify adverse effects in statins, to name a few topics in this episode.</description></item><item><title>#22 - Tom Dayspring, M.D., FACP, FNLA – Part III of V: HDL, reverse cholesterol transport, CETP inhibitors, and apolipoproteins | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000303/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000303/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this five-part series, Thomas Dayspring, M.D., FACP, FNLA, a world-renowned expert in lipidology, and one of Peter's most important clinical mentors, shares his wealth of knowledge on the subject of lipids. In Part III, Peter and Tom dig into HDL, why "reverse cholesterol transport" is a lot more nuanced than what most of us are taught, lipid transport, apolipoproteins, and more. In addition, this episode highlights the complexity of HDL and a discussion about the CETP inhibitor trials.</description></item><item><title>#21 - Tom Dayspring, M.D., FACP, FNLA – Part II of V: Lipid metrics, lipid measurements, and cholesterol regulation | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000304/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000304/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this five-part series, Thomas Dayspring, M.D., FACP, FNLA, a world-renowned expert in lipidology, and one of Peter's most important clinical mentors, shares his wealth of knowledge on the subject of lipids. In Part II, Tom provides a 101 on lipids and lipoproteins. Tom and Peter also discuss the history and techniques used to measure lipoproteins, and more. We discuss: Lipoprotein basics [1:30]; Gofman and the ultracentrifuge [5:15]; Lipoprotein structure, function, metabolism [6:45]; Lipoprotein and cholesterol measurement, and NMR technology [15:15]; LDL-C vs LDL-P and apoB [30:45]; Sterols and cholesterol synthesis [39:45]; and More.</description></item><item><title>#20 - Thomas Dayspring, M.D., FACP, FNLA – Part I of V: an introduction to lipidology | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000305/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000305/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this five-part series, Thomas Dayspring, M.D., FACP, FNLA, a world-renowned expert in lipidology, and one of Peter's most important clinical mentors, shares his wealth of knowledge on the subject of lipids. Part I serves as an introduction to Tom, his work, and an overview of lipid terminology.
We discuss:
Tom’s recent and remarkable physical transformation [6:30]; The moving stories behind Tom’s obsessions: firefighting, hockey, and, of course, lipids [20:30]; Tom’s medical background [39:30]; Producing some of the most accessible diagrams on lipids [50:00]; What are the different kinds of lipids, what do they do, and how are they transported?</description></item><item><title>#19 - Dave Feldman: stress testing the lipid energy model | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000306/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000306/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Dave Feldman, discusses his journey from software engineer to n=1 experimenter, his experience with low-carbohydrate diets, and his hypothesis that cholesterol levels are influenced by energy metabolism.
We discuss:
Peter’s synthesis of Dave’s energy model [5:00]; Dave’s journey from software engineer to cholesterol enthusiast [15:00]; Standard blood panels, sterol panels, and what moves the needle when it comes to particle numbers [18:30]; Hyper-responders [20:00]; Lipoprotein transport [33:45]; The lean mass hyper-responder phenotype [47:30]; The progression of atherosclerosis, CAC, and CIMT [52:30]; Testing for oxidized LDL [55:30]; All-cause mortality and clinical endpoints [1:01:15]; What does “LDL as causal” mean?</description></item><item><title>#18 - Richard Isaacson, M.D.: Alzheimer’s prevention | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000307/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000307/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Richard Isaacson, a neurologist and director of the Alzheimer’s Prevention Clinic at Weill Cornell Medicine and NewYork-Presbyterian, discusses strategies for staving off Alzheimer’s disease. Richard shares a wealth of insight for people who want to know more about Alzheimer’s and what you can do to help yourself and your loved ones – starting today and continuing throughout the entire lifespan.
We discuss: Richard’s fun-facts (and alter egos): “bling” phones, Doogie Howser, and DJ Rush [8:00]; Richard’s impetus to focus on Alzheimer’s disease: Uncle Bob [18:20]; Starting an Alzheimer’s Prevention Clinic [27:00]; How Alzheimer’s is diagnosed [30:00]; Short-term memory, processing speed, executive function and how they’re tested [35:45]; Prevention vs reduction of Alzheimer’s [44:00]; What is the prevalence of Alzheimer’s in America?</description></item><item><title>#17 - Mike Trevino: life-lessons from ultra-endurance, mindset, hard work, and removing limitations | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000308/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000308/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, ultra-endurance athlete and entrepreneur, Mike Trevino, discusses the lessons he’s learned from his remarkable athletic feats, and the training required to reach them. Not only is Mike’s advice practical for those looking to take their endurance training to the next level, but his lessons and insight are extraordinarily applicable to living everyday life.
We discuss:
Mike’s background, his crazy birthday tradition, and his transition from power to endurance [6:30]; Mike’s breakthrough year: setting a course record, and completing the Badwater 135 [16:00]; Race Across America (RAAM), perseverance, and extreme sleep deprivation [25:30]; Mindset, nutrition, fasting, and other advice from Mike for those looking to take the next step in their training [49:00]; What getting a parasite taught Mike about fasting [59:45]; The risks involved with cycling [1:03:00]; Mike setting the trans-Iowa (RAGBRAI) record [1:10:15]; PEDs, stimulants, and their effect on performance [1:15:00]; What motivates Mike (and others) to do this extreme stuff?</description></item><item><title>#16 - Formula 1 (with Paul Conti): the best drivers, Ayrton Senna, and the cautionary tales of driven individuals | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000309/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000309/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this bonus episode, Peter and med school colleague (and brilliant psychiatrist) Paul Conti reminisce on their favorite moments in Formula 1 history, their deep admiration for the late Ayrton Senna, and the remarkable careers of their all-time favorite drivers. Paul also helps to illuminate the psychological components that made the luminary drivers great, and the cautionary lessons we can take from their incredible lives.
We discuss:
Ayrton Senna [3:45]; How Senna’s death changed the sport [9:50]; The 80s &amp; 90s: a remarkable era of Formula 1 [12:55]; Hypothesizing what caused Senna’s fatal crash [17:45]; Comparing Stewart and Senna, their incredible bravery, and what lessons we can learn from them [23:30]; Best documentaries on racing, and some of Senna’s best moments [31:00]; Gilles Villeneuve, Stefan Bellof, and some of the other greats [39:15]; Why Senna is widely acknowledged as the best of all time [46:15]; Great rivalries and personalities [49:30]; Rendezvous, a high-speed drive through Paris [56:50]; and More.</description></item><item><title>#15 - Paul Conti, M.D.: trauma, suicide, community, and self-compassion | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000310/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000310/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, psychiatrist Paul Conti, M.D. discusses the impact of untreated trauma, the rising rate of suicide, and the influence of modern society on mental health, to name a few important topics covered. Paul also talks about how to deal with these challenges for yourself, your loved ones, and the community at large.
We discuss:
Paul’s background, and what drove him to psychiatry [5:00]; How silent bravado and incessant striving can lead to a functional (and actual) death, and why Paul is critical of the current state of psychiatry [14:45]; Psychedelics, psychotherapy and the dissolution of the ego [20:30]; How current society may be contributing to the increasing amount of suffering [25:00]; The ubiquity and impact of untreated trauma [31:45]; The rising rate of suicide, parasuicide, and “accidental” death [35:30]; Types of trauma, why we minimize it, and Peter’s introduction to Bridge to Recovery [44:00]; Triggering shame and fear, childhood trauma, and why trauma doesn’t care about time [48:00]; The impact of the brain on the body, and overcoming trauma with self-awareness [55:00]; How to recognize and stop the cycle of shame transference [1:04:30]; Peter’s profound experience at Bridge to Recovery, and the importance of finding shared experiences with others [1:11:15]; How to identify and deal with our own personal trauma [1:19:00]; Finding meaning in struggle, why we are less happy than ever, and the impact of an isolated society [1:25:30]; What steps can we take as a society to make an appreciable impact on the rising sense of desperation and misery?</description></item><item><title>#14 - Robert Lustig, M.D., M.S.L.: fructose, processed food, NAFLD, and changing the food system | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000311/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000311/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, Rob Lustig — a researcher, an expert in fructose metabolism, and a former pediatric endocrinologist — discusses what’s wrong with the current food environment, and what we can do to reduce our chances of becoming part of the obesity, diabetes, metabolic syndrome, and nonalcoholic fatty liver disease (NAFLD) epidemics. Rob recently earned a Master of Studies in Law because he believes that educating people about sugar from a scientific standpoint is only half the equation: the other half involves changing policy, which he explains in this episode.</description></item><item><title>#13 - Brett Kotlus, M.D.: How to look younger while you live longer | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000312/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Sep 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000312/</guid><description>Podcast Description This episode explores the question of how we can maintain a naturally youthful look as we get older. Brett — a New York City oculofacial plastic surgeon who specializes in both non-surgical and surgical cosmetic and reconstructive procedures of the eyes and face — shares some remarkably practical advice on everything from the most extensive procedural options, down to the simple steps one can do themselves, starting today, that can make a tremendous impact.</description></item><item><title>#12 - Corey McCarthy: Overcoming trauma, dealing with shame, finding meaning, changing the self-narrative, redemption, and the importance of gratitude | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000313/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000313/</guid><description>Podcast Description Corey and Peter met when they visited North Kern State Prison in California together as volunteers for Defy Ventures. Peter was moved by Corey’s remarkable story, who is a former inmate himself, and realized he had to have him on the podcast to share his experiences with a wider audience. You’ll almost assuredly take away something very important from listening to this episode. Understanding how your experiences can define you, what forgiveness means of both yourself and others, and how good people can do bad things, are just a few of the takeaways.</description></item><item><title>#11 - AMA #2: the Nothingburger — results from Peter’s week-long fast between two weeks of nutritional ketosis — and answering questions on all things fasting | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000314/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000314/</guid><description>Podcast Description Consider this episode a cross between an ask me anything (AMA) and a show-and-tell. Peter discusses his fasting experiment in great detail and answers questions from listeners and readers.
We discuss:
Why Peter did a one-week fast and the rationale for front- and back-ending it with a week-long ketogenic diet [6:30]; What Peter’s typical diet, exercise, sleep, stress management, and supplementation looks like [11:00]; What labs (e.g., glucose, ketones, lipids, inflammation and oxidation markers, thyroid- and sex hormones) Peter checked for the experiment [22:00]; Peter’s results after a week on a ketogenic diet [29:30]; Peter’s results after a week on a water-only fast [48:45]; Peter’s results after a week on a ketogenic diet following a week of fasting [58:30]; Peter’s “Top 6” surprises from the fasting experiment [1:08:30]; Different fasting-mimicking diet (FMD) protocols [1:29:20]; What is the optimal protocol, frequency, and duration for fasting?</description></item><item><title>#10 - Matt Kaeberlein, Ph.D.: rapamycin and dogs — man’s best friends? — living longer, healthier lives and turning back the clock on aging, and age-related diseases | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000315/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000315/</guid><description>Podcast Description Matt is someone who is deeply interested in understanding the biology of aging. Why do we age? What happens to us as we age? What are the things we can do to slow the aging process? How can we delay or prevent the onset of age-related diseases? These are all questions that Matt thinks deeply about, and explores these questions with his research at the University of Washington. He is currently investigating many of these questions through the Dog Aging Project and the compound rapamycin—the only known pharmacological agent to extend lifespan all the way from yeast to mammals—across a billion years of evolution.</description></item><item><title>#09 - David Sabatini, M.D., Ph.D.: rapamycin and the discovery of mTOR — the nexus of aging and longevity? | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000316/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000316/</guid><description>Podcast Description In this episode, my good friend David Sabatini delves into his extensive work with the mechanistic target of rapamycin—better known as mTOR—and rapamycin. The compound rapamycin is the only known pharmacological agent to extend lifespan all the way from yeast to mammals—across a billion years of evolution. David, a professor of biology and a member of the Whitehead Institute at MIT, shares his remarkable journey and discovery of mTOR in mammalian cells and its central role in nutrient sensing and longevity.</description></item><item><title>#08 - Tom Bilyeu: nutrition, fasting, meditation, mindset, immortality, and the secret formula of fulfillment | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000317/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000317/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tom Bilyeu is the founder of Impact Theory and a co-founder of Quest Nutrition. In this episode, among the highlights, Tom provides powerful insight he’s gained through his pursuit of fulfillment which led to a billion-dollar company in Quest Nutrition. Tom makes a compelling case that it starts with a growth mindset and he’s determined to impart this knowledge into as many people as possible.
We discuss:
Tom’s history with dieting and his changing views on fat [4:00]; Tom’s dream of immortality [10:00]; Life leading to Quest Nutrition and how “mindset” made the difference [18:45]; Why Tom helped start Quest Nutrition and what made it a success [27:00]; Why Tom started Impact Theory [35:00]; Money and motivation [44:00]; What Tom learned interviewing every employee at Quest, and the one question everyone answers exactly the same [54:15]; Tom’s secret formula of fulfillment and the ubiquity of suicide [1:00:00]; Nutrition, fasting, sleep, meditation, and other routines Tom uses to function at his best [1:13:15]; and More Learn more at www.</description></item><item><title>#07 - Deep Dive: Lp(a) — what every doctor, and the 10-20% of the population at risk, needs to know | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000318/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000318/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pronounced, el-pee-little-a, this lipoprotein is simply described as a low density lipoprotein (LDL) that has an apoprotein “a” attached to it...but Lp(a) goes far beyond its description in terms of its structure, function, and the role that it plays in cardiovascular health and disease. Affecting about 1-in-5 people, and not on the radar of many doctors, this is a deep dive into a very important subject for people to understand.</description></item><item><title>#06 - D.A. Wallach: music, medicine, cancer screening, and disruptive technologies | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000319/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000319/</guid><description>Podcast Description D.A. Wallach is a true polymath: recording artist, songwriter, essayist, investor, and so much more. In this episode, among the highlights, D.A. provides compelling and colorful insight into how the music industry works today vs the past, liquid biopsies, how to approach healthspan, cancer screening, and how we can reach a “singularity” in medicine.
We discuss:
How to learn music as a kid and an adult [7:30]; Chester French’s early struggles and ultimate success [16:45]; Learning to learn, fostering curiosity in kids, and balancing creativity with structure [31:30]; D.</description></item><item><title>#05 - Dom D’Agostino, Ph.D.: ketosis, n=1, exogenous ketones, HBOT, seizures, and cancer | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000320/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000320/</guid><description>Podcast Description Dom digs deep into the research and application of ketogenic diets, exogenous ketones, hyperbaric oxygen treatment, and treating cancer with a metabolic approach. Plus, we lost track of the number of n=Dom experiments mentioned in this episode.
We discuss:
Dom’s early medical training in hyperbaric chambers [7:00]; Effect of ketones on cancer cells [20:00]; Ketones and oxygen toxicity seizures [32:00]; HBOT &amp; its many applications [40:00]; Ketones, MCTs, and exogenous ketones [59:15]; How ketones affect blood glucose [1:20:00]; Ketone esters, salts, enantiomers vs.</description></item><item><title>#04 - AMA #1: alcohol, best lab tests, wearables, finding the right doc, racing, and more | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000321/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000321/</guid><description>Podcast Description In his first “Ask Me Anything” episode, Peter answered your questions submitted to him via Twitter.
We discuss:
What are Peter’s thoughts on alcohol consumption and health? [4:00] What are the best lab tests to request from your PCP, and what are the best markers for longevity? [14:00] What are the best wearables and why, and why does Peter use a continuous glucose monitor? [35:00] How does one select the right physician as a patient?</description></item><item><title>#03 - Ron Krauss, M.D.: a deep dive into heart disease | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000322/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 09:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000322/</guid><description>Podcast Description Whenever I’m stumped on a patient case or in my thinking about lipids, Ron is one of the first people I turn to for insight. Ron is recognized globally for his research into lipidology and has worn many hats in his career, including clinician, lipidologist, nutrition, genetics, and drug research.
In this episode, we explore heart disease at its origins before diving into the highly discussed, largely misunderstood, role of LDL and inflammation in atherosclerosis.</description></item><item><title>#02 - Rhonda Patrick, Ph.D.: the performance and longevity paradox of IGF-1, ketogenic diets and genetics, the health benefits of sauna, NAD+, and more | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000323/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 09:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000323/</guid><description>Podcast Description Rhonda and I go on a Nerd Safari into the jungle of health, nutrition, fitness, performance, and longevity. We visit IGF-1 and whether there’s a tradeoff of having high or low levels. We discuss the PPARs (receptor proteins) and genetic polymorphisms. Does Rhonda think there’s any benefit in a NAD+ booster for health and longevity? Can saunas lower the risk of heart disease, dementia, and all-cause mortality? Rhonda is a wealth of knowledge on so many topics and was the perfect companion to dig into so many fun topics in this episode.</description></item><item><title>#01 - Tim Ferriss: depression, psychedelics, and emotional resilience | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000324/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000324/</guid><description>Podcast Description Excited to kick off the podcast with special guest and close friend Tim Ferriss, lifehacker, podcaster extraordinaire, and author of multiple best-selling books that includes The 4-Hour Workweek, The 4-Hour Body, Tools of Titans, and Tribe of Mentors.
In this podcast we cover mental health, depression, and our mutual interest in psychedelics as potential therapeutic agents. Tim talks both experientially and from his own deep dive into the literature of psychedelics and mental health.</description></item><item><title>#00 - Sneak Peek: The Peter Attia Drive | The Peter Attia Drive</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/6648000325/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 14:56:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/6648000325/</guid><description>Podcast Description Welcome to a special sneak peek of The Peter Attia Drive. The Peter Attia Drive will feature guests and experts that will offer advice and insight to help you optimize performance, health, longevity, critical thinking, and life. It’s hosted by Stanford M.D., TED speaker, and longevity expert Dr. Peter Attia, founder of Attia Medical, PC, a medical practice with offices in San Diego and New York City.
Learn more at www.</description></item></channel></rss>