<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Global News Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/global-news-podcast/</link><description>Recent content in Global News Podcast on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 15:36:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/global-news-podcast/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>US defence secretary arrives in Israel for talks with Israeli counterpart | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550107/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 15:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550107/</guid><description>Podcast Description Lloyd Austin is expected to press for a reduction in the intensity of the offensive in Gaza. Also: Egypt's President Abdel Fattah al-Sisi wins a third term in office, and record rainfall causes flooding in the northern Australian state of Queensland.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>New Gaza crossing opens for aid trucks | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550108/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 00:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550108/</guid><description>Podcast Description Humanitarian aid has entered Gaza directly from Israel through the Kerem Shalom crossing for the first time in more than two months. Also: Serbia's Vucic claims election victory for his party, and a new rooster weathervane is fitted to Notre Dame spire in Paris.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Israeli hostages in Gaza were holding white cloth when shot - IDF | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550106/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2023 00:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550106/</guid><description>Podcast Description Three hostages were mistakenly killed in Gaza on Friday by Israeli troops in an area of intense fighting. Also: Vatican court convicts former Pope adviser of financial crimes, and Brazilian bossa nova musician Carlos Lyra dies aged 90.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Happy Pod: Refugees share their stories of hope | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550103/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 12:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550103/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our weekly collection of the happiest stories in the world. This week, the Somalian man who has brought the power of books to children living in refugee camps. Also: how a fascination with electricity inspired a Congolese woman to create a robotic medical tool. And the cyclist who took to the Olympic track after fleeing Afghanistan.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Israel says it mistakenly killed three hostages in Gaza | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550104/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550104/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Israeli military said the the three men were shot and killed by troops who were operating in northern Gaza. Also: Giuliani must pay $148m over false US election claims, and the Italian historian who is cooking up a controversy with a carbonara recipe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hungary blocks $55 billion EU aid for Ukraine | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550105/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 15:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550105/</guid><description>Podcast Description EU leaders said the aid negotiations would resume early next year. Also, a court rules that Prince Harry was a victim of phone hacking by a British newspaper group, and a state memorial service is held in Australia for the entertainer Barry Humphries.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EU to begin membership talks with Ukraine | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550101/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:21:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550101/</guid><description>Podcast Description European Council President Charles Michel says it is a "clear signal of hope" for the Ukrainian people and the continent as a whole. Also: Israeli leaders tell the visiting White House national security adviser that the war in Gaza will last until 'absolute victory' is achieved over Hamas. And in football, the English Premier League appoints its first female referee.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>EU leaders discuss support for Ukraine | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550102/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 15:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550102/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hungary resists Kyiv's bid to join the European Union and its pleas for aid. The EU's top diplomat said supporting Ukraine against Russian aggression was crucial to Europe's own stability. Also: President Putin resumes his annual press conferences, and why there's a marked increase in road deaths in Africa.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Israel defies calls for ceasefire | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550099/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 00:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550099/</guid><description>Podcast Description Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu says there can be no truce with Gaza until his forces have defeated Hamas. Also: As US Republicans launch an impeachment inquiry against Joe Biden, the president's son Hunter refuses a congressional subpoena to testify behind closed doors. And, what it takes to write a classic Christmas song.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>UN climate summit reaches divisive deal | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550100/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 15:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550100/</guid><description>Podcast Description The COP28 president said nations had "confronted realities and... set the world in the right direction". Also: Experts warn that Sudan is heading towards what's being called a "hunger catastrophe" after months of conflict. And, how Netflix's 'Stranger Things' universe is opening up a whole new chapter in a whole new format.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>UN: Gaza ceasefire resolution overwhelmingly approved | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550098/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 00:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550098/</guid><description>Podcast Description Analysts say this latest General Assembly vote acts as a powerful measure of international opinion, even though the United States opposed it. Also: Negotiations are continuing at the UN climate summit in Dubai where the search for consensus on a final agreement has continued deep into the night, and how to say no to all those Christmas party invitations without causing offence.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>UN climate summit: Race to save final deal | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550097/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 15:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550097/</guid><description>Podcast Description An earlier draft stopped short of calling for fossil fuels to be phased out. Also: Why Myanmar is now the world's leading producer of opium, and the president of a Turkish football club is arrested for attacking a referee at the end of a match.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Big backlash to COP 28 draft deal | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550001/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550001/</guid><description>Podcast Description There's widespread anger and disappointment as language promising 'phase out' of fossil fuels is dropped. Also: Polish legislators give Donald Tusk, who heads a pro-European Union coalition, the mandate for a new government, and the Japanese baseball sensation, Shohei Ohtani, signs a record-breaking 700 million dollar deal to play for the Los Angeles Dodgers.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>India rules decision to scrap Kashmir status is valid | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550002/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 15:53:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550002/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Supreme Court said the partial autonomy given following Indian independence had been temporary; Also: at COP 28 - a draft climate deal promises to 'reduce' fossil fuel reliance, and relaxed pantomime performances in Edinburgh with the raucousness reigned in for people with additional needs.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Argentina needs "shock treatment" to fix economy | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550003/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 00:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550003/</guid><description>Podcast Description At his swearing-in ceremony, President Javier Milei speaks of new era after decades of failure. Also: twin children of jailed Iranian activist Narges Mohammadi accept her Nobel Peace Prize, and the tomato that was lost in space.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Half of Gaza's population is starving - UN | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550004/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 00:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550004/</guid><description>Podcast Description The World Food Programme says conditions have made the delivery of food almost impossible. Also: DR Congo leader compares Rwandan president to Hitler, and is it worth collecting Star Wars merchandise?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Happy Pod: The giant Christmas 'tree' made of trees | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550005/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 12:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our weekly collection of the happiest stories in the world. This week, the Italian town of Gubbio lights its world record breaking Christmas Tree. Also: how a medical clinic in Borneo is helping to reduce deforestation. And the loneliest manatee, lonely no more.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>US vetoes UN Security Council resolution on Gaza ceasefire | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550006/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2023 00:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550006/</guid><description>Podcast Description The majority of the UN council supported an immediate ceasefire in Gaza, with 13 of 15 members voting in favour. Also: Russians to compete at Paris Olympics as neutrals, and Fairytale of New York sung at Pogues singer's funeral.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Vladimir Putin to stand for a fifth term as Russia President | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550007/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 15:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550007/</guid><description>Podcast Description A Kremlin official said that an 'astonishing' number of people wanted Mr Putin to continue. Also: the Palestinian health ministry in the occupied West Bank says six Palestinians have been killed in a raid by Israeli special forces on a refugee camp, and the scammers who are taking advantage of bed bugs in France.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>UN says aid operations in southern Gaza can no longer be 'called by that name' | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550008/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 01:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550008/</guid><description>Podcast Description The UN's head of humanitarian affairs, Martin Griffiths, said Israel's military offensive meant there were no safe spaces left for aid agencies in southern Gaza. Also: Blinken and Cameron agree about the dangers of blocking US financial support for Ukraine, and Italian opera is added to UNESCO world heritage list.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Israeli forces push further into Khan Younis | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550009/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 15:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550009/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tens of thousands of Palestinians flee intense fighting throughout southern Gaza. Also: a meeting between the Chinese president, Xi Jinping, and the EU highlights differences over trade, international affairs and human rights and, the novelist, poet and playwright, Benjamin Zephaniah has died aged 65.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>UN chief warns of 'humanitarian catastrophe' in Gaza | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550010/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 00:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Antonio Guterres has invoked a rarely used article, urging the Security Council to act immediately to achieve a truce. Also: President Biden makes an impassioned plea to Republicans to approve funding for Ukraine's war effort. And Time Magazine names the American singer Taylor Swift its Person of the Year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Israeli forces intensify fighting across Gaza | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550011/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 15:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550011/</guid><description>Podcast Description A journalist in Khan Younis told the BBC the ground has been shaking. The UN human rights chief Volker Türk says there's a heightened risk of atrocities. Also: the former British prime minister, Boris Johnson, says sorry to the Covid inquiry into the pandemic, and the BBC has spoken to one of the few families to escape from North Korea this year.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>IDF: Fiercest day of fighting in Gaza conflict | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550012/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550012/</guid><description>Podcast Description Residents in Khan Younis have told the BBC they're scared and hungry and don't know what to do. Also: Washington is to refuse visas for extremist Israeli settlers who have attacked Palestinians, and we hear about the rise of Rolex ripping in central London.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Israel steps up military operation in Khan Younis | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550013/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 15:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550013/</guid><description>Podcast Description The World Health Organisation says the situation in Gaza is getting worse by the hour. Also: Britain and Rwanda agree a new treaty aimed at getting the British government's centrepiece asylum policy operational, and 26 years after Grand Theft Auto was first released, it has a female main character.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>US says Israel's targeted evacuations in Gaza 'an improvement' | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550014/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Washington says it's too early to say if Israel is heeding US advice to protect civilians as Israel's offensive in southern Gaza continues. Also: the president of the UN climate summit says he's dismayed by what he called the constant attempts to undermine his work, and fears for the future of the Commonwealth Games as Australia's Gold Coast pulls out of hosting them in 2026.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Tens of thousands more Palestinians told to leave parts of Khan Younis | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 14:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550015/</guid><description>Podcast Description The call comes as Israel presses ahead with its military operations in southern Gaza. Also, the harrowing testimony of a Ukrainian soldier on the banks of the Dnipro, and why there will be no giant pandas left in Britain.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Israeli forces pushing into southern Gaza | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550016/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 00:35:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550016/</guid><description>Podcast Description The head of the military says the operation will be no less powerful than in the north of the enclave. Also: Iranian-backed Houthi rebels in Yemen say they've attacked two ships in the Red Sea, and a leading figure in Hong Kong's democracy movement goes to Canada to avoid the threat of arrest.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Residents of south Gaza city say Israeli strikes heaviest so far | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550017/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 00:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550017/</guid><description>Podcast Description Civilians in parts of southern Gaza have been told to evacuate as Israel's renewed bombardment continues. Also: Russia media say police raid gay clubs in Moscow, and how does art affect our brainwaves?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Happy Pod: India Tunnel Rescue Success | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550018/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 12:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550018/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our weekly collection of the happiest stories in the world. This week, how hope and perseverance prevailed in the rescue of 41 workers trapped in a tunnel in India. Also: a set of earbuds that could revolutionise wheelchair mobility. And celebrating 100 years of Scottish dancing.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hamas-run health ministry says scores killed in Gaza after fighting resumes | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550019/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Dec 2023 01:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550019/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Israeli military says it has struck hundreds of "terror targets" in Gaza. Also: George Santos expelled from US Congress in historic vote, and Putin's favourite conductor is to run the Bolshoi theatre.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Israel resumes airstrikes in Gaza as ceasefire ends | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550020/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 14:54:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550020/</guid><description>Podcast Description The IDF said the fighting resumed after it intercepted a rocket from inside the Gaza strip, while Hamas say Israel refused to accept offers to release other hostages. Also: world leaders address climate change at COP28, and author Omid Scobie denies naming two senior royals in controversial book.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Blinken warns Israel it must do more to protect civilians in Gaza | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550021/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 01:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550021/</guid><description>Podcast Description The US secretary of state says damage to hospitals and water supplies seen in the north of Gaza must not be repeated in the south. Also: surprise climate cash win for poor at COP28, and Russian court bans "LGBT movement".
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Temporary ceasefire extended in Gaza into a seventh day | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550022/</guid><description>Podcast Description Three people were killed by Hamas gunmen in Jerusalem hours after the ceasefire in Gaza was extended into a seventh day. Also on the programme: the UN climate summit begins in Dubai, and the former top US diplomat Henry Kissinger dies aged 100.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>More hostages released from Gaza on sixth day of truce | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550023/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 00:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550023/</guid><description>Podcast Description Thirty Palestinian prisoners are also due to be freed from Israeli jails. Also: US says it has foiled alleged plot to kill Sikh activist, and astronomers discover "the perfect solar system".
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Israeli forces raid occupied West Bank refugee camp | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 15:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550024/</guid><description>Podcast Description The IDF says it has killed two Palestinian militant commanders. Also: An EU report lists who experiences the most online hate, and why there's a new dress code in Kenya's Parliament.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Trapped Indian workers freed after 17 days | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550025/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 00:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550025/</guid><description>Podcast Description Amid scenes of jubilation, the operation was finally completed despite numerous problems and setbacks. Also: Hamas releases 12 more hostages and Israel hands over 30 more Palestinian prisoners on day 5 of a temporary truce, and the wolf spider that decided to lay its eggs in a cruise ship passenger's toe.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Indian rescuers reach 41 trapped tunnel builders | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550026/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 15:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550026/</guid><description>Podcast Description An evacuation pipe has been inserted into the collapsed tunnel, where the men had been trapped for more than two weeks. Also: the truce in Gaza appears to be holding for a fifth day - after a swap deal between Israel and Hamas was extended, and the first transatlantic flight powered by an alternative fuel has taken off from London.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Israel and Hamas truce extended by two days | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550027/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 00:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550027/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Israeli army says that eleven hostages released by Hamas from Gaza are now in Israeli territory. In return, thirty-three Palestinian prisoners are being freed. Also: The government of Sierra Leone blames renegade soldiers for a series of attacks in Freetown on Sunday that left twenty people dead, and the festive video by a family-run pub in Northern Ireland that's getting rave reviews and giving big retailers a run for their money.</description></item><item><title>Pressure mounts to extend Israel-Gaza ceasefire | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550028/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 15:29:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550028/</guid><description>Podcast Description Israel's allies and neighbours are hopeful that the pause in fighting can be extended beyond the fourth exchange of hostages and prisoners. Also, environmental activists say they're shocked at claims the United Arab Emirates has used its role as host of UN climate talks to make oil and gas deals. And six former pupils at a school in France go on trial over their alleged links to the beheading of teacher Samuel Paty in 2020.</description></item><item><title>Israel-Gaza: More prisoner and hostage exchanges | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550029/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 00:39:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550029/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamas and US President Joe Biden say they'd like an extension of the current four-day truce that's seen dozens released, but Israel's Prime Minister says that after the truce, his country will return to war. Also: The government of Sierra Leone says it's back in control, after gunmen attacked a barracks and several prisons in the capital, and The Irish writer Paul Lynch wins this year's Booker prize.</description></item><item><title>COP 28 special: Your climate questions answered | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550030/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550030/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our climate editor Justin Rowlatt and The Climate Question presenter Graihagh Jackson address issues including whether the oil-producing UAE is the right host for the meeting, what one thing we can all do to save the planet, and is a plant-based diet on the agenda?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Israel-Gaza: Second day of hostage and prisoner releases | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550031/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 00:34:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550031/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamas has handed back thirteen Israeli and four Thai nationals, and Israel is returning thirty-nine Palestinian prisoners. Also: Tens of thousands of Italians protest against gender based violence, and the BBC's Doctor Who marks its sixtieth anniversary with a special TV series.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Happy Pod: It's never too late to graduate | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550032/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 12:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550032/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our weekly collection of the happiest stories in the world. This week, the war veteran from Texas who's graduated from high school 60 years after he left. Also: the comic book that is educating girls all over the world about periods and menstruation. And: the cat meowing her way to a Christmas hit.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Twenty four hostages released by Hamas now back in Israel | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550033/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 00:18:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550033/</guid><description>Podcast Description Israel says the hostages, who were held in Gaza, are all in good health. In exchange for their freedom, thirty-nine Palestinian prisoners have been released. Also: A fishing vessel has been seized by suspected Somali pirates, and the French government urges shoppers to think twice before spending money on Black Friday.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Israel media says 13 hostages held in Gaza are freed | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550034/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 16:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550034/</guid><description>Podcast Description They have been handed over to the Red Cross and are on their way to the Egypt border. Also: the convicted murderer and South African former athlete Oscar Pistorius is to be released on parole; and the singer-songwriter Joan Armatrading on writing her first classical symphony.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Israel and Hamas truce imminent | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550035/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 00:19:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550035/</guid><description>Podcast Description Qatar says it hopes the pause in fighting it's helped arrange can be turned into a longer-term ceasefire. Also: Riot police in the Irish capital, Dublin, clash with crowds of protesters near the scene of a multiple stabbing, and parts of the state of Queensland in Australia have been over-run with a plague of rats.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Israel continues to bombard Gaza as truce delayed | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550036/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 15:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550036/</guid><description>Podcast Description Qatar says it's continuing work to finalise a pause in the fighting in Gaza. Also, Ukraine's stolen children, the return of the blue whales and Doctor Who at 60.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Anti-Islam populist leads in Dutch exit polls | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550037/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 23:49:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550037/</guid><description>Podcast Description Exit polls from the parliamentary election put the Freedom party well ahead of its rivals. Also: Relatives of the hostages held in Gaza wait to see who could be freed, and rescue workers close in on more than 40 workers trapped under a collapsed tunnel in India.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Israel's cabinet approves deal with Hamas to release hostages | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550038/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550038/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hamas will free 50 hostages in exchange for 150 Palestinian prisoners. Israel is continuing military operations against Hamas in Gaza ahead of a planned pause in the conflict. Also: OpenAI announces Sam Altman to return as CEO, and it's kimchi day in South Korea. How has the fermented vegetable dish become such a global phenomenon?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Israel's cabinet votes on hostage deal as Netanyahu says war will continue | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550039/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 00:47:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550039/</guid><description>Podcast Description The PM discusses with top officials a deal that could see at least 50 hostages freed from Gaza and a temporary pause in fighting. Also: the CEO of the world's largest crypto-exchange, Binance, pleads guilty to money laundering charges, and the venomous two metre long green mamba - on the loose in a Dutch city.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>US says Israel hostage deal 'closer than ever' | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550040/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 15:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550040/</guid><description>Podcast Description A deal to release hostages taken from Israel during Hamas attacks last month is "closer than ever before", according to a senior US official. Also : The first images have emerged of 41 men trapped for more than a week in a highway tunnel in the Indian Himalayas and a lost BBC interview with street artist Banksy is unearthed
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Majority of OpenAI staff threaten to quit | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550041/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 00:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550041/</guid><description>Podcast Description In a letter they demand the reinstatement of Sam Altman who was sacked on Friday. Also: The United Nations says the world is on course for a catastrophic warming -- even if countries meet their current pledges to cut emissions, and the global rise in the number of young sharing a bed to tackle the cost of living crisis.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Far-right outsider Javier Milei wins Argentina's presidential election | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550042/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 16:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550042/</guid><description>Podcast Description Mr Milei promises huge change for the country. Also: as 28 babies evacuated from a hospital in Gaza arrive in Egypt- another hospital has become embroiled in the conflict, and the Colombian pop star Shakira has reached a deal with Spanish prosecutors to settle a multi-million-dollar tax fraud case.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Israel says CCTV shows hostages at Gaza hospital | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550043/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550043/</guid><description>Podcast Description The Israeli military has released footage which it says shows captives being taken into Al-Shifa after the deadly Hamas attacks on 7 October. Also: the former US first lady, Rosalynn Carter, has died at 96, and Napoleon's hat has sold for almost two million euros.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Hundreds leave Gaza hospital as many feared killed at UN shelter | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550044/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 00:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550044/</guid><description>Podcast Description Hundreds of people including patients left Al Shifa Hospital on Saturday. The Hamas-run health authorities say 80 people were killed in two airstrikes on Jabaliya refugee camp. Also: Elon Musk has hailed the latest launch of his giant Starship rocket as a success, even though it blew up, and what's in the etiquette guide on the correct way to use mobile phones.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Happy Pod: Kenya's tree-planting holiday | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550045/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 12:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550045/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our weekly collection of the happiest stories in the world. This week, Kenya hands out 100 million saplings and calls a public holiday to plant them. Also: a new drug to treat two rare blood disorders, and a woman from Scotland who walked across Europe and met the Pope.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Charities: Israel's Gaza fuel offer not sufficient | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550046/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 00:20:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550046/</guid><description>Podcast Description The UN relief agency for Palestinians reiterates that the humanitarian situation in the territory is overwhelming. Also: The White House criticises Elon Musk after the head of Tesla appeared to promote an antisemitic post on his X platform. And, why some sailors are playing thrash metal music to fend off attacks on their boats by killer whales.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Israel to allow more fuel into Gaza | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550047/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 14:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550047/</guid><description>Podcast Description The move comes as the UN says the aid operation is 'impossible'. Also: A cholera outbreak in Zimbabwe triggers a state of emergency, and Amazon announces it will sell cars on its US site.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Israel says troops searching Al-Shifa have found the body of a hostage | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550048/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 23:59:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550048/</guid><description>Podcast Description Israeli forces say Yehudit Weiss was abducted by Hamas on 7 October. Also, Kenya approves a plan to send a thousand troops to Haiti to help deal with gang violence, and Britain's foreign secretary, the former prime minister David Cameron, visits Ukraine on his first official trip.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>BBC shown 'Hamas weapons and military equipment' in Al-Shifa | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550049/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 14:27:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550049/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our correspondent is taken inside the Gaza hospital raided by Israel's soldiers. Also: German police carry out countrywide raids on suspected Islamists with links to Hezbollah; and - in a world first - UK authorities approve gene therapy treatment to cure blood disorders.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Israel says weapons found in Gaza hospital | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550050/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 00:02:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550050/</guid><description>Podcast Description IDF releases video of what it says are arms and ammunition discovered at Al Shifa hospital. Also,the leaders of the two most powerful nations in the world meet in California, and how a heatwave is damaging Brazil's economy.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Israeli troops raid Gaza's main hospital | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550051/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 15:05:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550051/</guid><description>Podcast Description A doctor has spoken of fear among medics and patients as soldiers go room to room interrogating people. Also: Britain's Supreme Court rules the government's flagship policy of sending asylum seekers to Rwanda is unlawful, and a New Zealand competition to find its bird of the century ends with a grunting, puking creature with a colourful mullet.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>US: Hamas is using hospitals as command centres in Gaza | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550052/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 23:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550052/</guid><description>Podcast Description Pentagon says Hamas has stored weapons in tunnels at the Al Shifa hospital. Palestinian civilians are at risk as Israel attacks Gaza's biggest hospital. Also, the town kept awake by humming.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Dead hospital patients buried in mass grave in Gaza | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550053/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 15:11:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550053/</guid><description>Podcast Description The director of the Al-Shifa medical facility says there have been dozens of bodies. Also: flights are suspended in South Korea to help students with their exams, and the extraordinary relationship between a stuntman and the actor who plays Harry Potter.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>WHO says Gaza's biggest hospital 'becoming a cemetery' | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550054/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 23:24:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550054/</guid><description>Podcast Description Israel says Hamas is using the hospitals to hide its command centres. Also: Donald Trump's son returns to the witness stand in the family fraud trial; and the book that's so difficult to understand, it can take decades to read
Transcript</description></item><item><title>UK politics: Shock return for ex-PM David Cameron | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550055/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 16:17:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550055/</guid><description>Podcast Description Suella Braverman is sacked as home secretary in a surprise reshuffle and the former prime minister returns - but as foreign secretary. Also, Hamas reports babies dying in Gaza, and why Kenyans are planting millions of trees.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>WHO Chief: Gaza's main hospital no longer functioning | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550056/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 00:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550056/</guid><description>Podcast Description Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus says the situation at Al-Shifa is dire and perilous. The International Committee of the Red Cross says Gaza is rapidly approaching a humanitarian disaster. Also: The French Prime Minister leads a march in support of the Jewish community, which was boycotted by the far-left purportedly for being pro-Israel. And, the ongoing mystery surrounding the Loch Ness monster in Scotland.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Happy Pod: Protecting penguins in South America | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550057/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 12:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550057/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our weekly collection of the happiest stories in the world. This week, the biologist who's dedicated his life to protecting penguins in South America. Also: the award-winning Frenchman they call the Michelangelo of tattooists. And Peanut, the world’s oldest chicken
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Happy Pod: The 'Bee' song creating a buzz | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550058/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 12:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550058/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our weekly collection of the happiest stories in the world. This week, the Ukrainian musician whose bee-inspired song captured the hearts of millions. Also: the band pushing sustainability by walking 1400 kilometres between gigs. And, a new type of seal discovered in Greenland.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Happy Pod: Spreading joy: Finland's most positive person | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550059/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550059/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our weekly collection of the happiest stories in the world. This week, we meet Finland's happiest person, a giant tortoise is on the loose in Canada. And the pigeon set to fly off on a world book tour.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Israel-Gaza War: Your Questions Answered | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550060/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 16:41:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550060/</guid><description>Podcast Description We've teamed up with The Conflict podcast to answer your questions. These include Russia's role, the reaction from Israel, and what we can all do to be part of the solution.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Happy Pod: Why whales wear seaweed | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550061/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 11:10:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550061/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our weekly collection of the happiest stories in the world. This week, why are whales wearing seaweed on their heads? We celebrate 100 years of Disney. And a listener shares her children's orchestra in Colombia.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Israel-Gaza War: Your Questions Answered | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550062/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 21:07:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550062/</guid><description>Podcast Description These include why Hamas attacked Israel, the fate of the hostages, Israel's response so far, and whether both sides can overcome the trauma of their past.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Happy Pod: Bill Gates: Looking on the bright side | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550063/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550063/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our weekly collection of the happiest stories in the world. This week, how tech giant Bill Gates stays optimistic when it comes to climate change, what goes into growing the world's biggest pumpkin. And, what makes Alaska's perfect bear.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Gaza Special: Your Questions Answered | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550064/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 23:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550064/</guid><description>Podcast Description The build up to the Hamas attack, why now and what happens next? Is there any hope for peace between Israel and the Palestinians?
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Happy Pod: Biles is back with a bang | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550065/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550065/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our weekly collection of the happiest stories in the world. This week, the extraordinary comeback of US gymnast Simone Biles, an author who proves there is no age-limit on learning to read. And, solving the mystery of how cats purr.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Happy Pod: Uncovering the wonders of the universe | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550066/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550066/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our weekly collection of the happiest stories in the world. This week, will asteroid dust give clues to the origins of the universe? Jubilation in East Africa as the 2027 Cup of Nations is awarded to Kenya, Tanzania, and Uganda. And, celebrating words of hope and joy from around the world.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Happy Pod: Teamwork and pride - Saudi women's football | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550067/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2023 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550067/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our weekly collection of the happiest stories in the world. This week, the extraordinary growth of women's football in Saudi Arabia, ambitious plans to rewild southern rhinos in Africa, and the fierce competition to be crowned Montenegro's "laziest citizen".
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Happy Pod: Superhero dog saves family from fire | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550068/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550068/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our weekly collection of the happiest stories in the world. This week, the superhero hero dog who saved a family from a fire finds a forever home, the international effort to rescue a man from a cave in Turkey. And the electronic bra that can spot signs of breast cancer.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Special Edition - Artificial Intelligence - who cares? | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550069/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 15:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550069/</guid><description>Podcast Description What is AI? What can it do and what are its current limitations? A tool for good - or should we be worried? Will we lose our jobs? Are we ready to be cared for by machines? Our Tech Editor, Zoe Kleinman, and a panel of international experts explore AI's impact on healthcare, the environment, the law and the arts in a special edition recorded at Science Gallery London.</description></item><item><title>The Happy Pod: The little boy making a big difference | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550070/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550070/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our weekly collection of the happiest stories in the world. This week, the blind schoolboy who helped rebuild his school in Yemen, a new app teaching people literacy skills in the Horn of Africa. And, how Tilos has become the world's first zero-waste island.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Happy Pod: The gift of sight | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550071/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550071/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our weekly collection of the happiest stories in the world. This week, the extraordinary difference a pioneering stem cell treatment has made to one of its patients, the man who saved a toddler as she fell from an apartment block in Italy. And, a chance to hear our politics correspondent, Rob Watson, like you've never heard him before.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Happy Pod: Relief and joy: Pakistan cable car rescue | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550072/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550072/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our weekly collection of the happiest stories in the world. This week, huge relief in Pakistan after the rescue of two adults and six schoolboys after a cable car line snapped, the volunteers in Switzerland protecting livestock from wolves and therefore wolves from people, and some of the very best things about this year's Women's football world cup.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Happy Pod: The disabled TV director pushing for change | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550073/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550073/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our weekly collection of the happiest stories in the world. This week, Jordan Hogg and his campaign to get more disabled people working in the film and TV industry, the Ukrainian soldier who became a ballet star after losing both legs in the war, and the surfers rescued after 36 hours adrift off Indonesia.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Happy Pod: Six months on, revisiting the baby born under the rubble | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550074/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550074/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our weekly collection of the happiest stories in the world. This week, Afraa, the newborn rescued from the debris of Syria’s earthquake, is a symbol of hope, the mother and daughter who won the lottery to travel to space, and the dog who surfed to victory at the world championships.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Happy Pod : The Norwegian Nepali duo reaching new heights | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550075/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550075/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our weekly collection of the happiest stories in the world. This week, smashing the record for climbing the world's fourteen highest peaks, the remarkable musician who plays the French horn with his toes, and an eight-year-old chess prodigy from Nigeria - sharing her passion for the game.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Happy Pod: Farmers strike truce with bears | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550076/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550076/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our weekly collection of the happiest stories in the world. This week, the deal to get Colombian coffee growers and bears living in harmony, the power of sound in restoring Australian coral reefs, and how sending a fax can win you a fortune in Taiwan.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Happy Pod: New hope for Alzheimer's treatment | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550077/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550077/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our weekly collection of the happiest stories in the world. This week, a "breakthrough" drug that could slow down Alzheimer's, and the men remaking trees. Plus, solving a puzzle that stumped mathematicians for over 50 years.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Happy Pod: The portable incubator saving lives in a war zone | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550078/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550078/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our weekly collection of the happiest stories in the world. This week, the portable incubator saving lives in Ukraine, a tale of heroics on the streets of Taiwan. And, how putty might help to preserve Australia's coral reefs.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Happy Pod: Everyone has a story to tell | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550079/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550079/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our weekly collection of the happiest stories in the world. This week, how sharing life stories is helping elderly patients connect with their carers. Also, the baby born onboard an express train in Kenya, and China’s “butterfly father” dedicating his life to protecting the beautiful insects.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Happy Pod: Monkey rescue mission | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550080/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550080/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our weekly collection of the happiest stories in the world. This week, 100,000 Sri Lankan monkeys saved from export to China. Also: an Australian man born in a taxi seeks the driver, and the 16-year-old fulfilling a dream by playing Glastonbury.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Happy Pod: Magical voice from the past | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550081/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550081/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our weekly collection of the happiest stories in the world. This week, an old cassette tape brings a mother's voice back to life, researchers find that napping is good for your brain. And: The mission to bring light to bombed houses in Ukraine. Presented by Jackie Leonard and music produced by Iona Hampson.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Happy Pod: Saved from skin cancer | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550082/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550082/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our weekly collection of the happiest stories in the world. This week, thanks for the eagle eyed doctor in Australia who spotted a serious medical problem on a TV interview and issued a very timely warning. Praise in Colombia for the big sister who kept her little siblings alive in the jungle after their plane crashed. And the Mongolian women re-invigorating an old art-form for the twenty-first century. Presented by Jackie Leonard.</description></item><item><title>The Happy Pod: Rescue mission in Sudan | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550083/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550083/</guid><description>Podcast Description Around 300 children and babies rescued from an orphanage in the Sudanese capital, Khartoum. Also: We hear from one of the researchers helping a paralysed man to walk again, and why some people in Japan are relearning how to smile.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Happy Pod: Back to class for Afghan girls | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550084/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550084/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our new weekly collection of the happiest stories in the world. This week, educating girls in Afghanistan, the Finnish octogenarian mastering Taekwondo, and dogs enjoying art in Greece. Presented by Andrew Peach. Music produced by Iona Hampson.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Happy Pod: Striking gold | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550085/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 11:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550085/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our new weekly collection of the happiest stories in the world. This week, how an amateur digger in Australia hit the jackpot, the boy who spent three years camping out for charity, and could the secret to happiness lie in our sweat? Presented by Andrew Peach. Music produced by Iona Hampson.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Happy Pod: The smiling cow | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550086/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 12:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550086/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our new weekly collection of the happiest stories in the world. This week, an unusual cow brings joy to Australia, the happiest places in the world are revealed and how shrimps are saving lives. Presented by Andrew Peach. Music produced by Iona Hampson.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Happy Pod | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550087/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 12:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550087/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our new weekly collection of the happiest stories in the world. This week, how a computer data centre could heat pools around the globe, Paris Opera appoints its first black star ballet dancer, and a robotic elephant helping to improve animal rights in India. Presented by Andrew Peach. Music produced by Iona Hampson.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Happy Pod | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550088/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 12:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550088/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our new weekly collection of the happiest stories in the world. This week, sharing the things about your home country that make you happy, NASA's new head of science on how her dad gave her a love of space, and how bees can not only solve puzzles, but teach each other how to do it. Presented by Andrew Peach. Music produced by Iona Hampson.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>The Happy Podcast | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550089/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 12:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550089/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our new weekly collection of the happiest stories in the world along with the sounds that bring joy to our listeners. This week, the naughty Finnish huskies who've found a new home, the Caribbean sailor who survived 24 days at sea on ketchup, and the crafty octogenarian who knits for Hollywood. Presented by Andrew Peach. Music produced by Iona Hampson.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Special episode: Abortion rights around the world | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550090/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 15:26:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550090/</guid><description>Podcast Description In June, the US Supreme Court overruled Roe v Wade and ended the constitutional right to abortion in America. In a special episode, we investigate the changing dynamic of abortion rights globally in countries like Colombia, China and Ireland. We'll also be examining the restrictions still faced by women in Africa and places like Malta and El Salvador.
Audio for this episode was updated on 4 July 2022, due to a factual error in an earlier version.</description></item><item><title>Young voices special | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550091/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550091/</guid><description>Podcast Description Is the nuclear threat real? What does Putin want? Who is winning the war in Ukraine? We took questions on the invasion from young people around the world and looked for answers from BBC correspondents.
Jackie Leonard speaks to Martin Forster, a senior child psychologist with the healthcare company, Kry, in Sweden. Listeners' questions are tackled by Vitaliy Shevchenko, Paul Adams, Theo Leggett, Lyse Doucet and Mark Lowen.</description></item><item><title>Special: Global News Ukrainecast part 2 | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550092/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 12:44:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550092/</guid><description>Podcast Description A month since the Russian invasion of Ukraine, we are collaborating with Ukrainecast again. We answer more of your questions.
Jackie Leonard, presenter of the Global News Podcast, alongside Gabriel Gatehouse and Vitaliy Shevchenko from Ukrainecast, guide us through questions about civilian life in the country, military tactics, and the international response to the invasion. BBC chief international correspondent, Lyse Doucet, joins us from Kyiv to talk through what is happening on the ground there, and BBC security correspondent Frank Gardner, tells us the latest on the physical and information war.</description></item><item><title>Russia-Ukraine: On the brink of war? | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550093/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 13:15:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550093/</guid><description>Podcast Description Our experts in Moscow, Kyiv and London answer your questions about the crisis.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Omicron versus the world: Your questions answered | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550094/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 15:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550094/</guid><description>Podcast Description As the Omicron variant spreads around the world and cases surge, BBC correspondents tell us how Covid-19 is impacting our lives, our businesses and our economies.
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Afghanistan Special: Your Questions Answered | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550095/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 17:40:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550095/</guid><description>Podcast Description BBC correspondents answer your questions about the Taliban's takeover of Afghanistan. We ask how did the Taliban overthrow the Afghan government so quickly? What now for human rights, the economy and international relations?
Photo:People on board an evacuation flight out of Kabul airport, August 21, 2021 Credit:MoD/PA Wire
Transcript</description></item><item><title>Global News Brexitcast | Global News Podcast</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/8149550096/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 15:22:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/8149550096/</guid><description>Podcast Description We team up with the award-winning Brexitcast team to bring you a special update on what Britain leaving the EU means for you. You’ve sent us questions from around the world and Jackie Leonard puts them to the experts from the podcast that’s all about Brexit. There’s also cake, phew.
Spread the word! #GlobalNewsPod #Brexitcast
Find the Brexitcast podcast here: http://www.bbc.co.uk/brexitcast
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>