<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Not Past It on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/tags/not-past-it/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Not Past It on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/not-past-it/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Not Past It - The Price of Blood</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100096/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100096/</guid>
        <description>0:05
It&amp;rsquo;s the 1920s a young man is heading to the hospital.
As soon as he arrives, he&amp;rsquo;s rushed into surgery.
A damp towel is draped over his head.
An incision is made on his wrist, an artery exposed.
0:23
But this man, he&amp;rsquo;s not the actual patient beside him.
Doctors are more concerned with someone else in the next bed over surgeons hover over a still body.
Seemingly unconscious a doctor turns back to the young man, grabs his arm and connects is exposed artery to the unresponsive Patient.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - ‘Come On Barbie, Let’s Go Party’</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100095/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100095/</guid>
        <description>0:05
Paper plates, smeared with fluorescent frosting, forgotten, party favors Left Behind gift, wrap scattered all over the floor.
The Tell-Tale signs of an absolutely Rockin seventh birthday.
As a kid, I always had a hard time accepting when the party was over, but then I&amp;rsquo;d remember the table full of birthday presents and that usually consoled me pretty quickly.
0:32
My parents would help me go through the gifts and note down who brought what?</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - #OscarsSoWhat?</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100094/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100094/</guid>
        <description>0:02
It&amp;rsquo;s the Oscars 2017.
It&amp;rsquo;s a privilege for us to present the final Award of the evening.
The star-studded audience is on the edge of their seats, Warren Beatty, and Faye Dunaway are about to announce the Academy Award for best picture of the year.
0:19
The film&amp;rsquo;s we honor tonight, inspired us touched our emotions gave us hope and joy and may even have changed our thinking.
And after the scripted cliches baby pops open.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Who Let The Underdogs Out</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100093/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100093/</guid>
        <description>0:00
In February of 1964, 22 year, old boxer, Cassius Clay Was preparing for one of the most important fights of his young career.
He&amp;rsquo;d been a professional boxer for, just over three years.
And in that time, he hadn&amp;rsquo;t lost a single fight, but he was about to go toe-to-toe, against Sonny, Liston the heavyweight champion of the world known to many as the most intimidating boxer alive in the weeks leading up to the fight.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - F*** Your Slave Laws</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100092/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100092/</guid>
        <description>0:00
It&amp;rsquo;s 1851 a chilly February night in Boston&amp;rsquo;s Beacon Hill Neighborhood.
The hum of steam boats in the harbor.
Nearby Echoes through the air.
As black residents walk home from their jobs across town, they passed by posters lining, the cobblestone streets.
0:18
Posters warning them to avoid the police and stay vigilant inside a nearby meeting house.
Speakers approach a lectern one by I won forgiving impassioned, speeches about protecting their Community by breaking the law, a new federal law looming over the city which empowers slave owners to retrieve people who&amp;rsquo;ve escaped enslavement in the South and return them into bondage.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Conviction: Who&#39;s 40 Grand Not Tempting To?</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100091/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100091/</guid>
        <description>0:00
Hey, not past it listeners this week.
We&amp;rsquo;ve got a special episode for you from the new season of conviction.
And this time around, they&amp;rsquo;re telling the story of a harlem rapper Max B, who&amp;rsquo;s on the cusp of stardom.
But his life changes when he hears about an irresistible score worth forty thousand dollars.
0:22
Now, Max like many other rappers of the time wrote songs about a life of luxury that he didn&amp;rsquo;t yet have but was determined to get Get through Max B&amp;rsquo;s story, conviction, examines the US justice system and questions, who the system works for and who it works against all episodes are out now.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - TV&#39;s Hail Mary Pass</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100090/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100090/</guid>
        <description>0:00
Hey, not past it listeners.
We&amp;rsquo;re back with another historical, domino effect.
That&amp;rsquo;s where we travel through time and see how one moment in history, topples over a string of events, bringing us to unexpected places.
And in today&amp;rsquo;s episode, we&amp;rsquo;re hitting the field.
0:20
And the stage.
Revisiting a halftime show that revealed a lot more than it bargained for.
Oh my God, oh my God, the audacity From gimlet media.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Real Housewives, Real History!</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100089/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100089/</guid>
        <description>0:01
Hey, I&amp;rsquo;ve got a question for you, what do Dallas?
Salt Lake City, Miami and New York, all have in common.
It&amp;rsquo;s real housewives.
Bitches it all began with the ladies of Orange County.
0:18
Now, nearly 20 years later, the housewives have grown into a reality TV Empire fabulous.
Gone With the Wind Fabulous.
Okay, you are Psychotic.
Jesus jugs.
You&amp;rsquo;re psychotic, Jesus jugs and I said what I said, okay.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - The Saloon Smasher</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100088/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100088/</guid>
        <description>0:03
It&amp;rsquo;s 5 p.m. on a Friday in Boston.
Massachusetts, one of those damp New England days when all you want to do, is slide out of your wet coat, warm your hands and order a drink at a cozy bar.
This particular bar has a speakeasy Vibe, heavy velvet curtains and dark wood accents, but that&amp;rsquo;s not the first thing you notice.
0:25
When you walk in we sent reporter Amory sivertson to go check it out.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Big Tobacco&#39;s Minty Rebrand</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100087/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100087/</guid>
        <description>0:02
It&amp;rsquo;s 1981 and model, David Garlits is posing for Winston cigarettes.
Latest ad campaign near the top of Mount Evans in Colorado.
He&amp;rsquo;s got that feathered 80s hair but he looks tough Macho, even with a smoke dangling.
0:19
At the side of his mouth, a photo crew captures, the rugged model, while some Executives watch on And during this shoot, David is having a breathtaking experience.
That certainly felt the effects of my smoking addiction, not being able to breathe.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - We&#39;re Off To See The Wiz</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100086/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100086/</guid>
        <description>0:02
The Wizard of Oz was one of the first movies.
I remember falling in love, with reading.
We&amp;rsquo;re not in Kansas anymore.
Most mornings before kindergarten.
I begged.
My mom to braid.
My hair.
Dorothy style.
0:18
Two french braids that rested on my shoulders for Halloween Myoma, sold me a blue, gingham dress to match Judy Garland&amp;rsquo;s, frock.
And I even had my own craft glitter version of Dorothy&amp;rsquo;s, red ruby slippers.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - The Glow Down of the Green M&amp;M</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100085/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100085/</guid>
        <description>0:00
Happy holidays not past it listeners or bringing back one of our favorite Domino episodes for you.
It&amp;rsquo;s about green, the sexiest Eminem of them all this year.
Like many of us, green went through some changes, the Mars Inc brand revamped the images of their candy coated characters, but the most notable change was green.
0:26
Her iconic me high-heeled, white go-go boots.
You or replaced with some flat boring.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Undercover at the Debutante Ball</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100084/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100084/</guid>
        <description>0:00
In the summer of 2021, the actress Ellie, Kemper was kind of everywhere.
But it wasn&amp;rsquo;t for a new episode of the office or the unbreakable Kimmy Schmidt.
Ellie Kemper is at the center of a new controversy surrounding one of her hometowns.
0:16
Oldest traditions.
This was a controversy that originated more than 20 years earlier when she participated in a debutante ball and st.
Louis Missouri, Twitter users, discovered campers involvement with the Veep.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Santa Snafu</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100083/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100083/</guid>
        <description>0:02
Hey, not past it listeners.
Have you been naughty or nice?
Well I hope you&amp;rsquo;ve been good because this holiday season, we&amp;rsquo;re getting you another historical domino effect.
That&amp;rsquo;s where we travel back in time and see how one moment in history, topples over a string of events, bringing us to unexpected places.
0:22
And in today&amp;rsquo;s episode, we&amp;rsquo;ll be looking North Since noon today, we&amp;rsquo;ve been tracking an aerial object, making its way across Canada.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - American Terror: The Farm</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100082/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100082/</guid>
        <description>0:00
Hey, not past it.
Listeners this week, we&amp;rsquo;re bringing you a story from American Terror, a new podcast from gimlet and Vice news that takes you deep into the underbelly of Neo, Nazi Terror groups in the United States.
It&amp;rsquo;s a part of US history that we talked about in the past tense, but every day it seems, there&amp;rsquo;s a new headline, black people being targeted at their Neighborhood Grocery Store members of the lgbtq community being gunned down in a nightclub.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Wax Heads Will Roll</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100081/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100081/</guid>
        <description>0:02
Selena.
Quintanilla is necklace.
Was broken.
Audrey, Hepburn&amp;rsquo;s dress with shredded somehow.
I don&amp;rsquo;t know how it looks like an animal got to her, but we can, they&amp;rsquo;re often not animals.
So I don&amp;rsquo;t know how that happened.
We&amp;rsquo;re trying to figure it out.
0:18
I&amp;rsquo;m at Madame Tussauds wax, museum with producer Olivia Briley.
We&amp;rsquo;re getting a behind the scenes tour from Matt Hills Horst.
It&amp;rsquo;s his job to take care of the wax figures, but when it comes to Avid fan, Fans there&amp;rsquo;s only so much he can do.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Sabotaging the &#39;History&#39; of Thanksgiving</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100080/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100080/</guid>
        <description>0:01
Hey guys, hope you&amp;rsquo;re doing well out there in your corner of the world.
It&amp;rsquo;s a holiday week here in the US Thanksgiving.
And for many, this is a time to gather the family around a turkey to pile plates, high and Gorge ourselves on family traditions all while practicing gratitude, but for other Americans, the fourth Thursday in November has a different significance.
0:26
It&amp;rsquo;s a national day of mourning, a reminder of a dark History on the false myths, used to paper over it.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Oklahoma Is Not O.K.</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100079/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100079/</guid>
        <description>0:00
It&amp;rsquo;s November 16th, 1907 a crowd of around, 30,000 people has assembled in the city of Guthrie.
Oklahoma, the men are in their best suits.
The women look like they&amp;rsquo;re straight out of Little House on the Prairie, they&amp;rsquo;re gathered at the steps of the town library for a wedding.
0:20
The sound of Celebration is in the air military bands.
Played joyful Tunes.
Whistles ring out.
Bursts of fireworks.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - There’s No Girls in Baseball</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100078/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100078/</guid>
        <description>0:01
It&amp;rsquo;s 1943, the middle of the second world, war Americans, young and old are proudly doing their civic duty, rationing butter growing Victory Gardens and buying war bonds.
But in the midst of the war effort, there&amp;rsquo;s one some might say, equally pressing issue, facing the American people.
0:20
How do we watch baseball when all the men are gone, Debbie eyes and slides home with a run and a nice libros leg better.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Election Trivia Smackdown</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100077/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100077/</guid>
        <description>0:00
Hey, Pop Quiz.
How many congressional seats are on the ballot on November 8th?
The answer is 470.
Did you get it?
Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, I didn&amp;rsquo;t know either.
0:16
It&amp;rsquo;s all of the House Seats and more than a third of the Senate.
So today, we&amp;rsquo;re doing not passed.
It, trivia, election style will cover some political ground, but we&amp;rsquo;ve also got questions about pecan, pie, Madonna, Star Trek, plus some truly wild political slogans from history that you&amp;rsquo;re not going to want to miss feel free to Play along as you listen, put that knowledge to the test.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Frankenstein&#39;s Teen Mom</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100076/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100076/</guid>
        <description>0:03
Oh, hey there.
I see you&amp;rsquo;ve decided to press play.
You might want to reconsider the following broadcast is not for the faint of heart.
This story of such a moral themes with such unsavory characters.
0:19
It&amp;rsquo;s well we&amp;rsquo;ve warned you.
It&amp;rsquo;s 1803 London. the Royal College of Surgeons hosts a medical lecture to an audience of doctors and other curious onlookers at the front of the hall stands, Italian physicist Giovanni aldini next to him as a massive battery of copper and zinc and his subject, a corpse a recently executed, convict, who&amp;rsquo;d been hanged just an hour before for drowning his wife and child, an electrical current runs from the giant battery through Metal rods that aldini is holding he touches them to the corpses face it store.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - When Josephine Baker Had Enough</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100075/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100075/</guid>
        <description>0:04
It&amp;rsquo;s the Jazz Age, the 1920s in Paris picture this women on stage dancing, in their little flapper outfits, scored by trumpets and heavy drums.
You can imagine cigarette, smoke and cheers from Men in the audience.
0:23
The drums get faster, the flappers On Stage dance in unison, kicking their legs out and twirling around.
And then a woman breaks through their line.
She&amp;rsquo;s young, she has short slicked down hair, she wears, red lipstick, she&amp;rsquo;s black, she hurries across the stage frantically, taking her, dress off as she goes, she&amp;rsquo;s shaking her hips throwing her arms up, winding her waist that woman.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - ‘Lizzie Borden Took an Ax’</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100074/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100074/</guid>
        <description>0:01
A warning for our listeners, the story contains descriptions of violence, so please take care while you listen.
If you really want to get into the Halloween Spirit, New England and the fall is the perfect place to visit, you&amp;rsquo;ve probably heard of Salem, and they&amp;rsquo;re burning witches, but just a stone&amp;rsquo;s throw away as the Tiny Town of Fall River tucked away into a sleepy corner of Massachusetts.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - #13 Kenny from &#39;Heavyweight&#39;</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100073/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100073/</guid>
        <description>0:01
Hey, my past it listeners.
We&amp;rsquo;ve got a brand new episode coming up next week but in the meantime I wanted to tell you about one of my favorite podcasts called heavyweight.
I don&amp;rsquo;t like to be pretentious about people&amp;rsquo;s podcast choices, but when someone tells me they listen to heavy weight, I&amp;rsquo;m like, oh okay, so you&amp;rsquo;re cool.
0:21
Got it, you&amp;rsquo;ve got taste, you&amp;rsquo;ve got discernment.
Well, lucky for us.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - From Corsets to Climate Change</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100072/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100072/</guid>
        <description>0:00
Hey, not past it listeners.
It&amp;rsquo;s that time again this week the historical.
Domino effect is back.
That&amp;rsquo;s when we tell you a series of mini history stories, each story leads to the next and a chain reaction, and we&amp;rsquo;ll end up in a completely different place from where we started in the past.
0:21
We&amp;rsquo;ve gone from the Immaculate Conception to Miley Cyrus camels in the military, to the founding of West Hollywood.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Remember TGIF?</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100071/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100071/</guid>
        <description>0:00
So when we pitch ideas for this show, we usually start by looking up some event from that week in history.
And at one of our meetings, someone mentioned, hey this is actually the same week that TGIF launched a few people on the call were immediately like, oh my God.
0:18
Yes, I loved TGIF.
Meanwhile, I was trying to figure out why everyone was so excited about the chain restaurant that makes its employees dress like Candyland referees.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Mary Kay and the Rise of the Pink MLM</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100070/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100070/</guid>
        <description>0:03
Okay, picture.
This, you&amp;rsquo;re packed into a giant Convention Center in Dallas, Texas.
There are tens of thousands of women there.
They&amp;rsquo;ve got big hair and big shoulder pads.
It&amp;rsquo;s 1997 one by one.
Women come onto the stage.
0:18
Adorned in diamonds and sashes.
They offer Pepe testimonials.
Can you see why I work?
So hard to beat the top so that I can hang out with these million-dollar girlfriends that I have.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Are You Smarter Than A Podcast Host?</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100069/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100069/</guid>
        <description>0:01
When I was in high school, my dad and I used to have this tradition, he&amp;rsquo;d get home from work and pour himself a glass of wine.
I&amp;rsquo;d get home from school and change out of my uniform and at 7 p.m. sharp.
We plop down in front of the TV.
Flip it to channel, 7 and wait for the announcer to say that iconic line.
0:20
And now here is the host of Jeopardy.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Colonists, Criminals, and Nic Cage</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100068/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100068/</guid>
        <description>0:00
Hey, not past it listeners.
It&amp;rsquo;s that time again this week the historical.
Domino effect is back.
That&amp;rsquo;s when we tell you a series of many history stories that lead you through time in a chain reaction and we&amp;rsquo;ll end up in a completely different place from where we started and the past, we&amp;rsquo;ve gone from a Nazi battle to a hit movie musical.
0:23
A candy, Baron to the sexy green Eminem.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Tricky Dick Saves the Beach</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100067/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100067/</guid>
        <description>0:03
Surfing the ultimate extreme sport carving through roaring waves and soaring through ripping water.
And for a lot of people, it&amp;rsquo;s not just a sport, it&amp;rsquo;s a spiritual experience.
A lot of times, do you had this feeling in the morning?
0:19
When there&amp;rsquo;s no wind and it&amp;rsquo;s perfect glass, and you would just sit there and these thoughts would go through your mind.
Whether they be religious or just deep peace of mind, this is Bob martien or babo.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - On Wednesdays We Buy Companies</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100066/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100066/</guid>
        <description>0:02
You&amp;rsquo;ve probably heard the news that Elon Musk is buying Twitter.
Kinda, maybe it&amp;rsquo;s the hottest and messiest relationship drama.
This side of Riverdale, Elon Musk and Twitter.
He took to Twitter earlier this year and made an offer the board couldn&amp;rsquo;t refuse and then the Heat of the Moment musk tweeted.
0:22
This one melodramatic message, The Barbarians are at the gate despite what it Seems like this isn&amp;rsquo;t the name of some Tolkien fantasy novel, it&amp;rsquo;s a phrase lifted from 1980s Wall Street culture.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Every Little Thing: Behind the Pom Poms</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100065/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100065/</guid>
        <description>0:02
Hey, not past it listeners this week.
We&amp;rsquo;ve got a special episode for you.
From our friends over at every little thing every week, host floor Lichtman answers.
Your burning questions about well, every little thing and in this episode, she dives into the origins of cheerleading, where did all that rah-rah-sis-boom-bah start and who gets to Define what cheerleading really is?
0:28
It&amp;rsquo;s a wild ride through cheer camp.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Reefer Racism</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100064/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100064/</guid>
        <description>0:00
Did you ever come across the concept of like weed as a gateway drug?
Oh, yeah, absolutely.
We does a gateway.
Drug you do?
We, you&amp;rsquo;re going to be on heroin.
That&amp;rsquo;s Mary prior.
She&amp;rsquo;s the co-founder of a cannabis startup and an advocate for racial Equity within the Cannabis industry.
0:19
But Mary wasn&amp;rsquo;t always.
So, we&amp;rsquo;d positive growing up in the 90s.
She heard the weed is bad message.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - The First ‘Test Tube’ Baby</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100063/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100063/</guid>
        <description>0:01
I think you probably know the details of your birth more than any other person on earth, right?
Like most of us, don&amp;rsquo;t know.
The nitty-gritty of is how we were conceived.
Is pretty weird, watching yourself, be born.
It&amp;rsquo;s a yes, this is Louise Brown being interviewed by CBS News in 2018, Louise was famous before she was even, born cameras, were there, the moment she arrived?
0:25</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Operation Ice Pick</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100062/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100062/</guid>
        <description>0:01
Miss Ratched.
I&amp;rsquo;d like to ask a question, please, go ahead.
This is from The 1975 film.
One Flew Over the Cuckoo&amp;rsquo;s Nest I takes place in a mid-century mental institution and I&amp;rsquo;ve never been to a baseball game.
0:18
Well, I think I&amp;rsquo;d like to see one.
The staff isn&amp;rsquo;t letting the patient&amp;rsquo;s, watch the World, Series this infuriates.
Randall McMurphy played by Jack Nicholson.
He starts acting up series.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Live Aid Rocks the World</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100061/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100061/</guid>
        <description>0:01
I remember being a kid up late at night watching TV and seeing these ads for about 70 cents you can buy a can of soda regular or Diet in Ethiopia for just 70 cents.
A day, you can feed a child like Jamal nourishing meals this ad from the Christian Children&amp;rsquo;s Fund shows a young boy.
0:24
He looks to be around for years old, he&amp;rsquo;s wrapped in cloth.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Beefcakes and Bulges: Playgirl Magazine</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100060/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100060/</guid>
        <description>0:02
It&amp;rsquo;s the summer of 2006.
Nicole Caldwell has recently graduated from a prestigious journalism school and landed herself.
A fancy job at a storied Magazine on her first day.
She walks into the Magazine&amp;rsquo;s Manhattan office and she takes her first step into the professional life of a journalist.
0:23
She finds her desk, and then her boss hands.
Her, the essential guide to nailing the maggs signature.
Of they give you like a 30-page print out with like a staple in it of all synonyms for Genitalia and sex.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - You Are Killing Women</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100059/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100059/</guid>
        <description>0:02
On June 24th of this year, the US Supreme Court handed down a landmark decision.
And Dobbs V Jackson Women&amp;rsquo;s Health Organization.
The Court ruled that the right to an abortion does not exist in the Constitution.
Effectively overturning 1973 s row v Wade decision.
0:22
This means that United States federal law does not protect the right to an abortion.
Thirteen states have had, what are called trigger laws on their books.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Tour de Pride</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100058/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100058/</guid>
        <description>0:02
Lgbtq history is American history and we&amp;rsquo;re trying to make that visible can lust.
Bader is a co-founder and co-director of the New York City LGBT historic sites project and he&amp;rsquo;s a big believer in the power of landmarks.
0:18
The Statue of Liberty, is an important site for American history.
The Empire State Building the bridge in Selma, so those places are critical for people to understand the tangible.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - The Gay History of Camels</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100057/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100057/</guid>
        <description>0:00
Hey, not past it listeners.
This week&amp;rsquo;s show is another history.
Domino episode will line up some mini historical moments, will knock them down and end up in a completely different and unexpected place from gimlet media.
0:17
This is not passed it a show about the stories we can&amp;rsquo;t quite leave behind.
I&amp;rsquo;m Simone plannin on today&amp;rsquo;s episode, we&amp;rsquo;re going back 161 years ago this week.
To June 17.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - The Boys Are Back!</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100056/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100056/</guid>
        <description>0:03
Hey, not past it listeners.
It&amp;rsquo;s pride month.
And for the next few weeks.
We&amp;rsquo;re bringing you stories highlighting lgbtq+ communities.
Today.
We&amp;rsquo;re bringing you an episode.
We ran earlier this year about the drag Sensation that took over New York City in the 1990s, but it&amp;rsquo;s not the queens that were the toast of the Town.
0:24
These were Kings at Club Casanova over the last few months Moby Dick.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Still No HIV Vax</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100055/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100055/</guid>
        <description>0:03
Hey, not past it listeners.
It&amp;rsquo;s pride month.
And for the next four weeks.
We&amp;rsquo;re bringing you stories highlighting the experiences of lgbtq+ communities.
Our first story is an episode.
We ran last year about the search for an HIV vaccine and a trial in the 1990s that got really close to finding one this year.
0:25
The NIH launched clinical trials, for three new HIV, vaccines that all use.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - The Scopes&#39; Monkey Trial</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100054/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100054/</guid>
        <description>0:02
It is time to meet the beautiful women who want to be Miss USA.
I love pageants.
I love the performance of it, all vaseline on the teeth to keep you smiling.
0:18
I can of hairspray and an avalanche of bobby pins to help your hair defy gravity.
But my favorite part is, when the contestants are asked, really hard-hitting questions.
0:38
Not why do you want to win this pageant, or where do you see yourself in five years.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - What A Difference A Year Makes</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100053/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100053/</guid>
        <description>0:02
Could you tell our audience who you are?
Okay, my name is Peggy McKee.
And Simone is a former student of mine.
Peggy.
McKee was my high school history teacher.
I hope you got an A.
I think I did pretty well in your class.
0:17
Yeah, if I remember.
So, I&amp;rsquo;m talking with Miss McKee because today we&amp;rsquo;re revisiting a year a whole year of making not past it.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - The Nazi Hunter 2: The Capture</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100052/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100052/</guid>
        <description>0:02
Previously on not passed it.
The Nazi Hunter.
We told you about the fall of 1945, about how WWII just ended and how the Allied Powers put several captured Nazis on trial in Nuremberg.
0:20
Commit crimes against peace, war, crimes, and crimes against humanity.
One of these war, criminals, Adolf Eichmann charge of overseeing.
What was going to happen to the Jews.
I commend went on the run right after the war ended and was nowhere to be found.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - No More Cinco de Drinko</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100051/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100051/</guid>
        <description>0:02
You know, those family stories passed down from generation to generation.
They maybe aren&amp;rsquo;t always all the way true.
But they tell us who we are.
Where we come from.
Well, for David Hayes Bautista, his family myth begins in Mexico.
0:18
The family story.
I&amp;rsquo;ve heard since I was a kid is that my great-great-grandfather fought at the Battle of Puebla in the spring of 1862 at least 5,000 French soldiers, marched into recently independent.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - When Ukraine Fought Back</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100050/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100050/</guid>
        <description>0:02
Even though we&amp;rsquo;re a history, show.
It&amp;rsquo;s hard.
Not to address current events, especially when what we&amp;rsquo;re living through.
Now, the conflict between Russia and Ukraine is the result of a long and complicated history.
Ukraine has been an independent country since the fall of the Soviet Union in 1991, but that didn&amp;rsquo;t erase Russian President, Vladimir Putin&amp;rsquo;s desire, to bring it back, under Russian rule, on February 24th.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - The &#34;Crying Indian&#34; Ad</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100049/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100049/</guid>
        <description>0:03
Whether it&amp;rsquo;s 1971 and Dina gilja Whitaker is about 12 years old.
She&amp;rsquo;s doing what kids do watching TV and on comes a PSA, a memorable.
One one that would stick in her brain for decades.
0:20
It starred an American Indian.
So the commercial opens with this native guy and he&amp;rsquo;s clearly native because he&amp;rsquo;s wearing buckskins and it&amp;rsquo;s Fringe and he&amp;rsquo;s paddling a canoe.
For native people like me looking at thats like, wow, you know, I recognize that that&amp;rsquo;s like, you know, he&amp;rsquo;s like a hero figure.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - The Secret Abortion Conference</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100048/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100048/</guid>
        <description>0:02
Hey, you guys we found something really cool for this weeks episode.
It&amp;rsquo;s this nearly 70-year old document and reading it as like peering through a hole in the wall, back to a very specific moment in time.
It&amp;rsquo;s a book that was published in 1958.
0:22
We found a copy of it on eBay for something like 40 bucks.
It&amp;rsquo;s out of print hard to come by it&amp;rsquo;s torn and shabby-looking smells pretty old.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - The LSD No-No</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100047/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100047/</guid>
        <description>0:02
Hey, not past it listeners.
We&amp;rsquo;re hard at work on brand new episodes for you.
So this week, we&amp;rsquo;re going to rebroadcast an old favorite.
It&amp;rsquo;s about doc Ellis.
The legendary pitcher for the Pittsburgh Pirates, Who casually pitched a no-hitter in 1970 all while under the influence of a little drug called LSD. + this episode of not past.
0:26
It was nominated for an Ambien Ward.
Basically, like the Oscar&amp;rsquo;s of podcasting, not to brag.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - How The Joker Came To Be</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100046/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100046/</guid>
        <description>0:02
Hey, not past it listeners.
We&amp;rsquo;re back with another history.
Domino episode.
You know that thing where you line up a bunch of upright dominoes and then you tip over that first one and it hits the next one and the next one and the next one and it goes like, well, in our version, each Domino is a mini history story that leads you to the next event in a chain reaction, and will end up at a completely different and unexpected place than where we started.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Pirates of the Metric System</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100045/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100045/</guid>
        <description>0:04
It&amp;rsquo;s 1999.
And there&amp;rsquo;s one big thing on NASA&amp;rsquo;s mind.
The space agency is going back to Mars.
They are launching the Mars.
Climate Orbiter one of two weather satellites set to arrive at our sister Planet.
0:21
The Hope find evidence of water maybe even Signs of Life.
For almost 10 months, the spacecraft hurtles through the black of space.
And in September, the red Contours of Mars finally, come into full view.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - A UFO in the Southwestern Sky</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100044/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100044/</guid>
        <description>0:02
Pauli was just 10 years old.
When he saw something strange in the night sky, over his home, he and his family lived in the north of Phoenix and a neighborhood surrounded by Hills.
And on this night in March 1997.
0:18
There was supposed to be a super clear sighting of comet Hale-Bopp.
A lot of people were hoping to catch a glimpse of it.
I just remember thinking as a kid.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - A Notorious Life After Death</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100043/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100043/</guid>
        <description>0:04
I&amp;rsquo;m driving back in this rental car to go back to campus and I hear it on the radio.
Joel Anderson was a freshman in college.
When he heard that notorious b.i.g.
Biggie Smalls had been murdered 24 year old rap artist known as We shot early Sunday morning and later died of gunshot wounds in your by Cedars-Sinai Medical Center your book.
0:27
It was March 1997.
And at first I thought it was a joke.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It -  300 Years of the American Tween</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100042/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100042/</guid>
        <description>0:02
Hey, not past it listeners.
We&amp;rsquo;ve got a special episode for you.
Today.
We recorded our first live show at on are Fest in.
Brooklyn a history.
Domino special.
Well, hello on are Fest.
Welcome to not past it live.
0:22
So we&amp;rsquo;re going to play that for you today.
We hope you enjoy.
All right, first I am going to bring up our lovely guest.
You have heard her work in this American life and visit be Leah.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Korea’s Olympic Dream</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100041/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100041/</guid>
        <description>0:02
For a brief period in my early 20s.
I moved to Seoul South Korea, to do what?
So, many foreigners go there to do, teach English.
This was in, like, 2014 2015, a few years after sigh went viral with his hit song, Gangnam Style, but still a few more years before BTS.
0:24
Hit the Billboard Hot 100.
That&amp;rsquo;s for those of you who Mark time via major Kpop events, like I do.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - The Nazi Hunter</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100040/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100040/</guid>
        <description>0:02
A warning to our listeners.
This story contains graphic descriptions of violence.
Please.
Take care while you listen.
On a cool February evening in 1960, a family huddled together in a cemetery in Northern Australia dressed in somber colors.
0:25
They were there to mourn the loss of their patriarch who had died four days earlier.
The Cool Wind swirled as they watch the coffin, being cranked lower and lower into the Earth.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - We Found Love In A Historical Place</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100039/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100039/</guid>
        <description>0:02
When Clint Buffington was a kid, his family had a very specific vacation hobby, my family and I are kind of beachcombers most folks dig around in the sand to find.
The biggest shells or the prettiest ones, not the buffington&amp;rsquo;s, we would compete to find the smallest one because that would show who had the sharpest eyes.
0:23
He took a trip to the Caribbean with his dad and his early 20s.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Balto Wasn’t The (Only) Hero</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100038/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100038/</guid>
        <description>0:04
On January 20th. 1925.
Dr. Curtis Welch was making his rounds at the local hospital in Nome, a tiny remote City about halfway up the western coast of Alaska that afternoon.
0:20
He checked in on a three year.
Old boy named Billy Barnett Billy was showing a host of alarming, new symptoms, sunken eyes, dark lips and difficulty breathing.
And when dr.
Welch saw Billy in that condition, it confirmed, this terrible suspicion.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - The Last Queen of Hawaii</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100037/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100037/</guid>
        <description>0:04
January, 1891 Honolulu in the Hawaiian Kingdom.
The city was abuzz with preparation for the Kings return, triumphal arches decorated with Evergreen and inscribed with joyous Inspirations lined the route from The Wharf to the Palace.
0:22
The princess Regent had sent out invitations to a ball to be held on the evening of the arrival of King kalakaua from California.
But when the Islanders spotted the Kings ship, the Charleston sailing in the distance, they were shocked to see it.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - A New Sheriff in Town</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100036/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100036/</guid>
        <description>0:02
You may have never heard the name.
Lucius a mersenne.
He was a small town, sheriff in Alabama elected in the 1960s.
But as one of his former deputies JB Walker, says Emerson was a man to be reckoned with.
He wasn&amp;rsquo;t afraid of me, anything.
0:19
I remember a lady that new and well, and she said this in terms of Amos.
And you, you think you&amp;rsquo;re going to run for Sheriff?</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - The Sweet, but Deadly, Disaster</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100035/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100035/</guid>
        <description>0:06
Back in 1919 Boston&amp;rsquo;s, North End was an industrial Hub.
It was right on the Harbor were large freighter.
Ships, were constantly passing through some carrying goods from the Caribbean.
The neighborhood was a Melting Pot of immigrants, many of them from Italy.
0:26
When it was nice out.
Some workers would take their lunch break, along the busy.
Waterfront next to a Park were kids would often be playing above them loomed a 50-foot tall, rust Brown steel storage tank, filled with industrial-grade molasses.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - The Kings of Drag</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100034/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100034/</guid>
        <description>0:05
There&amp;rsquo;s a bar in New York City nestled in among graffiti buildings hollowed out and trimmed with scaffolding.
It&amp;rsquo;s nothing special.
But if you showed up here on a Sunday night, back in the 1990s, you&amp;rsquo;d find the bar transformed.
0:22
To be honest with you.
It was a small dump of a bar, get it was like the East Village, you know, is nothing fancy.
If it was very packed.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Zsa Zsa Gabor, Guilty As Charged</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100033/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100033/</guid>
        <description>0:02
As the holiday season comes to an end.
We made it our personal mission at not passed, it to bring some sparkle and shine to this last week of the year.
So today we&amp;rsquo;re sharing our episode about Zsa.
Zsa Gabor.
The legendary actress was known for her excessively glamorous lifestyle even by Hollywood standards.
0:24
Shahji was So Glamorous.
In fact that a few months before this episode originally aired her.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - The Beanie Baby Craze</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100032/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100032/</guid>
        <description>0:03
As a kid, the weeks leading up to Christmas for just the best.
So, full of excitement for family.
I hadn&amp;rsquo;t seen all year all the food.
I would inevitably Gorge myself on and obviously I had my mind on what goodies Santa would be bringing forget visions of sugarplums.
0:22
I was dreaming of Bratz dolls Furbys, and of course Beanie Babies, Today, I&amp;rsquo;m not past it, and the spirit of the holiday season and the toy shopping craze.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - World’s Most Famous Virgins</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100031/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100031/</guid>
        <description>0:02
Hey, not past it listeners, get your Domino&amp;rsquo;s ready.
We&amp;rsquo;re about to do the segment where we tell a series of little stories from history that are all connected.
Where one thing leads to another and another and we end up in a totally unpredictable place.
0:18
This is the historical domino effect.
From gimlet media.
This is not past it a show about the stories.
We can&amp;rsquo;t quite leave behind.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Where Are My Background Singers?</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100030/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100030/</guid>
        <description>0:02
This past Sunday night, December 5th, CBS broadcasted.
The nation&amp;rsquo;s 99th.
Annual National Christmas tree, lighting.
Ceremony.
It was a pretty tame wholesome event a moment to welcome in the holiday season hosted by LL Cool.
0:22
J.
It featured musical performances from the likes of Billy Porter.
Her and none other than the one and only miss Patty.
Bell.
Good friend, a beautiful person in one of the greatest singers of our time, Patti LaBelle Patti.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - How To Invent A Holiday</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100029/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100029/</guid>
        <description>0:02
You ever listen to the radio or scroll through Twitter and learn that it&amp;rsquo;s like hug and Australian day, or International moments of frustration, scream day or cook, something bold and pungent day.
And you just wonder to yourself.
0:19
Like how did this become holidays?
Well, those days and a lot of other silly holidays are all the work of one, man.
Tom Roy, how many of Have you written?</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Sabotaging Thanksgiving</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100028/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100028/</guid>
        <description>0:05
On Thanksgiving morning in 1997, a familiar scene, played out in Plymouth, Massachusetts, men and women dressed head-to-toe and colonial era.
Costumes paraded through the streets.
They were giant white collars, breaches, and bonnets and their hands.
0:23
They held Bibles some muskets and in their hearts, They Carried the true.
True spirit and story of Thanksgiving tourists lined, the streets to watch it all play out, but then indigenous protesters intercepted.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Introducing Not Past It</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100027/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100027/</guid>
        <description>0:00
Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Simone polenin and I&amp;rsquo;m the host of a new weekly show from gimlet about history and wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait before you skip this.
Yes.
It&amp;rsquo;s a history show.
Okay, but it&amp;rsquo;s not like a boring history show.
It&amp;rsquo;s called not past it.
And it&amp;rsquo;s all about the weird and interesting and crazy things that have happened in the past.
0:22
I&amp;rsquo;m not a historian or a scholar, but I am a writer, a filmmaker and, you know, All-American Girl.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Murder in Ogoniland</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100026/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100026/</guid>
        <description>0:04
Hear the call of the ravaged land.
The Rockers Cry of feminist Earth.
Here 0 here.
Stunted crops fast.
Decay fish has died and float away butterflies lose wing and fall neater.
0:24
So comes to the ecological War.
0:39
In early January of 1993 300,000 ogoni people marched to their traditional capital city in the Niger.
Delta to protest against Royal Dutch Shell.
For nearly four decades, she&amp;rsquo;ll had been drilling a no-go, Neil and a region in southern Nigeria and their operations had caused widespread and devastating pollution by the early 90s.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Ma Barker’s True Crime</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100025/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100025/</guid>
        <description>0:05
Hey guys, it&amp;rsquo;s Simone.
I just wanted to take a minute to say, thank you.
Thank you for listening to not past it.
Whether this is your first time or your back for more.
We love taking this weekly Journey back through time and exploring history and all of its complicated mess.
0:25
And if you love it, too, please tell the people in your life.
Friends, your family, your co-workers, your cat sitter that Tinder match you&amp;rsquo;ve been chatting with, but we&amp;rsquo;ll probably never meet in person.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - King Tut Died for Tourism</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100024/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100024/</guid>
        <description>0:01
Have you heard the one about the canary and the Cobra?
It goes something like this?
Which man is living in, Egypt?
He&amp;rsquo;s an archaeologist and he&amp;rsquo;s getting ready for the winter digging season.
He tells his friends.
0:17
I&amp;rsquo;m going to need some company during those long months.
So I&amp;rsquo;m bringing a special companion for all like, ooh, la la, who could it be?
But when this special companion arrives from England, they find out.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Houdini: The OG Ghostbuster</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100023/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100023/</guid>
        <description>0:04
High atop the Knickerbocker Hotel in Los Angeles and the year 1936 stand, a man and a woman dressed to the nines and formal wear.
He sporting a long goatee.
0:20
She a shock of white hair and a double strand of pearls they appear, ghostly withered, behind them.
The old Hollywood Sign lights, up the Eerie night sky in front of them, sit, 300 star-studded guests.
0:39
The date is October, 31st Halloween at 8:00 p.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - What’s Haunting The Lake ?</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100022/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100022/</guid>
        <description>0:01
A warning for our listeners.
This story touches on different forms of racial violence and Trauma, so, please take care while you listen.
Roughly 40 miles, Northeast of Atlanta and Forsyth County, lies Lake Lanier.
0:22
That&amp;rsquo;s a real destination spot over 12 million visitors a year relaxing on its Shores partying on its water.
It&amp;rsquo;s a man-made lake and rumor has it.
It&amp;rsquo;s filled with haunted Souls.
There&amp;rsquo;s definitely 11 or 12 goes down there that I The locals say there&amp;rsquo;s something in the water you reach out in the dark and all of a sudden you feel an arm and a leg and it doesn&amp;rsquo;t move.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Hooked on Black Horror</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100021/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100021/</guid>
        <description>0:00
Tell me if this Rings true.
I found that when I ask someone, if they like, scary movies, I basically get one of two responses.
It&amp;rsquo;s either like no way.
I get scared way too easily, or it&amp;rsquo;s like scary movies.
0:19
I&amp;rsquo;m obsessed with scary movies.
I myself fall very much into the latter category.
There&amp;rsquo;s something weirdly addictive about the thrill of the suspense that feeling you get in your stomach when you&amp;rsquo;re like, oh no something bad&amp;rsquo;s about to happen.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - The Witch of Delray</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100020/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100020/</guid>
        <description>0:04
Welcome, not past it listeners.
You feel that, that chill in the air October is here.
And that means spooky, season is in full swing.
All month long.
0:20
We&amp;rsquo;re bringing you true scary stories ripped, right?
From the pages of History because sometimes hauntings are just histories unresolved.
And for our first stop in this spooky tour, we&amp;rsquo;re traveling to Detroit Michigan in the early, 1930s.
0:49
Picture.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - How The Green M&amp;M Got Sexy</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100019/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100019/</guid>
        <description>0:01
Hey, not past it listeners.
It&amp;rsquo;s time for the return of the historical, domino effect.
You know that thing where you line up a bunch of upright, Domino&amp;rsquo;s and then you tip over that first one, and it hits the next one.
And the next one, and the next one.
0:16
And it goes like well, and our version, each Domino will be a mini history story, that leads you to the next event in a chain reaction.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - 💩🌠The Birth of Emojis 😂🤰🏾</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100018/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100018/</guid>
        <description>0:04
It&amp;rsquo;s a cold Fall, New England night in 2012.
I&amp;rsquo;m laying back on my dorm room bed.
Still buzzed from whatever, college party.
I just come from and emboldened by the shots of cheap.
Vodka.
I decide to drunk text this guy.
I like This is a younger Simone.
0:21
Okay.
Be gentle.
I sent some version of hey, want to come over question mark and I wait and wait and wait until finally, he replies instead of a yes or a no or an absolutely.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Zsa Zsa Slaps a Cop</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100017/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100017/</guid>
        <description>0:13
Picture.
This.
We open on a white Rolls Royce zipping down, a Beverly Hill Street on a hot afternoon.
Behind the wheel is a woman platinum, blond, and Oh, So Glamorous, but before long the fuzz show up a cop on a motorcycle signals to the woman to pull over.
0:40
He asks, if she knows her tags are expired and to see her license.
The officer asks her to step out of her car for almost an hour.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - 9/11 Makes Me Uncomfortable</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100016/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100016/</guid>
        <description>0:01
The 20th anniversary of 9/11 is this week and our team here at not past it?
We&amp;rsquo;ve spent the past few weeks talking, a lot about how to cover that on the show.
And as we were talking, one of the questions that came up was basically like, well Simone, what do you want to say about 9/11?
0:20
And I thought about it for a while and I really struggled to find an answer.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Your Beanie Babies Are Worthless</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100015/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100015/</guid>
        <description>0:00
My God, I was so into Beanie Babies.
He was ready for one of them to be worth so much money.
One day.
Remember Beanie Babies.
Those cute under stuffed toys with clever names, like chocolate the moose or Patti.
0:15
The Platypus people went crazy over them.
We put out a call to you.
Our dear listeners to hear how you bought into the beanie crazed with your hearts, your minds, and your hard-earned cash.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - The Enron Whistleblower</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100014/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100014/</guid>
        <description>0:02
Do we have security at the door?
It&amp;rsquo;s February, 2002 crowd of anxious, on Lookers fills, an official-looking room and Miss Watkins.
If you would pull the microphone as close as you can and speak up.
0:21
All righty would very much.
Appreciate it.
At the front of the room is a woman with a neat blond Bob and a printed silk scarf.
Tied around her neck.
She sitting at a long table facing a panel of people with a very lengthy named the oversight and investigation subcommittee of the Energy and Commerce Committee and front of her a name placard reads.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Woodstock 69: A Peaceful Disaster</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100013/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100013/</guid>
        <description>0:07
In a Faraway field at the edge of civilization, heaps of trash and collapsed hence are piling up.
It smells absolutely rancid and it&amp;rsquo;s packed with people.
Some naked, most are bedraggled one reporter called the seen a floating garbage.
0:24
Heap.
Another wrote more than 300,000 persons wandered about Out in a sea of mud, comma sickness young people.
So packed and jammed together that they could not get proper food or water or adequate medical help.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Secret Billboard Chart Topper from Crime Show</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100012/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100012/</guid>
        <description>0:05
Hey, not past it listeners.
Before we get to Today&amp;rsquo;s Show.
I have a favor to ask you.
If you&amp;rsquo;ve been liking the podcast, whether you&amp;rsquo;re a bender or a weekly listener.
Why not?
Tell someone about it.
Your friends, your family, your neighbors.
Your Twitter followers word-of-mouth.
0:21
Really helps people find new podcasts and you know, where a new podcast and you all have words and And mouths.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - The Olympic GOAT Gets Snubbed</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100011/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100011/</guid>
        <description>0:05
It&amp;rsquo;s a hot sunny day in Havana Cuba, December 1936.
And a crowd of a few thousand are gathered in the stands.
Below them.
A racetrack were two competitors are gearing up for the big race.
But first is Jesse Owens the Buckeye bullet black magic.
0:23
The ebony streak.
He&amp;rsquo;s fresh off of his impressive showing at the Olympic Games in Berlin.
Just four months prior.
Fire where he won, four gold medals, but today&amp;rsquo;s race is different because of who Jesse&amp;rsquo;s opponent is all this Fanfare.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - The Notorious Ma Barker</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100010/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100010/</guid>
        <description>0:05
When we walked in the door, I could not believe it.
This place looked like it was from another time period.
Retired Community College instructor.
Sue Sutton was a teenager in the mid-60s.
0:22
When her family moved to Concordia, Kansas soos father took her and her sister to the local bank to open bank accounts.
Yes, but when she walked in, she couldn&amp;rsquo;t believe what she saw.
The bank tellers were separated by bulletproof glass.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It  - Bitch, I’m an Astrophysicist</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100019/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100019/</guid>
        <description>0:04
Wow, what a beautiful night sky, I just love stargazing.
Don&amp;rsquo;t you producer?
Julie Carly?
I sure do just gorgeous.
Holy crap.
Did you just see that shooting star?
0:21
Quick?
Make a wish?
Okay?
Okay.
I&amp;rsquo;m Jiminy cricketing.
Have you ever thought about traveling to space?
No, honestly, gravity is done.
Um so much for me in my community, but I do love a good space person.
Especially Sally Ride, you know.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Small Town Secession</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100008/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100008/</guid>
        <description>0:05
So, even on our cell phones, we have no reception in Kitty.
We&amp;rsquo;re sitting in a hole, think about it, as being a volcano and we&amp;rsquo;re in the mouth of the volcano and we got the crust all the way around us.
Surely.
0:21
I can only as one of only about a hundred and forty residents who live in Kinney, a tiny town in northern Minnesota.
The city centre is just two blocks wide and four blocks long on Main Street, you&amp;rsquo;ll find Library a bar, a town hall and not much else.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - United States of Illuminati</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100007/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100007/</guid>
        <description>0:06
I divided family will destroy itself, a divided nation will anticipate ruin prepared by its enemies.
The year is 1798, think waistcoats and powdered white hair.
It&amp;rsquo;s July 4th and a young United States of America, a celebrating her 22nd birthday.
0:26
The perfect time to have an identity crisis.
The scene is Yale College, which had already been around for nearly a century.
The school&amp;rsquo;s president.
Reverend Timothy, Dwight stands in front of a crowd of his fellow New England, Elites and delivers a sermon.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It  - Rated PG-13 for Sex and Violence</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100006/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100006/</guid>
        <description>0:00
In 2007, the biggest movie event of the summer at least for me was the premiere of Superbad, you know, Michael Cera and Jonah Hill on a quest to lose their virginity.
At the end of high school.
It&amp;rsquo;s the movie that gave us McLovin my friends and I desperately wanted to see it but it was rated R and we were still a couple of years shy of 17.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - Nazi Battle to Pop Musical?</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100005/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100005/</guid>
        <description>0:00
Hey, not past it listeners.
We&amp;rsquo;ve got something a little different for you this week.
We&amp;rsquo;re calling it a historical domino effect.
You know that thing where you line up a bunch of bright Domino&amp;rsquo;s and then you tip over that first one and it hits the next one and the next one and the next one and it goes like this is an idea that&amp;rsquo;s actually inspired by a viral Tick.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - The Paris Hilton Sex Tape</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100004/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100004/</guid>
        <description>0:03
At a Los Angeles, Grammy Awards party in 2004, photographers gathered around the red carpet hungry for the it girl to arrive.
And when she finally did, they erupted and shouts to get her attention.
It was Paris, Hilton socialite, and heiress to the Hilton Hotel.
0:24
Fortune on this day.
She was all smiles and her pink ruffle dress and matching headband, but she declined to talk to the photographers.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - The LSD No-Hitter</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100003/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100003/</guid>
        <description>0:01
Running out of the scoreboard.
You can see 000 where it says San Diego.
Now, Doc Ellis comes down.
He&amp;rsquo;s fine side ball, just off the bill of the cap.
When the year is 1970, Dock Ellis is on the mound, pitching for the Pittsburgh Pirates.
0:17
He&amp;rsquo;s got his cap on his curls, peeking out the side, and he&amp;rsquo;s chewing a piece of bubble gum to a pulp.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It  - The Vax That Got Axed</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100002/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100002/</guid>
        <description>0:03
My fellow Americans.
If the 21st century is to be the century of biology.
Let us make an AIDS vaccine.
Its first great Triumph.
That&amp;rsquo;s our first black President Bill Clinton.
Those are Toni Morrison&amp;rsquo;s words.
0:20
Not mine.
Okay, just Google it.
It&amp;rsquo;s June, 1997, and President Clinton is giving a commencement speech at Morgan State University in Baltimore, Maryland, and he&amp;rsquo;s got quite a big announcement to make but they let us commit ourselves to developing an AIDS vaccine within the next decade.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Not Past It - A Race for a Better Breakfast</title>
        <link>https://swiest.com/en/1302100001/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://swiest.com/en/1302100001/</guid>
        <description>0:02
Hello, where do you keep your cereal cereal?
Thanks.
There are a few constants in this world, but I know one thing&amp;rsquo;s for sure.
If I walk down the cereal aisle and pretty much any grocery store or stumble around the bodega down the block.
0:19
Oh, second second row.
I see this way.
The one thing I am bound to find our Corn Flakes.
So crispy Corn Flakes.</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
