<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Let's Be Honest with Kristin Cavallari on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</title><link>https://swiest.com/tags/lets-be-honest-with-kristin-cavallari/</link><description>Recent content in Let's Be Honest with Kristin Cavallari on SWIEST - Transcripts · Screenplays · Lyrics</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://swiest.com/tags/lets-be-honest-with-kristin-cavallari/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Over Here Chasing Boys | Let's Be Honest with Kristin Cavallari</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1482820001/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1482820001/</guid><description>Podcast Description Time for an update on my dating life! My bestie Justin Anderson and I bring everyone up to speed on where things stand with Hot Man from Raya. Plus we discuss why passive aggressiveness is a buzzkill, ignoring every red flag, the pros and cons of dating outside of where you live, the conversation that made me feel like I couldn't breathe, why everyone should be the star of their show, and how I started talking to Justin's perfect guy for me.</description></item><item><title>Couples Therapy with Heidi and Spencer Pratt | Let's Be Honest with Kristin Cavallari</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1482820002/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1482820002/</guid><description>Podcast Description I sit down with the one and only Heidi and Spencer to discuss their first impressions of each other, how Spencer first joined The Hills to piss off Heidi, Spencer's conspiracy theory about the real reason they ended The Hills the way they did, working the press for their benefit, keeping things spicy after 16 years, and what a typical day looks like for them. We clear up the biggest misconception about their relationship, fake storylines on The Hills, and if Heidi and I should do another show together.</description></item><item><title>It Doesn’t Matter When You Sleep With Him — Listener Questions Pt. 2 | Let's Be Honest with Kristin Cavallari</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1482820003/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1482820003/</guid><description>Podcast Description Part two of fan questions and we’re covering my non-negotiables in my next relationship, attracting all the wrong guys after being on TV at such a young age, my media training, NDAs, how to know when to leave a relationship when kids are involved, the cringiest thing I had to do on reality TV, mini update on Hotman from Raya and my favorite date, my ideal man, why celebrity guys aren’t for me, if I would get married again and have another kid, what made me change my tune on plastic surgery, and a real convo about money and why having my own is so important to me.</description></item><item><title>Match That Energy — Listener Questions Pt. 1 | Let's Be Honest with Kristin Cavallari</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1482820004/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1482820004/</guid><description>Podcast Description You guys submitted questions that cover all the things: update on the Aussie, a normal day for me, we discuss all of my boyfriends, if I regret marrying so young, the best date I've been on post-divorce, something I never thought I would say in a million years, if I feel pressure to get work done being in the public eye, creating a business, why motivation doesn't always come from a pure place, why I keep my children private, and hanging with Mr.</description></item><item><title>Staying On Track This Holiday Season with Nutritionist Ivey Leidy | Let's Be Honest with Kristin Cavallari</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1482820005/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1482820005/</guid><description>Podcast Description Integrative health coach and nutritionist Ivey Leidy and I discuss how to make smarter choices on Thanksgiving and all season long, eating disorders, the #1 thing everyone should eliminate from their bodies, how to get rid of toxins in your home, and why we think diet culture is bullsh*t.
If you or a loved one is struggling with an eating disorder, help is available:
National Eating Disorders Association (NEDA) Resources</description></item><item><title>My Own Real Life Bachelorette | Let's Be Honest with Kristin Cavallari</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1482820006/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1482820006/</guid><description>Podcast Description My bestie (and dating detective) Justin Anderson is back to break down Raya with me and dish on my first date with "Hot Man" from the app. We discuss men's dating profiles, why I feel like I'm a catfish, if I would have another kid, Justin's big dick theory, and my epiphany with what my issue has been when it comes to dating and men and what my game plan is moving forward.</description></item><item><title>Nick Viall Wants You to End Your Situationship | Let's Be Honest with Kristin Cavallari</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1482820007/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1482820007/</guid><description>Podcast Description Podcast host, reality TV alum, and incredible advice giver Nick Viall and I discuss everything going on with men when it comes to dating from flirting on Instagram to when it's your responsibility to make the first move, how to tell if he's not into you, why to never ask a guy "what are we", guys' biggest dating insecurity, what percentage of men cheat, how guys fall in love, and what Nick blew my mind about.</description></item><item><title>My First 72 Hours in LA That You Couldn't Write | Let's Be Honest with Kristin Cavallari</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1482820008/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1482820008/</guid><description>Podcast Description I was in LA for a week and you'll never believe how much stuff went down just within the first 3 days. Literally so much that I needed to call my BFF Justin Anderson to help me tell you all about it. It started with girls night that ended up with the Australian rugby team, my journey of caving and finally joining Raya to find one specific man, a coffee date that ended up in jail, and why I might be changing my tune on girls making the first move.</description></item><item><title>Getting Honest with Nikki Glaser | Let's Be Honest with Kristin Cavallari</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1482820009/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1482820009/</guid><description>Podcast Description I sit down with the hilarious and refreshingly candid Nikki to talk about why the heck she's been on again/off again with the same boyfriend for 10 years, the stereotype that all comedians are insecure, red flags for spotting a narcissist (hello, love bombing!), how meeting your idols is always a letdown, when you should first sleep with a guy, and why giving your partner freedom could be the best thing to make them not stray.</description></item><item><title>Do What Makes You F*cking Happy | Let's Be Honest with Kristin Cavallari</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1482820010/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1482820010/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join me in this feel-good episode to discuss why I think we're completely screwed as a society when it comes to body image and how to start living your life just for you. Also, let's get into why our triggers are so important and why no one else's opinion matters.
A word from our sponsors:
Seed: Join me in my gut health journey with Seed. Visit seed.com/HONEST and use code HONEST to redeem 25% off your first month of Seed's DS-01® Daily Synbiotic.</description></item><item><title>A Brutally Honest Convo with My BFF Justin Anderson | Let's Be Honest with Kristin Cavallari</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1482820011/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1482820011/</guid><description>Podcast Description My best friend and incredible hair stylist, Justin Anderson, joins me to have one of our very real, honest conversations about our similar dating paths going from narcissist relationships to attracting good guys, why we're soulmates, what we believe the key to happiness actually is, and why he hopes his mom isn't listening to this interview.
A word from our sponsors:
Amika: Go to loveamika.com/honest to shop all my faves and to get 20% off your order.</description></item><item><title>There Goes My Dating Game | Let's Be Honest with Kristin Cavallari</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1482820012/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1482820012/</guid><description>Podcast Description I'm back with another solo episode to talk about all things dating — particularly in those early stages. From texting, social media, and getting love bombed, to how to tell if you're one of a few in rotation, when it's okay to send nudes, and why you should let people pursue you. Also, it's time to reveal my current boyfriend... even though it's gonna mess up my dating game.</description></item><item><title>Getting Into The Mind of a Man With Travis Kelce | Let's Be Honest with Kristin Cavallari</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1482820013/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1482820013/</guid><description>Podcast Description Two-time Super Bowl champion, Travis Kelce, joins me from Kansas City for a conversation that covers everything. The fan-favorite opens up about being on reality TV, staying grounded throughout his success, dating deal breakers, why dating with zero pressure is the best, and what he's hoping the stars align on soon. And a quick game of Two Truths and a Lie leaves me absolutely stumped. A word from my sponsors:</description></item><item><title>Holy Sh*t This Is Really Happening | Let's Be Honest with Kristin Cavallari</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1482820014/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1482820014/</guid><description>Podcast Description Join me for my first solo episode! Let's start at the beginning and dig a little into my journey of self-discovery through relationships, how my voice and image has been controlled since I was just 17, and realizing how that tough girl that everyone saw on Laguna Beach and The Hills was actually me overcompensating for the lack I felt within myself. Also, this is really the first time in my entire life that I'm actively dating and get ready because we are going to talk about that a LOT.</description></item><item><title>So, You're Telling Me You Don't Miss Reality TV? With Stassi Schroeder | Let's Be Honest with Kristin Cavallari</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1482820015/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1482820015/</guid><description>Podcast Description When I started this podcast, I had a list of people I was dying to sit down with. And one of them was the very beautiful (and at the time, very pregnant) reality TV princess, Stassi Schroeder. We all know her from Vanderpump Rules and her two hit podcasts but I'm so glad we sat down just before she had her baby because this episode goes so far beyond who we think Stassi is.</description></item><item><title>Let's Be Honest Starting September 12th | Let's Be Honest with Kristin Cavallari</title><link>https://swiest.com/en/1482820016/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://swiest.com/en/1482820016/</guid><description>Podcast Description Kristin Cavallari isn't holding anything back in her new lifestyle podcast, Let's Be Honest. Get ready to dive into all things relationships, dating, health, wellness and so much more — nothing is off limits.
Starting September 12th, it's time to get honest.
Produced by Dear Media.
See Privacy Policy at https://art19.com/privacy and California Privacy Notice at https://art19.com/privacy#do-not-sell-my-info.
Transcript</description></item></channel></rss>